135. Hidden Sword Sect

The youth turned his head and he saw a slender young man, who looked cold and refined, similar to the young masters he had seen in the city.

The youth didn't speak. But someone nearby did.

"Heh, want to carry someone to the peak? People have tried it in the past. But you have to be at least an acquired martial artist to do that. Body Refining martial artists face danger just by climbing themselves, let alone carrying someone."

Hidden Sword Sect welcomes all, regardless of background. Even acquired martial artists could join the sect. However, acquired martial artists must disperse all their inner power before joining Hidden Sword Sect. How many acquired martial artists have the courage?"

Many people shook their heads. The one thousand and eight stone steps of Hidden Sword Sect had stumped countless people. Carrying another person meant bearing their weight as well. It was such a steep and treacherous cliff. One misstep could send them both plummeting.

Lin Fei didn't speak. His eyes were on the youth. What others said didn't matter, he was waiting for the youth's decision.

The next moment, without hesitation, the youth knelt down with a "thud" and kowtowed to Lin Fei, "Please, take me up the mountain. I'll be forever grateful for your kindness!"

"Indeed, a clever one. Very well, let's go."

Lin Fei nodded. He was just intrigued and he thought the youth was promising. So he wanted to carry the youth up the mountain. That was all.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei grabbed the youth with his right hand. And not only that, with his left hand, he picked up the youth's little sister, the seven or eight-year-old girl. He then took a step onto the stone steps.

Seeing this scene, many people at the foot of the mountain widened their eyes. Their gazes filled with disbelief. It wasn't enough for Lin Fei to carry one person. He was actually going to carry two?

The youth didn't expect Lin Fei to be willing to carry his sister as well. He was about to say something. But the next moment, he couldn't speak. Because Lin Fei's stride spanned more than a dozen meters. Holding two people in his hands, he walked as if strolling leisurely.

He headed towards the peak. It was called "walking." But in reality, Lin Fei's speed was beyond belief. The howling wind made it impossible for the youth to open his eyes or speak. So, he could only tightly close his mouth and eyes.

Seeing this scene, people at the foot of the mountain were dumbfounded. Never had anyone seen someone like Lin Fei, carrying two people and still walking briskly. Moreover, each step covered more than a dozen meters. They knew they had encountered a "master." Only those top martial artists possessed such abilities.

It didn't take long for Lin Fei to "walk" from the foot of the mountain to the peak. He saw the Hidden Sword Sect at the top of the mountain. In front of the gate of the Hidden Sword Sect, two disciples saw Lin Fei carrying two people up.

One was a youth and the other was a seven or eight-year-old girl. Carrying two people and strolling up the treacherous Hidden Sword Sect stone steps, it was obviously not an ordinary person. Therefore, the two disciples immediately greeted them.

Lin Fei took the initiative to ask: "I brought these two people to the peak. According to the rules of your Hidden Sword Sect, can they join the sect?"

The two Hidden Sword Sect disciples glanced at the somewhat dazed youth and little girl and then they nodded: "No problem. According to Hidden Sword Sect rules, no matter how one reaches the peak. As long as they are here and want to join Hidden Sword Sect, there is no problem. Are you two willing to join Hidden Sword Sect?"

The youth was the first to come to his senses. Immediately pulling his sister, they said in unison: "We are willing, we want to join Hidden Sword Sect!"

The youth was incredibly overjoyed. Who could have thought that he barely climbed the steps and was carried all the way from the foot of the mountain to the peak? Even his sister was brought to the peak as well.

The two of them joined Hidden Sword Sect together. This sudden happiness made the youth feel as if he were in a dream. However, the youth knew their benefactor was Lin Fei.

At this moment, the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples spoke solemnly: "Our Hidden Sword Sect welcomes all, without regard for one's background or age. As long as they reach the peak and are willing to join Hidden Sword Sect, they can.

However, if one is an acquired martial artist, one must first disperse their inner power. Considering you were able to carry two people to the peak, your inner power must be extremely profound. We wonder, are you willing to disperse your inner power and join the Hidden Sword Sect?"

What the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples said had precedents to follow.

In the history of the Hidden Sword Sect, there had even been martial artists at the twelfth level of the acquired realm who were unable to break through to the innate. They then came to the peak of the Hidden Sword Sect, voluntarily dispersed their inner power, and joined the sect.

Therefore, among the Hidden Sword Sect disciples, those who had once possessed profound inner power were not few. After all, for a loose martial artist to become innate was as difficult as reaching the sky.

If one dispersed their inner power and joined the Hidden Sword Sect, there might still be a glimmer of hope to advance to the innate realm. Of course, such people were ultimately in the minority. Those who could reach the twelfth level of the acquired realm were all geniuses.

Many would rather risk everything to attempt a breakthrough to the innate realm rather than be willing to disperse their inner power and start all over again.

At this moment, the youth looked at Lin Fei. If Lin Fei could also join the Hidden Sword Sect, wouldn't he become a fellow disciple with his benefactor?

"Benefactor, you're still so young. Even if you disperse your inner power, you will surely stand out and become the most outstanding disciple of the Hidden Sword Sect. I've heard that there are peerless swordsmen in the Hidden Sword Sect, with divine swordsmanship like immortal beings. If the benefactor also joins the Hidden Sword Sect, you will surely become a peerless swordsman!"

In the eyes of the youth, becoming a peerless swordsman of the Hidden Sword Sect would be the dream of his life. Lin Fei was so young, yet so powerful. Even if he dispersed his inner power, he would certainly not be inferior to others.

This was also what the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples were looking forward to. They also had high hopes for disciples like Lin Fei who had strong original strength but were willing to disperse their inner power and join the Hidden Sword Sect.

Once such disciples joined the Hidden Sword Sect, most of them would become outstanding among the disciples of the sect. Even some could truly advance to the innate realm and become martial arts masters!

Lin Fei looked at the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples. Then he looked at the youth. He shook his head slightly and said calmly: "I am a saber practitioner, I don't practice the sword. I won't join the Hidden Sword Sect."

"Eh?"

The expressions of the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples changed.

"You've come to the peak. You don't practice the sword, nor do you want to be a disciple. So, what is the purpose of your visit to our Hidden Sword Sect?"

Lin Fei glanced at the gate of the Hidden Sword Sect. Then he gave a faint smile.

"I don't want to be a disciple, I've come to pay my respects to the mountain!"

The next moment, the saber intent within Lin Fei's body was stimulated.

"Boom."

A terrifying saber intent soared into the sky. The vast saber intent aura instantly enveloped the airspace of the Hidden Sword Sect.

"Nine Profound Sect Lin Fei, especially here to pay respects to the Hidden Sword Sect!"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back. His voice was very calm, but it was like a thunderbolt, penetrating deep into the Hidden Sword Sect. It even emitted bursts of rumbling sounds.

136. He is the Immortal Slayer Saber

Lin Fei released his saber intent. It was sharp and revealing as if the entire sky above the Hidden Sword Sect was suspended with a huge saber. This was clearly a provocation to the entire Hidden Sword Sect.

After all, the Hidden Sword Sect used swords. All of their disciples wielded only swords. They lived with swords, accompanied by swords, practicing the sword, fighting with swords, and understanding the sword.

The sword was the lifelong belief of the Hidden Sword Sect disciples. As long as the sword exists, they exist; when the sword perishes, they perish. Hidden Sword Sect disciples would never allow anyone else to surpass their sect, especially a saber practitioner!

At this moment, the two acquired realm disciples guarding the entrance of the Hidden Sword Sect were drenched in sweat. Being suppressed by Lin Fei's saber intent at close range was not a pleasant experience.

Their eyes were filled with shock. Not only were they shocked by Lin Fei's saber intent, but they were also shocked by Lin Fei's identity. Nine Profound Sect Grand Elder meant an innate martial artist. And Lin Fei had another identity. Immortal Slayer Saber!

"He is the Immortal Slayer Saber!"

The two disciples' faces were full of horror. It seemed that the three words "Immortal Slayer Saber" were extremely shocking to them.

"Boom."

As Lin Fei released his saber intent, a sword intent suddenly burst out from within the Hidden Sword Sect. This sword intent soared into the sky. Moreover, Lin Fei had a familiar feeling. Hidden Sword Sect, Lu Zongyi!

"Hahaha, it's been two months, Brother Lin has finally come to our Hidden Sword Sect. Our Hidden Sword Sect, of course, welcomes Brother Lin. However, isn't this a bit too grand, Brother Lin?"

Accompanied by this soaring sword intent, a shadow flickered from within the Hidden Sword Sect. Every flicker covered a distance of several dozen meters. In the blink of an eye, it rushed out of the mountain gate of the Hidden Sword Sect and came to a stop in front of Lin Fei. It was none other than Lu Zongyi, whom Lin Fei had met at the Martial Alliance Exchange!

"Disciple pays respect to Grand Elder!"

The two Hidden Sword Sect disciples, upon seeing Lu Zongyi, were shaken. They immediately stepped forward and respectfully saluted. Lu Zongyi was a Grand Elder of the Hidden Sword Sect. Now that he had personally come to greet Lin Fei, It showed just how important Lin Fei, the "Immortal Slayer Saber," was!

"Alright, you may leave. I will personally escort Brother Lin inside."

Lu Zongyi waved his hand slightly, and the two disciples stepped aside. Lin Fei also withdrew his saber intent. He followed Lu Zongyi into the Hidden Sword Sect.

Watching Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi's disappearing figures, the two Hidden Sword Sect disciples looked at each other. There was a hint of astonishment in their eyes.

"I didn't expect him to be the 'Immortal Slayer Saber,' and so young."

"Also, that saber intent just now was terrifying. It felt even stronger than Elder Lu's sword intent."

"I wonder what the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' has come to the Hidden Sword Sect for this time?"

For a moment, the two disciples whispered in discussion. It seemed that they had forgotten the young boy and the little girl.

The boy was still somewhat bewildered. When Lin Fei showed his saber intent just now, as an ordinary person, He didn't feel much. He just thought that Lin Fei had suddenly become terrifying. Then, another person from the Hidden Sword Sect took Lin Fei in.

The boy couldn't help but ask, "Senior Brothers, it seems that my benefactor has no intention of joining the Hidden Sword Sect. Why did he enter the Hidden Sword Sect?"

The two disciples noticed the boy and smiled, "Your benefactor is the well-known 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, who is currently widely known throughout the world. He is a respected innate martial artist and a martial arts master. Even our Hidden Sword Sect's Grand Elder Lu is somewhat inferior to him.

Actually, you're lucky to have met the 'Immortal Slayer Saber.' Why would you need to join our Hidden Sword Sect? If you were to become a disciple of Master Lin Fei, you would be soaring to the heavens in one step!"

The two disciples said with a smile. They were also a bit envious of the boy in front of them. He was so fortunate to be favored by the "Immortal Slayer Saber" and even brought the boy directly to the mountaintop.

However, the boy ultimately missed this opportunity. He didn't become Lin Fei's disciple. Instead, he joined the Hidden Sword Sect as an ordinary disciple.

"I don't regret it! Even if my benefactor is a great master, even comparable to the peerless swordsmen, I believe that joining the Hidden Sword Sect will also enable me to become a peerless master like my benefactor!"

The boy's expression was solemn, and his demeanor was serious. His words just now were obviously from the heart. This surprised the two disciples.

"Oh? With a firm will, you're indeed a good seedling. Maybe one day, you'll achieve something. And, you're right. Although 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Elder Lin is powerful, our Hidden Sword Sect is not bad.

Centuries ago, our Hidden Sword Sect had a Sword Saint whose fame shook the world! Even the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' is far from being as powerful as that Sword Saint of our Hidden Sword Sect. If you join the Hidden Sword Sect and diligently practice the sword, you will have an extraordinary achievement in the future. By the way, what's your name?"

"My name is Jing Hong."

"Jing Hong, follow me. First, enter the Hidden Sword Sect to worship our ancestors, and then you can begin as a novice."

Jing Hong nodded. But after walking two steps, he stopped It seemed like he remembered something. Then he knelt down in the direction where Lin Fei had left earlier and performed a deep bow.

"Benefactor, I will always remember your kindness today and never forget it in my lifetime!"

After that, with his sister, he followed one of the disciples into the Hidden Sword Sect.

Lin Fei followed Lu Zongyi. They came to Lu Zongyi's cave dwelling. The two sat down, and a maid served them fragrant tea.

Lu Zongyi smiled and said, "Brother Lin, it's been two months since we last met. Every time I recall the events of the last martial arts exchange, I am grateful to Brother Lin. Since Brother Lin has come to my Hidden Sword Sect this time, I'm afraid there must be something. Brother Lin, please speak, I will definitely help with all my might!"

Lu Zongyi didn't say any polite words. He directly stated his attitude.

Lin Fei nodded and said, "With Brother Lu's words, I can rest assured. I have only one purpose for visiting the Hidden Sword Sect, to sharpen my saber intent! My saber intent is about to transcend.

I heard that besides Brother Lu, the Hidden Sword Sect has the world's number one sword in this generation, which has also comprehended sword intent, and it is very powerful. I would like to ask for the opportunity to exchange martial dao true intent with the world's number one sword. I hope it can help me break through my bottleneck and achieve saber intent transcendence!"

Lin Fei also directly stated his purpose.

"What? Brother Lin's saber intent is about to transcend?"

Lu Zongyi widened his eyes. His eyes were full of disbelief. That's saber intent transcendence!

Lu Zongyi had mastered sword intent a few years ago.

And now?

His sword intent had almost stagnated to achieve sword intent transcendence, Lu Zongyi even felt it was hopeless in his lifetime.

Last time at the martial arts exchange, Lu Zongyi confronted Lin Fei's saber intent with his sword intent. He didn't expect Lin Fei's saber intent to transcend so soon. This progress was so fast. It was hard for Lu Zongyi to believe.

"Brother Lin, sabers and swords are ruthless, let alone exchanging martial dao true intent? Moreover, the world's number one sword in this generation of my Hidden Sword Sect has been in seclusion. As for when he will come out, I don't know."

Lin Fei frowned slightly, "So there's no way to exchange?"

Although Lu Zongyi had sword intent, Lin Fei's saber intent was far stronger than his even if they exchanged, Lin Fei's saber intent wouldn't improve at all.

"There is no way to exchange. However, if Brother Lin wants to sharpen your saber intent and wants it to transcend, I have a way. It's just that this method may have some risks. It depends on whether Brother Lin is willing to take the risk."

Lu Zongyi looked solemn and stared at Lin Fei with a serious gaze.

137. Sword Tomb

"Brother Lu, please tell me, what is the method?" Lin Fei slowly asked.

"In Hidden Sword Sect, there is a place called the Sword Tomb! All the predecessors in the sect, after their death, their accompanying swords are buried in the Sword Tomb. Among them, there are quite a few martial arts masters who have comprehended sword intent.

Over a thousand years, the number of swords buried in the Sword Tomb has accumulated to be countless! When the swordsmen of my Hidden Sword Sect condense sword intent, over time, the sword intent will attach itself to the accompanying swords. Even after hundreds or thousands of years, they will not dissipate.

If someone enters the Sword Tomb and stimulates Martial Dao True Intent, it will certainly provoke the sword intent inside the tomb, isn't this a way to sharpen your intent?

However, there are too many sword intents in the Sword Tomb. More than a hundred sword intents once provoked, are unparalleled in their attack. If you cannot withstand it, Brother Lin, I'm afraid your saber intent will be damaged, and the consequences would be unimaginable!"

Lin Fei's eyes lit up.

"Sword Tomb?"

Lin Fei didn't expect that the Hidden Sword Sect would have such a place. The depth of its foundation was simply unimaginable. More than a hundred sword intents! That meant that the Hidden Sword Sect had at least given birth to more than a hundred powerful martial artists who had comprehended sword intent. This deep foundation was far beyond what the Nine Profound Sect could compare to.

"Brother Lu, I would like to try my luck in the Sword Tomb."

Lin Fei immediately expressed his stance. This Sword Tomb was an excellent place. More than a hundred sword intents sharpening his saber intent together, as long as he could withstand it, Lin Fei was confident that he could achieve saber intent transcendence!

"The Sword Tomb is of great significance to my Hidden Sword Sect. Generally, outsiders are not allowed to enter. However, Brother Lin has done me a great favor. With my guarantee, Brother Lin can naturally enter the Sword Tomb," Lu Zongyi got up, "Brother Lin, come with me."

Lin Fei also stood up and followed behind Lu Zongyi. They left the cave dwelling. Lin Fei followed Lu Zongyi to another mountain peak. He didn't know if it was his illusion. This mountain peak, at first glance, seemed like a long sword, reaching the sky!

"What a majestic mountain peak!" Lin Fei exclaimed.

"Brother Lin, this is the Sword Tomb Peak, and the Sword Tomb is right above. Under normal circumstances, no one wants to come to the Sword Tomb. Besides sword intent, there is also sorrow here, which is the sadness of the sword, and it will affect people's emotions as well.

Especially for the swordsmen of our Hidden Sword Sect, the impact is even greater. Therefore, I will not accompany you up there.

Oh, one last thing. I hope that you won't touch the items inside the Sword Tomb, Brother Lin. Especially those swords, as they are the relics of our Hidden Sword Sect's predecessors for our disciples."

Lin Fei nodded and said, "I will only hone my saber intent and will not disturb the items in the Sword Tomb!"

Having said that, Lin Fei looked at the narrow staircase leading up to the Sword Tomb Peak.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei took a step and instantly set foot on the stone steps of the Sword Tomb Peak. Step by step, he walked towards the top of Sword Tomb Peak.

The higher he went, the stronger the wind became. The cold was bone-chilling. Moreover, faintly, it seemed as if there were whispers of sorrow. That was the sorrowful cry of the swords.

Lin Fei was undeterred and quickly reached the summit. The summit was the Sword Tomb. Underneath every piece of the ground, there might be a sword buried. Each sword once represented a disciple of the Hidden Sword Sect.

Whether it was a disciple at the body refining level or a martial arts master, in the Sword Tomb, they were all treated equally, all were qualified to have their swords buried in the Sword Tomb after death. Therefore, the number of swords buried in the Sword Tomb was far more than ten thousand.

"Crack."

Lin Fei walked in the Sword Tomb. He accidentally stepped on a sword. The sword was broken.

It was just a broken sword. And it was rusty. It was unclear how long it had been there.

Lin Fei looked around. In all directions, there were similar broken swords.

At this moment, Lin Fei didn't show his saber intent. Naturally, no sword intent appeared.

"Forgive me, predecessors of Hidden Sword Sect!"

Lin Fei took a deep breath and bowed with his fists toward the four corners of the Sword Tomb.

The next moment, Lin Fei mobilized his saber intent and burst forth.

"Boom."

A terrifying saber intent erupted from Lin Fei's body. The horrifying saber intent, like a tidal wave, swept towards all directions. The originally calm Sword Tomb, at this moment, the tranquility was completely shattered.

"Buzz."

Suddenly, the entire Sword Tomb seemed to vibrate. There were faint bursts of "sword cries" echoing throughout the Sword Tomb.

"Boom."

The first sword intent appeared. It was a rusty iron sword. It looked plain and ordinary, but it didn't affect the terrifying sword intent. It instantly rushed towards Lin Fei's saber intent.

"A transcendence-level sword intent?"

Lin Fei's whole body shook. This sword intent was indeed strong. It was only slightly weaker than perfection-level sword intent. With the appearance of the first one, the second followed, then came the third, fourth, fifth...

In a blink of an eye, there were dozens, even hundreds of sword intents soaring into the sky. It was as if hundreds of divine swords had gathered in the sky above the Sword Tomb.

The strength of these sword intents far exceeded any perfection-level sword intent. Even Lin Fei was initially hit hard and his face turned deathly pale.

This was the first time Lin Fei's saber intent was suppressed by other Martial Dao True Intents. Of course, the sword intent on the stone tablet of the Ancestral Master Peak didn't count.

Although the sword intent on the Ancestral Master Peak's stone tablet was perfection-level, its quantity was small and it had been weakened a lot after being preserved for hundreds of years. Lin Fei could completely resist it.

But now it was different. The sword intents in the Sword Tomb had also been preserved for hundreds, even thousands of years. There were so many of them. Not only ordinary sword intents, but also mastery, transcendence, and even perfection-level sword intents. All of them were in the Sword Tomb.

Therefore, when hundreds of sword intents erupted at once, The impact on Lin Fei's saber intent was tremendous. However, this also gave Lin Fei's saber intent an opportunity. This was the true test!

One second, two seconds, three seconds...

As he forcefully persevered with his saber intent, finally, Lin Fei reaped the rewards. A voice rang in Lin Fei's mind, from the system.

"Your saber intent is being attacked by hundreds of sword intents."

"Your saber intent is tenacious and becomes stronger as the battle continues, increasing its cultivation progress by 10%."

"Your saber intent has transcended!"

"Boom."

As the voice in his mind fell, Lin Fei's mind began to roar. Then, a memory emerged in Lin Fei's mind. It was a memory about saber intent.

At this moment, Lin Fei was overjoyed. He could feel it his saber intent had completely transformed.

Lin Fei's aura was visibly increasing at a rapid pace. In the sky above the Sword Tomb, the overwhelming saber intent seemed to condense into a large saber, hanging above the Sword Tomb.

Dozens, even hundreds of sword intents constantly attacked Lin Fei's saber intent. However, it had no effect. Lin Fei's saber intent only grew stronger. In the end, it faintly seemed to condense into a substantial form and formed a vast saber intent web, enveloping the Sword Tomb.

Lin Fei's robe fluttered in the wind. His saber intent grew more and more intense.

"Slash!"

Lin Fei's eyes were cold. The invisible saber intent seemed to descend from the sky and slashed fiercely at the Sword Tomb.

"Boom."

An invisible force suddenly exploded in the entire Sword Tomb. The shockwave spread out in all directions. Lin Fei's saber intent actually suppressed hundreds of sword intents.

"Buzz."

At this moment, Lin Fei seemed to hear the sorrowful cries of the swords. Perhaps, these swords in the Sword Tomb had never felt as aggrieved as they did now. They had once followed their masters, conquering all sides, sweeping across all obstacles, and being invincible.

However, after being buried in the Sword Tomb, they were suppressed by saber intent. Each sword intent was incredibly angry! Then, one by one, the swords buried in the Sword Tomb began to tremble slightly.

Ten swords, a hundred, a thousand, ten thousand...

When tens of thousands of swords began to tremble, a series of soft cries echoed, as if they were weeping. That was the lament of ten thousand swords!

"Rumble."

At this moment, the entire Hidden Sword Sect shook violently. Even the Sword Tomb Peak began to tremble.

Lu Zongyi at the foot of the Sword Tomb Peak suddenly looked up. His eyes were filled with shock as he stared at Sword Tomb Peak. In his ears, the mournful cries of swords also reached him.

"Ten Thousand Swords Lament! Brother Lin, what exactly did you do in the Sword Tomb?"

Lu Zongyi suddenly had an ominous feeling in his heart.

138. Number One Sword Under Heaven

At this moment, the entire Hidden Sword Sect was shaken.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

One innate martial artist after another, some were in seclusion, and some were practicing their sword skills. But at this moment, they all turned their eyes towards the Sword Tomb Peak. Some even rushed directly to the foot of the Sword Tomb Peak.

"What happened to the Sword Tomb?"

"Elder Lu, what's going on at the foot of the Sword Tomb Peak?"

"Why would Sword Tomb Peak tremble for no reason?"

"Moreover, there's the sound of swords from the Sword Tomb."

"This is the lament of ten thousand swords. What happened?"

In a short time, more than a dozen innate martial artists had gathered. This was not the entire Hidden Sword Sect. There were definitely more than twenty innate martial artists in the Hidden Sword Sect.

This was the foundation of the Hidden Sword Sect. Each generation had the world's number one sword master and could be considered the world's number one martial arts sect!

Everyone's eyes were on Lu Zongyi. Lu Zongyi smiled bitterly and said, "I don't know what's going on with the Sword Tomb either. But, I have a rough idea of who is involved. It's the Immortal Slayer Saber on the Sword Tomb Peak!"

"What, Immortal Slayer Saber?"

"Lu Zongyi, you let the Immortal Slayer Saber enter the Sword Tomb?"

"No wonder the Sword Tomb is lamenting. The Immortal Slayer Saber has comprehended saber intent, and it must have done something in the Sword Tomb."

For a moment, all the martial arts masters were indignant. The Sword Tomb was the "sacred place" of the Hidden Sword Sect. Now Lu Zongyi had allowed a saber-wielding guest who had comprehended saber intent to enter, which made the martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect feel very uncomfortable. Especially the sword intent erupted from the Sword Tomb was obviously at a disadvantage.

"Clang!"

However, before these martial arts masters could climb the mountain, from a distant peak, an overwhelming aura surged out. This aura was majestic and vast. Like an unparalleled treasure sword, it soared straight into the sky.

"That's Soaring Skies Peak, it's Senior Brother Liu's sword intent!"

"Senior Brother Liu has also been alerted and even came out of seclusion."

All the martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect had a look of astonishment. Soaring Skies Peak was Liu Yibai's mountain. The world's number one sword master of this generation in the Hidden Sword Sect, Liu Yibai, finally came out of seclusion!

At this moment, inside the Sword Tomb, Lin Fei's transcended saber intent, with an incredibly domineering manner, directly suppressed hundreds of sword intents.

Ten thousand swords lamented. The entire Sword Tomb began to tremble. However, Lin Fei had indeed gained enormous benefits. Because the system's voice rang in his mind.

"Your saber intent has overcome difficulties, breaking through the suppression of hundreds of sword intents, and your cultivation progress has increased by 10%."

"Your saber intent, with its supreme dominance, has suppressed ten thousand swords, making them lament."

"Your saber intent has gained immense satisfaction, and its cultivation progress has increased by 20%."

Lin Fei was shocked. His saber intent was rapidly increasing. Moreover, having previously resisted the impact of hundreds of sword intents, his saber intent's cultivation progress had already increased by 10%. Now it had increased by 40%. This was a terrifying number.

Lin Fei's saber intent had already transcended and it was not over yet. The saber intent was not just saber intent. It was also related to the True Intention Scroll.

Because the Saber Qi Lin Fei cultivated from his True Intention Scroll was actually a fusion of saber intent. The stronger the saber intent, the stronger the Saber Qi. Naturally, it could drive the cultivation progress of the True Intention Scroll.

Now, the saber intent had suddenly increased the cultivation progress by 40%. Immediately, the Saber Qi within Lin Fei's body began to increase crazily.

"Your increase in saber intent makes the True Intention Scroll suffer twice as much."

"Under the double incentive of saber intent, the True Intention Scroll fuses the saber intent crazily, and the Saber Qi surges."

"Your True Intention Scroll cultivation progress has increased by 40%."

"Your True Intention Scroll breaks through to the late stage!"

Lin Fei's Saber Qi within his body finally broke through another bottleneck, reaching the late stage directly! At the same time, the Saber Qi within Lin Fei's body was also surging wildly. Not an increase of 10% or 20%, but doubling, tripling five times, or even ten times!

The True Intention Scroll, created by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect, was the fusion of Innate True Qi and saber intent. An increase in a realm had an incredibly large span.

"Boom."

Above the Sword Tomb, in the void, a faint, translucent vortex appeared. Only innate martial artists could "sense" this vortex. This was a spiritual energy vortex!

For Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll to break through and his Saber Qi to surge, he naturally needed a large amount of Spiritual Qi. Therefore, Lin Fei's transcendent saber intent was able to cover a part of the void, helping Lin Fei "capture" a large amount of Spiritual Qi from the heavens and the earth.

In the void, it was as if a Spiritual Qi pillar had formed, pouring straight into Lin Fei's body. From innate Spiritual Qi to Innate True Qi, and then to Saber Qi.

This conversion speed was very fast. Lin Fei seemed to feel that the True Intention Scroll was desperately transforming. With the pride of the True Intention Scroll, it certainly didn't want to be so desperate. But now that the Saber Qi was too strong, and the True Intention Scroll was being suppressed by the saber intent, it could only practice desperately.

At every moment, Lin Fei could feel his strength improving. It had been a long time since he had experienced such a rapid increase in power.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately summoned the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Late Stage

True Intention Scroll: Late Stage (32% Progress)

Saber Intent: Transcendence (36% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (51% Progress)

Heavenly Saber Art: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Indeed, on the system panel, Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll had reached the late stage. His saber intent had even reached transcendence. Moreover, the distance to perfection wasn't too far. At least, it was now within reach.

"Coming to the Hidden Sword Sect was the right choice!" Lin Fei muttered to himself.

"Swish."

At this moment, a terrifying sword intent soared into the sky, piercing straight into the clouds. This sword intent was sharp and pure, like a peerless divine sword that had been hidden for decades and was finally unsheathed. Its sharp aura seemed as if it could pierce the heavens.

Lin Fei suddenly looked up. Vaguely, he saw a figure dressed in white as pure as snow. Step by step, it slowly walked into the Sword Tomb.

Lin Fei saw the figure clearly. It was a man who didn't appear to be young. His temples were already graying. It seemed to reveal traces of the passage of time. His eyes were extremely deep, showing no hint of sharpness. However, his sword intent was sharp to the extreme.

As the man walked step by step, his sword intent seemed to be gathering strength. When he arrived at the Sword Tomb, the man's sword intent reached its peak. The terrifying sword intent solidified as if it had become real, continuously colliding, cutting, and entangling with Lin Fei's saber intent.

For the first time, Lin Fei encountered a living martial artist whose Martial Dao True Intent could rival his saber intent. It should be known that Lin Fei's saber intent had already reached transcendence, but when it came to Martial Dao True Intent alone, the two sides were evenly matched and equally strong.

In the Hidden Sword Sect, there was only one person who could reach the transcendence of sword intent.

"Number One Sword Under Heaven, Liu Yibai!"

Lin Fei looked at the man with graying temples in front of him.

139. Two Hundred And Fifty Meters Of Saber Energy

Hidden Sword Sect was a very strange sect. They had an obsession with swords that was difficult for ordinary people to understand. For the disciples of the Hidden Sword Sect, swords were their family, even a part of their bodies.

They practice swordsmanship, fight with swords, and consider being second-best a disgrace. They all strive to be the best. Among them, the title "Number One Sword Under Heaven" is the most typical.

Every generation of the Hidden Sword Sect must fight to claim the title of "Number One Sword Under Heaven." If they cannot win the title, the whole sect would be shamed and seen as a disgrace!

For thousands of years, almost every generation of the Hidden Sword Sect had had the title of "Number One Sword Under Heaven." However, there have been exceptions.

For example, 900 years ago, during the era of the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. That era belonged to the founder of the Nine Profound Sect! No matter fists, swords, or sabers, the founder of Nine Profound Sect was the best in the world!

When the founder of the Nine Profound Sect dominated the world, the Hidden Sword Sect was very frustrated. Because they couldn't win the title of the Number One Sword Under Heaven no matter what. So, for an entire generation, Hidden Sword Sect was suppressed by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. And this generation's "Number One Sword Under Heaven" of the Hidden Sword Sect was this man with graying temples in front of him, Liu Yibai!

Liu Yibai stopped. He calmly looked at Lin Fei.

"Immortal Slayer Saber, Lin Fei! Moreover, you're from the Nine Profound Sect. Back then, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect suppressed our Hidden Sword Sect for an entire generation. It seems that the Nine Profound Sect is about to rise again.

Late stage Master, saber intent at transcendence. You once defeated He Yuanzi and He Qingzi, two high-level Qi Condensation experts with your saber, making your name known throughout the world.

Not long ago, at the Martial Alliance Exchange, you defeated Yuan Gangzi, another top-tier Qi Condensation expert with your saber. Your martial talent is almost on par with the founder of the Nine Profound Sect back then."

Liu Yibai recounted Lin Fei's past achievements as if they were old friends reminiscing. However, their saber and sword intents constantly clashed and fought in the void. Some innate martial artists didn't even dare to approach them. Getting too close would cause them to be affected by the aftershocks of the two's Martial Dao True Intent, even innate martial artists couldn't withstand it.

The entire Sword Tomb could now only accommodate Lin Fei and Liu Yibai.

Lin Fei's gaze was also calm. He said lightly, "Number One Sword Under Heaven' Liu Yibai. Thirty years ago, you left Hidden Sword Sect to challenge the thirteen martial factions, remaining undefeated. Later, you defeated numerous sword masters to claim the title of Number One Sword Under Heaven. Since then, you returned to Hidden Sword Sect and sealed your sword for thirty years. Thirty years without drawing the sword. Liu Yibai, are you going to unsheath your sword today?"

Liu Yibai stared at Lin Fei and said calmly, "I've been sitting in my cave dwelling for thirty years, just to break through my shackles. Unfortunately, I haven't been able to break through my shackles in thirty years. I understand, I need an opportunity. An opportunity to unsheathe my sword.

Now that you're here, I sense that opportunity. After thirty years of concealing my sword, today, I shall reveal it in your presence. With this strike, I hope the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' will oblige!"

Gradually, Liu Yibai's hand gripped the sword hilt.

"I, too, possess a saber; when my saber is unleashed, all others bow!"

Lin Fei also reached out his fair hand. A terrifying saber energy brewed within him. Once it erupted, it would surely shake the heavens.

Liu Yibai had concealed his sword for thirty years. To break through, he needed someone to test his sword against. Not just anyone was worthy of being Liu Yibai's test subject.

Lin Fei was qualified. Because he was the Immortal Slayer Saber. He could suppress a hundred sword intents, making ten thousand swords wail in despair!

Lin Fei had now advanced to the late master stage. His saber intent had reached transcendence. He, too, wished to test his saber. It had been a long time since he had swung his saber with all his might.

In the entire world, few could now compel Lin Fei to strike with all his strength. One who had once dominated the world's swordsmen as the world's number one sword. Another, the Immortal Slayer Saber, whose saber would surely slay immortals, its fame shaking the world!

One to test a sword. One to test a saber.

Suddenly, the wind began to blow atop the Sword Tomb. The cold wind pierced to the bone. Clothes rustled in the wind. Both stood silently in their places and no one spoke.

"Whoosh."

Liu Yibai made his move. His swordsmanship was never about reacting. His sword emphasized the word "first." One step ahead, always ahead!

Thus, Liu Yibai unsheathed his sword first. A dazzling sword light instantly tore through the void.

In Lin Fei's eyes, it seemed as if the entire world contained only this single sword. Brilliant white light. A sharp sword edge.

Liu Yibai was, after all, the only Grand Master of the entire Hidden Sword Sect. His Innate True Qi had already reached perfection!

This strike was also the first time the Grand Master, Liu Yibai, had taken action after concealing his sword for thirty years. And it was a full-force strike. His sword had always been a one-strike weapon. Victory or defeat all in this single strike.

Lin Fei also unleashed his saber. However, his method of doing so was quite unique. He extended his hand. Then, the Saber Qi within his body exploded with a roar.

"Vroom."

In the next moment, a surging, torrential saber energy, like a volcanic eruption, instantly burst forth from his body.

"Tyrant Saber!"

The saber Lin Fei condensed was the Tyrant Saber from the "Heavenly Saber Art." The vast saber energy rapidly converged in the void. However, this time the saber energy extended far beyond thirty meters.

Thirty meters, sixty meters, ninety meters, one hundred and twenty meters, one hundred and fifty meters...

The saber energy in front of Lin Fei rapidly soared. Incredibly, it rose from thirty meters to two hundred and fifty meters! The terrifying saber energy exuded an endless aura of dominance. This was the Tyrant Saber! Moreover, it was the Tyrant Saber condensed from two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy!

Lin Fei's eyes were deep. He calmly gazed at the sword light in the void.

"This is my saber! Heavenly Saber Art, strike!"

Lin Fei used his palm as a saber. Then, with a wave of his hand,

"Boom."

two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy resembled a towering pillar, emanating a ruthless Tyrant Saber energy, vast and overwhelming, crushing everything in its path.

Originally, the sky around them seemed to contain only that single sword light. But now, as soon as Lin Fei's two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy appeared, the sword light shattered.

Seeing Lin Fei's two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy, Liu Yibai felt a shock in his heart. Then, the sword light in his hand unexpectedly surged again. Even the saber intent seemed to be on the verge of reaching its limit, about to transform.

But it wasn't enough. Still not enough. Nowhere near enough!

...

Just a little bit more. With just a little bit more, Liu Yibai's sword intent could reach perfection.

"Crack."

The next moment, the saber energy and sword light didn't even collide. Liu Yibai's sword actually began to show faint cracks, as if it would shatter completely at any moment.

"The sword... is breaking..."

Liu Yibai closed his eyes. This sword had accompanied him for decades, once wielding to dominate the world, earning the reputation of "Number One Sword Under Heaven."

But now, the sword was about to break. One crack after another appeared on its surface, torn apart by the saber energy. If it weren't for his Innate True Qi protecting it, it would have shattered long ago.

"Bang."

Finally, the sword in Liu Yibai's hand completely crumbled.

"Whoosh."

However, the next moment, Liu Yibai suddenly opened his eyes. And his sword intent, at this very moment, transformed like a butterfly breaking free from its cocoon, reaching perfection!

Sword intent perfected!

At this moment, Liu Yibai finally achieved perfection in his sword intent!

"Sword, come forth!"

Liu Yibai beckoned. His voice seemed to reverberate through the void.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

Instantly, countless swords on the Sword Tomb flew out, numerous swords hummed softly. Yet, they did not wail in despair but rejoiced. They were jubilant. It was as if these swords, hidden deep within the Sword Tomb, had been granted a new lease on life.

One sword after another overlapped, radiating dazzling sword light. It also stretched almost one hundred meters.

"Slash!"

Liu Yibai also fiercely waved his hand.

Immediately, the one hundred meters of sword light, likewise slashed towards the void.

"Boom."

Two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy and one hundred meters of sword light, at this moment, finally collided completely!

140. Number One Saber Under Heaven

At the foot of Sword Tomb Peak, many martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect gathered together.

Their eyes widened, staring intently at the scene above the Sword Tomb. The two hundred and fifty meters saber energy was vast and overwhelming as if it could destroy everything. Everyone knew it was the saber energy of the Immortal Slayer Saber!

At the Martial Alliance Exchange, Lu Zongyi had personally witnessed Lin Fei unleashing more than thirty meters of saber energy. With one strike, he defeated the top-tier Qi Condensation expert Yuan Gangzi.

And now?

Two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy!

Seeing this scene, Lu Zongyi fell silent. How much time had passed? From the Martial Alliance Exchange to now, it had only been a mere two months. And in just two months, Lin Fei was already able to slash out two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy.

On the other hand, there was the pride of the Hidden Sword Sect, the "Number One Sword Under Heaven" of this generation in the Hidden Sword Sect, Liu Yibai!

They all knew Liu Yibai's situation. His Innate True Qi had long reached perfection, and he had advanced to the Grand Master realm. His sword intent had also transcended long ago but always fell just a bit short. He had concealed his sword for thirty years, all in search of an opportunity to break through.

Therefore, when Liu Yibai drew his sword, it would surely be earth-shattering and the strongest sword in his life. Almost one hundred meters of sword light lived up to everyone's expectations. It made the martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect feel their hearts tremble. The sword light was simply astonishing.

However, who was stronger and who was weaker? Was it the Number One Sword Under Heaven? Or the Immortal Slayer Saber?

No one knew. Even Lin Fei and Liu Yibai, who were confronting each other on the Sword Tomb, didn't know.

"Crack."

The two terrifying forces of saber energy and sword light continuously collided and intertwined. The aftermath spread out in all directions like ripples on the water. Wherever it passed, the Sword Tomb was leveled.

Finally, the clouds dispersed, and the wind was gentle. Both the saber energy and the sword light had disappeared.

Lin Fei stood quietly on the Sword Tomb. All around were broken sword fragments. And opposite Lin Fei, Liu Yibai, wearing a white robe, spotlessly clean. He also stood quietly, neither of them spoke.

At this time, seeing that there was no movement on the Sword Tomb, the dozen or so Hidden Sword Sect martial arts masters at the foot of the mountain also hurried to the Sword Tomb.

"Grand Elder Liu, you..."

A martial arts master wanted to step forward and support Liu Yibai, but Liu Yibai slightly shook his head.

The crowd was puzzled. Both of them seemed to be fine. They didn't know who had the upper hand in the end.

Liu Yibai lowered his head. Everyone followed Liu Yibai's gaze. A corner of Liu Yibai's robe, with a "puff" sound, was cut off and fell to the ground.

Everyone was astonished but Liu Yibai laughed.

"The 'Immortal Slayer Saber' lives up to its name. I admit defeat!"

Liu Yibai's words shocked everyone. All the martial arts masters widened their eyes as if they couldn't believe Liu Yibai's words.

How could Liu Yibai lose? How could the Number One Sword Under Heaven lose? How could a Grand Master lose?

Lin Fei's tone was very calm, responding indifferently, "The 'Number One Sword Under Heaven' is indeed well-deserved. Grand Master is also well-deserved. Actually, this time, it's not really about who wins and who loses.

If it wasn't for your sword intent just breaking through and fighting hastily, I wouldn't have been able to cut your robe's corner. You are the first martial artist to ever block my saber energy!"

Liu Yibai shook his head, "I just took advantage of the location. Without the hundreds of sword intents in the Sword Tomb to assist me, I'm afraid I wouldn't be able to withstand your saber.

However, no matter what, I must thank you. Concealing my sword for thirty years, I finally found the opportunity today. I drew my sword and unleashed thirty years of sharpness, also cutting away thirty years of depression. Now, my achievements are perfection, and my sword intent has reached perfection as well. I owe you a favor, Brother Lin!"

Liu Yibai didn't seem to care too much about winning or losing anymore. His initial shout of "Sword, come forth!" was not just a casual one. After his sword intent reached perfection, the power of the hundreds of sword intents in the Sword Tomb reinforced his sword. Only then could he compete with Lin Fei's two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy.

Otherwise, in other places, without so many sword intents, Liu Yibai would probably not be able to withstand Lin Fei's saber.

This saber was truly earth-shattering. Even now, as Liu Yibai recalled it, he still felt palpitations. Even though his sword intent had reached perfection and he was a true Grand Master, he had no confidence that he could block Lin Fei's saber again.

"Lin Fei, I am the Number One Sword Under Heaven. And you, you shall be Number One Saber Under Heaven!"

Today, the surrounding Hidden Sword Sect martial arts masters had already been shocked countless times.

Number One Saber Under Heaven!

If these words were spoken by someone else, it would probably be taken as a joke. But these words were spoken by Liu Yibai. From the Number One Sword Under Heaven, from the mouth of a martial arts Grand Master. It was different.

Moreover, just now Lin Fei's saber had unleashed two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy. Just with this one saber! Lin Fei's title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven" was truly well-deserved!

"Back then, the Nine Profound Sect's founder was unparalleled in fist, saber, and sword. Whether it was the Number One Sword Under Heaven or the Number One Saber Under Heaven, they were all from the Nine Profound Sect's founder."

"Unexpectedly, now the Nine Profound Sect has given birth to another 'Number One Saber Under Heaven'."

"And, 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei hasn't even become a martial arts Grand Master yet. He can still continue to improve, and his future achievements are unimaginable."

"Could this be another figure like the Nine Profound Sect's founder?"

The many martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect were extremely shocked in their hearts. They looked at Lin Fei with complicated gazes.

As martial artists, especially the martial arts masters of Hidden Sword Sect, they actually didn't want any martial artist to surpass Hidden Sword Sect. Hidden Sword Sect had been glorious for thousands of years. Except when Great Chang's founding emperor swept the world and established Great Chang.

At that time, Hidden Sword Sect had no Martial Saint. It was suppressed by Great Chang's founding emperor. Being suppressed by a Martial Saint was somewhat understandable.

However, there was another era. That was the era of the Nine Profound Sect's founder. The Nine Profound Sect's founder, as a Grand Master, suppressed the entire world's martial arts! Hidden Sword Sect was also unable to hold its head high. At that time, Hidden Sword Sect also had a Grand Master.

But what about it?

No matter how many Grand Masters, the Nine Profound Sect's founder only needed one sword, one saber, and one punch. He didn't even need to use a second move.

Such a peerless figure suppressed Hidden Sword Sect for an entire generation, making the millennium of the glory of the Hidden Sword Sect seem dim and dull.

Now, the Hidden Sword Sect has finally gradually recovered its vitality and a Grand Master had been born. Moreover, his sword intent had reached perfection. He was a Grand Master with perfected sword intent.

But now, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei appeared. Just as astonishingly talented as the Nine Profound Sect's founder but even younger than the Nine Profound Sect's founder.

Lin Fei was now only at the late stage of the Master level, but he could slightly surpass the perfected sword intent of Liu Yibai. In the future, when Lin Fei's saber intent reached perfection and he achieved the level of Grand Master, wouldn't he be able to suppress the world horizontally?

Hidden Sword Sect was very likely to be suppressed by Lin Fei for an entire generation again! For a moment, the martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect felt bitter in their hearts. Everyone looked at Lin Fei with complicated expressions. The atmosphere in the entire Sword Tomb seemed to quiet down all at once.

"Lin Fei, do you want to build your foundation?"

At this moment, Liu Yibai suddenly spoke and his gaze fixed on Lin Fei.

141. The Secret of Foundation Establishment

Lin Fei's gaze was as sharp as a saber. He stared intently at Liu Yibai.

This was not the first time Lin Fei had heard this term. Martial artists also needed to build their foundation, but it was different from Qi Condensation practitioners. Martial artists build the foundation of their martial arts.

This martial arts foundation was even more difficult than the immortal dao foundation! Even the Nine Profound Sect's founder, who once suppressed the world and was peerlessly brilliant, ultimately failed to build his foundation successfully. This showed how difficult foundation building was!

"Which martial artist in the world doesn't want to build their foundation? However, the difficulty of foundation building is as difficult as ascending to the heavens. Could it be that Elder Liu has a way to build the foundation?" Lin Fei spoke slowly, word by word.

Liu Yibai did not speak. He waved his hand.

"Clang clang."

The broken swords on the Sword Tomb all vibrated. Then they were buried underground.

"Elder Lin, this is where the predecessors of our Hidden Sword Sect buried their swords. Let's not disturb the swords of our predecessors. How about going to my cave dwelling to talk?"

Lin Fei nodded and said, "In that case, I will respectfully comply!"

Lin Fei had no problem becoming a martial arts Grand Master with his perfected saber intent and saber energy.

Even Lin Fei believed that he would not be inferior to the founder of the Nine Profound Sect in the future, but it was the foundation building that Lin Fei had no confidence. After all, even the Nine Profound Sect's founder failed to build his foundation successfully. He didn't know any information about foundation building. He was naturally very interested in Liu Yibai's invitation.

Liu Yibai glanced at the surrounding martial arts masters and spoke calmly, "I ask that today's matter not be spread by the elders present."

Liu Yibai was not afraid that others would know he couldn't handle Lin Fei. It was just that the current situation in Great Chang was unfavorable for martial artists. What he and Lin Fei were going to do was not a trivial matter. The news must not be leaked.

"Elder Liu, rest assured, we understand and will not spread the news!"

The surrounding martial arts masters also responded one after another. At the same time, their hearts gradually settled down. Foundation building was the pursuit of martial arts masters. Even if Lin Fei, the Number One Saber Under Heaven, was strong, so what?

Once Liu Yibai successfully built his foundation. Their Hidden Sword Sect would have been the only Martial Saint in Great Chang for the past three hundred years.

A Martial Saint is a saint in martial arts! Once they achieved the status of a Martial Saint, they would be much stronger than ordinary Foundation Establishment cultivators.

More importantly, martial Saints had a long lifespan. They could protect the Hidden Sword Sect for hundreds of years, allowing the Hidden Sword Sect to remain at its peak and flourish during this time.

Thus, talents would continue to emerge and there would be no fear of the sect's decline. The two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy that Lin Fei had unleashed earlier had shocked the martial arts masters, but they gradually calmed down now.

Their Hidden Sword Sect's Grand Elder Liu Yibai had already achieved sword intent perfection and True Qi perfection. He was now ready to start building his foundation.

Even if Lin Fei were really another founder of the Nine Profound Sect, if the Hidden Sword Sect gave birth to a Martial Saint, there would be no fear of being suppressed for an era.

Everyone left the Sword Tomb one after another. Lin Fei followed Liu Yibai, flying towards his cave dwelling. Soon, the two arrived at Liu Yibai's cave dwelling. This cave dwelling was located on Soaring Skies Peak, which was Liu Yibai's mountain.

Entering the cave dwelling, Lin Fei saw that the surrounding arrangements were very simple. There was no unnecessary clutter. Everything was practical and minimalist to be able to cultivate.

In such a cave dwelling for thirty years, Lin Fei admitted to himself that he couldn't do it. How strong and determined must one's spirit and will be? It was no coincidence that Liu Yibai achieved sword intent perfection.

The two sat down cross-legged. Liu Yibai was the first to speak, asking, "Elder Lin, do you know the conditions for foundation building in martial arts?"

"Conditions?"

Lin Fei shook his head and said, "I'm not hiding anything from Elder Liu. Nine Profound Sect has never produced a Martial Saint who has built its foundation. Thus, I know nothing about foundation building in martial arts. Please enlighten me, Elder Liu!"

Liu Yibai nodded slightly and said with a smile, "The so-called foundation building, those Qi cultivators say it's like a carp leaping over the dragon's gate, it's the foundation for 'becoming immortal' or 'achieving dao.' It sounds profound and mysterious.

However, in the eyes of us martial artists, foundation building is actually very simple. It's a metamorphosis, allowing our bodies to transform anew. The human body has its limits. This is a natural restriction; we can't infinitely increase our Innate True Qi, nor can our physical bodies be infinitely strengthened.

What should we do when our bodies reach their true limits? That's when we build our foundation! Once the foundation is successfully built, it's equivalent to a different level of life, a sublimation of life.

That's why those Qi cultivators call those who have built their foundation 'True Person.' And we martial artists, after building our foundation, are called Martial Saints, transcending the mundane and becoming holy in martial arts!"

Lin Fei understood. Both Immortal Dao Qi cultivators and martial artists could build their foundation. Although the foundation-building methods were different, in fact, both were the sublimation of life. Otherwise, it would not be possible for one's lifespan to increase significantly upon building their foundation.

It was equivalent to a different level of life. Only in this way could they break free from the original constraints of the human body and continue to enhance their strength.

"Martial arts foundation building requires one to reach their limit. The limit, which we also call perfection, requires three perfections! Physical Body Perfection, True Qi Perfection, and Mental Perfection.

In fact, these three perfections represent the essence, qi, and spirit of the human body, and none can be lacking. True Qi Perfection is when Innate True Qi reaches perfection, which is commonly known as a martial arts Grand Master.

The mind is unfathomable. Martial artists use their will to represent the mind, so martial artists need to comprehend Martial Dao True Intent. Once Martial Dao True Intent reaches perfection, it represents mental perfection.

The last one, physical body perfection, refers to the body. We, martial artists, have been refining the body from the beginning, which, in a sense, is actually laying the foundation for physical body perfection. However, is the ultimate Body Refining, giving birth to inner power, truly the ultimate?

Not necessarily. That is not the ultimate physical body; if we want to build our foundation, we must cultivate the physical body to the extreme and elevate it to the extreme.

And this is actually very difficult. Because physical body perfection is the only one that cannot be achieved solely by the martial artist. It also requires the help of external objects."

"External objects?"

Lin Fei's heart was moved.

"Yes, external objects. All kinds of heavenly materials and earthly treasures, rare birds, exotic beasts, etc. In short, it is about sparing no effort to nourish one's own body to make it reach perfection."

"What characteristics represent physical body perfection?" Lin Fei asked.

Liu Yibai paused for a moment. Then, he said solemnly, word by word: "Skin like a baby, body exuding a unique fragrance, flawless and pure, untainted golden body! This is physical body perfection!

Once the physical body reaches perfection, it is like the legendary Buddha or a holy being. The physical body is impervious to swords and spears, invulnerable to water and fire, unsinkable in water, and immune to all diseases!"

Lin Fei stretched out his hand. His hand had fair and tender skin, but there was still a significant difference compared to a baby's skin.

As for the unique body fragrance, that was even more impossible. Not to mention being impervious to swords and spears, invulnerable to water and fire, and unsinkable in water.

This was almost like a myth. Such a person with this kind of physical body, even without building their foundation, would be free from diseases and live a long life for hundreds of years! Because this represents the limit that a mortal body can reach!

Lin Fei knew that his physical body had reached its limit. No matter how much he practiced hard martial arts or Body Refining techniques, it would be of no use.

Achieve physical body perfection, it was almost impossible for martial artists to do it on their own. External objects were needed.

"Elder Liu, please tell me straight. What kind of heavenly materials and earthly treasures, rare birds, and exotic beasts? How much effect can they have? To truly reach physical body perfection, what exactly is this external object?"

Lin Fei's gaze was fixed on Liu Yibai. He knew that this was the key.

142. The Key of Foundation Establishment

"Exotic beasts!" Liu Yibai spoke directly, "To truly achieve physical body perfection, one must consume the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. Actually, martial arts were very prosperous thousands of years ago, not inferior to Qi cultivators, and even more flourishing.

At that time, there were many treasures that could help achieve physical body perfection. It wasn't necessarily required to consume the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. After all, exotic beasts are too powerful. Most adult exotic beasts are comparable to Foundation Establishment cultivators or Martial Saints."

Unfortunately, later martial artists and Qi cultivators seemed to have had a great war. The specific reason for that war is unknown. But since that war, the number of experts in Great Chang sharply decreased. There were even powerful beings above the Foundation Establishment realm left, and it's unknown where they went.

Perhaps they went to the outer seas, or perhaps to the northern countries. After that war, it seemed that various heavenly and earthly spiritual objects gradually decreased. In the beginning. some Martial Saints could hunt exotic beasts to prepare their flesh and blood for their younger disciples.

However, as time went by, the number of exotic beasts became fewer and fewer, and eventually, they were almost extinct. When there were no exotic beasts, even the most astonishingly talented people could not establish their foundation and become Martial Saints.

Do you think that there hasn't been a Martial Saint born in Great Chang for three hundred years since the Sword Saint of my Hidden Sword Sect passed away because martial artists are not talented enough?

Elder Lin, Nine Profound Sect's founder was talented enough, right? Even among the Martial Saints that my Hidden Sword Sect has produced, I'm afraid none can compare to the talent of the Nine Profound Sect's founder.

Even Foundation Establishment cultivators praised the Nine Profound Sect's founder. If he became a Martial Saint, the Nine Profound Sect's founder might have been even more powerful than the Great Chang's founding emperor and even had the potential to surpass the Foundation Establishment level.

Unfortunately, the Nine Profound Sect's founder was born in the wrong era. By the time his unparalleled talent dominated the world, exotic beasts had already become extinct.

Even if he traveled the world, he couldn't find a single exotic beast. Without the flesh and blood of exotic beasts, the physical body could never achieve perfection. Even if one forcefully established their foundation, it would be futile. In the end, he could only be depressed and regretful until their time was up."

Lin Fei's heart was moved. Liu Yibai mentioned the Nine Profound Sect's founder. It turns out that the Nine Profound Sect's founder couldn't find an exotic beast. In the end, his physical body couldn't achieve perfection. That's why he couldn't establish his foundation and become a Martial Saint.

No wonder the royal elders mentioned after the Nine Profound Sect's founder had read the martial arts secret records left by the Great Chang's founding emperor, he had shouted several times "I don't believe it!"

Most likely, the Nine Profound Sect's founder had also seen in the martial arts secret records, that to achieve Martial Saint, one's physical body must achieve perfection. And to achieve physical body perfection, one must consume the flesh and blood of exotic beasts.

Otherwise, it would be impossible to successfully establish one's foundation and become a Martial Saint. Both the founding emperor of Great Chang and the Sword Saint of Hidden Sword Sect from 300 years ago most likely had the fortune to consume the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. That's why they were able to successfully establish their foundation and become Martial Saints.

"So, Elder Liu knows the whereabouts of exotic beasts?"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes as he stared intently at Liu Yibai. Without any information on exotic beasts, Liu Yibai would not have wasted time telling Lin Fei so many secrets.

"That's right, I accidentally encountered an exotic beast decades ago. Later, I tracked it several times and discovered that there were actually several exotic beasts. I can't do it alone, I can't kill the exotic beasts. So, I need to find someone. Now in the entire Great Chang, there is probably no martial artist who can surpass you and me.

Only by joining forces with Elder Lin can we have a glimmer of hope to kill that exotic beast and obtain its flesh and blood. By then, both of us can achieve physical body perfection and have the hope of successfully establishing our foundation and becoming Martial Saints!"

Lin Fei's mind was shaken. As expected, Liu Yibai knew the whereabouts of the exotic beasts.

"But, exotic beasts are at the Foundation Establishment level. Do you know how difficult would it be to kill one? Those Martial Saints in the past were usually from powerful families or sects, capturing exotic beasts to have a chance to consume their flesh and blood.

But now there are no Martial Saints. Elder Liu, can we two handle a Foundation Establishment level exotic beast?" Lin Fei was still very clear-headed.

Liu Yibai nodded appreciatively and said in a deep voice, "Indeed, if it's a Foundation Establishment level exotic beast, even if we join forces, the odds are against us. However, decades ago, I tracked down those exotic beasts, and they gave birth to two young ones.

After decades of growth, those two exotic beasts have grown up but have not yet reached adulthood, and their strength is not comparable to that of adult exotic beasts. If we join forces, there might be some chance.

But, we can't delay any longer. Those two exotic beasts are about to reach adulthood. Once they become adults, we will have no chance left!"

This was the real reason why Liu Yibai urgently told Lin Fei about the secrets of the Martial Saint Foundation Establishment and exotic beasts.

Liu Yibai couldn't wait any longer! If he waited any longer, those two exotic beasts would become adults. By then, he would completely lose the opportunity to kill the exotic beasts. Which is equivalent to completely losing the chance to establish his foundation and become a Martial Saint.

Lin Fei was also considering it. If the matter about the exotic beasts was true, he absolutely could not miss it. Even though Lin Fei's saber intent and True Qi had not yet reached perfection, that didn't matter. It wouldn't affect his physical body's attainment of perfection.

Once his physical body reached perfection first, after his True Qi and saber intent reached perfection, Lin Fei could directly attempt to establish his foundation and challenge the Martial Saint realm.

If he missed this opportunity, even if Lin Fei had confidence in his Saber Qi, what if he still couldn't kill an adult exotic beast? That would be troublesome.

"When do we set off?"

Lin Fei didn't think too long. He raised his head and asked. He had already made a decision.

"At the beginning of the third month, when the weather turns warmer, those adult exotic beasts seem to migrate to give birth to new exotic beasts. Those two immature exotic beasts are most likely to stay behind. That will be the best opportunity we have in a year!"

Lin Fei calculated. There were still more than four months from now. In these four months, Lin Fei could make some preparations. He could even learn more about Martial Saints, Foundation Establishment, and exotic beasts to see if what Liu Yibai said was true.

He couldn't rely solely on Liu Yibai's words. Lin Fei had to have his own judgment.

"Alright, let's set off at the beginning of the third month," Lin Fei agreed, "By then, I'll give you a letter to confirm the specific location and time."

"No problem."

With that, the two discussed some more details. Lin Fei then bid farewell to Liu Yibai and left the Hidden Sword Sect.

Watching Lin Fei's departing figure, Liu Yibai's eyes became deeper.

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei. I didn't expect that the Nine Profound Sect would give birth to such a powerful martial artist. In terms of talent, he is no less than the Nine Profound Sect's founder. However, this is a good thing. With Lin Fei, the chances of slaying that exotic beast are even greater."

Liu Yibai knew very well. This was almost his last chance. If he didn't succeed, once detected by the exotic beasts, there would be no chance for the next attempt. Therefore, this time, success was the only option; failure was not allowed!

143. Ambition

Upon returning to the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei headed straight to the main hall. The sect master, seeing Lin Fei, finally breathed a sigh of relief: "Elder Lin, was your trip to the Hidden Sword Sect smooth?"

"Very smooth. I even gained some unexpected benefits. Hidden Sword Sect does have a deep foundation. There are actually over a hundred sword intents in their Sword Tomb. We don't have such a foundation in the Nine Profound Sect."

The sect master was slightly taken aback, "Sword Tomb? Over a hundred sword intents? That place is a vital area of the Hidden Sword Sect, and ordinary people are not allowed to enter, let alone Elder Lin, who is a saber cultivator..."

The sect master had a bad feeling in his heart.

"Yes, the hundred sword intents in the Sword Tomb honed me, and helped my saber intent finally reach transcendence! Besides, Liu Yibai is also quite good, capable of withstanding one of my sabers. Ever since I comprehended saber intent, almost no one has been able to withstand one of my sabers. Liu Yibai is truly worthy of the title 'Number One Sword Under Heaven!'"

As Lin Fei casually spoke of all this, the sect master's face turned ugly. He had originally thought that since there had been no news from the foot of the mountain, Lin Fei shouldn't have caused any trouble. But now it seemed he was a bit too optimistic.

From Lin Fei's words, it sounded like he had fought a battle with the "Number One Sword Under Heaven" Liu Yibai? The sect master knew how powerful Lin Fei's saber energy was, which was more than thirty meters long. It was so powerful that even Zhao Kongming refused to discuss the matter of "sparring."

Liu Yibai, the Number One Sword Under Heaven, had a long-standing reputation. Thirty years ago, he was already invincible and he was also a Grand Master. Could Lin Fei really provoke such a strong person?

"Elder Lin, you didn't kill Liu Yibai, did you?"

The sect master's voice trembled.

"I didn't. Liu Yibai is very strong. In the Hidden Sword Sect, I could barely defeat him, but I couldn't kill him."

Lin Fei told the truth. The Hidden Sword Sect's Sword Tomb had over a hundred sword intents. Liu Yibai's sword intent had already reached perfection. With the blessing of over a hundred sword intents in the Hidden Sword Sect, Lin Fei couldn't do anything to Liu Yibai. However, if they were outside the Hidden Sword Sect, the situation might be different.

The sect master sighed in relief. As long as Liu Yibai didn't die, that was enough. If Liu Yibai had really died, it would probably lead to a life-or-death struggle between the Hidden Sword Sect and the Nine Profound Sect.

But being able to barely defeat Liu Yibai, didn't that mean Lin Fei was now on par with a martial arts Grand Master?

"Sect master, has the founder not left any information about foundation building?" Lin Fei asked.

The sect master was still shocked by Lin Fei's "barely" defeating Liu Yibai. After hearing Lin Fei's question, he shook his head and said, "The founder had traveled extensively for a long time. He only returned to the Nine Profound Sect when his life was nearing its end. Besides leaving the stele on the Ancestral Master Peak, he didn't leave anything else. As for martial arts foundation building, there is no record of it in the Nine Profound Sect."

Lin Fei thought for a moment. It was probably because the founder of the Nine Profound Sect couldn't find any exotic beasts during his travels. In the end, he returned to the Nine Profound Sect disheartened.

As for martial arts foundation building, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect couldn't find any exotic beasts himself. Without exotic beasts, the path of foundation building for martial artists might be completely severed.

Therefore, the Nine Profound Sect naturally didn't leave any information about foundation building. There would be no use in leaving it.

"It seems that I have to go to Chang City. I hope the royal family will allow me to read the martial arts secret records left by the founder emperor, only then can I learn the specifics of martial arts foundation building."

Lin Fei knew, at present, there were only a few places in this world where information about martial arts foundation building and Martial Saints could be found. The royal family had martial arts secret records. The information about martial arts foundation building was probably the most comprehensive.

Although Lin Fei believed that Liu Yibai's words were true, he still had to gather more information. So he could make his own judgment.

"Elder Lin, are you going to Chang City again?" The sect master asked softly.

"Yes, going to Chang City. Don't worry, this time I'm just asking the royal family to let me read the martial arts secret records. I won't cause any trouble."

Lin Fei knew the sect master's concerns. He was afraid that Lin Fei would cause big trouble in Chang City again. But what kind of big trouble could there be now?

Killing a perfection-stage Qi Condensation cultivator or provoking a Foundation Establishment expert? That was simply impossible!

Lin Fei wasn't going to cause trouble this time. He was asking the royal family for help.

"Alright, Elder Lin, but you have to be careful on your journey. Recently, the Guardian Primordial Mountain seems to be making quite a lot of moves. We don't know what they're up to. Moreover, there have been signs of rebellion in various places within the Great Chang territory. The world is becoming more and more turbulent."

The sect master also sighed. The more turbulent the world was, it meant that the Great Chang royal family's control over various places was getting weaker. Once the royal family couldn't hold on, and chaos spread across the world, He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain wouldn't be polite to the Nine Profound Sect.

"Guardian Primordial Mountain…"

A strange light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. Now that Foundation Establishment couldn't come out, who could trouble him?

If the Guardian Primordial Mountain quietly lurked and waited for the royal family's Supreme Elder life to end, it would be fine. But if they dared to make a move against him, Lin Fei wouldn't mind cutting down a few more top Qi Condensation cultivators from the Guardian Primordial Mountain.

So Lin Fei went down the mountain alone again. He still didn't ride a horse. Using Saber Qi, he traveled using the Close Yet Distant technique. Often, he could cover a distance of thirty meters in one step.

This was not Lin Fei's full power. If he exerted his full power, his Close Yet Distant technique would definitely cover more than forty meters in one step.

Lin Fei didn't use his full power to travel, because he wasn't in a hurry. After all, there were still about four months left until his agreement with Liu Yibai. There was still plenty of time.

On his journey from the Nine Profound Sect to Chang City, Lin Fei saw scenes different from before. It seemed that there were many more refugees than before. Some villages were filled with corpses. It was unclear whether they were the work of chaotic soldiers or bandits.

Although it wasn't as severe as widespread starvation or people resorting to cannibalism, the whole world was indeed becoming chaotic. And when the world was in chaos, it was the common people who suffered the most.

Lin Fei had heard from the sect master before. It seemed that there had already been rebellions in various places in Great Chang. Once there were chaotic soldiers, the world might quickly decay.

"Prosperity brings suffering to the people, and decline also brings suffering to the people. Better to be a peaceful dog than a person in a chaotic world."

Lin Fei shook his head. He was just a martial artist. He couldn't take care of all the people in the world. However, when he encountered bandits or chaotic soldiers killing ordinary people on the way, Lin Fei would take action, killing those chaotic soldiers or bandits.

But in comparison to all the people in the world, the ones Lin Fei saved were just a drop in the bucket. In the end, even when he was near Great Chang, there were actually large numbers of refugees. Lin Fei knew that the situation in Great Chang was already very serious.

"Chiyang Prefecture has fallen again."

"I heard that it was those Paradise Sect members who stirred up trouble in Chiyang Prefecture, leading to its fall."

"The Paradise Sect's chaotic army is now powerful, and they have successively conquered various prefectures."

"Sigh, now that trade routes are cut off and prices are soaring, when will this end?"

"I hope the court will quell the rebellion soon..."

These ordinary people and merchants, obviously, all disliked the chaotic army of the Paradise Sect. They all hoped that the court would quickly put down the rebellion.

"Paradise Sect…"

Lin Fei frowned. He had a vague feeling that behind the Paradise Sect, there might be some immortal sects. Otherwise, their rise would not be so rapid.

"Immortal sects, high above. For the interests of the immortal sects, they disrupt the world. No wonder the founder emperor suppressed the various immortal sects back then. One day, if I can establish my foundation and become a Martial Saint. I will definitely eliminate those chaotic immortal sects!"

A hint of murderous intent flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. Some immortal sects truly deserved to have their mountain gates trampled and their lineage exterminated!

Martial arts sects could at least integrate with the common people, sharing both glory and loss. But those immortal sects were high above, with an attitude of pointing out the world and saving the people.

They even incited some chaotic soldiers, causing the world to decay and lives to be lost. They deserved to be killed!

"Your saber intent, upon hearing the host's ambitious aspirations, is stirred and its cultivation progress increases by 10%."

"Your fist intent, upon hearing the host's ambitious aspirations, is stirred and its cultivation progress increases by 30%."

"Your Heavenly Saber Art, upon hearing the host's ambitious aspirations, is stirred and wishes to help the host sweep the world. Cultivation progress increases by 50%."

"Your Immeasurable Fist, upon hearing the host's ambitious aspirations, is stirred and wishes to help the host sweep the world. Cultivation progress increases by 50%."

In Lin Fei's mind, a series of system voices rang out. Apart from the True Intention Scroll and Close Yet Distant, the progress of many other martial arts skills, surprisingly, improved due to Lin Fei's ambition to sweep the world.

A note from RighteousEgg

Lin Fei's vow here is to eradicate all evil cultivation sects, not to sever the inheritance of all Qi cultivators.

144. Saber Qi Suppressed The Three Elders

"Here we are, Chang City!"

Lin Fei raised his head and he saw the towering and majestic walls of Chang City. However, unlike the last time, outside the city gates of Chang City, on both sides of the road, a large number of refugees had gathered. Many corpses of refugees lay on the ground, emitting a stench and nobody cared.

The number of soldiers at the city gate had clearly increased several times compared to before. Each of them was nervously looking at these refugees outside the city.

Lin Fei frowned. If even the area outside Chang City was like this scene, the entire Great Chang Empire was probably hanging by a thread.

"Stop, the city is under martial law, entry is not allowed."

Lin Fei was about to enter Chang City, but he was stopped by the soldiers guarding the city.

No entry was allowed. Even those who could enter, all had a pass token, otherwise, they were not allowed in.

"Take a good look."

Lin Fei directly threw out a token. This was the Princess Token given by Ling Yao, which could be used to travel throughout the Great Chang Empire.

Upon seeing the token, the guard immediately became serious and saluted, "Please pass, sir!"

With Lin Fei holding the Princess Token, how could the city guards dare to stop him? So, they immediately let him pass.

Lin Fei didn't hesitate and took back the token handed over by the soldier. With a stride of thirty meters, he directly entered Chang City.

Inside Chang City, there were very few pedestrians on the streets. It seemed a bit deserted. After all, Chang City had begun to restrict entry. The city naturally lost its former prosperity.

Judging from the situation in Chang City, the situation in Great Chang was also very grim. All this was happening while the Royal Supreme Elder was still alive and sitting in Chang City. If the Royal Supreme Elder passed away, to what extent would the entire Great Chang Empire fall apart?

Lin Fei arrived at the residence of South King Mansion and threw out the Princess Token. As a result, he was able to meet Princess Ling Yao smoothly.

"Lin Fei, why are you here?"

Ling Yao's expression was a bit haggard. Her face didn't look good. She seemed very tired.

"Senior Sister Ling, I have a request. I hope Senior Sister Ling can take me to meet an elder of the royal family and tell them I have something to discuss," Lin Fei said directly.

"Requesting to meet the elder?"

Ling Yao hesitated for a moment, unable to help but ask, "Lin Fei, if you want to meet the elder, can you tell me what it's for?"

Lin Fei thought about it and didn't hide it from Ling Yao. He said directly, "I want to borrow the martial arts secret records left behind by the Great Chang Founding Emperor."

Ling Yao didn't know about any martial arts secret records. However, she expressed her concerns, "Lin Fei, the situation in the Great Chang has been unstable lately. I believe you saw it on the way here.

Paradise Sect is causing chaos. They have conquered several Prefectures, causing shock throughout the Empire. The court has already dispatched a large army to suppress the rebellion, but they were defeated.

Some of the elders of the royal family have gone to assist the army in quelling the chaos. So, there aren't many elders left in the royal family now. Whether they will agree or not, I don't know."

Lin Fei nodded and said, "As long as Senior Sister Ling can let me meet the elder, that's enough. As for whether the elder agrees or not, I will try to persuade them myself."

"Alright, then wait for a while. There shouldn't be any problem in letting you meet the elder."

So, Ling Yao got up and went to the palace. She went to explain Lin Fei's situation. Lin Fei waited quietly at the South King Mansion. About two hours later, Ling Yao returned.

"It's fine, you can go to the palace directly with my token. This time, I won't accompany you. As long as the Paradise Sect's rebels are not dealt with, the more troubles I, as a princess, have to deal with."

"Okay, I'll go by myself."

Ling Yao left in a hurry again. It seemed she was really busy.

"Paradise Sect..."

Lin Fei shook his head slightly. Now was not the time to think about these matters.

Lin Fei moved at thirty meters per step, his figure fleeting. He quickly arrived at the entrance of the palace. At the palace gate, a eunuch was already waiting.

"Is it Young Master Lin Fei?"

"Yes, it's Lin."

"Please follow me."

Following the eunuch, Lin Fei saw the familiar stairs again.

Along the stairs, Lin Fei came to the underground Ascending Dragon Chamber of the palace. This time, there were still three elders of the royal family in the Ascending Dragon Chamber. However, these three were not the same elders Lin Fei had met the last time.

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, the princess told us that you have something to discuss with us?" One of the elders spoke slowly.

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Three elders, I would like to borrow the martial arts secret records left behind by the Great Chang Founding Emperor."

Lin Fei directly stated his request.

"Martial arts secret records?"

The three elders shook their heads slightly, "We, the royal family, have been paying attention to your situation all along. Originally, our royal family established a good relationship with you. However, we must still follow the rules.

The martial arts secret records left behind by the Founding Emperor are only for those who have achieved the level of Martial Arts Grand Master. You haven't become a Martial Arts Grand Master yet, have you? So, you cannot see the martial arts secret records now."

The three elders directly refused Lin Fei's request. Lin Fei frowned. However, he wasn't surprised. Because last time, he also wanted to take a look at the martial arts secret records and he was refused.

Only Martial Arts Grand Masters were allowed to view the martial arts secret records. This was a rule set by the Great Chang Founding Emperor, and it could not be easily changed.

"Can't you make an exception? The Founding Emperor set this rule only because achieving Martial Saint through building the foundation can only be done by Martial Arts Grand Masters.

Although I am not a Martial Arts Grand Master now, it's only a matter of time before I become one. Moreover, even if I am not a Martial Arts Grand Master, I can defeat them with one saber strike. Is that not enough to qualify me to view the martial arts secret records?"

Lin Fei frowned deeply. Aside from the royal martial arts secret records, Lin Fei couldn't find any information on martial arts foundation building elsewhere.

As for the rigid requirement of being a Martial Arts Grand Master, Lin Fei could now defeat a Martial Arts Grand Master with just one saber strike. He felt he was already qualified to view the martial arts secret records.

The three elders looked at each other and were speechless.

"Lin Fei, I know about the fame of your 'Immortal Slayer Saber'. However, you said that you can defeat a Martial Arts Grand Master with one saber strike, isn't that a bit too overconfident?

We are just Qi cultivators, so it's not a big deal. But if a Martial Arts Grand Master heard your words, it might bring about disaster. So, it's best not to say such things."

All three elders shook their heads. Defeating a Martial Arts Grand Master with one saber strike? Even if Lin Fei the Immortal Slayer Saber was famous, he seemed to underestimate a Martial Arts Grand Master too much.

Seeing the three elders didn't believe him, Lin Fei took a deep breath and said, "My apologies to the three elders!"

"Boom."

The next moment, Lin Fei mobilized the Saber Qi within his body. Immediately, the Saber Qi surged and burst forth. It instantly condensed into a saber energy within the Ascending Dragon Chamber.

"Crack."

The saber energy even pierced directly through the roof of the Ascending Dragon Chamber. Above it was a thick layer of soil and bricks.

Lin Fei stopped immediately. If he continued like this, the Ascending Dragon Chamber would be destroyed.

At the same time, Lin Fei's transcendent saber intent also suppressed the entire Ascending Dragon Chamber. Even the three Qi Condensation Level 7 elders felt as if they were being crushed by a mountain. It seemed they couldn't even breathe.

This was definitely not pressured that any ordinary martial arts Master could possess.

Grand Master! This must be a Martial Arts Grand Master!

"Three elders, am I now qualified to view the martial arts secret records?"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, his eyes calmly looking at the three royal elders.

145. The Task Of Suppressing Rebellion

"Lin Fei, you..."

The faces of the three royal elders changed drastically. Lin Fei's behavior was forcing their hand. They were royal elders! They represented the Great Chang royal family!

"Let him see it!"

At this moment, an old voice suddenly came from the void.

"Huh?"

Lin Fei quickly raised his head, trying to see who was speaking. However, Lin Fei looked around and didn't find anyone. With Lin Fei's current senses, he could detect any movement or person within a hundred meters. But now, someone was clearly speaking, yet Lin Fei couldn't sense anything.

Moreover, it sounded like someone was speaking, but in reality, the voice seemed to be coming directly into his ear.

Upon hearing this voice, the three royal elders were immediately startled. They all knelt down excitedly and respectfully saluted, "Greetings to the Supreme Elder!"

"Supreme Elder?"

Lin Fei's heart stirred. He knew who the owner of this voice was.

There was only one Royal Supreme Elder. That was the Foundation Establishment True Person! Having lived for nearly five hundred years, he was the pillar of the royal family.

The Great Chang Dynasty had been lasting for nine hundred years. The appearance of this Royal Supreme Elder had almost extended its life by another five hundred years.

Thus, the prestige of the Royal Supreme Elder was even slightly higher than that of the Great Chang Founding Emperor.

"Greetings, Supreme Elder!"

Lin Fei also gave a slight salute. He was very respectful to the Foundation Establishment True Person. After all, it was equivalent to a Martial Saint level powerhouse.

"Lin Fei, you may view the Founding Emperor's martial arts secret records. However, the royal family has been facing many difficulties recently.

Paradise Sect's rebel army is attacking cities and seizing territories. The royal family has dispatched several high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, but they still cannot stop them.

I estimate that some immortal sects are directly involved in the rebellion. 'Immortal Slayer Saber' is famous for its ability to slay top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

If you go, you will definitely be able to assist the imperial army in suppressing the rebels and quelling the rebellion. Once you succeed, you may return to the royal family and view the martial arts secret records! Furthermore, I can even meet with you and answer your many questions."

The words of the Royal Supreme Elder echoed in Lin Fei's ears, but Lin Fei couldn't find its figure. This must be the means of the Foundation Establishment True Person. Mysterious and unfathomable, impossible to fathom.

Lin Fei couldn't help but ask, "Does the royal family not have top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators or powerful Martial Arts Masters?"

The Royal Supreme Elder replied, "The royal family has top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, but they have been sent to other places. Currently, there are unstable factors everywhere in Great Chang.

As for powerful Martial Arts Masters, unless they are Martial Arts Grand Masters or have comprehended Martial Dao True Intent, how much chance do you think they have against those immortal sect Qi cultivators?"

Lin Fei understood. The Royal Supreme Elder had said so much, but the message he wanted to convey was just one thing, the royal family was in great difficulty!

At least for now, it was very difficult. Even a small Paradise Sect's rebel army could not be suppressed. Moreover, they had to ask for help from an outsider like Lin Fei, relying on external forces to suppress the rebellion.

"Supreme Elder, I agree! After suppressing the rebellion, I will return to view the martial arts secrets!"

Lin Fei didn't think too long. In fact, he didn't even need to consider this. The royal family had also been helpful to Lin Fei. Moreover, the relationship between the Nine Profound Sect and the royal family was quite good. In addition, the Paradise Sect's rebellion caused the common people to be displaced and suffer. They were truly a chaotic army.

Lin Fei had seen so many refugees along the way. All of them had to flee because of the Paradise Sect. He had no good feelings toward such a chaotic army. Suppressing the rebellion as soon as possible would bring peace to the world sooner.

"Good, you are a straightforward person. Go and ask the emperor for a decree and token for Lin Fei. With it, he can smoothly travel to the imperial army that is suppressing the rebellion."

After the Royal Supreme Elder finished speaking, his voice disappeared. The three royal elders respectfully said, "Yes, Supreme Elder!"

The three elders slowly got up. They glanced at Lin Fei and then smiled, "Master Lin, please wait a moment. We will go to the emperor for a decree right away."

"Thank you, elder."

Lin Fei sat in the Ascending Dragon Chamber. He closed his eyes to rest and quietly waited. Before long, the elder returned. He brought a decree and a token.

Lin Fei took the decree. The general idea was to inform the frontline imperial army generals that Lin Fei was a martial arts expert sent by the emperor and that he would assist the imperial army in suppressing the rebellion. If necessary, they should follow Lin Fei's lead.

"Master Lin, this is just a decree. After all, your speed may be faster. The imperial court will also issue orders to the frontline later, but they may be much slower than you. This decree and token can save you a lot of trouble."

Lin Fei nodded. He directly took the decree and token and put them in his pocket.

"Three elders, I take my leave!"

Lin Fei didn't delay. He just wanted to suppress the rebellion as soon as possible and then come back to view the martial arts secret records.

Lin Fei calculated the time. He had four months until the agreed time with Liu Yibai. It should be enough.

Watching Lin Fei's departing figure, the three elders couldn't help but sigh, "Our Great Chang, how did it come to this? We can't suppress a mere Paradise Sect rebellion and even have to rely on external forces."

"It's because we, the descendants of the royal family, are incompetent. Otherwise, how could the Supreme Elder be so worried?"

"Lin Fei is a martial artist after all. Can he really suppress the rebellion?"

The three elders were all worried. Martial artists were incomparable to Qi cultivators. Qi cultivators wield powerful magical artifacts, capable of suppressing thousands, even tens of thousands of people. Unstoppable on the battlefield. They could even collapse city walls with their magical artifacts.

But martial artists?

How many could they kill with their personal strength?

Although the three elders didn't have high hopes for Lin Fei to quell the rebellion, it was the Supreme Elder's decision. They dared not say more.

Lin Fei returned to the South King Mansion from the palace. Ling Yao hurried over upon hearing the news.

"Lin Fei, how was your visit to the palace? Did the elders agree to let you view the Martial Arts Secret Records?"

Ling Yao asked directly.

Lin Fei shook his head: "At first, the royal elders didn't agree, but then the Royal Supreme Elder sent a message, asking me to go to Chiyang Prefecture to assist the imperial army in suppressing the rebels and putting down the Paradise Sect's rebellion. Upon success, I can return to the Ascending Dragon Chamber and view the Martial Arts Secret Records.

I agreed. I came here to ask the princess for information on the recent movements of the Paradise Sect's rebel forces. What's the situation on the frontline?"

Lin Fei didn't rush to the frontlines without preparation. He needed to understand the situation on the frontlines before making a decision.

"You're going to the frontlines to quell the rebellion?"

Ling Yao's expression changed slightly.

"Lin Fei, the situation on the frontline is complicated. Behind the Paradise Sect's rebellion, there are traces of the Immortal Sects' involvement. Moreover, there's definitely more than one Immortal Sect.

The royal family has sent Qi cultivators and martial artists to the frontlines. Even the high-level Qi Condensation cultivators from the royal family, those elders, have also gone.

However, they still couldn't put down the rebellion and instead suffered a great defeat with heavy casualties. Going into this muddy water at this time is too dangerous."

Ling Yao's voice was filled with urgency even some worry. At this moment, she wasn't concerned about whether the court could quell the rebellion. Instead, she was concerned about Lin Fei's personal safety.

Lin Fei glanced at Ling Yao. Then, with a calm tone, he said lightly, "Without a Foundation Establishment cultivator, who can kill me?"

"Lin Fei, you..."

Ling Yao's mind was shaken. During this period, she didn't know the news about Lin Fei. Why did Lin Fei seem to have changed somehow? It seemed that he had become more confident! His every move seemed to carry an air of disdainful arrogance!

"Senior Sister Ling, you only need to know that without a Foundation Establishment cultivator, no one can harm me. Otherwise, do you think the Supreme Elder's personal request for me to go to the frontlines to quell the rebellion is just casual talk?"

When Lin Fei returned to the South King Mansion, he already had a faint suspicion. The Royal Supreme Elder might have already known about his battle with Liu Yibai in the Hidden Sword Sect.

After all, the Royal Supreme Elder had lived for five hundred years. He was a true antique. In the entire world, there was no one who had lived longer than the Royal Supreme Elder. Not a single one!

With such an ancient existence, what could be kept hidden from the Royal Supreme Elder?

Ling Yao didn't know how strong Lin Fei was now. But she believed in Lin Fei. That was enough.

So, Ling Yao nodded and said solemnly, "The court had once dispatched an army to quell the rebellion, but they were defeated and retreated. This time, the commander of the army is General Li Yuhu. General Li Yuhu has fought battles all his life and has very rich experience.

If you can eliminate some hidden Qi Condensation cultivators or other hidden experts within the Paradise Sect's rebels, then leave the battles to General Li Yuhu, who can certainly quell the rebellion in the shortest possible time!"

Lin Fei nodded, "I understand. The commander of the imperial army is a capable general. Leave the battles to him and the slaying of rebel experts to me. Only in this way can the Paradise Sect's rebellion be quelled!"

Lin Fei asked Ling Yao because he was afraid the commander of the imperial army was incompetent. By that time, even if he killed the experts within the Paradise Sect's rebels, if the commander of the army was incompetent, leading to the army's defeat, there would be trouble.

Now it seemed that the court was not foolish. They had dispatched a steady and experienced general to command the army.

"Alright, Senior Sister Ling, there's no time to lose. I will depart for the frontlines immediately, strive to quell the rebellion as soon as possible, and then return to Chang City."

"Lin Fei, on the battlefield, sabers and swords are blind. Be careful!"

Lin Fei nodded. Then, he took a step forward. In a few leaps, he disappeared without a trace.

146. Grasp Flying Sword With Bare Hands

Lin Fei left Chang City, turning his course towards Chiyang Prefecture. The court's army, engaged in quelling the rebellion, had reached Chiyang Prefecture. And so, a fierce assault was launched. The course of the battle was unknown. With this in mind, Lin Fei pressed on with all haste. His figure was elusive as a faint afterimage.

The closer he got to Chiyang Prefecture from Chang City, the less populated it became. Refugees were everywhere, and so were corpses. Even the sides of the official road were littered with bodies.

Although it wasn't summer yet, the smell of decay wafted from these bodies. The villages Lin Fei passed were merely remnants of broken walls.

Such were the times of war. Whether it was the rebels or the imperial army, their passage was never a good omen for the common folk.

The imperial army was somewhat bearable, some semblance of military discipline still remained. But the rebels, they were utterly lawless, worse than bandits.

Lin Fei knew this. In wars, the directly killed were not the majority. But the devastation brought by war was dreadful. Famine and disease caused by war were the true horrors.

In the cold weather of winter, the chance of corpses breeding plague was minimal. But come summer, if the Paradise Sect's rebellion was not quelled, then the heat and the swarms of untreated corpses would breed plague. And should an epidemic break out, death would claim far more.

The more Lin Fei saw, the stronger the killing intent toward the Paradise Sect grew in his heart.

"At last!"

Finally, Lin Fei beheld Chiyang Prefecture. Above it yet hung the flag of the Paradise Sect's rebels. While outside, a multitude of military camps were stationed. That was the court's grand army, tasked with suppressing the rebellion. Many bodies lay scattered on the ground.

The air was dense with the reek of blood. It was clear that both sides had likely already fought numerous battles. Yet, the lingering resistance of Chiyang Prefecture suggested the court's forces had encountered difficulties.

With a flicker, Lin Fei appeared before the army's encampment after a few leaps.

"Halt, this is a strategic area, approach is forbidden, violators will be executed without mercy!" A soldier roared, brimming with killing intent.

Lin Fei glanced at the camp within. He did not feel the need to announce his arrival. With a soft whistle, Lin Fei stepped forth. He covered a distance of sixty meters in an instant. Just like that, he breezed past the guarding soldiers.

Startled, the soldiers cried out, "Assassin!"

A din arose as countless armored soldiers, wielding hefty sabers and long spears, instantly formed a battle line. Spears stood tall as trees, their sabers gleaming frostily all pointed at Lin Fei, the "assassin" who had audaciously trespassed into their camp.

Such a formidable array would have been difficult to break through even for an innate martial artist.

"Hmph."

Lin Fei snorted dismissively. None could draw their saber in his presence. And so, Lin Fei's figure came to a slight halt. Then, his saber intent trembled minutely.

With a boom, the terrifying saber intent immediately enveloped the soldiers on the front line. Instantly, all the sabers within the formation began to vibrate.

"What's happening? I can't draw my saber."

"Sorcery, this is sorcery!"

"Quickly fetch the camp's immortal masters, only immortal masters can dispel this sorcery."

The soldiers were seized by intense fear. As for the formation, it crumbled at the surge of Lin Fei's saber intent.

Lin Fei silently shook his head. These soldiers hardly constituted an elite force. If they were truly elite soldiers, even with his saber intent pressing down on them, they would have maintained their formation.

And more so, they would have launched a courageous charge. After all, Lin Fei's saber intent could only suppress the sabers. It did not have much of an effect on those wielding long spears.

With a soft whistle, Lin Fei took another stride. He passed this row of soldiers, preparing to step into the commander's tent.

"Whence came this assassin? Trespassing into the military camp is a capital offense!"

A streak of white light shot out from the commander's tent.

A flying sword!

This was Lin Fei's second encounter with such a weapon. Moreover, judging by the spiritual power accompanying the sword, it was evident that it was being controlled by a high-level Qi Condensation cultivator.

Caught off guard, even a martial arts Grand Master might be severely disadvantaged. One would even be pierced through the head by the flying sword.

With a "snap", Lin Fei simply extended a fair hand and seized the white streak of light. As the white glow faded, it revealed a delicate flying sword about a foot long.

The flying sword attempted to struggle in Lin Fei's grasp but was brutally suppressed by his saber energy.

Holding the flying sword, Lin Fei walked straight into the commander's tent.

"Whoosh."

Inside the tent, countless gazes converged on Lin Fei. Especially on his right hand.

Catching a flying sword barehanded! Even a martial arts Grand Master wouldn't dare to attempt such a feat. But now, Lin Fei had actually caught a flying sword barehanded.

What could this mean?

Regardless of whether they were martial arts Masters or high-level Qi Condensation cultivators within the tent, everyone held their breath. Their hearts were filled with shock!

"Immortal Slayer Saber, Lin Fei!"

At this moment, a white-haired Daoist spoke. He obviously recognized Lin Fei.

"You recognize me?"

Lin Fei looked at the white-haired Daoist. He didn't know the man.

The white-haired Daoist sighed deeply, "I saw 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Master Lin from the sidelines during the Royal Competition."

Lin Fei understood. The man was probably a Qi Condensation cultivator of the royal family whose hiding in the crowd. Lin Fei, of course, hadn't noticed him.

"Master Lin, what is the purpose of your audacious entry into the military camp?" The Daoist asked.

Lin Fei did not answer directly. Instead, he held up the flying sword in his hand. His gaze swept across those within the tent, "Whose sword is this?"

At his question, another black-robed Daoist stood up. His face flushed, but he was compelled to speak, "Master Lin, it is mine."

Seeing that Lin Fei had made no move to return the flying sword, the Daoist continued, "I acted rashly. Please forgive me, Master Lin."

Seeing the Daoist admit his mistake, Lin Fei said calmly, "The material of the flying sword is too poor, it can't compare with Yuan Gangzi's flying sword."

Afterward, Lin Fei casually flicked the flying sword.

"Whoosh."

The flying sword flew back into the Daoist's hands. The Daoist's face grew even more uncomfortable. However, the fact was right in front of him. Lin Fei had caught his flying sword barehanded. What else could he say?

As for the comparison with Yuan Gangzi, he was naturally far inferior. Yuan Gangzi, after all, was a core elder of the Guardian Primordial Mountain. A top-notch Qi Condensation cultivator! How could he compare with Yuan Gangzi?

Although the Daoist felt frustrated in his heart. He was also quite shocked.

No one knew better than him how formidable his flying sword was. But Lin Fei had actually caught the flying sword with his bare hands. And it seemed to have been done effortlessly.

Such power was truly terrifying. Living up to the renown of the "Immortal Slayer Saber"!

Lin Fei's gaze swept over everyone, finally resting on a burly but already aging general.

"Are you General Li Yuhu?"

Lin Fei asked.

"I am indeed Li Yuhu. May I ask why Master Lin is trespassing into the camp?"

"Take a look. The emperor's imperial edict." Lin Fei directly took out the imperial edict and tossed it in front of Li Yuhu.

Upon careful examination, Li Yuhu finally breathed a sigh of relief. He immediately stood up, respectfully returned the imperial edict to Lin Fei, and said, "Master Lin, the emperor has dispatched you to assist the imperial court in quelling the rebel army. If necessary, the emperor has ordered me to follow your command. I will certainly obey!"

Lin Fei asked indifferently, "General Li, the imperial court's army has been in Chiyang Prefecture for many days. Why have they been unable to break through Chiyang Prefecture and crush the rebels?"

Upon hearing Lin Fei's question, General Li Yuhu gave a bitter smile, "Master Lin may not be aware, but the military under the rebel banner, though a ragtag bunch, is receiving aid from a significant number of evil demonic beings within their camp.

Among them, there is no lack of high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. Some Daoist masters from the royal family and the court have gone into battle, but they were no match for those demonic beings.

Moreover, the entire city wall and gate have been reinforced by formations from those demonic beings. Even if our army attacks for several days in a row, they cannot breach the city gate. At present, we can only besiege Chiyang Prefecture, hoping to find a way to breach the city.

However, our army's food and forage supply is somewhat insufficient. If we cannot breach the city after a prolonged period, I fear we may have to retreat."

Li Yuhu was also helpless. Leading soldiers in battle was not a problem for him. Against these ragtag rebels, if it were a field battle, he could crush them in less than an hour.

But this was a siege. The rebels were huddled in Chiyang Prefecture, guarding the city gate and walls with formations by those demonic beings. Ordinary soldiers were completely helpless.

"Demonic beings? Where do these demonic beings come from that they can withstand the Qi Condensation cultivator of the court and royal family? It must be the support from some immortal sects or Daoist schools."

Lin Fei's eyes turned cold. Then, he looked at Li Yuhu and said solemnly, "General Li, you immediately muster the troops. I'll go and blast open the city gate and walls. When the time comes, I will take care of those demonic beings. The task of crushing the rebel Paradise Sect is yours. Any problems?"

"Ah? Master Lin wants to go and blast open the city gate alone? Even the Daoist masters casting magical artifacts couldn't do that..." Li Yuhu was somewhat surprised.

"Speed is of the essence in war, I will go and return quickly."

After saying that, Lin Fei turned around and took a step out, leaving the tent. Despite being somewhat surprised, Li Yuhu understood. The emperor's decree had made it very clear. If necessary, everything would follow Lin Fei's command.

Thinking of this, Li Yuhu gritted his teeth and immediately shouted, "All generals, muster the troops immediately and prepare to siege the city!"

"The general of the rear obeys!"

And so, the imperial court's army to quell the rebellion also started to move.

"Blasting open the city gate... Even for the 'Immortal Slayer Saber', is it possible?"

People still had some disbelief in their hearts. The strength of a martial artist was indeed powerful. But in terms of destructive power, it was far inferior to the magical artifacts of Qi Condensation cultivators.

Magical artifacts couldn't break open those city gates and walls reinforced by formations, what more a martial artist?

The crowd could only hold their doubts in their hearts. They also quickly followed the army, preparing for the siege.

147. The City Wall Was Broken With A Single Saber

Chiyang Prefecture was now occupied by the leader of the Paradise Sect and a group of Daoists.

The leader of the Paradise Sect did not dare to show off in front of these Daoists. These Daoists were all powerful immortals. The reason why the Paradise Sect could succeed this time, even blocking the imperial court's army to quell the rebellion, was because of the efforts of these immortals. Otherwise, he, as the leader of the rebels, would have been captured and beheaded by the imperial army to quell the rebellion long ago.

"Esteemed immortals, I wonder how long the Chiyang Prefecture will be besieged by the imperial army this time. The food and fodder in the city may be a bit tight. Do you immortals have any ingenious methods?" The leader of the Paradise Sect asked cautiously.

One of the Daoists in a gray robe spoke leisurely, "General, there's no need to worry. The food and fodder in Chiyang Prefecture are enough for three months.

Moreover, the city walls and gates have been reinforced by us using formations. Even the top Qi Condensation cultivators can't break through the city gate in a short time. And the imperial court can't send top Qi Condensation cultivators now.

Although the imperial army is besieging us, their food and fodder can only last for ten more days. After ten days, the imperial army will definitely retreat. At that time, we will have won this battle!"

Upon hearing this, the leader of the Paradise Sect was overjoyed. The Paradise Sect has now occupied several prefectures and it has defeated the imperial army once before.

If it defeated the imperial army again this time, then in a short time, the imperial court would find it difficult to dispatch a large army again.

In this way, the reputation of the Paradise Sect would surely soar. At that time, they could capture more cities, and even occupying a province was not impossible.

Moreover, according to these immortals, Great Chang was now decadent and degenerate. Once the Paradise Sect established its footing, there would surely be a response from all corners of Great Chang.

At that time, when various forces rose up in rebellion, Great Chang would be overwhelmed and the Paradise Sect could achieve its great cause! This made the leader of the Paradise Sect extremely excited.

Seeing the excited expression of the leader of the Paradise Sect, the surrounding Daoists couldn't help but sneer in their hearts. A mere leader of the Paradise Sect, an ignorant fool, also vying for the world?

They supported the Paradise Sect merely to probe the real "strength" of Great Chang, to see if the Great Chang royal family still has the ability to suppress the world.

If the Great Chang royal family really couldn't do it anymore, they didn't even have to wait for the Royal Supreme Elder to die. Many immortal sects could support more people to "rise in rebellion," thereby causing chaos in the world.

By then, Great Chang would collapse. The immortal sects could return to their state a thousand years ago. High above, detached from the mundane, yet firmly controlling the entire world! As for Paradise Sect, it was just a pawn. If it was useless by the time, they could easily get rid of it.

This leader of the Paradise Sect was still immersed in the excitement of "great things to come". He was foolishly dreaming of becoming an emperor. How ridiculous.

"Report, the imperial army has come to attack the city again."

"Attacking the city again? How many people have come this time?"

The leader of the Paradise Sect asked hurriedly.

"Uh... One person."

"One person?"

The leader of the Paradise Sect and the Daoists looked at each other. There was a hint of doubt in their eyes.

"Let's go, let's go to the city wall to take a look."

So, everyone rushed towards the city wall. At this moment, the army to quell the rebellion had already assembled its soldiers and horses. Formations were set up.

However, the army to quell the rebellion did not attack the city. They were quietly waiting in place.

Lin Fei was among the army. He glanced at the city gate and wall of Chiyang Prefecture in the distance.

It was a strong city. The city wall was tall and strong. Even without reinforcing with formations, it would also be very hard to break through. Not to mention, there were high-level Qi Condensation cultivators reinforcing it with formations.

Such a formation, even top Qi Condensation cultivators would find it hard to break in a short time. Unless there was a very powerful magical artifact.

Lin Fei no longer hesitated. He took a step forward.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei took sixty meters in one stride. In just a few steps, he had already arrived at the city gate of Chiyang Prefecture.

On the city wall, the soldiers were all looking at each other. One man attacking the city?

"Shoot!"

Suddenly, the soldiers on the city wall began to shoot arrows. Arrows rained down like a downpour, but Lin Fei didn't move at all.

Saber energy permeated his entire body. The rain of arrows hit him but all bounced off around him. It didn't hurt Lin Fei at all.

At this moment, the leader of the Paradise Sect and many Daoists had also arrived at the city wall.

Seeing this scene, the leader of the Paradise Sect was somewhat panicked and quickly asked, "Who is this? Is he an Immortal Master sent by the imperial court?"

The leader of the Paradise Sect felt that if one could remain unharmed under so much arrow rain, it could only be the method of the Immortal Master.

However, the expressions of these Daoists were very solemn, and they all shook their heads, "This person is not a Qi cultivator, but a martial artist. If I'm not mistaken, it should be the recently famous 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei of Great Chang. I didn't expect that the imperial court actually requested this person."

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei? A martial artist with such a title?"

The leader of the Paradise Sect felt that it somewhat subverted his understanding.

Usually, these fairy masters were very arrogant, even innate martial artists, martial arts Masters, these immortal masters did not take seriously.

But now, mentioning this "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei, they all looked solemn. Even the leader of the Paradise Sect could vaguely feel that these Immortal Masters seemed to be somewhat wary of the "Immortal Slayer Saber."

Yes, wariness!

At this point, the leader of the Paradise Sect was sure he wasn't mistaken.

"Could it be that this 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei is very powerful?" the leader of the Paradise Sect asked carefully.

"Powerful, although he is a martial artist, we have to admit, he is indeed very powerful."

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' has slain two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators from He Mountain Dao and a top Qi Condensation cultivator from Guardian Primordial Mountain. The name 'Immortal Slayer Saber' is not just called, it's earned by killing! But no matter how powerful his 'Immortal Slayer Saber' is, he has no use before this army."

"Indeed, we have jointly used formations to strengthen the city walls and gates. How can he, a martial artist, breakthrough?"

"If he dares to climb the city wall, we will besiege him. No matter how powerful the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' is, he will inevitably be defeated under our many high-level Qi Condensation cultivators' siege."

"Chiyang Prefecture is still as solid as a rock!"

These Daoists were also somewhat confident in their words. Although the "Immortal Slayer Saber" was strong, but he alone could not break Chiyang Prefecture.

However, was it really so?

The leader of the Paradise Sect always felt that something was wrong. So he looked at the figure under the city again.

At this moment, Lin Fei was also looking at the city gate and walls of Chiyang Prefecture. There were runes flashing on it. Indeed, there was the enhancement of formations.

"Formations..."

Lin Fei took a deep breath, and a sharp light flashed in his eyes.

"No matter if it's a formation or a city wall. My saber can break it!"

Lin Fei did not hesitate any longer. The Saber Qi within his body was released without restraint.

"Boom."

The surging Saber Qi gushed out from Lin Fei's body. A huge amount of saber energy condensed a giant saber in the void.

Thirty meters, sixty meters, one hundred and twenty meters...

Lin Fei's saber energy expanded crazily. In an instant, it reached two hundred and fifty meters! Two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy spanned across the void.

Chiyang Prefecture could be considered a fortified city with very high walls. However, the two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy that Lin Fei displayed was more than twice as high as the city wall!

Moreover, with the emergence of the two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy, Lin Fei's saber intent also spread out, enveloping the sky above Chiyang Prefecture.

"Buzz."

Suddenly, the city-defending soldiers, originally holding a large saber, began to tremble violently and emit light sounds.

"What's going on, I can't pull out my saber?"

"My saber seems to be attracted by some force."

"What kind of sorcery is this?"

Even the leader of the Paradise Sect on the city wall turned pale, unable to hold his saber.

"Sorcery, this is sorcery..."

"Humph, this is not any sorcery, this is saber intent! This saber intent is terrifying, but it can't affect the army. The only thing is this two hundred and fifty meters saber glow in the void, this should be saber glow, right?"

"I wonder how powerful this two hundred and fifty meters saber glow is? It should not be able to break through the city gate reinforced by the formation..."

Seeing the two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy in the void, these Qi Condensation cultivators mistook it for saber glow and were uncertain. Even if they had confidence in the formation, who had seen two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy?

"Heavenly Saber Art, slash!"

At this moment, Lin Fei, like a divine being, was demonstrating supreme power. He slashed out this saber from the void.

Immediately, the massive two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy slashed toward the city wall ferociously.

Yes, not the city gate, but the city wall. Lin Fei directly slashed toward the city wall!

The two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy landed on the city wall. The formation on the city wall was almost instantly broken at the touch.

"Boom."

The formation was broken, and it was instantly cut open by the violent saber energy as if it were tofu.

"Boom."

Finally, the two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy fell on the city wall. The sturdy city wall actually collapsed with a loud bang. A huge gap appeared in the long city wall.

For a moment, the entire battlefield fell silent. Looking at the figure of Lin Fei under the city wall, everyone's eyes were incredibly shocked.

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei, in front of the two armies, broke the city wall with a single slash!

148. Unexpected Joy, Heavenly Saber Art Perfection

"The...the city wall is broken?"

Looking at that huge gap, the leader of the Paradise Sect was stunned, with an undeniable look of fear in his eyes. He was afraid!

Two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy descending from the sky, who could stop it? Lin Fei was a martial artist? Is there such a powerful martial artist? He'd believe it if one said Lin Fei was a god!

"What to do, what to do? The city wall is broken, it can't be blocked at all. Immortal Masters, quickly find a way to remedy this."

The leader of the Paradise Sect urgently sought help from the cultivators beside him. However, these Qi cultivators, upon seeing the huge gap in the city wall and "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei standing below the wall, looked at each other and understood each other's intentions.

"Retreat!"

Almost without any hesitation, the several Qi cultivators immediately left the city wall and even Chiyang Prefecture. They retreated!

After all, with the city wall broken, what could they do? Besides, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei was right below the city. They were confident and didn't put martial artists in their eyes. But, this did not include the "Immortal Slayer Saber".

After all, "Immortal Slayer Saber" made his great name known by killing countless Qi cultivators. They did not want to become souls under Lin Fei's saber. So, the several Qi cultivators left very simply, without any hesitation.

As for the leader of the Paradise Sect? They didn't care about him at all.

At this moment, the leader of the Paradise Sect was slightly stunned. It seemed that he hadn't reacted yet to why the cultivators disappeared.

"Immortal Masters, why did you leave? What should I do? What about the Paradise Sect?"

The leader of the Paradise Sect glanced at the huge gap in the city wall. He also didn't dare to stay. He immediately said, "Quickly, retreat first, leave Chiyang Prefecture."

The leader of the Paradise Sect didn't even dare to take many people with him. He just hoped that the cannon fodder of Chiyang Prefecture could hold back some of the imperial troops, and then he could escape smoothly.

Lin Fei saw the movement on the city wall. Regardless of the departure of those Qi cultivators or the leader of the Paradise Sect, Lin Fei didn't care. He and Li Yuhu had agreed before that he would break the city gate, and Li Yuhu would lead the troops to quell the rebellion.

Now, Lin Fei didn't break the city gate but collapsed the city wall. And those Qi cultivators just left, they did not obstruct the imperial army. So Lin Fei had no interest in chasing them. Besides, he might not even be able to catch up with them. As for capturing Chiyang Prefecture and annihilating the rebel forces, that was Li Yuhu's job.

At this moment, the morale of the imperial troops soared. Their side had someone like Lin Fei, who was like a god, what was there to be afraid of? Li Yuhu, as an experienced veteran, made a decisive decision and immediately ordered, "Enter the city and annihilate the rebels!"

The army began to charge. Countless imperial troops, mighty and majestic, rushed into Chiyang Prefecture through the gap in the city wall.

Lin Fei still stood in place, motionless. Because the voice of the system unexpectedly sounded in his mind.

"Your saber intent, because you broke the city wall with one saber, is greatly encouraged and excited. Its training progress has increased by 10%."

"Your True Intention Scroll, because you broke the city wall with one saber, is greatly encouraged and excited. Its training progress has increased by 10%."

"Your Heavenly Saber Art, because you broke the city wall with one saber, greatly displaying the might of Heavenly Saber Art, and being excited, its training progress has increased by 50%."

"Your Heavenly Saber Art has broken through to perfection!"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. Unexpectedly, he could gain so much from breaking the city wall with one saber in front of both armies.

The increase in the True Intention Scroll and saber intent was fine. The magnitude of the increase was not large. But the Heavenly Saber Art had increased by a full 50%. This was extraordinary. It directly allowed Heavenly Saber Art to reach perfection from transcendence.

Lin Fei closed his eyes. He carefully sorted out the memories in his mind. There was an additional bundle of memories in his mind. It is the memory of Heavenly Saber Art. Or rather, the memory of Heavenly Saber Art's perfection.

"Heavenly Saber Art Perfection can condense a Heavenly Saber."

"When the Heavenly Saber appears, all sabers bow their heads!"

"When you cast the Heavenly Saber, you can possess a 'Heavenly Saber Momentum', which forms a huge suppression on all saber users."

"Even if it's not a saber user, even Qi cultivators and martial arts Masters, can be suppressed by at least 20% of their strength."

"For those whose will is not firm, even more strength is suppressed."

The more Lin Fei examined the memory, the more shocked he was. This Heavenly Saber Art, once it reached perfection, was completely different from the Fierce saber and the Tyrant saber he had condensed before. Or to say, it was on two different levels.

Only by condensing the "Heavenly Saber" could one truly be considered a Heavenly Saber Art practitioner.

Both the fierce saber and the Tyrant saber were just transitional phases of the "Heavenly Saber". Their power didn't even amount to one-tenth of the Heavenly Saber. Only Heavenly Saber Art Perfection could condense the true Heavenly Saber.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately called up the system panel to check his martial arts status.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Late Stage

True Intention Scroll: Late Stage (Progress 42%)

Saber Intent: Transcendence (Progress 56%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Heavenly Saber Art: Perfection (Progress 0%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei's saber intent had moved a step closer to perfection. even the True Intention Scroll had improved a lot. This time, Lin Fei didn't expect to have an unexpected gain.

Lin Fei raised his head. He saw that on the city wall of Chiyang Prefecture, the flag of the Paradise Sect had fallen and it was replaced with the flag of the imperial court again. This indicated that the battle was going smoothly.

Lin Fei took a step forward and directly arrived at Chiyang Prefecture. There were bodies everywhere, most of them were Paradise Sect rebels. The entire Chiyang Prefecture was filled with the smell of blood.

Soon, a squad of soldiers came to Lin Fei. They respectfully said to Lin Fei, "The general invites Master Lin to the Yamen."

Lin Fei nodded and followed the soldiers to the Yamen. Li Yuhu was in the Yamen.

"Master Lin, you came just in time. We have captured the leader of the rebels. We have learned about the situation in detail. These rebels really are a rabble. The cities they occupied before basically had no troops.

Now that the rebels have suffered a great defeat, they no longer have the strength to fight. Other cities will soon be recaptured by the imperial army. In less than ten days, the rebellion will be completely quelled!"

Li Yuhu was very excited. This was a great achievement!

Originally, Li Yuhu was almost at the end of his rope. If it weren't for Lin Fei, the official army might have had to retreat due to a lack of food. Perhaps they would have been ambushed by the rebels and suffered a defeat.

Fortunately, Lin Fei came. With Lin Fei, Li Yuhu was able to completely crush the rebels and suppress the Paradise Sect rebellion.

"Ten days? That's good. General Li, the task of cleaning up the rebels is left to you."

Lin Fei nodded. Suppressing the rebellion in ten days. He was quite satisfied.

"Master Lin, there's one more thing. According to the confessions of the rebel leader, there were several unidentified Taoists who helped them defend Chiyang Prefecture. However, those Taoists, after Master Lin slashed the city wall with one saber, all fled in all directions, their whereabouts unknown."

Li Yuhu was a bit wary of these fleeing Taoists. After all, they were all Qi cultivators. Their methods were mysterious and unpredictable.

"Let them run. They wouldn't dare to come back. If they dare to, Lin will cut them down with one saber."

Lin Fei said indifferently. Killing Qi cultivators was Lin Fei's most skilled technique. After all, he was the "Immortal Slayer Saber". When the saber comes out, immortals must be slain!

149. "Capture" the Saber Technique, Force Integration!

Outside of Chiyang Prefecture.

Four Taoists looked at the fiery Chiyang Prefecture. Vaguely, there were still bursts of killing shouts. They knew that Chiyang Prefecture was done for and the Paradise Sect was also finished. Suppressing this rebellion was just a matter of time.

"Fellow Taoists, this time the royal family actually invited the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' to quell the rebellion. It seems that we have lost this time. Great Chang can also take a breather for now, which is not good for our major immortal sects."

"That's right, the biggest reason for this failure is the appearance of 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei."

"This 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, first slayed a Qi cultivator of He Mountain Dao, then killed my top Qi cultivator of Guardian Primordial Mountain, now disrupting the major events of our immortal sects."

"Lin Fei is from Nine Profound Sect. And the Nine Profound Sect has always been very close to the royal family,"

"This Lin Fei must be removed. Otherwise, in the future, he will still ruin our big plans."

"However, Lin Fei is the 'Immortal Slayer Saber', even Yuan Gangzi, a top Qi Condensation cultivator, was killed by him with one saber. Even if there are a few more top Qi Condensation cultivators, they may not be his opponents."

"Do we have to ask for Qi Condensation perfection or a Foundation Establishment True Person to come out?"

For a while, the four Taoists also fell into silence.

Qi Condensation perfection was impossible to come out of. No matter what happened, nothing was as important as Qi Condensation perfection cultivator establishing their foundation. So, the Qi Condensation perfection cultivator cannot come down the mountain.

As for Foundation Establishment True Person, that's even less likely to come down the mountain. The True Persons were waiting for the royal family's Supreme Elder to pass away. If the True Person moved, in case the royal family's Supreme Elder took a few True Persons down with him before he died, that would be in trouble. No sect could afford such a loss.

So, Foundation Establishment True Person cannot come down the mountain. At least, before the death of the royal family's Supreme Elder, there couldn't be a Foundation Establishment True Person coming down the mountain.

"Fellow Taoists, don't forget, we are Qi cultivators! Our strength as Qi cultivators is not just spells, talismans, and magical artifacts, but also arrays! Our Guardian Primordial Mountain has an array called the Five Directions Killing Array! If five top Qi cultivators set up the array together, below Foundation Establishment, death is certain!"

For a while, the eyes of the four Taoists flickered with excitement. It seemed that they were all weighing the situation.

"Our Guardian Primordial Mountain can dispatch a top Qi cultivator. After all, Lin Fei killed Elder Yuan Gangzi. This is a great revenge, and it must be avenged!"

"He Mountain Dao has sealed the mountain, but they should be able to be contacted. Given the current situation of Great Chang, the royal family's Supreme Elder can't do anything to He Mountain Dao."

"Lin Fei stepped on He Mountain Dao to achieve the reputation of 'Immortal Slayer Saber'. They should be able to send a top Qi Condensation cultivator."

"We, Purple Sun Mountain, can also send a top Qi Condensation cultivator."

"Our Mysterious Sky Cave can also send a top Qi Condensation cultivator."

"And we, Taiyi Sect, can also send a top Qi Condensation cultivator."

"Good, in this way, the Five Directions Killing Array can be formed. Now we will return to our sects first. As quickly as three days or as slow as ten days, there will surely be top Qi Condensation cultivators coming down. By then, Lin Fei must die!"

The four Taoists did not stay any longer. They quickly dispersed and moved far away from Chiyang Prefecture.

......

Longshan City was the last city occupied by the rebels because they had nowhere to go. Therefore, this time the rebels held the city in defense.

In order to survive, the rebels also began to fight desperately. This caused great losses to the official army.

In the end, Li Yuhu invited Lin Fei. Then, Lin Fei swung his saber, generating two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy. Just like in Chiyang Prefecture, the city wall collapsed instantly.

As a result, Longshan City was naturally retaken by the royal army. The last force of the rebels was also annihilated. At this point, the entire Paradise Sect was annihilated. The rebellion was completely suppressed.

Starting from the day Lin Fei arrived at Chiyang Prefecture, it took only five days. The army completely suppressed the rebellion.

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' Senior Lin."

At this time, a young man dressed as a martial artist came to Lin Fei.

"I am passionate about saber techniques. In the world today, when it comes to saber techniques, you are at the top, Senior Lin. I want to become your disciple, I hope you agree."

"Become my disciple?"

Lin Fei looked up and down at the man.

"The perfection stage saber technique 'One Leaf Saber Technique' was captured by your Heavenly Saber Art."

"Your Heavenly Saber Art forcibly integrated the 'One Leaf Saber Technique', improving the practice progress by 1%."

Lin Fei was slightly surprised.

"Capture the saber technique? And it can even increase the progress of practicing the Heavenly Saber Art. Is this characteristic that appears after the Heavenly Saber Art reaches perfection?"

Lin Fei immediately reacted. Once the Heavenly Saber Art reached perfection, its nature was quite domineering, directly capturing other saber techniques to enhance its own foundation.

Although the Heavenly Saber Art was already at perfection, the practice progress could still be improved. And it was improved through this technique of forcibly "capturing" other saber techniques.

Once the practice progress reached 100% again, there was a high probability that the Heavenly Saber Art would generate saber intent! At that time, Lin Fei would have two types of saber intent. Even the two types of saber intent might merge.

To what extent would the practice progress of the saber intent improve then? For a moment, many thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

"Senior?" Seeing that Lin Fei didn't respond, the martial artist couldn't help but carefully reminded him again.

"Are you practicing the One Leaf Saber Technique?" Lin Fei asked.

The man was slightly startled and then nodded, "Senior has keen eyes, I am indeed practicing the One Leaf Saber Technique. And, I have already practiced it to perfection..."

"I understand."

After Lin Fei finished speaking, he turned around and walked away directly.

"If you want to practice the saber, go to the Nine Profound Sect. I do not take disciples."

Lin Fei's voice came from afar. He had already walked far away. The man could only stare blankly at Lin Fei's retreating figure.

Lin Fei arrived at the government office and found General Li Yuhu.

"General Li, the rebellion has been completely suppressed, and I should return to Chang City."

"Master Lin is leaving?"

Li Yuhu was slightly startled. Since Lin Fei arrived, he found that fighting didn't seem difficult at all. It was even quite simple.

When encountering rebels defending the city, Lin Fei made a move, one saber strike, and the city wall was broken. When encountering tough nuts to crack, Lin Fei made a move, one saber strike, and all rebel leaders were killed.

With such a powerhouse present, Li Yuhu became someone who picked up the credit.

"I have some things to do back in Chang City. General Li, we shall part here."

After saying that, Lin Fei turned around and left. The system's voice just now in his mind made Lin Fei vaguely understand a direction.

The way to further improve Heavenly Saber Art was to find some saber practitioners. Especially powerful saber practitioners. Preferably those who have perfected the saber technique.

In this way, Lin Fei's "Heavenly Saber Art" could continue to "capture" those martial arts, to merge and increase its foundation.

Someday, if he practiced the saber intent and merged it with the current saber intent, then Lin Fei's saber intent might increase instantly. It could even reach the realm of perfection!

This was the domineering of Heavenly Saber Art. Lin Fei finally understood the phrase in Heavenly Saber Art.

"When the Heavenly Saber appears, all other sabers bow!"

Once the Heavenly Saber reaches perfection, it could almost suppress all lower-level saber techniques.

Lin Fei left Longshan City. He rushed towards Chang City all the way. This time he helped the imperial court suppress the Paradise Sect rebellion. Once he returned to Chang City, he could watch the martial arts secret records. At that time, whether what Liu Yibai said was true or false, Lin Fei could tell by himself.

As Lin Fei got closer to Chang City, there were fewer and fewer refugees.

Lin Fei was a bit strange. Even if the court suppressed the rebellion, refugees had already become refugees. It was impossible to disappear all at once. Even when Lin Fei arrived at a bamboo forest, it was very quiet around. There was not a single refugee.

"Something is wrong!"

Lin Fei suddenly stopped. His eyes were keenly looking around. But it was already too late!

"Hum".

The next moment, the environment around turned blood-red all at once. It had suddenly become a bloody space here and enveloped Lin Fei instantly.

150. The Five Directions Killing Array

"A formation array!"

Lin Fei surveyed this blood-hued domain. The potent fluctuations of spiritual power instantly clarified his understanding it was an array formed by Qi cultivators.

"Lin Fei, stepping into our Five Directions Killing Array, arranged by five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, your death is certain!"

Within the bloody space, a chorus of voices echoed, yet Lin Fei couldn't discern their origins. Such was the nature of an array, Qi cultivators had methods to conceal their aura and location.

"Five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. You truly hold me in high regard!"

Lin Fei's tone remained calm, his mind was equally serene. In such moments, one must maintain a cool head.

Since this Five Directions Killing Array was the collective effort of five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, it suggested that they hold considerable confidence to kill Lin Fei through this array.

"Cowards, come out!"

A glint flashed within Lin Fei's eyes.

"Boom."

Instantaneously, his saber intent erupted. Transcendent saber intent, mighty and overwhelming, blanketed the entire crimson expanse in an instant.

Lin Fei's saber intent wasn't intended to break the Five Directions Killing Array. It was to locate the positions of the five Qi cultivators. Only then could he execute them. Only by executing them, perhaps, could he break this array.

However, as Lin Fei unfurled his overwhelming saber intent, it proved to be of no avail. Even his saber intent seemed to be suppressed within a certain area.

This Five Directions Killing Array could even suppress saber intent!

"Hehe, Lin Fei, don't waste your energy. We're operating the array from outside the Five Directions Killing Array. Unless you can break the Five Directions Killing Array, otherwise, you can't touch us. However, you have no hope. Five Directions Killing Array, unleash the sword energy!"

As the words of the Qi cultivator fell, within the Five Directions Killing Array, strands of sword energy appeared. These strands of sword energy were finer than silkworm thread. This was the transformation of sword energy into the thread!

The sword energy appearing as fine as thread, it didn't seem very powerful. But in reality, transforming sword energy into thread could amplify the 'sharpness' attribute of sword energy to its peak. Its sole trait was sharpness, capable of slicing through everything!

Moreover, it wasn't a single thread, but the entirety of the Five Directions Killing Array filled with these Sword Threads. Even a Martial Arts Grandmaster within this Five Directions Killing Array would likely die instantly.

There would be no room for struggle. After all, a Grand Master's Innate True Qi hadn't yet reached the extent of withstanding so many Sword Threads.

"Saber energy encompasses the body!"

Yet Lin Fei exhibited not the slightest panic. With a flicker of thought, saber energy covered his entire body, leaving no crevices exposed.

"Hiss hiss hiss."

Subsequently, within the blood-colored space, the sky filled with Sword Threads began to slice at Lin Fei. Each strand of sharp sword energy, when cutting across Lin Fei, collided with the saber energy enveloping him. Instantly, the sword energy dissipated into nothingness. Swiftly, the sword energy within the blood-colored space was consumed completely.

At this moment, outside the Five Directions Killing Array, the faces of the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators darkened upon observing the situation within the array.

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' isn't easily killed, otherwise, why would it necessitate the five of us, top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, to form an array to surround and kill him?"

"Indeed, this was only the first killing array. The Five Directions Killing Array has a total of five killing arrays, each more formidable than the last."

"If the sword energy array can't kill him, activate the second killing array!"

With the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators urging the array, the entire Five Directions Killing Array underwent another transformation. The sword energy had already vanished. Next, the blood-colored space seemed to ignite. The entirety of the bloody space subtly turned a fiery red.

"Five Directions Killing Array, Blood Flame Kill!"

Lin Fei's internal Qi and blood seemed to tremble, faintly drawn by the surrounding bloody flames as if about to ignite. This was the Blood Flame Kill. Roaring flames of fire capable of reducing any person's blood to ash.

But Lin Fei's body was encompassed by saber energy and remained unshakeable. Unless his saber energy was broken, Lin Fei was impervious.

"Cold Ice Kill!"

"Bone Erosion Kill!"

Four consecutive layers of killing arrays, all powerless against Lin Fei. But Lin Fei hadn't taken action all this while. Because he hadn't discovered a weak point in the Five Directions Killing Array.

Just now, he had already used a few tactics, attempting to destroy the Five Directions Killing Array, but he found that he could not break it. Even Lin Fei's saber energy was formidable, it too had its limits.

When dealing with an array, as long as the weak point of the array was found, breaking the array becomes easy. Otherwise, even with ten or a hundred times the power, it was still not necessarily breakable.

"Four layers of killing arrays were unable to handle Lin Fei. It seems we can only resort to the final layer of the killing array. With this final layer of the killing array, Lin Fei is bound to die. Five Directions Killing Array, Heavenly Thunder Kill!"

Suddenly, the thunder rolled. A massive thunderbolt descended from the sky, directly bombing into the Five Directions Killing Array.

However, in this instant, Lin Fei immediately perceived the auras of the five Qi Condensation cultivators. The Five Directions Killing Array, upon the thunderbolt's bombardment, finally revealed a flaw.

At this moment, Lin Fei did not hesitate.

"Heavenly Saber Art, slash!"

"Boom."

Instantly, Lin Fei employed the Heavenly Saber Art.

Two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy, exuding terrifying power and following the direction of the thunderbolt's descent, which was the only flaw in the entire Five Directions Killing Array.

The "Heavenly Saber" condensed by Lin Fei, slashed down mercilessly.

"Boom."

The two hundred and fifty meters saber energy Heavenly Saber directly split the massive thunderbolt. Next, the overwhelming saber energy fiercely landed on the unobstructed killing array.

"Crack."

Finally, the unobstructed killing array shattered. The surrounding blood-colored space also disappeared.

Lin Fei's vision returned to normal. He saw five unfamiliar Qi Condensation cultivators before him. The fluctuations of spiritual power in their bodies were exceedingly terrifying. Clearly, they were all top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

"How could he break the Five Directions Killing Array, how is this possible?"

"The Five Directions Killing Array couldn't kill him!? How could he directly split the final Heavenly Thunder Kill with saber energy?"

"What a terrifying saber energy. Can a martial artist without a foundation stage be so strong?"

"The array has been broken, we can't kill him anymore, let's go!"

The five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, seeing that the situation was hopeless, immediately prepared to flee.

Under normal circumstances, if a Qi cultivator wanted to leave, a martial artist certainly couldn't hold them back. After all, Qi cultivators have magical artifacts, controlling magical artifacts allows them to directly ascend and fly.

And martial artists? Even a martial arts Grand Master cannot fly. Only upon achieving Martial Saint can one's body undergo a rebirth and then possess various martial arts divine abilities and walking on air would no longer be a difficult feat. But in the innate realm, the methods of martial artists were far inferior to those of these Qi cultivators.

The five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators were also quite decisive. They directly employed their magical artifacts and immediately turned into five streaks of rainbow light, attempting to escape.

If it were in the past, Lin Fei truly wouldn't be able to do anything about these five. However, Lin Fei's Heavenly Saber Art has now reached perfection. He did have a few tricks up his sleeve.

"Want to escape?"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly, his Saber Qi erupted once again.

"Heavenly Saber Art!"

"Hum."

With the implementation of the Heavenly Saber Art, two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy was again condensed in the void.

This is the Heavenly Saber. With the appearance of the Heavenly Saber, not only was there saber intent but also a peculiar power.

It was like a large net, instantly enveloping the bodies of the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

"Boom."

Immediately, the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators felt a jolt throughout their bodies. Even the spiritual power within their bodies was somewhat suppressed.

"What's happening?"

"Our spiritual power is being suppressed."

"What kind of technique is this?"

"Even the Martial Dao True Intent doesn't have this kind of capability."

The five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators were flustered. They couldn't escape!

"Is this the power of the Heavenly Saber under the state of perfection? Under the power of the Heavenly Saber, the enemy's strength will be suppressed. It's as if they're burdened by a heavy mountain. Want to escape? Their speed could be instantly slowed, enough for me to kill with one saber."

Lin Fei looked at the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, whose speeds sharply dropped.

Even though he was very shocked by the effect of the Heavenly Saber's power, Lin Fei didn't hesitate at all.

"Slash!"

Immediately, Lin Fei's saber energy divided into five, instantly slashing toward the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

"No..."

The five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators never expected that this would happen. Their attempt to surround and kill Lin Fei failed, and even escaping turned out to be a luxury.

Consequently, they let out terrified screams. They were all top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. In theory, they all had the opportunity to establish their foundation. Who would want to die here?

"Pfft."

However, Lin Fei's saber energy didn't care about that. Each saber energy was more than thirty meters long.

With a slash of the saber, the bodies of the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators were cut in half by the saber energy.

With a "thud," they fell to the ground from mid-air. The five Qi Condensation cultivators fell.

Lin Fei, with a single saber, slaughtered the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators!

151. How strong is Foundation Establishment True Person?

Lin Fei approached the bodies of the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. Their bodies had been cleaved into two by the saber energy. There was absolutely no chance of survival.

Lin Fei was not worried about any feigned death. Even if Qi cultivators had unusual techniques, under these circumstances, they were surely dead.

However, Lin Fei needed to ascertain the identities of these five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. After all, so far, the immortal sects that Lin Fei had offended were really only the He Mountain Dao and the Guardian Primordial Mountain.

The two Immortal sects sending out five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, Lin Fei found it somewhat unlikely. Hence, Lin Fei searched through the five bodies, seeking the identities of these five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

After searching for a while, Lin Fei figured out the identities of the five Qi Condensation cultivators.

"Guardian Primordial Mountain, He Mountain Dao, Purple Sun Mountain, Mysterious Sky Cave, and Taiyi Sect. Five major Immortal Sects in total.

I can understand Guardian Primordial Mountain and He Mountain Dao. I've killed Qi cultivators from them, so it's normal for them to want revenge.

But what about Purple Sun Mountain, Mysterious Sky Cave, and Taiyi Sect? I've never even heard of these three Immortal sects before..."

Lin Fei's brow furrowed slightly. The intervention of these three Immortal sects, even dispatching five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators to besiege him was not normal.

Immortal sects were not monolithic. It wasn't a given that the He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, by inviting these sects, would definitely have Qi Condensation cultivators act.

Qi Condensation cultivators were, in fact, experts at calculating. Why would they do anything without benefits?

"Could it be that these three sects are actually related to the rebel forces?"

Lin Fei had a thought. He considered a possibility. These sects were probably the backers of the Paradise Sect rebels. Lin Fei had helped the court to suppress the rebel army, resolving the rebellion. These five major Immortal sects saw him as a threat, so they wanted to eliminate him in advance.

This made sense.

"Five major immortal sects...all should be killed! If I become a Martial Saint, I will trample these five major Immortal sects!"

A glint of coldness flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He didn't care what these five major immortal sects were plotting, but they supported the Paradise Sect rebellion.

Moreover, this rebellion was instigated by these five major Immortal sects. All Lin Fei saw along the way were fields of white bones. Millions of people were displaced. That's all because of this rebellion incited by the five major Immortal sects. The direct or indirect deaths due to this amounted to hundreds of thousands! Lin Fei could not turn a blind eye.

However, Immortal sects had magical treasures to guard their sects. At least for now, Lin Fei was powerless against them.

"I have to return to Chang City first."

Lin Fei did not linger. With a step, he was instantly on his way back to Chang City.

......

Chang City, the Imperial Palace.

Lin Fei had a token given by the Emperor. Therefore, he could directly enter the palace.

Lin Fei arrived at the Ascending Dragon Chamber and saw the three elders from before.

"I have assisted the court army in suppressing the Paradise Sect rebellion. Should I be able to read the martial arts secret records left by the ancestor now?" Lin Fei calmly said.

The three elders looked at Lin Fei with complex expressions. Although the official report had not yet reached the court, they had already learned through some intelligence about Lin Fei's visit to the frontlines and the specific battle situation.

Lin Fei collapsed a city wall with one saber strike, scaring four high-level Qi Condensation cultivators into fleeing. The court army, in just a few days, quelled all the rebellion as if breaking a bamboo.

The efficiency was high. This shocked all three elders of the royal family. Of course, they were still unaware of Lin Fei's mid-way killing of five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

It's estimated that those immortal sects might not necessarily spread the news. But even so, it was already enough to stun the elders of the royal family.

"Master Lin, you may read the martial arts secret records left by the ancestor. Please follow me."

Thus, one of the elders rose. He took Lin Fei to a secret room.

"The martial arts secret records left by the ancestor are in this secret room. There's no time limit, Master Lin. You can read as long as you want. But there's one rule. You cannot copy, nor disclose the contents."

Lin Fei nodded. Actually, the second rule, not to disclose the contents, was very hard for the royal family to monitor. Even the rule of not copying was hard to monitor. If Lin Fei secretly memorized and then wrote it down himself, there would be no problem.

However, there was no need for that. Those who could view the martial arts secret records were extremely confident in themselves.

If they wanted to leave it for future generations, they could just succeed in foundation building and become a Martial Saint in the future.

By then, these pieces of information would become left by the mouth of a Martial Saint, the royal family would have nothing to say.

"Rumble."

The stone door of the secret room fell. Only Lin Fei was left in the secret room.

Lin Fei sat cross-legged. He grabbed the martial arts secret records from the stone table.

The martial arts secret records were engraved on sheets of paper that were neither gold nor jade. Even after hundreds of years, there was no change.

Lin Fei opened the martial arts secret records. Page by page, he scrutinized very carefully.

The further he read, the more solemn his expression became.

About half an hour later, Lin Fei had finished reading the martial arts secret records. He directly closed it.

The content of the martial arts secret records was divided into several parts. One part was the personal experience of the Great Chang's Ancestor.

For example, the Great Chang's Ancestor initially accidentally discovered an ancient sect's relics from a thousand years ago. In there, he found many martial arts secret scripts. Then he made rapid progress and became a martial arts Grand Master.

Moreover, in that ancient sect, he also discovered a thousand-year-old blood orchid that was still growing. With this thousand-year-old blood orchid, the Great Chang's Ancestor achieved physical perfection, which allowed him to successfully build his foundation and become a Martial Saint. He later swept across the world and established Great Chang.

Another part was some of the Great Chang's Ancestor's martial arts insights and some martial arts common knowledge.

For example, the Great Chang's Ancestor learned from the ancient texts of that sect. Martial Saint was not the end of martial arts. Above Martial Saint, there are even stronger existences. The perfection of Martial Dao True Intent was not the limit either. After the perfection of Martial Dao True Intent, comes momentum!

For example, sword intent transforms into sword momentum. Saber intent transforms into saber momentum.

Once Martial Dao True Intent transforms into momentum, one can suppress others with their "momentum". In the "momentum" of a martial artist, one can suppress enemies and weaken their strength. Once a martial artist comprehends "momentum", they are comparable to a Martial Saint!

The difference between a Martial Saint with and without momentum is like night and day.

Great Chang's Ancestor was fortunate enough to comprehend momentum. So, he was able to sweep through all opposition as a Martial Saint. Even those Foundation Establishment True Persons were not Great Chang's Ancestor's opponents.

This "momentum" immediately reminded Lin Fei of his Heavenly Saber Art.

Once the Heavenly Saber Art was perfected, one could have the "momentum of the heavenly saber". It could also suppress enemies.

However, compared to the momentum mentioned by Great Chang's Ancestor, capable of suppressing Foundation Establishment True Persons, the momentum of the heavenly saber was clearly much weaker. At most, it could be considered a weakened version of momentum.

Lin Fei speculated. Most likely, this Heavenly Saber Art was passed down from a martial arts sect from a thousand years ago. It was probably created based on the "momentum" of a Martial Saint. But even a weakened version of momentum was very powerful.

The last part was about cultivation techniques. Great Chang's Ancestor left behind a cultivation technique. This cultivation technique was obtained from the scriptures of a sect from a thousand years ago.

It was called "Refining The Golden Body". It was not a particularly profound martial arts technique, but an auxiliary cultivation method used specifically to absorb some heaven and earth treasures, or the flesh and blood of exotic beasts.

It allowed martial artists to avoid waste when consuming heaven and earth treasures, or the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. It could significantly increase the efficiency of consumption, allowing the body to achieve perfection faster.

Once the body had achieved perfection, this cultivation method becomes irrelevant. This was a very common auxiliary cultivation method a thousand years ago. So, Great Chang's Ancestor also left it behind to help future generations have a greater chance of achieving physical perfection.

Moreover, from the martial arts secret records left by the ancestor, in order for a martial artist to build their foundation and become a Martial Saint, the physical body did need to reach perfection, and to reach physical perfection, one must consume some heaven and earth treasures or the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. That is to say, one must rely on external help.

In fact, Qi cultivators also need to rely on external help when building their foundations. The spiritual herbs needed for the refinement of Foundation Establishment Pills were precious.

Most of the major sects had some blessed lands where they could cultivate these spiritual herbs. Therefore, they could barely refine Foundation Establishment Pills.

However, martial arts sects didn't have any blessed lands. Even if some sects were strong enough to keep exotic beasts during their prime. After the decline of martial arts, they gradually lost this ability, making it difficult to even find traces of an exotic beast now.

"That is to say, what Liu Yibai said is all true. Exotic beasts are hard to find. The exotic beasts that Liu Yibai knows about might be the only remaining exotic beasts in Great Chang.

If I miss this opportunity, even if my martial arts talent is strong, I will end up like the Ancestor of the Nine Profound Sect, unable to reach physical perfection, and forever unable to build my foundation. In the end, I can only sit and transform on the Ancestral Master Peak, becoming a mound of yellow earth."

Lin Fei seemed to be able to feel the despair of the Nine Profound Sect's founder when he saw the martial arts secret records.

At that time, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect must have known about reaching physical perfection and building a foundation. He even searched the entire Great Chang but couldn't find any traces of exotic beasts.

The martial arts secret records left by Great Chang's Ancestor were his only chance. He wanted to see if he could find other ways to build a foundation. Unfortunately, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect eventually left in disappointment.

Lin Fei closed the martial arts secret records. He had understood everything he needed to know. As for "Refining The Golden Body", it's very simple.

Lin Fei slightly recalled the method of Refining The Golden Body in his mind. Immediately, the system's voice sounded in his mind.

"Your martial arts technique, Refining The Golden Body, due to the absence of exotic beast flesh and blood, is like a good wife with no rice to cook, the progress of practice is 0."

Lin Fei was not too surprised. This martial arts technique was only useful when consuming the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. At other times, there was not even a hint of improvement.

Lin Fei got up and left the secret room.

"Master Lin, you came out so soon?"

The three old men of the royal family were somewhat surprised to see Lin Fei coming out so soon. After all, anyone who sees the martial arts secret records would carefully ponder and check, staying in the secret room for several days, which was quite common. But Lin Fei, took less than two hours before he came out.

"I have already got the answer from the martial arts secret records. Therefore, naturally, I came out. But there is one last thing. The Supreme Elder previously said that if I suppress the rebellion, he might even meet me. Now, I just want to ask the Supreme Elder to agree to one thing. I want to know, how strong is a Foundation Establishment True Person?"

Lin Fei's eyes were sharp as a saber and there was a hint of fighting intent on his body!

----------------------

Due to cultural differences, you might feel confused about certain expressions, so I'll provide explanations for some phrases.

In Chinese culture, bamboo is often regarded as a symbol of strength and resilience. Therefore, "breaking a bamboo" is used to describe a person or a team's unstoppable momentum, progress, victory, or achievement, just like the breaking of bamboo that cannot be hindered.

152. I have a saber, please try it

"How audacious, Lin Fei, do you realize what you're saying?"

The three elders of the royal family's faces instantly changed.

What was Lin Fei doing? He was actually thinking about challenging the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family!

One must know the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family within the royal family was like a steadfast pillar. His prestige was unimaginably high. Lin Fei's "disrespect" naturally made the three elders furious.

However, Lin Fei's expression remained calm.

At this point in time, Lin Fei had already slain six top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. The power of the Five Directions Killing Array set up by the five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators earlier was even more formidable than a perfect Qi Condensation cultivator.

Now the only thing that can make Lin Fei feel cautious was only Foundation Establishment! Foundation Establishment was very mysterious and high above. Like a dragon that is often heard but seldom seen.

Even though Lin Fei had heard of Foundation Establishment True Person many times now. Great Chang's Ancestor, Hidden Sword Sect's Sword Saint, and the Foundation Establishment True Persons of various major sects, etc.

However, Lin Fei had never seen even one of them, let alone "sparring" with them. Lin Fei really wanted to try where was his current limit? Or to put it another way, where was the gap between him and Foundation Establishment?

"A martial artist should be fearless and dauntless. He should have the courage to battle against heaven and earth! I just want to see the gap between me and Foundation Establishment. True Person, won't you even grant me this small request?"

Lin Fei suddenly looked up, looking at the ceiling. There was nothing on the ceiling of the Ascending Dragon Chamber. However, Lin Fei seemed to have pierced through the Ascending Dragon Chamber.

Even, through countless distances, he seemed to "see" a Foundation Establishment True Person with an immortal demeanor somewhere.

Supreme Elder of the Royal Family!

Lin Fei believed that at this moment, whatever he saw, the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family would definitely know.

Even more so, the saber intent on Lin Fei gradually began to rise.

Facing the transcendent saber intent, even the three elders of the royal family, high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, couldn't help but take a few steps back. They looked at Lin Fei with shock and awe on their faces. The 'Immortal Slayer Saber' was renowned. They were no match for him.

"Lin Fei, I hope you don't misjudge yourself. The Supreme Elder is the pillar of our royal family and even of Great Chang, how can you challenge him at will?"

"Not to mention you, even if the founder of Nine Profound Sect were to reincarnate, he wouldn't dare to speak to the Supreme Elder like that."

The three elder's faces were dark and they reprimanded loudly. However, Lin Fei didn't pay any heed. Instead, he continued to gaze at the ceiling. After a long time, a sigh echoed.

"Enough. Since you've made a request. I will satisfy you. Bring Lin Fei to the Imperial Garden, do not alert others."

A hoarse voice came from the void. This was the voice of the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family.

"Yes, Ancestor!"

The three royal elders responded respectfully. They might look very old. Even though they were the elder of the royal family. However, compared to the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family who has lived for five hundred years, they were merely juniors.

"Lin Fei, come with us."

Since the Supreme Elder had spoken, the three royal elders no longer stopped him. They directly left the Ascending Dragon Chamber with Lin Fei.

Lin Fei followed behind the three elders, turning several corridors. Finally, it was wide open in front of him.

This was an open area surrounded by lush trees. Although it was already winter, but here, it was warm like spring. Even some flowers and trees didn't seem to be affected by the winter.

Lin Fei looked up, looking at the void. In the void, there was a faint light, visible to the naked eye.

"Formation!"

Lin Fei understood. The entire Imperial Garden was covered by a formation. That's why it could be warm like spring here.

In the Imperial Garden, there was a black-robed old man standing quietly. This old man, in fact, didn't look very old. He seemed to be about fifty years old. He even looked younger than the three elders. However, despite his youthful appearance, his eyes revealed a sense of age.

"Greetings to the Ancestor!"

The three elders were very excited. They respectfully saluted the black-robed old man. The old man waved his hand, his gaze fell on Lin Fei.

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei. Although your Innate True Qi is not perfect, and your saber intent is not perfect either, you are the most talented person I've seen in the last five hundred years. Even the Sword Saint of the Hidden Sword Sect from three hundred years ago did not have your martial arts talent."

The old man spoke in a hoarse, calm voice, his hands behind his back.

"True Person!"

Lin Fei also respectfully saluted. Then he lifted his head, looking at the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family, and said in a deep voice, "Without becoming a Martial Saint, all is empty. The founder of the Nine Profound Sect was like this. What's the use of being more brilliant? In the end, isn't it just turning into a handful of dust?"

The Supreme Elder nodded, "Indeed, you are very clear-headed. Without becoming a Martial Saint, all is empty, no matter how brilliant, it can't withstand the passage of time. Only by reaching Foundation Establishment, can one extend one's life by hundreds of years.

However, whether you can establish a foundation and become a Martial Saint, I can't help you. After all, I don't have any exotic beast flesh to give you, and I don't have the good fortune of the Founding Emperor, who was able to obtain a thousand-year-old blood orchid. Whether or not you can establish a foundation depends on you."

Lin Fei nodded, he didn't expect the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family to give him exotic beast meat. That was impossible.

"Senior, this time I came to see you. I have only one request. I hope you can let me know how strong Foundation Establishment is."

The eyes of the Supreme Elder were profound. He calmly looked at Lin Fei, "How would you like to test?"

"Whoosh."

In the next moment, the aura on Lin Fei began to rise bit by bit. Even his saber intent gradually spread out. Above his head, a sharp great saber vaguely formed. A terrifying saber intent suddenly filled the entire Imperial Garden.

Lin Fei's expression was very serious. The opponent he faced was the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family, a True Person who had lived for five hundred years!

Furthermore, the Supreme Elder was definitely not an ordinary True Person. He was very likely to be the top True Person. Otherwise, how could he suppress the world for hundreds of years?

The suppressed immortal sects could only hide in their mountain gates. They could only wait until the time limit of the Supreme Elder was approaching, and then slowly move.

Therefore, facing this unprecedented opponent, Lin Fei would concentrate all his attention, and adjust the state of his body to reach its peak state!

The three elders of the royal family, at this moment, after feeling Lin Fei's saber intent, couldn't help but retreat a few steps. It was just saber intent, but they couldn't even handle it.

This also exposed their shortcomings. They were always in the royal family, living in comfort. Their minds and wills were too poor. Naturally, they couldn't block Lin Fei's transcendent saber intent.

However, Lin Fei's opponent, the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family seemed to be very casual. Even his spiritual power didn't fluctuate.

As for Lin Fei's saber intent. It was as if he didn't feel it at all. He was still standing quietly in the same place.

Lin Fei's momentum had reached its peak. At this point, he took a deep breath.

"Boom."

A sky-high saber energy, up to two hundred and fifty meters, condensed in the void. And this wasn't just saber energy. It was the Heavenly Saber condensed by Lin Fei!

Under the Heavenly Saber, all sabers bowed! The might of the Heavenly Saber suddenly pressed down.

The three elders, at this moment, felt like they were carrying a mountain on their backs.

Under these circumstances, if they were to face Lin Fei, they couldn't even resist, let alone fight back.

"So this is the 'Immortal Slayer Saber'? So terrifying..."

It was only at this time that the three elders understood how terrifying Lin Fei was.

High-level Qi Condensation cultivators? Top-level Qi Condensation cultivators? It was nothing more than a casual saber from Lin Fei.

When the Heavenly Saber was condensed, the power of the Heavenly Saber covered the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family.

Lin Fei's momentum finally reached its peak. He reached out his hand as if holding the Heavenly Saber in the void. His gaze was arrogant, with a momentum of cutting down all enemies with one saber!

"I have a saber, please try it!"

As soon as Lin Fei's words fell, he used his hand as a saber, swinging it down.

"Boom."

The two hundred and fifty meters Heavenly Saber instantly cut through the void. It came down from the sky and slashed toward the Supreme Elder!

153. Fighting Against Foundation Establishment

One saber slashed down. It was like the earth sinking and the sky collapsing.

In everyone's eyes, this saber came down from the sky. It seemed not to be a saber but the sky was collapsing. This was the might of the sky falling!

This saber was Lin Fei's strongest saber so far. Without a doubt, whether it's saber intent, saber energy, or the saber technique, they were all Lin Fei's current strongest!

Facing this saber, the three elders of the royal family, and even the top Qi condensation cultivators probably only have deep despair.

However, Lin Fei's opponent was the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family, a Foundation Establishment realm cultivator who had lived for five hundred years!

"Good saber technique! This saber technique has even some implications of saber momentum. If your saber intent really turns into saber momentum, maybe it can really make me feel a headache.

However, it's just a saber momentum simulated by the saber technique, it's not worth mentioning. Now, let me show you what is Foundation Establishment."

The Supreme Elder of the Royal Family slowly extended his hand. This hand was somewhat withered and looked a little thin. It was an old hand, but it was this hand that turned gently.

"Boom."

The whole heaven and earth, or to say, the whole imperial garden, all of them shook instantly. In the void, countless heaven and earth Spiritual Qi, all seemed to collectively "agitate".

These heaven and earth Spiritual Qi turned into a huge palm. It seemed like the palm of the Supreme Elder had been magnified countless times, and then clenched hard.

"Boom."

Heaven and earth shook. Lin Fei's saber energy, which seemed capable of slashing everything, even the earth turning upside down, two hundred and fifty meters tall, actually disintegrated instantly under this huge palm made up of Spiritual Qi. Endless saber energy was annihilated by this huge palm of Spiritual Qi and disappeared without a trace.

"Hoo..."

Everything became quiet. The entire imperial garden seemed to have returned to its calm. It didn't even look like there had been a fight. Even the flowers, plants, and trees in the imperial garden hadn't suffered any damage at all.

The breeze was blowing. There seemed to be a hint of chill.

A hint of astonishment appeared in Lin Fei's eyes. Once upon a time, Lin Fei thought he could cut through the Foundation Establishment with his Heavenly Saber Art and Saber Qi.

However, when he truly faced a Foundation Establishment cultivator, he found that his saber energy, his saber intent even his saber technique, seemed... insignificant!

The Supreme Elder of the Royal Family looked at the slightly shocked Lin Fei. He shook his head slightly and said, "It's not that your saber technique is too weak. Rather, it's a difference in the realm. Do you know how much strength I used just now?"

Lin Fei asked solemnly, "Please enlighten me, True Person."

"Not even one percent of my power."

"Boom."

Lin Fei's mind roared instantly.

"This can't be possible..."

Even if Lin Fei knew that the gap between him and a Foundation Establishment cultivator was large, it couldn't possibly be so large that he couldn't even withstand one percent of a Foundation Establishment cultivator's strength. This was simply impossible!

"As I said, different realms lead to different understandings. Just now, the palm that I struck used a very limited amount of my own spiritual power. I simply used my realm to manipulate the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth in the entire imperial garden.

We Qi cultivators pursue coexistence with heaven and earth and make use of the mighty power of nature. Just now, I merely used a trace of spiritual power to leverage the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth in the entire imperial garden to cast a sealing spell."

Lin Fei understood. The Supreme Elder only used a small amount of his own power. But he was able to leverage the Spiritual Qi of the entire imperial garden. Therefore, the power of the spell he cast was so great.

However, was the palm that the Supreme Elder just struck really a spell? That palm, it looked a bit like a martial arts technique.

"Supreme Elder, was that palm really a spell?" Lin Fei couldn't help but ask.

"Of course it was a spell. However, different paths lead to the same goal. Once a martial artist builds his foundation and becomes a Martial Saint, he will possess Martial Dao Divine Power, which is even more formidable than that of spells."

Lin Fei understood.

He bowed to the Supreme Elder and said, "Thank you, True Person, for helping me understand the gap between me and the Foundation Establishment. Without becoming a Martial Saint, everything is in vain! I have disturbed you. I will take my leave."

After speaking, Lin Fei turned around and strode away. In a few leaps, he disappeared without a trace.

"Supreme Elder, this Lin Fei..."

The three elders of the royal family watched as Lin Fei left. Their faces changed slightly. It seemed that they wanted to say something.

But the Supreme Elder gently shook his head and said, "There's no need to try to win him over, no need to say anything superfluous. Lin Fei knows what he's doing. Right now, the Nine Profound Sect, the Royal Family, and even Great Chang are all inextricably linked. We either rise together, or we fall together."

It's just a pity that exotic beasts are now extinct, so it's almost impossible for Lin Fei to build his foundation and become a Martial Saint. Otherwise, if Great Chang wants to extend its national destiny for another few hundred years, it might depend on him."

The three elders were shocked. They hadn't expected the Supreme Elder to rate Lin Fei so highly. He even said that the continuation of Great Chang's national destiny might depend on Lin Fei.

"Supreme Elder, your ultimate fate..."

"Go back, let nature take its course, what's supposed to come will come eventually."

"Yes, Supreme Elder."

The three dared not ask any further. They quickly left the imperial garden.

Lin Fei returned to the South King Mansion. He didn't go to see Ling Yao. Instead, he went directly back to his own room.

"System."

Lin Fei called out the system to check.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Art Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Late stage

True Intention Scroll: Late stage (Progress 42%)

Saber Intent: Transcendence (Progress 56%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Heavenly Saber Art: Perfection (Progress 1%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Refining The Golden Body: (Progress 0%)

During this period, Lin Fei's martial arts almost reached a bottleneck. Hard cultivation alone didn't mean much. At least, there wasn't much hope for a rapid increase in strength in a short time.

The scene of his fight with the Supreme Elder of the Royal Family was still lingering in Lin Fei's mind. He had no chance of winning!

Even more so, Lin Fei had a faint feeling. Even if his True Qi reached perfection and he became a Grand Master, his Saber Qi could be stronger, he still wouldn't be a match for the Supreme Elder.

"If my saber intent progresses further, it becomes saber momentum! Saber momentum can rival a Martial Saint, naturally, it can contend with a Foundation Establishment cultivator.

However, to turn saber intent into saber momentum, one must first cultivate the saber intent to perfection. There are very few in the world who can have perfection in saber intent. It's too hard to make saber intent perfection just by grinding!

However, there is another way. That is the fusion of saber intents. If Heavenly Saber Art can generate saber intent, and then fuse with the original saber intent, there's a good chance that the saber intent will reach perfection. To push Heavenly Saber Art further, I must absorb more saber techniques at the perfection stage."

Lin Fei's train of thought was clear. If he wanted to quickly improve his strength in a short time, there was only one way, to improve his saber intent. To get saber intent to perfection had to fall on Heavenly Saber Art. There were more than three months left until Liu Yibai's appointment. That's enough time.

"There are many saber wielders in the world, especially famous ones. It seems that I have to learn from the Hidden Sword Sect. Use the title of 'Number One Saber Under Heaven' as a pretext to challenge all saber wielders in the world. In this way, I can forcibly make Heavenly Saber Art 'capture' those saber techniques at the perfection stage, and enhance its foundation."

Lin Fei also made a decision in his heart. This method required him to act high-profile. This was a bit contrary to Lin Fei's usual style.

However, this was the only way. Moreover, with Lin Fei's current strength, he couldn't afford to be low-key.

So, this "Number One Saber Under Heaven", he would be!

154. Your saber has become dull

"Lin Fei."

Ling Yao came back. Lin Fei didn't know what she was busy with all day. Every day she left early and returned late. Moreover, it seemed that her martial arts had completely fallen into disrepair. After all, she was busy every day. Where would she have time to practice martial arts?

"Senior Sister Lin, I just came back from the front line and went to the palace, I didn't have time to tell you."

"Lin Fei, I already know about your situation on the front line. How strong are you really?"

Ling Yao couldn't help but ask. When she received a report from the court's rebellion suppression army and the messages that came in successively, the whole person was a bit dazed. She was shocked. Lin Fei actually collapsed the city wall of Chiyang Prefecture with a single saber stroke.

It was not the city gate, but a wall! She also knew about Chiyang Prefecture. The city wall was high and strong. But even so, it couldn't resist Lin Fei's single saber stroke.

During the suppression of the rebellion, whatever problem or trouble the court's army encountered, it was Lin Fei who made a move, solved directly with a single saber stroke. There was almost never a second saber stroke.

For such a long time, Ling Yao only knew that her junior brother was the top genius of the Nine Profound Sect and his strength was very strong. But exactly how strong Lin Fei was, Ling Yao didn't know.

If it were anyone else asking, Lin Fei wouldn't bother. But, when Ling Yao asked, Lin Fei thought for a moment and said, "Under the Foundation Establishment, I should be invincible! Perhaps, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect in the past could barely beat me."

Lin Fei told the truth. The founder of the Nine Profound Sect, although his True Qi was perfect and his Martial Dao True Intent was perfect and he also mastered three types of Martial Dao True Intents, Lin Fei had cultivated Saber Qi and he also had Heavenly Saber Art. He could exert the power of the heavenly saber.

Even if the founder of the Nine Profound Sect came back to life, who was really stronger and who was weaker would have to be determined by a fight.

"Invincible under the Foundation Establishment..."

Ling Yao was shocked. Of course she understood what this meant. And she also knew how heavy the weight of "invincible under the Foundation Establishment" was. Not to mention that she is only a princess now, even if she inherited the title of the South King, even if she were the Great Chang Emperor, facing Lin Fei, she would have to treat him as an equal even with added respect.

She finally understood the reason Lin Fei had advised her to practice martial arts back then. Back then, Lin Fei was only a mere acquired martial artist. Even if he had become innate, actually, in terms of status, it was still slightly lower than a princess.

However, now it's completely different. Invincible under the Foundation Establishment! In the royal family, no one was an opponent except the Supreme Elder.

Such a person was a dominant force. Moreover, many immortal sects did not have a True Person in the Foundation Establishment. That is to say, they were not as good as Lin Fei. Lin Fei alone could be compared to many immortal sects!

"Senior Sister Lin, I plan to continue honing my saber intent. I hope to be able to train it to perfection. Therefore, I need to exchange ideas with some top saber practitioners. I wonder who in Chang City are the masters of saber techniques?

It's not necessarily about being strong, as long as the saber technique is outstanding, and there are one or several martial artists who have trained a saber technique to perfection, it will do."

Lin Fei planned to stay in Chang City for a while. First, "challenge" all the top saber practitioners in Chang City. Then go to meet the top saber practitioners in the world, completely solidifying his title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven", and also capturing some saber techniques to enhance the foundation of Heavenly Saber Art.

"Lin Fei, if you want to exchange ideas with the saber practitioners in Chang City, that's easy."

Ling Yao had people investigate. She soon gave Lin Fei a list. On the list, there were some masters of saber techniques in Chang City, belonging to top saber practitioners.

Of course, perfection realm saber techniques were not necessarily top saber practitioners. After all, some people could only perfect their saber technique at the Body Refining level. But those who could perfect the saber technique, especially those who could perfect the acquired saber technique, must be the top saber practitioners. They would definitely not be nameless.

The probability of "capturing" the perfection realm saber techniques was much higher.

Lin Fei looked at the masters of saber techniques in Chang City given by Ling Yao. With a sweep of his eyes, he saw the first top saber practitioner.

"Mad Saber Xiahou Zheng, who has perfected the Mad Wind Saber Technique. One of the top masters of saber techniques in Chang City. Let's start with this Xiahou Zheng tomorrow."

Lin Fei made a decision in his heart.

...

Chang City, Changping Street. Here, there was a Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall. Although it was a martial arts hall, those familiar knew that this hall was not easy to provoke.

Because the owner of the hall was "Mad Wind Saber" Xiahou Zheng, who was an innate martial artist, a generation of Masters!

Although a master opening a martial arts hall seemed a bit of a step down, in fact, the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall did not rely on accepting disciples to make a living.

The hall only accepted disciples who were either rich or distinguished, and then relying on the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall opened a series of businesses such as a dart bureau, restaurant, silk and satin store, and so on.

Of course, many people knew it was not that Xiahou Zheng had a business mind, but he has a few children. Relying on the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall, they had developed to this point today.

However, no matter what, this unprofitable Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall, in fact, was the foundation of the Xiahou family.

At this moment, inside the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall, all of Xiahou Zheng's children were present.

"Father, our Mad Wind Restaurant needs to continue expanding. We need a lot of silver. This Zhang Cheng is a famous wealthy businessman in Chang City. He just wants to pay his respects to you and use your reputation as an innate martial artist to grow his business even bigger, and he will also cooperate with our restaurant. In this way, wouldn't the problem of our Mad Wind Restaurant lacking silver be solved?"

"Yeah, that Zhang Cheng is quite sincere, you just need to accept Zhang's invitation every month and show your face..."

"Shut up!"

Xiahou Zheng's face turned pale. His gaze swept over each of his sons and daughters. Finally, he said coldly: "The martial way is the foundation. And you? All day long, all you talk about is business and silver, do you still look like martial artists?"

"Father, not everyone can become innate. If you are an acquired martial artist, what can you count in this Chang City?"

"Exactly, even if it's an innate Master, it's just a bit of face in Chang City. There are nobles and even Qi Condensation cultivators everywhere here. It's better to take advantage of your reputation as an innate Master and develop the business of our Xiahou family first. If there are any troubles, we have plenty of connections to smooth things over."

"You all..."

Xiahou Zheng was furious. He had practiced martial arts his whole life. As a result, when he came to Chang City, his children didn't practice martial arts anymore. They switched to business.

Although it seemed like they had connections and money now, Xiahou Zheng was very clear. Once he died, these connections, relationships, and money were all useless. But his sons and daughters couldn't see through it. They didn't know the true weight of an innate martial artist.

"Is 'Mad Wind Saber' Xiahou Zheng in? I, Lin, have come specially to learn from Master's Mad Wind Saber Technique!"

Just then, a cold voice came from the courtyard.

"Hm?"

Xiahou Zheng suddenly looked up and towards the entrance. At the same time, his children also stepped out. Upon seeing the visitor, his eldest son furrowed his brows slightly and said, "This is not a place where anyone can just walk in. Furthermore, my father does not accept any challenges, you'd best leave now."

However, the visitor seemed to ignore his words. He stood in the courtyard, not moving. The eldest son, a bit irked, loudly rebuked, "Who let this ruffian in? He has no manners! If you don't leave soon, I'll have the constables take you to jail. This is Chang City, how dare a martial artist like you be so presumptuous? Even if you're an innate martial artist, we can still throw you in jail!"

In Chang City, there were dedicated constables. Among them were Qi Condensation cultivators and Innate martial artists. They were specifically there to deal with troublesome Innate martial artists or Qi Condensation cultivators.

Xiahou Zheng's son, having a good relationship with some officials, had the confidence to say this.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei's gaze landed on Xiahou Zheng's eldest son. Suddenly, Xiahou Zheng felt his body trembling. It felt like facing a treasure saber with its sharp edge exposed. A slight lack of attention, and he would be cut in half.

"Talk more, end up like this tree!"

Lin Fei flicked his finger.

"Whoosh".

A strand of saber energy instantly flew towards a big tree in the courtyard.

"Crack".

The big tree was instantly cut in half by this strand of saber energy, collapsing with a rumble.

Immediately, the faces of Xiahou Zheng's children all turned pale. Their gaze filled with fear as they looked at the young man in front of them.

"Back down!"

Xiahou Zheng came out. There was a hint of shock in his eyes.

"May I ask who you are?" Xiahou Zheng asked.

"Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei!"

"You are the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei?"

Xiahou Zheng's eyes widened, and his heart suddenly shocked. He no longer counted as a member of the martial world. All these years in Chang City, he was practically a rich man.

However, Xiahou Zheng was still an innate martial artist after all. And, he was a top-level saberist. He still had some understanding of major events in the martial world.

Who was Lin Fei?

He was the notorious Immortal Slayer Saber! His saber could slay immortals!

Xiahou Zheng had heard of Lin Fei's strength. So, how could he dare to accept the challenge?

Seeing Xiahou Zheng not speaking, Lin Fei's eyes were icy, his gaze slightly disappointed.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei, with his hand acting as a saber, made a gentle slash toward Xiahou Zheng.

"Crack".

A strand of saber energy instantly landed on the treasured saber in Xiahou Zheng's hand. Immediately, the treasured saber shattered, turning into pieces on the ground. Throughout, Xiahou Zheng didn't even draw his saber.

"'Mad Wind Saber Technique' is extremely disappointed with the original host, and actively merges into your Heavenly Saber Art."

"The progress of Heavenly Saber Art increases by 5%."

The system's voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind. This was the first time Lin Fei had encountered a martial art actively leaving its original host.

However, Lin Fei had already achieved his goal. So, he didn't seek to fight Xiahou Zheng anymore. He turned around and left directly.

However, as Lin Fei was stepping out of the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall, he paused for a moment.

"Xiahou Zheng, your saber has become dull."

Having said that, Lin Fei took a step forward. In a few leaps, he had disappeared without a trace.

155. The Path of Martial Arts

"Father, are you okay? That person is too arrogant, he just attacked without warning. This is Chang City, is it a place where a martial artist like him can act recklessly?

I'm going to inform Lord Liu, let him send the Qi Condensation cultivators and innate martial artists to directly arrest this unruly martial artist and throw him into jail!"

It was only then that Xiahou Zheng's eldest son seemed to come back to his senses and immediately spoke fiercely.

"Slap".

Suddenly, Xiahou Zheng slapped his eldest son's face. Immediately, there were five clear finger marks left on his son's face.

"Father, you..."

"Unfilial son shut up!"

Xiahou Zheng's eyes instantly turned red, he roared angrily, "He is 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, his saber is bound to slay immortals! Even the top-level Qi Condensation cultivators have been slain by his single saber stroke.

Does your so-called Lord Liu dare to provoke Lin Fei? There is no one in the entire Chang City that Lin Fei does not dare to kill!

Only Lin Fei is a real martial artist. And I... I have not deserved to draw my saber..."

Xiahou Zheng's expression was full of despair. As for his son, he was completely dumbfounded. Covering his mouth, he didn't dare to speak. Top-level Qi Condensation cultivators all slain by a single saber stroke of Lin Fei?

He didn't know what the concept of a martial artist like Lin Fei was. However, he knew what it meant to be a top-level Qi Condensation cultivator. That was an immortal master who even the emperor had to respect!

Yet to Lin Fei, even such top-level Qi Condensation cultivators could be slain. Could a martial artist be this powerful? For a moment, the entire Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall fell quiet.

Lin Fei had already left the Mad Wind Martial Arts Hall. Heavenly Saber Art had integrated the "Mad Wind Saber Technique". This was an acquired martial art. It was a pity that it only increased the practice progress of Heavenly Saber Art by 5%.

According to Lin Fei's previous experience, the perfection saber techniques of the body refining level could increase the practice progress by 1%. Acquired level saber techniques could roughly increase the practice progress by 5%.

Of course, this was not absolute. Some saber techniques were especially powerful. Once they reached the perfection state and were integrated into Heavenly Saber Art, it was certain that they could increase the practice progress even more.

"There are three great saber masters in Chang City. Besides 'Mad Wind Saber' Xiahou Zheng, there are also 'Astonishing Goose Saber' Shen He and 'Soul Chasing Saber' Tie Lin. The next one, go find 'Astonishing Goose Saber' Shen He."

Lin Fei directly arrived at the Astonishing Goose Gate. This was a sect established by Shen He.

"Nine Profound Sect's Lin Fei especially came to learn saber techniques from 'Astonishing Goose Saber' Master Shen He!"

Lin Fei directly strode into the Astonishing Goose Gate.

A quarter of an hour later.

"Swish."

"Astonishing Goose Saber" Shen He, was disheveled. His hair was cut off by a strand of saber energy.

Lin Fei turned around and walked out.

"Shen He, your saber technique is stronger than Xiahou Zheng's. At least, you can draw your saber."

Having said that, Lin Fei didn't care what Shen He would do, he directly went to the Soul Chasing Gang, where "Soul Chasing Saber" Tie Lin was. This was a gang.

"Nine Profound Sect's Lin Fei especially came to learn saber techniques from 'Soul Chasing Saber' Master Tie Lin!"

Another quarter of an hour later. Lin Fei walked out of the Soul Chasing Gang. Tie Lin was also disheveled, a picture of desolation.

In one day, Lin Fei challenged the three great saber masters of Chang City and all of them were defeated with one move. Especially Mad Wind Saber Xiahou Zheng didn't even have the courage to draw his saber.

For a time, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei, in Chang City, stirred up another frenzy.

However, Lin Fei was very disappointed. Among the three great saber masters, he only integrated three perfection-stage acquired saber techniques. It only increased his practice progress by a total of 15%. There was still a long way to go before Heavenly Saber Art could birth the saber intent.

"Looking for martial artists with perfect saber techniques is too inefficient. Especially now in Chang City, there are only three saber masters, and I've sought them all out.

Those Body Refining martial artists, or martial artists who have only perfected the Body Refining stage saber techniques, can also increase my saber technique foundation.

I need to find a way to get them to come to me. But how can I attract these Body Refining martial artists and acquired martial artists to come to me?"

A light flashed in Lin Fei's mind. He took out a porcelain bottle from his bosom. In the porcelain bottle, there was a pill. Heavenly Meridian Pill!

Lin Fei helped Ling Yao become the champion of the Royal Competition. He received a Heavenly Meridian Pill.

However, Lin Fei later consumed the blood of the Treasure Snake. Relying on its blood, Lin Fei directly reached the twelfth level of the acquired stage. Therefore, he didn't use this Heavenly Meridian Pill. He always carried it with him. Unexpectedly, it came into use now.

A Heavenly Meridian Pill, for Acquired martial artists and Body Refining martial artists, had an unimaginable attraction. After all, it could directly open up a meridian.

So, Lin Fei directly announced through the South King Mansion that anyone who had perfected saber techniques could challenge him. Just discussing saber techniques. No need for True Qi or inner power. If they can defeat him, they could get a Heavenly Meridian Pill!

Suddenly, countless acquired martial artists, especially saber practitioners, flocked to the South King Mansion.

However, even if they didn't use True Qi or inner power, just comparing saber techniques, Lin Fei was still one of the top saber practitioners.

In the blink of an eye, ten days passed. Lin Fei spent ten days at the South King Mansion and he defeated countless martial artists.

But although the Heavenly Saber Art integrated many martial arts, they were basically saber techniques at the Body Refining level. There were very few acquired-level perfection saber techniques. Therefore, in ten days, the cultivation progress of Heavenly Saber Art only increased by 20%.

Adding the 15% cultivation progress gained from defeating the three great saber masters, there was a total of 35% cultivation progress.

Previously, Heavenly Saber Art only had 1% cultivation progress. Up to now, it was only 36%. There was still a long way to go.

"Basically all the saber practitioners in Chang City have come to the South King Mansion. Continuing to wait has no meaning. When Liu Yibai obtained the 'Number One Sword Under Heaven', he did it by traveling all over the world and defeating everyone.

Now if I want to collect countless perfection saber techniques, and allow Heavenly Saber Art to birth saber intent. I'm afraid I also have to travel the world and meet saber practitioners from all over!"

Lin Fei had already made up his mind. Even, he gradually spread some news that he wanted to follow the disciples of the Hidden Sword Sect, travel all over the world, meet all the saber practitioners in the world, and seize the title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven"!

Whoever could defeat him, whether it was by martial arts or purely by saber techniques, he could give them a Heavenly Meridian Pill!

This news, with the constant spread by travelers and martial artists, spread all over the world in just a few days. It quickly caused a stir in the entire martial world.

After all, this was "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei! Now he was openly vying for the title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven". As the saying goes, there is no first in literature and no second in martial arts. Even the martial artist who was indifferent to fame and fortune, at this moment, couldn't sit still.

Number One Saber Under Heaven! The entire Great Chang hadn't had a Number One Saber Under Heaven for a long time. Instead, the Hidden Sword Sect's "Number One Sword Under Heaven" was well-known and revered.

South King Mansion.

Ling Yao looked at Lin Fei with a complex expression.

"Lin Fei, have you really decided?"

"Senior Sister Ling, I've made up my mind. The title of 'Number One Saber Under Heaven' must be mine! Only in this way can I attract the top saber practitioners in the world," Lin Fei said calmly.

"The title of 'Number One Saber Under Heaven' plus a Heavenly Meridian Pill. I believe it's enough to attract all the saber practitioners in the world."

Ling Yao knew that Lin Fei's grand display, known to everyone, was actually for the perfection of saber intent. Lin Fei was single-mindedly focused on the path of martial arts. But no matter how strong he was, he was still only innate. Was it worth it?

"Senior Sister Ling, what were you fighting for when you were contending for the position of a princess?" Lin Fei suddenly asked.

"To control my own destiny!" Ling Yao immediately replied. That was what she thought back then.

"But even if you inherit the title of the South Princess, can you really control your own destiny?"

Ling Yao fell silent. Only after becoming the princess did she realize how complex and difficult it was to seize power.

Lin Fei looked at Ling Yao, his gaze deep and calm. He spoke slowly, word by word, "Senior Sister Ling, if you want power, what's so difficult about it? Don't even mention the title of South Princess, even if you want to become the Empress of Great Chang, it's not a big deal. If I become a Martial Saint, everything will be easy! I follow the path of martial arts for longevity.

Senior Sister wishes for power. But even if you gain power and control your destiny, it's just a few decades. What does it amount to?"

Lin Fei spoke word by word, staring at Ling Yao.

"Senior Sister Ling, I hope you can figure out what you want during this time. Next time I return to Chang City, it will be time to help you achieve your wishes. Martial arts, power... you can choose either!

If you choose martial arts, I will do my best to help you become innate! If you choose power, even if you want to become an empress, I will help you!"

Lin Fei's voice echoed in Ling Yao's ears. By the time Ling Yao came to her senses, Lin Fei had already left the South King Mansion, disappearing without a trace.

--------------------------

There is no first in literature and no second in martial arts: This is a proverb. It means that even someone who writes exceptionally well would not dare to boast that their writing is the best in the world, while someone with great martial arts skills often boasts that their skills are unparalleled. It often refers to the tendency of martial artists to always claim superiority in their abilities. You know, martial artists are always competitive.

-------------------------

Actually, I've always wanted to write a romantic scene between Ling Yao and Lin Fei, but I realized that I'm not really good at it, so you might find it a bit awkward.

A note from RighteousEgg

Volume 1 is over. You can check out all the chapters on my Patreon.

156. Jiangyang Was Shocked

Jiangyang City, the largest city in the Middle State of Great Chang, was virtually the core of the entire Middle State. Lin Fei's first stop was here.

Lin Fei sat at a wooden table in a tavern, observing the diverse crowd of customers, servers, and the owner. Everything seemed ordinary. However, when Lin Fei glanced at the food on the table, his expression became even colder.

"The world of martial arts is not just about martial skills. There are also schemes! I intend to solve matters with martial arts, but there are those who resort to schemes."

Lin Fei's tone was calm, but there was a hint of coldness in his voice. The food on the table was poisoned!

This was the first time Lin Fei encountered such a situation. Throughout his journey in the martial world, whether he encountered Qi cultivators or martial artists, Lin Fei had never faced someone attempting to poison him.

But now, as he sought the title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven" and attracted saber cultivators from around the world, he encountered a nefarious tactic he had never seen before at his first stop in the martial world.

Poison!

This poison was colorless and tasteless. However, Lin Fei's perception was incredibly strong. As a result, when these people quietly poisoned the food, he already knew.

Since they dared to poison him, it meant that the poison could affect innate martial artists and even potentially kill them. It was a formidable poison!

"Come out, all of you! These tricks are not worth mentioning!" Lin Fei rebuked in a low voice.

With a "whoosh", the expressions of those who were just ordinary pedestrians, servers, and the owner drastically changed. They all stood up, pulling out weapons from their bodies, and stared at Lin Fei.

These people, totaling dozens, were all martial artists! At this moment, they all looked at Lin Fei with fear. Their attempt to poison him had failed.

"Immortal Slayer Saber," one of them began, "We all know you are formidable, your saber can slay immortals. Even the three saber masters of Chang City are no match for your saber. However, your Heavenly Meridian Pill is too tempting. For the sake of the Heavenly Meridian Pill, we can only take risks!"

Lin Fei understood. The Heavenly Meridian Pill! He had underestimated the allure of the Heavenly Meridian Pill for acquired martial artists. Or perhaps he had underestimated human nature.

Lin Fei lifted his head, looking at these martial artists, and said calmly, "I came to martial worlds to meet the saber cultivators of Jiangyang and confirm the saber techniques. I haven't killed anyone in Jiangyang, but you want to poison me. As matters of the martial world, they should be resolved in the martial world. You should be killed!"

At this moment, Lin Fei's intent to kill was evident. Since they had attempted to poison him, Lin Fei would not be polite. After all, the martial world was never devoid of killing.

In the next moment, Lin Fei flicked his finger.

"Whoosh whoosh whoosh".

Immediately, strands of saber energy burst out from his body and flew towards these dozens of martial artists.

To deal with these martial artists, Lin Fei didn't even need to use any saber techniques, let alone his saber intent. Just his saber energy was enough.

The strands of saber energy moved incredibly fast. With just a slight flash, they were instantly in front of these martial artists.

"Pfff".

"Crack".

The saber energy instantly cut off the weapons of the martial artists and entered their bodies. No one could block Lin Fei's strand of saber energy. Therefore, within a short time, dozens of bodies fell on the floor of the tavern.

Lin Fei stood up and left the tavern. Among these martial artists, there was not even a single one who had perfected saber techniques. Clearly, they were hardly considered saber cultivators. Even if they were saber cultivators, they were very ordinary ones. They didn't come to challenge Lin Fei in a saber duel but for the Heavenly Meridian Pill.

Leaving the tavern, Lin Fei came to the lake and saw an old man with a bamboo hat. The old man was holding an iron hammer and seemed to be hitting a rusty saber.

The saber was very old and dull. It was repeatedly hammered by the old man, but it remained dull without any edge. Lin Fei quietly watched the old man continuously hammering the dull saber. After a long time, Lin Fei finally spoke, "Your saber is dull, it can't be sharpened anymore!"

"Yes, my saber hasn't been used for forty years." The old man replied. "Only today, did I dig it up from the ground again. I may not care about profit, but in the end, I can't escape the word 'fame'."

The old man looked up, his eyes were sharp as a saber, "'Immortal Slayer Saber' Master Lin, if you want to become the Number One Saber Under Heaven, and you chose Jiangyang as your first stop, then I had no choice but to come out of retirement. I'm Li Sandao of Jiangyang."

Lin Fei's eyes remained calm. He had never heard of this old man, but he could guess that he was a senior figure in the martial arts world of Jiangyang, especially among saber cultivators. This old man had retired his saber for forty years but had now returned because of him.

"I'm Lin Fei from Nine Profound Sect," Lin Fei responded.

"Aren't you drawing your saber?" Li Sandao asked.

Lin Fei remained silent.

Li Sandao gently held the hilt of the rusty saber, as if talking to himself, "Sealed for forty years, old friend, I am holding you again! Forty years ago, the martial world called me 'Three Sabers' because I had three unique saber techniques. But after sealing my saber for forty years, I've condensed those three into one. 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Master Lin, do you dare to receive one saber strike from this old man?"

"Senior, please draw your saber," Lin Fei said calmly.

"Very well!"

"Swish."

The next moment, the old man made his move.

Previously, the old man didn't have any noticeable fluctuations of True Qi or inner power. Even Lin Fei couldn't tell whether the old man was an acquired martial artist or an innate martial artist.

But now, as the old man made his move, a trace of True Qi fluctuation, although very subtle, was still detected by Lin Fei.

The old man in front of him was an innate master and even one step away from the realm of martial Grand Master.

"One saber!"

The old man's saber strike completely converged its sharpness, not even much True Qi erupted. Only when it was in front of Lin Fei did the innate True Qi explode instantly.

This was the old man's all-out strike, his strongest saber! This one saber, even if it was a martial Grand Master, the old man felt, perhaps would not be much different. However, Lin Fei just slightly shook his head, remaining unmoved.

The next moment, the old man's body shook. Following that, his whole body seemed to tremble. He held the hilt of the rusty saber tightly in his hand, but despite exerting all his strength, he seemed to be unable to control the saber.

At this moment, the old man looked horrified.

"Saber intent!"

The old man's eyes widened in shock, his heart filled with astonishment!

What a terrifying saber intent!

Although there were rumors in the martial world that Lin Fei, the "Immortal Slayer Saber", had a terrible saber energy that could cut through anything when he drew his saber, and the saber intent was also very powerful.

However, in the vast majority of cases, the Martial Dao True Intent could only play a supporting role in martial artists' battles. Li Sandao did not expect that simply unleashing the saber intent would render him unable to control his own blade against Lin Fei.

Lin Fei looked calm, looked at the old man, and said lightly, "Senior, you lost. You sealed your saber for forty years, but you didn't comprehend saber intent. It doesn't matter if you condensed three sabers into one. Even if you condensed thirty sabers into one, what use is it?

You've spent a lifetime studying saber techniques, but you don't know the true essence of saber arts. In front of me, you can't even draw your saber. This saber, you've wasted a lifetime practicing it!"

After finishing his words, Lin Fei stepped forward. After a few leaps, he disappeared without a trace.

"I... I've wasted a lifetime practicing this saber..."

The old man's face turned pale. Then, it seemed like he realized something.

"Yes, I've wasted a lifetime practicing this saber. Hahaha, this saber, I don't need it!"

The old man grabbed his saber and threw it hard. With a "plop" sound, the rusty old saber instantly sank into the bottom of the lake. Without looking back, the old man strode away.

Lin Fei, the "Immortal Slayer Saber", descended from Chang City along the river to Jiangyang.

In three days in Jiangyang, he defeated five saber technique masters. All the saber masters in Jiangyang surrendered and willingly respected Lin Fei as the Number One Saber Under Heaven.

When the news spread out, Jiangyang was shocked!

157. A Saber Severing the River!

"Chang City, Jiangyang."

Lin Fei reclined on a modest skiff. By this time, he had bidden farewell to Jiangyang and said his goodbyes to Middle State.

Nineteen states under the heavens, a realm rich in resources and vast in territory. Great Chang, truly, was a kingdom flourishing in prosperity. Hence, the scope of merely two states, Lin Fei's Heavenly Saber Art had already attained a mastery of 60%. It could be acclaimed his gains were abundant.

However, the sole thing inducing a twinge of regret within Lin Fei was that in the entirety of Jiangyang and even throughout the whole of Middle State, not a single soul had comprehended the essence of the saber.

Thus, Lin Fei continued to navigate downstream. This time, he was venturing towards a place of utmost importance.

Saber City! This city bore the name of the saber. There was no other reason than this place had given birth to a revered saber saint!

Fifteen hundred years ago, this place had given birth to an unrivaled saber saint. He was also the most widely acclaimed saber saint throughout the entirety of Great Chang.

Every person in Great Chang knew of the Hidden Sword Sect and the Sword Saint. But little did they know, Great Chang had also fostered a saber saint. Even more so, there existed a noble lineage of saber saints, continuing the bloodline of the saber saint, residing in Saber City!

In Lin Fei's aspirations to become the "Number One Saber Under Heaven" and even to facilitate the birth of saber essence within his Heavenly Saber Art, he must necessarily journey to Saber City. And now, he wasn't far from Saber City. Or rather, this very river also fell within the confines of Saber City.

The ferryman, a man of sixty winters, upon reaching midday, pulled out the fish stored in the cabin, using a kitchen saber, he swiftly gutted the fish.

"Swish, swish, swish."

With each rise and fall of the ferryman's hand, his speed and proficiency were remarkable.

Lin Fei, in tranquility, observed the ferryman carving the fish. In a muted voice, he uttered, "Old man, your skill with the saber is adept. With such mastery of the saber, if you held a deadly saber instead of a kitchen one, you would undoubtedly be a saber master!"

The ferryman, hearing this, couldn't help but chuckle, "Honored guest, you flatter me too much. However, having been born and raised in Saber City, I've been steeped in its traditions since my youth. Wouldn't it be a joke if I didn't know a few saber techniques? In Saber City, there's not a soul who doesn't know how to wield a saber."

The elderly man seemed quite proud.

"Oh? Every person in Saber City is skilled in saber techniques? Do you, old man, know of the Saber Saint?" Lin Fei inquired.

"Of course, I do! The story of the Saber Saint, even if I narrated it for three days and nights, wouldn't be enough. From my youth, I've been familiar with the tales of the Saber Saint. He's the pride of our Saber City!"

Merely mentioning the Saber Saint sent the ferryman into a wave of enthusiastic storytelling, seemingly without end. Tales of sabers splitting mountains, of sabers breaking rivers, of the change in heaven and earth with a single swing of a saber, and more.

To the common people, these were all figures akin to demigods. Naturally, the tales were as exaggerated as they could possibly be.

Lin Fei didn't interrupt the ferryman's passionate discourse. He silently listened to the narratives about the Saber Saint.

After a long while, the ferryman's mouth turned dry from talking. Lin Fei passed him a cup of tea, then continued his inquiry, "Does the old man know about the noble lineage of Saber Saints within Saber City? Being descendants of the Saber Saint, they must possess many top-class saber masters, right? After all, they are the bloodline of the Saber Saint, surely their legacy is substantial."

The ferryman's face darkened slightly, then he shook his head and said, "The lineage of the Saber Saint... the current lineage has long lost the spirit of the Saber Saint. I've heard it said that the beneficial influence of a good man ceases after five generations. As the common saying goes, wealth does not pass through three generations. But the lineage of the Saber Saint? They've been continuing for over a thousand years. Heh, continuing for a millennium, is that so easy? The intricacies within... Well, it's better not to speak of the Saber Saint lineage."

Every time the ferryman mentioned the "lineage of the Saber Saint," he shook his head. He seemed quite unsatisfied with the lineage, or perhaps, many people in Saber City were dissatisfied with them. This was also normal.

A millennial lineage, how could there not be degenerates? Over a thousand years, the Saber Saint lineage had become an overwhelming entity, its reach extending to every facet of Saber City.

However, what the Saber Saint lineage amounted to had nothing to do with Lin Fei. Lin Fei needed that mastery, even perfect, in saber techniques – the top-class saber masters. Therefore, regardless, he needed to visit this lineage of Saber Saints.

Soon, the ferryman finished preparing the fish. "Honored guest, come and taste how well this old man's craft fares," he warmly invited Lin Fei for a taste.

"Hm?"

Lin Fei suddenly looked up. His eyes narrowed slightly. At that moment, on the distant river surface, a ship stretching several dozen meters slowly approached. Hanging on the ship was a banner.

Upon seeing it, the ferryman's face subtly changed. In a low voice, he said, "It's a ship from the lineage of the Saber Saint. We should steer clear."

The ferryman immediately began to paddle, steering the small boat away from the lineage of the Saber Saint's massive ship. However, the large ship unexpectedly adjusted its course slightly. Its destination was directly towards Lin Fei's little boat.

"Is the person aboard the small boat ahead the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Master Lin Fei?"

Suddenly, a voice echoed from the large ship.

Lin Fei narrowed his eyes slightly. He moved to the front of the boat and responded loudly, "It is indeed Lin, who are you?"

"We are members of the Saber Saint lineage from Saber City. We heard that Master Lin is here to engage in a saber meet, aiming for the title 'Number One Saber Under Heaven.' Our Saber Saint lineage has come specially to welcome Master Lin."

"Welcome?"

Lin Fei's gaze turned cold. He looked at the huge ship, "If you're here to welcome me, why do you bring so much oil and ax saber wielders?"

At this, the faces of the people aboard the ship from the Saber Saint lineage changed dramatically. The Saber Saint lineage gave a wave of their hand, no longer concealing their intentions. A large number of archers poured out from the ship's cabin, holding strong bows. Furthermore, the arrowheads were soaked in oil, ablaze with roaring flames.

One by one, the "fire arrows" aimed at Lin Fei's small boat. At this moment, the ferryman's face turned deathly pale, his body trembling uncontrollably.

"Disaster, disaster!" He murmured repeatedly.

He was just a small ferryman, earning a living by ferrying boats. How could he have anticipated running into such a disaster today? Judging by the posture of the Saber Saint lineage, they were not merely trying to intimidate.

"Those martial artists want to kill me for the Heavenly Meridian Pill. I can understand this point. But you, the Saber Saint lineage, even without the Heavenly Meridian Pill, should have no shortage of martial artists, right? You even have Innate Masters. Why are you trying to kill me?"

Lin Fei's tone remained calm.

"Why? You're just too confident, Master Lin. You want to claim 'Number One Saber Under Heaven,' and we, the Saber Saint lineage, do not object. But you should not have come to Saber City. This Saber City is the Saber City of our Saber Saint lineage!

Once you arrive at the Saber City, you'll inevitably challenge us. Given the strength of your 'Immortal Slayer Saber,' we, the Saber Saint lineage, have enough self-awareness to know we can't resist. If our lineage loses its prestige, how can we stand in Saber City? So, we have no choice but to take action."

Lin Fei finally understood. In the end, it all came down to "fame and profit."

The Saber Saint lineage had managed to continue for over a thousand years primarily because of its prestige. Their word was law in Saber City. However, if Lin Fei were to topple the Saber Saint lineage, what prestige would they have left? Over time, the Saber Saint lineage would slowly decline in Saber City.

This was the power of "fame and profit"!

"But aren't you afraid of me?"

"Hahaha, who doesn't know the fame of 'Immortal Slayer Saber'? If we were on land, of course, we'd fear you. However, on this vast river, even the mighty 'Immortal Slayer Saber' can only succumb!"

Lin Fei looked around. Indeed. Here he was at the center of a great river, surrounded by endless water, with no sight of the shore.

Martial artists were not Qi cultivators. They didn't have magical artifacts and couldn't fly. If they fell into the water, even the strongest martial artist wouldn't be able to exert much power.

Apparently, the Saber Saint lineage had been keeping an eye on Lin Fei all along, hence their decision to strike now. This was their only chance to kill Lin Fei!

"Your plan is impeccable, and your arrangement meticulous. It seems the Saber Saint lineage has some wise individuals. However, no matter the amount of scheming or strategizing, we, as martial artists and saber practitioners, rely ultimately on our sabers!"

With that, Lin Fei jumped directly into the water.

"Huh?"

Everyone, whether from the Saber Saint lineage or the old ferryman, showed surprise on their faces.

Instead of staying on the boat and fighting for his life, Lin Fei voluntarily jumped into the water. Was he trying to commit suicide?

However, when Lin Fei leaped off the small boat, he stepped on the water's surface.

Immediately, ripples appeared on the water's surface. Even under Lin Fei's feet, a whirlpool formed. Lin Fei, step by step, walked on the water's surface as if he were on land, heading directly towards the Saber Saint lineage's large ship.

"He's walking on water!"

"How is this possible?"

"The records left by our Saber Saint lineage say that only those who have achieved physical perfection can walk on water without sinking."

"Could it be, Lin Fei has achieved physical perfection?"

"But there have been no traces of exotic beasts, so how could he achieve physical perfection?"

For a moment, the people from the Saber Saint lineage were shocked.

"No, he hasn't achieved physical perfection. His Innate True Qi is extremely rich, and there's a rumor that Lin Fei doesn't cultivate Innate True Qi, but Saber Qi! He's using his thick Saber Qi to walk on water! We must stop him, shoot the arrows, kill him!"

Despite their shock, the people of the Saber Saint lineage had to take action. They had no other choice.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

Suddenly, a rain of arrows was launched toward Lin Fei.

A layer of saber energy enveloped Lin Fei, bouncing off the arrows that struck him. They fell into the water.

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, walking on the water just like a land-bound immortal, completely at ease. The rain of arrows couldn't touch him at all.

Step by step, Lin Fei was nearing the colossal ship of the Saber Saint lineage. A glint of peculiarity flashed in his eyes.

"I have heard that the original Saber Saint could split the river with a single slash of his saber. Today, I, Lin Fei, would like to emulate the Saber Saint. Let's see if I can split the river with my saber."

Lin Fei's voice was calm, but it resonated clearly in everyone's ears.

"Boom."

The next moment, Lin Fei's saber energy burst forth, and two hundred and fifty meters long saber energy suspended in mid-air.

This was Lin Fei's condensed Heavenly Saber!

The martial artists on the giant ship were all from Saber City, and almost every one of them carried a saber. However, in the presence of the Heavenly Saber, all of their sabers were trembling. Regardless of how hard they tried to pull their sabers out, they were unable to do so.

"Splash."

The sabers actually flew out of their hands, ascending into mid-air as if drawn by an invisible force. The scene looked as if the sabers were showing their "submission" to the Heavenly Saber. Everyone was stunned as if they couldn't believe their own eyes.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

In the next moment, Lin Fei waved his hand. Instantly, the two hundred and fifty meters long Heavenly Saber, carrying the might of overturning the heavens, slashed fiercely toward the giant ship below.

"Boom."

In an instant, the giant ship was cut in half from top to bottom! Simultaneously, the horrifying saber energy even cut several hundred meters long and thirty meters wide trenches into the river, deep enough to see the bottom.

Such power was akin to the divine!

"Can... can a saber really split the river? Is it true?"

The old man who witnessed this scene was wide-eyed, seemingly unable to believe it!

"Old man, I'll be on my way now."

With that, Lin Fei tossed a silver ingot. He didn't even glance at the people of the Saber Saint lineage floating in the water. Instead, he continued his leisurely walk on the water, heading towards Saber City.

Five days later, news spread from Saber City.

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei, walked on water, split the river with a single saber strike, annihilated the Saber Saint lineage, and defeated all the Saber Masters in Saber City!

Tens of thousands of saber practitioners in Saber City willingly acknowledged Lin Fei as the Number One Saber Under Heaven!

As the news spread, Saber City was shocked! The martial arts world was shocked!

158. Discussing Saber Techniques, a Matter of Life and Death

"The so-called millennium-old families are nothing more than worms and dogs!"

Lin Fei shook his head. He was referring to the Saber Saint lineage. Ever since he had sliced the Saber Saint lineage's ship in half with a single saber strike and paid a personal visit to Saber City, he had wiped out the entire Saber Saint lineage.

Regrettably, he only encountered two martial arts Masters, and they were the weakest ones. In front of Lin Fei, they couldn't even draw their sabers.

While Lin Fei's saber intent was indeed formidable, a martial artist with firm conviction and strong willpower could overcome the intimidation of the saber intent and draw their saber for combat.

Unfortunately, the supposedly prestigious Saber Saint lineage, the descendants of the Saber Saint, were unable to even draw their sabers. They had all been reduced to mere worms and dogs and were easily killed by Lin Fei with a single saber strike.

His trip to Saber City also pushed his cultivation progress in the Heavenly Saber Art to 90%. Its progress had increased by almost 30%.

Indeed, Saber City lived up to its reputation. Whether it was saber techniques at the Body Refining perfection level or the Acquired perfection level, there were countless. They had all integrated into Lin Fei's Heavenly Saber Art, enabling it to progress rapidly.

The birth of saber intent in the Heavenly Saber Art seemed not far off. The number of saber techniques that Lin Fei had integrated into the Heavenly Saber Art was already in the dozens. There were too many to count.

However, to generate saber intent in the Heavenly Saber Art, more perfection-level saber techniques were needed. Lin Fei could only continue to move forward.

However, with Lin Fei demonstrating his invincible prowess in Chang City, Jiangyang, and Saber City, his journey henceforth became much smoother. Even saber practitioners were becoming scarce. Almost no one came looking for Lin Fei anymore. Apparently, they had implicitly acknowledged Lin Fei's title of "Number One Saber Under Heaven".

Moreover, even if they were coveting the Heavenly Meridian Pill, those Body Refining martial artists and Acquired martial artists also knew they were no match for Lin Fei. Even in a pure competition of saber techniques, they could not compete with Lin Fei.

As such, Lin Fei continued on his journey for over a month without encountering a single martial artist who had reached the perfection level in saber techniques.

"There's still 10% left in my Heavenly Saber Art cultivation progress. The perfection level saber techniques at the Body Refining stage can increase the Heavenly Saber Art's cultivation progress by 1%. Acquired level perfection saber techniques can increase the Heavenly Saber Art's cultivation progress by 5%."

According to this assumption, innate-level perfection saber techniques should be able to increase the Heavenly Saber Art's cultivation progress by over 10%. That means I don't need to find other martial artists. I just need to find a Saber Technique Master who has reached the perfection level of the innate saber technique.

By then, the cultivation progress of the Heavenly Saber Art will surely reach 100%, thus giving birth to saber intent. But where can I find a martial artist who has cultivated innate level saber techniques to perfection?"

Lin Fei fell into deep thought. The Hidden Sword Sect had the Number One Sword Under Heaven and was filled with master swordsmen. Going to the Hidden Sword Sect, one could certainly find top-tier swordsmen.

But in the whole of Great Chang, there wasn't a sect dedicated to saber techniques like the Hidden Sword Sect. Hence, finding top-tier saber masters was difficult.

Lin Fei sat by the river, holding a wine gourd in his hand. He took a sip of the wine. It was a little spicy and strong.

However, Lin Fei had grown to like this feeling. Now, Lin Fei felt a tinge of loneliness in his heart. A kind of "unrivaled" loneliness.

This was not to say that Lin Fei was invincible in terms of strength. He was still far from being truly invincible. At least for now, Lin Fei was no match for those who have reached the Foundation Establishment stage.

Lin Fei felt invincible in terms of saber techniques. He felt lonely in terms of saber techniques.

Back when he started his martial arts journey in the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei chose saber techniques, boxing, and lightness techniques. Among them, both saber techniques and boxing generated intent.

But till this day, Lin Fei's saber intent had reached transcendence, even approaching perfection, while his boxing intent remained at Mastery.

Lin Fei was better suited to the saber. Not all martial arts need to be perfected and the strongest.

In Lin Fei's view, any martial art, once practiced to the extreme, was invincible! Even if in martial arts, at the Body Refining, Acquired, and even Innate levels, they were actually weaker than those Qi cultivators.

Lin Fei was a special case. Other martial artists, even Martial Arts Masters, were weaker than those high-level, top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators.

But once martial artists established their foundation and became Martial Saints, it was different. They might even be stronger than the average Foundation Establishment cultivators by a small margin.

This was the result of practicing martial arts to the extreme!

"Perhaps the founder was also this lonely. And the Sword Saint of Hidden Sword Sect three hundred years ago was also as lonely. In this world, who can challenge me in saber techniques?"

As he gazed at the vast river, Lin Fei muttered to himself. His saber techniques, cultivated to such an extent, were nearly invincible. The number of people who could keep up with his pace, or even become his opponent, was very few.

"The feeling of loneliness is uncomfortable. I felt this twenty years ago. So, twenty years ago, I sealed away my saber and went back to the countryside to be an old farmer."

Suddenly, a strong voice sounded in Lin Fei's ear.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei swiftly lifted his head. With his current five senses, very few people could approach him without him noticing. But this person had intruded into his ten meters radius before he sensed it.

Danger! This was a very dangerous person!

Lin Fei saw the newcomer. It was a middle-aged man who seemed to have seen many hardships. Dressed in the tight clothing of an ordinary martial artist, he looked very ordinary.

However, Lin Fei was very clear. Anyone who could get within his ten meters range definitely wasn't ordinary.

"Who are you?" Lin Fei asked.

"Someone who can debate saber techniques with you."

The middle-aged man replied calmly.

"Debate saber techniques?"

Lin Fei's eyes became sharp. He saw the saber in the man's hand. It was an utterly ordinary looking saber. Even the traces of the passage of time could be seen on the scabbard. It was a bit old.

"It's rare to see someone actively seeking to debate saber techniques with me. Just comparing saber techniques, without using inner power or True Qi?" Lin Fei said.

These days, even when Lin Fei debated saber techniques with others, they didn't really put up a serious fight. Because no one was his match. They could only simply compete in saber techniques.

"Those who practice the saber do it to kill, not for practicing martial arts forms. If they don't fully commit to defeating their opponent and aim to kill, why practice the saber? I am here to debate saber techniques with you, naturally, I will use all means necessary. Debating saber techniques also involves life and death!"

"Whoosh."

The words of the middle-aged man made Lin Fei's gaze incredibly sharp.

"Good, debating saber techniques also involve life and death! Since you came to debate saber techniques with me, you should know who I am."

"Of course I do, 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, your saber slays immortals! Starting from Chang City, you went to Jiangyang, Saber City, defeating all the master saber practitioners.

On the surface, you are fighting for 'Number One Saber Under Heaven'. But in reality, I know you're not fighting for the title of Number One Saber Under Heaven. You are honing your saber intent, hoping that your saber intent can reach perfection. You are testing your saber against all saber practitioners in the world!"

At this moment, Lin Fei was certain. This middle-aged man truly came to debate saber techniques with him. Moreover, he might be an unprecedented top-tier saber practitioner.

A ripple of excitement formed in Lin Fei's heart. That was the feeling of excitement!

159. Top Match

Lin Fei slowly stood up. He stared directly at this middle-aged man. This was the only one, and possibly the last one, who sought him out for a saber debate. And also, a saber practitioner who considered life and death.

Lin Fei felt a sense of respect. This was a real martial artist, a true saber master!

"Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei!"

"Wanderer of the martial world, Shen Lianxin!"

A flash of enlightenment struck Lin Fei's mind.

"Twenty years ago, there was a transient figure in the martial world, Shen Lianxin, a saber fanatic who defeated all opponents across two states with a single saber!"

Lin Fei finally remembered. Since he was aiming to meet all the saber masters under the heavens with his saber. He naturally had to know about the top saber masters in Great Chang. He had also asked Ling Yao to collect the list of all the top saber masters in the past fifty years. Among them, was Saber Fanatic Shen Lianxin.

However, the information that Lin Fei collected clearly stated twenty years ago, Shen Lianxin suddenly appeared and then suddenly disappeared. Like a flash in the pan, it was only three months.

But during those three months, Shen Lianxin, with a single saber, defeated all the martial arts Masters of the two states and eighteen prefectures! He also got a nickname in the martial world, known as the "Saber Fanatic".

However, the Saber Fanatic then disappeared, vanishing without a trace. No one could investigate any clues as if evaporated from the world out of thin air.

When Lin Fei first saw "Saber Fanatic" Shen Lianxin. He didn't really care. After all, the records at that time stated Shen Lianxin was only at the mid-stage of a Master. Not worth mentioning.

With Lin Fei's strength, even a Grand Master in martial arts was not his opponent, let alone a mid-stage martial artist Master. Perhaps, only an opponent like Liu Yibai from Hidden Sword Sect was worthy of Lin Fei's attention.

However, he didn't expect this "Saber Fanatic" to actually come to him. Moreover, he even dared to initiate a "saber debate". Truly worthy of the name "Saber Fanatic". Obsessed with the saber, regardless of all costs!

Shen Lianxin didn't speak. He slowly reached out to the hilt of his saber. However, he didn't rashly draw his saber.

At their level, who struck first and who struck last didn't really matter anymore. A single saber could decide victory or defeat!

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber intent exploded at the moment Shen Lianxin's hand had just grasped the hilt of his saber.

As a saber master especially one who had comprehended saber intent, even reaching saber intent transcendence, all saber practitioners were at a natural disadvantage in front of Lin Fei. For some saber practitioners with a weaker will, in front of Lin Fei, even drawing their sabers was a luxury.

The vast saber intent like a raging flood surged toward Shen Lianxin. It was as if thousands of sabers were cutting at Shen Lianxin. However, the moment Shen Lianxin's hand grasped the hilt of his saber, a more terrifying saber intent shot up to the sky.

"Buzz."

The void seemed to twist all at once. Lin Fei's eyes narrowed sharply. He sensed a terrifying saber intent from the Saber Fanatic, exploding in an instant.

Moreover, this saber intent was extremely condensed! Also extremely pure, it was like a regular saber, but it was this purity that was very terrifying. Because this was saber intent perfection!

For the first time, Lin Fei's saber intent was suppressed. Even though his saber intent was transcendent, at this moment, it was also suppressed.

"Good, a good Saber Fanatic!"

A strange light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

Shen Lianxin, who had sealed his saber for twenty years, was very different from Li Sandao, who had buried his saber for forty years.

Shen Lianxin, even if his saber was sealed, his heart had a saber. In fact, in every moment of the past twenty years, he had been progressing. It seemed like his saber was sealed, but he was actually comprehending the saber!

Shen Lianxin twenty years ago, surely his saber technique was powerful. Even, he had also comprehended saber intent. Whether it was mastery or transcendence, but definitely not perfection.

But, just twenty years. Saber Fanatic Shen Lianxin's saber intent had already reached perfection. This was something Shen Lianxin comprehended entirely on his own. By himself, he had slowly elevated his saber intent to perfection.

And what about Li Sandao?

Forty years. Only simplified three saber moves into one.

The vast saber intent suppressed Lin Fei firmly. For the first time, Lin Fei was suppressed by someone else's Martial Dao True Intent. He also felt the pain as if there was always a saber edge cutting his body. It seemed like at any moment, there was a hanging saber that would fall and kill him. This was the feeling of being suppressed by saber intent.

Lin Fei knew that he couldn't win against Shen Lianxin with saber intent. Therefore, he didn't hesitate and immediately mobilized all the Saber Qi in his body.

"Boom."

A saber energy of up to two hundred and fifty meters appeared. It was vast and traversed in the void.

Heavenly Saber!

Lin Fei directly condensed a Heavenly Saber. With the appearance of the Heavenly Saber, an invisible momentum enveloped the entire void.

The momentum of the Heavenly Saber!

Once Heavenly Saber Art reached perfection, it could generate the momentum of the Heavenly Saber.

Back then, Lin Fei used the momentum of the Heavenly Saber, suppressed the strength of five top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, and killed all of them.

Now, with the emergence of the momentum of the Heavenly Saber, Lin Fei, who was originally suppressed by Shen Lianxin's saber intent, that feeling of being suppressed has reduced by about eighty to ninety percent. Only a little bit was left.

At the same time, Shen Lianxin felt a kind of suppression.

"This is......"

A glint flashed in Shen Lianxin's eyes. He had never seen this kind of power. This kind of suppression made him feel as if there was a flash of insight in his mind. It seemed that saber intent could also be like this.

Suppression!

To suppress with a certain power!

Shen Lianxin's saber intent had already reached perfection. But he didn't know that above saber intent was saber momentum. He just saw Lin Fei's Heavenly Saber momentum and immediately had an outburst of inspiration and a slight touch of his saber intent. This understanding of the saber could be described as terrifying!

However, no matter what his realization was, it must be after this battle. If he failed in this battle, that was death! When dead, everything is in vain!

Therefore, when Lin Fei's saber energy and Heavenly Saber momentum had not reached their peak, Shen Lianxin drew his saber.

"Swish".

This saber was earth-shattering. Quick to the extreme and also simple to the extreme. Just like the Saber-drawing Technique. Yes, it was the Saber-drawing Technique! Lin Fei saw a shadow of the Saber-drawing Technique in it.

"Ultimate Saber Slash!"

Shen Lianxin's voice echoed in the void. At the same time, a more than two hundred meters huge saber glow that seemed no less than Lin Fei's saber energy suddenly penetrated the void. There was also a sharp edge and an unparalleled Innate True Qi.

This saber exhausted Shen Lianxin's twenty years of accumulation! This was not the Saber-drawing Technique but the Ultimate Saber Slash he created by referring to the Saber-drawing Technique.

Dangerous!

Lin Fei felt a trace of danger. Ever since he understood the saber intent, for the first time, Lin Fei felt danger in a battle with a martial artist. Even when he was in the Hidden Sword Sect, fighting against Liu Yibai, the number one swordsman in the world, Lin Fei did not feel this kind of danger.

And now, he felt danger. That saber glow was very terrifying. Moreover, Shen Lianxin's Innate True Qi, obviously, had also reached perfection. Shen Lianxin was a martial arts Grand Master!

True Qi perfection, saber intent perfection! Shen Lianxin could be described as the strongest martial artist Lin Fei has ever encountered!

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

Facing this saber, Lin Fei also didn't think about anything. Without any reservation, instantly erupted all his Saber Qi.

Immediately, that two hundred and fifty meters Heavenly Saber in the void was also directly vast and mighty, with the momentum of Heaven falling, slashed fiercely toward Shen Lianxin.

"Boom."

Saber glow and saber energy collided with each other. This was their strongest blow. Endless saber energy and saber glow were entangled and collided crazily.

At the same time, they were also wreaking havoc in the void. Even on the lake's surface, it set off waves of shockwaves, like rolling waves.

"Ch."

A saber glow cut open Lin Fei's arm and drew a half-finger-long bloodstain.

Lin Fei did not move. He looked at Shen Lianxin not far away.

160. Two Saber Intents

"Puh."

Shen Lianxin's robe was torn apart in an instant. Stunning bloodstains covered his body, making him look like a blood man.

However, Shen Lianxin did not fall. He reached out his hand, touching a bloodstain on his neck. This bloodstain was very shallow. Although it was also bleeding, it was just a skin wound. If it was a little deeper, it would have cut the carotid artery.

At that time, the blood would not stop, even if he was a martial arts Grand Master, he cannot escape the fate of death.

Shen Lianxin's expression was somewhat complex, and he asked in a low voice, "Why didn't you kill me? Your saber energy can tear my body apart. But why did you hold back your saber energy at the last moment?"

Shen Lianxin knew very well. If Lin Fei didn't hold back his saber energy at the last moment, he would definitely died!

For Shen Lianxin, death was not something to be afraid of. He had been looking for exotic beasts all over the place, but there was no hope at all. In his lifetime, he could never reach body perfection nor could he establish a foundation to become a Martial Saint.

Therefore, even if he had good luck and obtained countless superior saber techniques and martial arts, what about it? A hundred years later, it's still a mound of yellow earth. Dying in the hands of a top saber master could be considered a worthy life.

Lin Fei looked at Shen Lianxin. He calmly said, "There are too few real saber masters in the world. If I become a Martial Saint in the future, but there are no peers, how lonely it would be? Besides, your talent in saber techniques is no less than mine. If you die now, won't there be one less stunning Human Saber Saint in the future?"

"Saber Saint?"

Shen Lianxin sighed deeply and shook his head, "Although your True Qi has not reached perfection, with your strength and status, you must have known about martial arts foundation building, right?

In Great Chang, exotic beasts have become extinct. I have searched everywhere, even all over Great Chang. But there is not a trace of an exotic beast."

Without the flesh and blood of an exotic beast, how can one achieve body perfection? If the body is not perfect, one can never become a Martial Saint, so, whether it's a Martial Saint or a Saber Saint, no matter how stunning you are, in the end, you are just a mound of yellow earth."

Obviously, Shen Lianxin had given up. He couldn't become a Martial Saint. No matter how high the talent of the saber technique was, what was the use? Not dead now. A hundred years later, he would die.

"Yes, without the flesh and blood of exotic beasts, whether it's a Saber Saint or a Martial Saint, it's ultimately an unreachable dream!"

Lin Fei also sighed. The founder of the Nine Profound Sect probably experienced such despair.

"Lin Fei, I owe you a life. If you need me someday. You can take this life!"

Shen Lianxin said solemnly. Then, he turned around and prepared to leave. This time it was over. Having seen the saber technique of the "Immortal Slayer Saber", he had no regrets. He would return to the countryside and end this crippled life.

"Interested in hunting exotic beasts?"

Suddenly, Lin Fei's voice came from behind.

"Whoosh."

Shen Lianxin abruptly turned around, staring intently at Lin Fei. Even his gaze was like a sharp saber.

"You... what did you just say?"

"Hunting exotic beasts, are you interested?"

"Exotic beasts... you know where the exotic beasts are?"

Shen Lianxin was very excited. Originally, he had completely given up. He thought he could not become a Martial Saint in this life. But now, Lin Fei's words gave him a glimmer of hope.

"Yes, I know something about the whereabouts of exotic beasts. So, do you dare to hunt exotic beasts?"

"Hahaha, the heavens have mercy, the path of martial arts is not cut off! Hunt exotic beasts, why not? I've been waiting for this day for twenty years!"

Shen Lianxin's body once again emitted a terrifying saber intent. It was as if he had turned back into a peerless saber. Sharp and compelling!

"Where are the exotic beasts?"

"Don't worry, wait for me for a while, my saber intent is about to reach perfection!"

"Saber intent perfection?"

Shen Lianxin suddenly looked at Lin Fei, unsure. He just remembered Lin Fei was testing his saber technique with all the saber masters in the world. Now, Lin Fei has defeated him.

Did that mean he had succeeded in testing the saber?

However, Lin Fei did not speak. He immediately sat cross-legged on the ground, and the saber intent on his body began to radiate little by little. At the same time, a system voice sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"Your martial art, Heavenly Saber Art, has captured the innate perfection level saber technique, Mountain Saber Technique. Training progress increased by 10%."

"Your martial art, Heavenly Saber Art, has captured the innate perfection level saber technique, Ultimate Saber Slash. Training progress increased by 20%."

"Your martial art, Heavenly Saber Art, has given birth to saber intent!"

Lin Fei was somewhat surprised. Unexpectedly, Shen Lianxin actually possessed two innate perfection-level saber techniques. Moreover, one of them could actually increase the training progress of Heavenly Saber Art by 20%. This was enough to show the terror of this saber technique. It was by no means a common innate saber technique.

However, whether it was an increase of 20% or 10%, actually, it's the same. Because once the training progress of Heavenly Saber Art reaches 100%, it would generate saber intent. And now, the saber intent was born.

"Hum."

A dominant and unparalleled saber intent suddenly erupted from Lin Fei's body. At the same time, Shen Lianxin's saber was even shaking violently. Obviously, it was also affected by Lin Fei's saber intent.

"Your saber intent of Saber Drawing Technique is trying to devour the saber intent Heavenly Saber Art."

"The two saber intents have started to duel."

"The duel is in progress..."

Then, Lin Fei began to concentrate his consciousness in his mind again. At the same time, two distinct saber intents appeared on Lin Fei.

For Shen Lianxin, who was very sensitive to saber intent, noticed it immediately.

"Two saber intents?"

Shen Lianxin was very surprised. Lin Fei actually comprehended two saber intents. This was very rare in the world!

Shen Lianxin himself had achieved saber intent perfection. He knew very well. Comprehending one kind of saber intent is already very difficult, let alone comprehending two saber intents.

Usually, one would comprehend a kind of saber intent, then use this saber intent as a foundation, continuously refining and understanding it. Finally, train it to perfection.

And Lin Fei? Seemed to be taking a different path.

"Two saber intents are conflicting, but Lin Fei did not interfere, instead letting the two saber intents conflict. Could it be that he's walking the path of merging saber intents? He wants to merge two kinds of saber intents, and then make the saber intent reach perfection?"

Shen Lianxin thought of a possibility. However, merging saber intents was much more difficult than simply comprehending a single saber intent to perfection. Not many people would choose this method of merging saber intents.

However, if this method was successful, the saber intent would be very strong. It would possess the characteristics and advantages of two kinds of saber intents.

Moreover, if one could truly comprehend saber intent at an extremely fast speed, then, merging saber intents could also make the saber intent reach perfection in the shortest time.

Clearly, Lin Fei was such a top talent. At a young age, he had comprehended two kinds of saber intents.

At this moment, in Lin Fei's mind, the Saber-drawing Technique's saber intent and the Heavenly Saber's saber intent were fiercely fighting.

The Heavenly Saber's saber intent, although it had just been born and even the Mastery couldn't be considered, it was too powerful that even able to make other saber techniques bow down. This was the reason why when the Heavenly Saber was out, all the sabers bow down.

Therefore, the saber intent born of Heavenly Saber Art was naturally extremely powerful. Even if the saber intent of the Saber-drawing Technique had already transcended, it was still unable to devour Heavenly Saber Art in a short time.

At this time, Lin Fei needed to intervene. Saber-drawing Technique's saber intent? Or Heavenly Saber's saber intent? He fell into a dilemma.

However, no matter which saber intent was the main one, Lin Fei must make a choice.

161. Finally Became A Martial Arts Grand Master

Lin Fei closed his eyes. Memories emerged in his mind.

Saber-drawing Technique!

Lin Fei obviously had affection for Saber-drawing Technique. His saber intent generated was based on the Saber-drawing Technique and it helped Lin Fei to become the "Number One Saber Under Heaven".

However, Lin Fei knew the Saber-drawing Technique was ultimately inferior to the Heavenly Saber Art.

Heavenly Saber Art was not only an innate level saber technique, more importantly, Saber-drawing Technique also had the momentum of the heavenly saber. This was imitating the "saber momentum". There were some traces of saber momentum.

If the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art was the main one, then when Lin Fei's saber intent tried to transform into saber momentum in the future, there would definitely be advantages.

Thinking of this, Lin Fei made a decision instantly.

"Heavenly Saber Art, slash!"

Lin Fei shouted lowly. Immediately, in his mind, the illusion of the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art instantly wiped out the saber intent of the Saber-drawing Technique.

"Hum".

The two saber intents in Lin Fei's mind disappeared instantly.

At the same time, Lin Fei felt that the transcended saber intent in his body seemed to have actively integrated into the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art and the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art was rapidly improving at a visible speed.

Mastery, transcendence, perfection! There was almost no pause, no obstacles. The saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art directly reached perfection! Even more than that after reaching perfection, the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art even improved a little bit more.

Lin Fei could vaguely feel the progress of cultivation after saber intent reached perfection. It was actually improving in the direction of "saber momentum". Although it was just a direction, this was already luckier than countless martial artists. After all, even the direction, many martial artists didn't have this method.

Like Shen Lianxin's saber intent had long reached perfection. However, he couldn't find the direction to continue improving his saber intent.

And Lin Fei used the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art as the main one, integrating the transcendent saber intent of the Saber-drawing Technique, not only did the saber intent reach perfection, he even directly found the direction above the saber intent.

"Did it work? It really worked, the fusion of the two saber intents, Lin Fei's saber intent has reached perfection."

A hint of seriousness appeared on Shen Lianxin's face. Lin Fei actually fused two kinds of saber intents and made the saber intent reach perfection!

"Boom."

The saber intent of Lin Fei's perfection spread out in all directions, vast and powerful.

Shen Lianxin felt as if a huge mountain was weighing on him. So, Shen Lianxin naturally erupted his saber intent as well. His saber intent was also perfection. And before, Shen Lianxin's saber intent had suppressed Lin Fei's transcendent saber intent.

But now, when Shen Lianxin once again erupted his perfection saber intent, he found out his saber intent was actually being suppressed by Lin Fei's saber intent.

"How is this possible?"

Shen Lianxin was very confident in his own saber intent. He knew that saber intent also has strengths and weaknesses. Even if they were all perfection saber intent, there were still strengths and weaknesses.

Shen Lianxin's saber intent had been honed through countless trials. It was the purest saber intent. It could be considered as the "ultimate" saber intent. Therefore, he created the "Ultimate Saber Slash". Its power was extremely terrifying. Among the innate saber techniques, it could be considered one of the top saber techniques. But even so, his saber intent was actually suppressed by Lin Fei's saber intent. This was simply incredible.

Shen Lianxin didn't know Lin Fei's saber intent was based on the saber intent of Heavenly Saber Art the top innate saber technique that imitates "saber momentum".

The heavenly saber was out, and all sabers bow their heads! It could almost suppress all saber techniques. This was the terrifying part of Heavenly Saber Art. Otherwise, Heavenly Saber Art could not capture other saber techniques, forcefully integrate them, then give birth to saber intent.

Lin Fei's saber intent finally reached perfection and even suppressed Shen Lianxin's saber intent, but it was not over yet. On the contrary, this was just the beginning.

With the perfection of Lin Fei's saber intent, the Saber Qi in Lin Fei's body was also increasing crazily, as if boiling. After all, Lin Fei's Saber Qi was closely related to saber intent.

The progress of Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll was only 42%. But now, with the perfection of Lin Fei's saber intent, its progress began to skyrocket.

50%, 60%, 70%, 80%, 90%......

At the same time, in Lin Fei's mind, the system's voice sounded again.

"Your martial arts True Intention Scroll, inspired by the perfection of saber intent, begins to actively integrate saber intent."

"Your True Intention Scroll's progress has increased to 100%."

"Your True Intention Scroll has reached perfection!"

"Boom."

In the void, countless Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth converged above Lin Fei's head, just like a giant vortex. The terrifying spiritual Qi, like a river rushing back, rushed crazily into Lin Fei's body.

Countless heavenly and earthly Spiritual Qi transformed into Innate True Qi, then fused with Lin Fei's saber intent, and converted into Saber Qi.

Lin Fei's Saber Qi almost at a speed visible to the naked eye, quickly expanding. The pressure on Lin Fei was also revealed without concealment. This was the pure pressure of Saber Qi.

"Is this... True Qi perfection? Martial Arts Grand Master?"

Shen Lianxin was even more shocked. Lin Fei tried sabers with the world's saber users not to temper the saber intent but to generate a second type of saber intent. Then the two types of saber intent fused, making the saber intent complete perfection.

Shen Lianxin could understand that. But what did saber intent perfection have to do with Innate True Qi?

The two were completely unrelated! But now, not only had Lin Fei's saber intent reached perfection, but even True Qi had also reached perfection, was this a coincidence?

Shen Lianxin simply didn't believe that this was any coincidence. Lin Fei's Innate True Qi definitely had a lot to do with the saber intent!

"Shh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes. At this moment, his Saber Qi and saber intent all radiated without scruples. Even Shen Lianxin had to take a few steps back. He felt that Lin Fei's strength now had increased by more than ten times!?

If he fought with Lin Fei again, Shen Lianxin estimated that he couldn't even block a move!

"Lin Fei, congratulations. Now that True Qi is perfection and saber intent is perfection. You are truly a martial arts grandmaster now! And it's just a step away from being a Martial Saint!" Shen Lianxin spoke, congratulating Lin Fei.

"Saber Qi perfection. Saber intent perfection. Today, I finally became a martial arts grandmaster!"

Lin Fei's eyes were very calm. But, his heart was not calm.

Martial Arts Grand Master!

This was almost standing at the pinnacle of the innate. The next step was only one goal.

Foundation Establishment!

At this moment, Lin Fei's Saber Qi was boiling inside his body. He couldn't help but let out a long howl.

"Boom."

The next moment, Lin Fei's saber energy quickly condensed into a giant heavenly saber in the void.

Heavenly Saber Art!

And this time the condensed heavenly saber was not two hundred and fifty meters but one thousand meters!

One thousand meters of saber energy, as if it cut open the void. Looking far away, as if a huge crack had appeared in the sky.

"System."

Lin Fei murmured in his heart. Immediately, the system panel appeared in front of him.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Martial Arts Grand Master

True Intention Scroll: Perfection

Saber Intent: Perfection (Progress 5%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Refining The Golden Body: (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei looked at the system panel.

The martial arts realm had already become a Martial Arts Grand Master. Moreover, saber intent had reached perfection. And after perfection, there was still a 5% progress in cultivation.

Lin Fei estimated that if the saber intent continued to improve, once it reached 100% progress in cultivation, then the saber intent could transform into saber momentum!

Saber momentum could be compared to Martial Saints!

Of course, this would definitely be difficult. However, this represented that Lin Fei now had a direction toward saber momentum. This point had already surpassed countless martial artists.

Now that Lin Fei's Saber Qi was perfect, and saber intent was perfect. His entire martial arts cultivation had reached a point where it can no longer progress. Next, he only had one goal. That was, to build the foundation.

"Brother Shen, let's go."

Lin Fei left the riverside directly with Shen Lianxin.

162. Saber Cleaves a Snow Avalanche

The Northern Territory of Great Chang.

This place was once known as the North Country, the Snow Country. It snowed all year round, with nearly three hundred days of icy weather. The climate was extremely cold.

The people living here were called the Snow Clan. They once established a kingdom called "Snow Country". However, it was later annihilated by Great Chang.

Great Chang incorporated Snow Country into its territory, becoming its own northern frontier.

Extreme North City. As the name suggests, it was the city at the farthest north. Beyond Extreme North City lay an endless snowfield. The people of the Snow Clan all had white hair and their bodies were tall. They were different from people in other parts of Great Chang.

At the city gate, there were two men of average stature, at least when compared to the people of the Snow Clan here, standing quietly at the city gate. They were staring at the situation outside the city gate. Motionless.

After an unknown amount of time. Shen Lianxin slowly said, "Today is the day we agreed with Liu Yibai. Brother Lin, but Liu Yibai hasn't arrived yet!"

These two men were none other than Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin. Since the day of their battle by the river, the two had been nearly inseparable. Every day they would spar with each other in saber techniques, honing their saber intent. Moreover, Lin Fei even shared the situation he had learned about saber momentum with Shen Lianxin.

Lin Fei also wrote a letter to Liu Yibai explaining Shen Lianxin's situation. He hoped that Shen Lianxin could join them in hunting exotic beasts. Liu Yibai readily agreed, of course. After all, even an underage exotic beast was quite terrifying, even if he and Lin Fei joined forces, they would not be entirely confident.

As for Shen Lianxin, according to Lin Fei, he was also a powerful figure at the same level as them, nearly unbeatable below the Foundation Establishment realm.

Therefore, with Shen Lianxin's participation, the hunting of exotic beasts might go more smoothly. Of course, the most important point was an underage exotic beast was very huge. Its flesh and blood were enough for four or five people to reach body perfection.

Therefore, even with the addition of Shen Lianxin, it would not pose a threat to the interests of Liu Yibai and Lin Fei.

Liu Yibai wrote back agreeing to Shen Lianxin's participation. Then he set the time. They would meet in the Extreme North City of the Northern Territory on the eighth day of the third month.

Today was the eighth day of the third month. Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin arrived at Extreme North City three days in advance. But Liu Yibai has not shown up yet.

"Continue to wait."

Lin Fei calmly replied. Shen Lianxin also nodded. The two had been waiting in Extreme North City for three days. They didn't mind waiting a little longer.

"Huu..."

The cold wind whistled. Snowflakes fell.

"Shush."

Both Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin suddenly looked up, looking straight ahead. On the deserted street, a man wearing a thick cotton coat, with a long sword on his back, was walking step by step towards the city gate.

"Number One Sword Under Heaven, Liu Yibai!"

Shen Lianxin said solemnly. He had never seen Liu Yibai. But he had heard of Liu Yibai's reputation a long time ago.

Number One Sword Under Heaven! What an honor!

Once, Shen Lianxin even thought about seeking Liu Yibai. However, Liu Yibai had been in seclusion for many years, with his sword sealed. Shen Lianxin gave up on the idea.

"Saber Fanatic, Shen Lianxin!"

Liu Yibai said calmly, "Master Lin says that your saber techniques are divine and are not weaker than his."

"Brother Lin overpraises me."

Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai met each other and thus got acquainted. However, Liu Yibai did not mention the idea of comparing notes with Shen Lianxin. Shen Lianxin was a person recognized by Lin Fei. He trusted Lin Fei quite a bit.

"Brother Liu, you asked us to meet in Extreme North City. Could it be that the exotic beast is in the Northern Territory?"

Shen Lianxin couldn't help but ask. He was even more anxious than Lin Fei. After all, both he and Liu Yibai were much older than Lin Fei. If they missed this opportunity, even if they had the flesh and blood of an exotic beast in the future, their age would be too great, their energy would not be up to par, and their vital energy would be declining. It's doubtful they would be able to reach body perfection.

"It's not in the Northern Territory, but beyond the Northern Territory! Brother Lin, Brother Shen, let's go."

With that, Liu Yibai directly led Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin out of Extreme North City. They arrived outside the city. Outside Extreme North City, everywhere was a snowfield. The three of them walked through the snow, continuing northward.

The further north they went, the colder it became. This kind of cold was already unbearable for ordinary people. Even acquired martial artist, it was afraid they would be frozen to death in this snowfield.

"The Northern Territory is cold, especially this extreme northern place, which is extremely cold. Go further north, and we'll encounter the cold current. The cold current could even freeze our Innate True Qi, it's a huge drain on Innate True Qi.

So, we need to be quick. We must get through the cold current as quickly as possible. Remember, never burst out your Innate True Qi. Otherwise, once a big avalanche is triggered, we would probably have no place to be buried!"

Liu Yibai reminded Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin with a serious expression. In fact, without Liu Yibai's reminder, both Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin knew that this extreme northern place was not to be underestimated. Because, of the cold right now, they had to use their Innate True Qi and saber energy to resist it.

"Let's go!"

The next moment, Liu Yibai's figure darted forward. He directly sprinted forward. Lin Fei also used the Close Yet Distant technique, following behind him. Shen Lianxin was not to be outdone. He also followed closely.

The three of them ran wildly all the way. The Innate True Qi and Saber Qi in their bodies seemed to be vaguely frozen, running not smoothly.

"Huu..."

The gale howled. On both sides were towering snow mountains. Below was only a small canyon. There were hardly any traces of human activity. Even the birds and beasts had vanished. This place seemed like a forbidden zone for life.

Suddenly, Liu Yibai raised his head sharply. In the sky, the snow fell even heavier, and more terrifying was the wild wind, blowing incessantly. The snow mountains on all sides were faintly trembling and roaring.

"Rumble..."

Soon, the snow mountains on all sides were roaring.

"Not good, it's an avalanche."

Liu Yibai's face changed.

Avalanche! And it was a large one. There were avalanches on all sides. At such a fast speed, even with the speed of Lin Fei and the others, they could not retreat. This was the power of nature. It was the power of heaven and earth.

Even if they were martial arts Grand Masters, standing at the peak of humanity, in the face of this natural force, they still seemed insignificant. This was the difference from a Qi cultivator. A Qi cultivator could at least fly.

However, in this extreme northern place, there were cold currents, which could freeze True Qi and spiritual power. If a Qi Condensation cultivator really tried to fly using magical artifacts, their spiritual power would be frozen, and they would instantly fall down and be smashed into a mush.

This extreme northern place was a true forbidden zone for life. Neither martial artists nor Qi Condensation cultivators dared to come here.

"We must rush through, regardless of the cost!"

Liu Yibai was furiously stimulating his Innate True Qi. He used his body technique to try to rush through at the fastest speed before the avalanche arrived. However, he was ultimately too slow!

"Boom."

The avalanche arrived. It directly fell onto the path in front of the three of them. This only path in the canyon was completely blocked.

At the same time, a more massive avalanche was rolling down from the mountain peak. At this moment, the three of them seemed to have fallen into a death trap!

"This is the power of heaven and earth, the power of nature. How insignificant our power seems in the face of the power of heaven and earth. We can't withstand a single avalanche..."

Shen Lianxin murmured quietly. He seemed to have foreseen the end.

"Man can conquer nature! If there is no way, then I will cut a path!"

Lin Fei dashed to the front where the path was blocked by the avalanche.

A large amount of snow, rocks, and dirt blocked the path, like a small mountain. It was despairing.

Lin Fei's saber energy surged out wildly from his body. In an instant, a thousand meters high saber energy appeared in the void, emitting infinite sharpness.

One thousand meters was almost as high as some mountain peaks.

Lin Fei's clothes were flapping. His expression was solemn, filled with a murderous aura. He joined his hands together toward the direction that was blocked in front and direct slash downward.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

Suddenly, the one thousand meters saber energy, magnificent and carrying endless sharpness, was like a divine saber descending from the heavens, slashed fiercely onto the snow heap.

"Boom."

The huge snow heap was directly shredded by the terrifying saber energy. A snow heap as high as thousand meters, similar to a small mountain peak.

But at this moment, it was sliced open by Lin Fei's one thousand meters saber energy, directly creating a huge ravine!

Even if it was Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai, who had already reached the pinnacle of the world's martial arts, at this moment, they also felt an unparalleled shock in their hearts.

This saber of Lin Fei was unlike any earthly saber technique! This was the real power of heaven and earth!

163. The Exotic Beast is Here!

"Let's go!"

Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin were shocked. But after all, the two were martial arts Grand Masters, they quickly recovered their senses.

Immediately, they employed their lightness skills, following the path that Lin Fei had cut out with his saber energy, they swiftly moved away.

"Rumble."

Just after they left, the big avalanche arrived. The entire valley was completely sealed off.

"Huff..."

The three of them breathed a sigh of relief. They looked back and glanced behind them. The valley was gone. In its place was a new mountain peak. It was a snowy mountain!

Facing such power of nature, once they were still in the valley, would undoubtedly die. There would be no chance of luck.

"Brother Lin, you..."

Despite having interacted with Lin Fei for one or two months, ever since Lin Fei achieved perfection in Saber Qi and saber intent, the two had never made a full effort again.

Unexpectedly, today, when Lin Fei made a move again, it was so shocking! He forcibly cut out a path with his saber energy.

That terrifying power, even if those top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators used magical treasures, might not be able to match it.

Magical treasures! These were usually owned by those who have achieved the Foundation Establishment realm.

Lin Fei's this saber seemed to be approaching the power of the Foundation Establishment realm. Even if it was not, it was not far off.

Lin Fei was able to slash out such a terrifying saber. Even if the founder of the Nine Profound Sect were to resurrect, it probably wouldn't be much different.

In terms of combat power, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect was truly invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm. And now Lin Fei, also vaguely possessed this kind of grandeur and style. Invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm.

Especially that saber. It was no longer like any earthly saber technique. At least, Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai, fairly speaking, couldn't block that saber.

However, despite being shocked, Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai understood the most important thing right now was to slay the exotic beast and become martial saints, once they became martial saints, they could slash a sword or saber stronger than Lin Fei just now. Foundation Establishment was the key!

The three continued to head north. The further north they went, the colder it became.

One day, two days, three days...

They didn't know how long had passed. Suddenly, Liu Yibai stopped.

"We're here."

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin looked ahead. It was a flat plain, and there was nothing in sight. No mountains, no vegetation, no animals. Only glaciers. Endless glaciers. It was so vast that one couldn't see the end.

"Are there exotic beasts here?"

Lin Fei looked around. It was empty, where could there be traces of any exotic beast?

Shen Lianxin couldn't help but ask, "Brother Liu, this is an empty and vast expanse. It's endless, where could an exotic beast possibly hide? Could you have remembered wrong?"

Although the possibility was low, it was not impossible. After all, this snowy field looked the same everywhere. Not much difference.

Liu Yibai shook his head slightly, pointing to the glacier in front of him. He said calmly, "I didn't remember wrong, the exotic beast is under the glacier."

"Under the glacier?"

Shen Lianxin had a thought in his heart. Since it was under the glacier, wouldn't that require breaking the glacier? Therefore, Shen Lianxin pulled out his saber and was ready to break the glacier.

"Brother Shen, I advise you not to touch the glacier, otherwise, it will be hard to predict life and death," Liu Yibai warned.

"Hard to predict life and death?"

Shen Lianxin didn't understand. What danger could this mere glacier pose?

Liu Yibai didn't speak. A strand of Innate True Qi flew out directly and fell above the glacier.

"Crack."

When the Innate True Qi had just arrived above the glacier, it was actually frozen into an ice block and fell to the ground, shattered to pieces. This scene made both Shen Lianxin and Lin Fei can't help but feel shocked in their hearts.

"This is..."

Shen Lianxin also released a strand of True Qi. However, the result was the same as Liu Yibai's. Both were frozen, fell on the glacier, and shattered into pieces.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei flicked his finger. His Saber Qi flew into the air above the glacier and stayed a little longer. However, it was only a little longer. It was still the same as Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai's Innate True Qi. It was frozen into ice crystals, fell on the glacier, and shattered.

"It can actually freeze my Saber Qi. There's something strange about this glacier!"

Lin Fei had a slight chill in his heart. He knew very well how strong his Saber Qi is currently.

Lin Fei's inner power was three-in-one. This foundation surpassed countless martial artists. Later, it was transformed into Innate True Qi, which combined with saber intent to transform into saber energy. In essence, Lin Fei underwent an additional enhancement at the innate level.

Overall, from inner power to Saber Qi, Lin Fei had almost undergone two enhancements. Therefore, Lin Fei's Saber Qi was now so strong, so terrifying, and far exceeding other martial arts Grand Masters.

However, even so, it still couldn't resist this strange glacier.

Liu Yibai said solemnly, "This glacier is very strange, it seems to be a real forbidden area for life. Whether it's inner power, True Qi, spiritual power, magical artifact, etc, once step into the glacier, it will be frozen. Even if a martial arts Grand Master steps in, within a breath, he will turn into an ice sculpture, forever left on the glacier. Perhaps only a Martial Saint or a Foundation Establishment True Person can forcefully break into the glacier. But even such existences probably won't get far on the glacier..."

Lin Fei nodded. This world had too many secrets. This land of the extreme north was actually such a terrifying place.

Lin Fei was afraid that many people want to leave the Great Chang through the land of the extreme north was wishful thinking.

Great Chang was vast, but there were still people who want to leave. However, upon reaching the land of the extreme north. This glacier was almost impassable.

As for what was at the end of the glacier, nobody knew.

"What about the exotic beast?" Shen Lianxin asked.

"It's under this glacier. Under the glacier, is the sea, called the North Ice Sea! The exotic beast I found lives under the sea. It should be naturally adapted to the cold of the sea area.

When the exotic beasts of Great Chang were completely extinct, only this harsh environment of the North Ice Sea could possibly allow exotic beasts to survive."

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin thought carefully. It seemed to make sense. If the exotic beasts were not in harsh environments, they would probably have been killed by some Martial Saints long ago.

Only in the North Ice Sea were even the Martial Saints helpless, so they have been able to reproduce safely till now. This also gave hope to people like Lin Fei.

"Brother Liu, the glacier is so dangerous, how can we lure out that exotic beast?"

Shen Lianxin asked again. If the exotic beast was in the North Ice Sea, then the three of them, even as martial arts Grand Masters, were helpless. After all, they dared not step on the glacier. How could they hunt the exotic beast in the North Ice Sea?

"Young exotic beasts are very playful. I have observed that around the end of March each year, young exotic beasts will appear. Sometimes it's one, sometimes it's two. We just need to wait quietly.

Wait for the exotic beast to come ashore from the North Ice Sea, and then immediately take action. We must kill the exotic beast at all costs! This is our only hope!

Once failed, the exotic beast may not come ashore again. By then, none of us will be able to build a foundation and become Martial Saint. This is also why, although I knew the whereabouts of the exotic beast many years ago, I have not taken any action. After all, once we fail, it would cut off our last hope!"

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin looked at each other. They understood what Liu Yibai meant.

"Alright, let's wait then."

So, the three of Lin Fei found a place that could slightly hide their bodies. Then they sat down cross-legged. They have Innate True Qi or Saber Qi to protect their bodies. It was not a problem to hold on for half a month.

Time passed bit by bit. They set off on the eighth of March. It took some time on the road, but it should only be a few days, now it's only mid-March at most.

The exotic beast had not yet appeared. The three of them sat cross-legged on the ground, unmoving. They were quickly covered by snowflakes, forming three ice sculptures. Perfectly blending with the icy and snowy environment around.

One day, two days, three days... They didn't know how long it had passed.

"Crack."

Suddenly, on the usually calm glacier, there was a faint vibration. On the solid glacier, a faint crack appeared.

"Boom boom boom."

As if something terrifying was hitting the glacier from underneath.

"The exotic beast is here!"

"Whoosh."

The three ice sculptures in front of the glacier opened their eyes instantly.

164. It seems too weak

"Crack."

The glacier was cracking. Numerous cracks appear, densely packed. The impact from below was getting louder and stronger.

"Boom."

Finally, the glacier shattered. A region of the glacier hundreds of meters in size was completely shattered.

"Splash."

A huge head slowly emerged from the North Ice Sea beneath the glacier. It looked somewhat like a bear.

However, when the head and body of this exotic beast gradually emerged, the three ice sculptures fell silent.

This exotic beast was a bear enlarged several hundreds of times. It was several hundred meters tall, as large as a mountain. It slowly crawled from the North Ice Sea onto the shore With every step it took, the ground shook.

"Liu Yibai, was this the exotic beast you spoke of? And it's a juvenile exotic beast?"

Shen Lianxin sent a message.

"Last time, it wasn't this big."

"When was the last time?"

"Thirty years ago."

Lin Fei fell silent. Shen Lianxin fell silent. Even Liu Yibai fell silent.

Previously, in Liu Yibai's description, this exotic beast was strong, but it was far from being as big as it was now, reaching several hundred of meters tall.

Thirty years ago, the exotic beast wasn't even thirty meters tall. What did this exotic beast eat in these thirty years? It directly grew to several hundreds of meters! Just looking at its size, that was the most straightforward deterrent.

Thirty years ago, Liu Yibai, facing an exotic beast less than thirty meters tall, already found it tricky and needed to bring Lin Fei along.

Now, facing the giant bear exotic beast reaching several hundred meters tall, the three of them really didn't have confidence. They didn't even have a glimmer of assurance.

"Should we go back, cultivate for some more time, and then come back?"

Shen Lianxin proposed a suggestion. Martial artists fight against the heavens and the earth, they do not fear. But not being afraid does not mean courting death.

Facing such a terrifying giant beast. Just the three of them? They probably couldn't even withstand a slap.

"Cultivate? At our level, we have reached the limit. Not to mention cultivating for some time. What if we cultivate for thirty or fifty years? Without foundation-building, there was no hope for even the slightest improvement.

The next time we come, we will still face this exotic beast. By then, this exotic beast will no longer be a juvenile exotic beast, but an adult exotic beast. It might even be stronger than a typical Foundation Establishment cultivator or Martial Saint!" Liu Yibai slowly spoke.

Their communication was done through spiritual messages. Therefore, it wouldn't affect the exotic beast.

Shen Lianxin also fell silent. He knew that Liu Yibai was right. Even if they cultivated for another thirty, fifty years, what could they achieve?

"Brother Lin, do we fight or not?"

Ever since the exotic beast appeared. It was Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai who were communicating. While Lin Fei had remained silent the whole time, not uttering a single word.

"Its eyes were its weak points! Even the strongest exotic beast has weaknesses. My saber was too conspicuous, it won't be able to harm its eyes. Brother Liu, your sword was silent and traceless, perhaps, it can blind its eyes. This was our only chance! And there's no way back!"

Lin Fei finally spoke. However, he didn't really answer the question of whether to fight or not. Instead, he pointed out the weak point of the exotic beast.

From the beginning, Lin Fei had never considered retreating. Instead, he had been looking for the weaknesses of the exotic beast.

Shen Lianxin was taken aback. Liu Yibai fell silent.

"Hahaha, excellent, Brother Lin's determination is admirable. I didn't expect that after hiding my sword for thirty years, my mental will still hasn't improved. What does it matter if I die today? Without becoming a Martial Saint, even if I survive, there would be no meaning!"

Liu Yibai began to laugh. His tone was incredibly determined.

"That's right, I have sealed my saber for twenty years. The loneliness and pain from not being able to improve have tortured me greatly. I would rather die than endure another day without any hope."

Shen Lianxin also solidified his resolve. In this battle, they might die, but they had to go ahead regardless. Because this was their only chance to establish a foundation. Their only hope!

"Brother Shen, we will hold off this exotic beast first, distract it. Brother Liu will seize the opportunity. However, Brother Liu, I hope you can seize the opportunity. We may not be able to hold on for long."

Lin Fei calmly arranged. And so, the three quietly waited.

Shen Lianxin was also brewing the timing, trying to lead the exotic beast as far away from the North Ice Sea as possible.

Otherwise, once they made their move, if they scared off the exotic beast and let the exotic beast escape into the North Ice Sea, wouldn't it all be for nothing? So, they waited quietly.

One step, two steps, three steps... The exotic beast was gradually moving away from the North Ice Sea. It was almost in front of the three ice sculptures.

"Swish".

In the next moment, one of the ice sculptures shattered. Shen Lianxin made His move with all his strength. Several hundreds of meters long saber light suddenly cut through the sky. The sharp saber blade pointed directly at the exotic beast.

"Ultimate Saber Slash!"

Shen Lianxin slashed out with His saber.

"Roar..."

The exotic beast roared angrily. It didn't look at Shen Lianxin's several hundred-meter-long saber light. It slapped directly out.

Amazingly, under the giant palm of the exotic beast, the saber light shattered. Even the skin of the exotic beast was not broken. Shen Lianxin could only watch as the giant palm fell.

"Boom".

The next moment, Lin Fei also made His move. Just as the exotic beast's giant palm was about to hit Shen Lianxin, he didn't try to save Shen Lianxin. Instead, he took advantage of the exotic beast's palm swing when its defense was open, and the Saber Qi in Lin Fei's body burst out.

In the void, there appeared a one thousand-meter-high saber energy, condensed into a heavenly saber! Exuding the power of a heavenly saber!

The terrifying power of the heavenly saber, like a huge mountain, pressed down on the exotic beast. Immediately, the exotic beast roared crazily, seemingly very angry.

This was the characteristic of "momentum". Whether it was a person or an exotic beast, as long as it was a living being, it will be suppressed by "momentum". And this was only the momentum of the heavenly saber. If it was real saber momentum. How strong would that be? Even, perhaps there would be no need to make a move. Just using the saber momentum to suppress would immobilize this exotic beast.

The roar of the exotic beast did not stop Lin Fei, he didn't hesitate at all. He clasped his hands together, just like holding up a big saber.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

The one thousand meters high saber energy, with Lin Fei's saber intent bolstered, and the mysterious momentum of the heavenly saber suppressing.

This saber was Lin Fei's peak saber! Even, vaguely, this saber seemed to have broken some kind of boundary.

In the void, a trace of black cracks appeared. But it also disappeared in an instant as if it never appeared.

Lin Fei didn't care. His entire mind was on this saber. In his mind, there were no other thoughts, only this saber!

"Boom".

Finally, Lin Fei's one thousand meters saber energy landed on the head of the exotic beast. From top to bottom, it slashed down fiercely.

At the same time, Liu Yibai's figure didn't know when actually appeared on the head of the exotic beast. Silent and traceless, even Lin Fei did not perceive it.

Just as Liu Yibai's sword was about to pierce the exotic beast's eye, a line of blood appeared on the beast's head.

"Squash".

The next moment, the beast's head exploded, extending to its entire body.

With a "plop", the several hundred meters of the exotic beast was split in two. It was cut in half by Lin Fei's saber energy.

For a moment, Shen Lianxin fell silent. Liu Yibai fell silent. Even Lin Fei himself fell silent.

"It, it seems too weak..."

After a long while, Lin Fei slowly spoke.

165. Swallowing Flesh and Blood, Heart Stops Suddenly

On the snow-covered ground, the body of the exotic beast was sliced in half by the saber energy. It quickly froze over. The cold wind was still howling, but the three of them seemed to be very quiet.

"It's not that it's too weak. Perhaps you are too strong."

After a long while, Shen Lianxin looked at Lin Fei with a complex gaze and slowly said.

"Brother Lin, I've always had a question. Are you really still an innate martial artist?"

That saber just now and the one that split the avalanche, in fact, had already exceeded Shen Lianxin's understanding of "innate martial artists".

"We don't need to say much. Since the exotic beast is already dead, this is our opportunity. Such a big exotic beast, not to mention the three of us, even if there were three more people, it should be enough for our bodies to reach perfection."

Liu Yibai looked at the body of the exotic beast on the ground. There was a faint excitement in his eyes. The hope for physical perfection lay in this exotic beast's body.

"We can't stay here. In case, an adult exotic beast breaks through the ice, we'll be in trouble. So, take as much of this exotic beast's flesh and blood as we can. Try to get as far away from here as possible."

Lin Fei looked at the endless glacier. Even though the glacier had been cracked open by the exotic beast just now, in just a moment's time, the glacier froze over again, restored to its original state.

Although he could kill an exotic beast with a single saber, this exotic beast had not yet reached adulthood. That is to say, it had not yet reached the Foundation Establishment realm. If an adult exotic beast of the Foundation Establishment realm came, that would be a different story. The three of them would probably not be able to get away.

"Right, we need to leave here as soon as possible. First, take some of the exotic beast's flesh and blood. Bury the rest here. If the exotic beast's flesh and blood are not enough, we can dig it out later."

Liu Yibai drew out his longsword.

"Whoosh".

A sword light slashed out. He wanted to cut off a piece of the exotic beast's flesh.

"Sizzle".

However, when Liu Yibai's sword energy cut into the exotic beast's body, it couldn't even break the skin. It merely left a white mark on the exotic beast's body.

Liu Yibai decided to let the sword burst with Innate True Qi and stabbed it hard.

"Squish".

The sword finally pierced into the skin of the exotic beast, but only about a dozen centimeters. Dozen centimeters, compared to a several hundred-meter-long exotic beast, what use would it do?

If the exotic beast closed its eyes, Liu Yibai probably couldn't even pierce the beast's eyelid.

Shen Lianxin looked at Liu Yibai and said helplessly, "You understand what I felt before, don't you? Cutting the body of the exotic beast is something only Brother Lin can do."

So, Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin both turned their gaze to Lin Fei.

Lin Fei stepped forward. He came to the body of the exotic beast, used his saber energy, and cut toward the body of the exotic beast.

"Squish".

The body of the exotic beast was indeed very tough. Even Lin Fei's Saber Qi couldn't easily cut through it for a time. However, Lin Fei's Saber Qi was plentiful. If one time didn't work, then two times.

Soon, Lin Fei cut the exotic beast into many pieces of meat. The three of them could only carry about one-third of the exotic beast's body. However, that was already quite a bit. The remaining two-thirds of the exotic beast's body was buried on the spot.

"Let's go!"

After everything was settled. Lin Fei and the other two immediately used their body skills and quickly moved away from the glacier.

The three of them ran wildly. Until the evening, they finally saw a snow-capped peak.

Halfway up the peak, there was a cave. The three of them went straight into it.

"Now we have two choices. One is to return directly to the northern city and then slowly digest this exotic beast's flesh and blood.

However, if the exotic beast's flesh and blood are not enough, we will have to travel thousands of miles, risk going to the glacier again, and dig out the buried exotic beast's flesh and blood.

Nobody knows what would happen then. The second option is to consume the exotic beast's flesh and blood right here until the body reaches perfection. If the exotic beast's flesh and blood are not enough, we can quickly reach the glacier from here, which is very convenient."

Lin Fei looked at the exotic beast's flesh and blood in the cave and said calmly.

"Of course, we should consume the exotic beast's flesh and blood right here."

"Right, even though it's a bit cold here, we are martial arts grandmasters, we can handle it. Achieving body perfection is the priority now!"

Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai immediately made their choice, to consume the exotic beast's flesh and blood right here. Lin Fei also thought the same way.

"I have a body refining method here. It's a method left by Great Chang's founder specifically for refining the flesh and blood of exotic beasts. You can try practicing it. Perhaps, it can help you better digest the flesh and blood of the exotic beast."

Lin Fei gave the body refining method to Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai.

This was just a common method for refining the flesh and blood of exotic beasts left by the founder of Great Chang.

"Then we must thank Brother Lin."

Soon, Lin Fei finished imparting the technique. The three of them began in the cave, following the method of body refining, and started consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast for refinement.

Lin Fei took out an ice cube from the body of the exotic beast. This ice cube was filled with the fresh blood of the exotic beast.

Lin Fei opened his mouth and swallowed it. Immediately, the ice cube melted and the fresh blood of the exotic beast flowed into Lin Fei's body.

"Hum".

Immediately, Lin Fei's body felt a warm sensation. At the same time, there seemed to be a very strange force, with the digestion of the fresh blood of the exotic beast, that entered his body.

It seemed to be causing some unknown changes in Lin Fei's body. So, Lin Fei continued to consume the flesh and blood of the exotic beast. He did not know how long it had been. The system's voice sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"Your Refining The Golden Body, due to consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast, your progress has increased by 1%."

"As expected, consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast, there is a change."

Lin Fei was excited. Finally, there was a change. In that case, he would continue to consume it. Physical perfection didn't require any technique, only need to consume the flesh and blood of the exotic beast. Therefore, the three of them stayed in the cave, consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast every day.

One day, two days, three days, four days, five days......

Lin Fei and the others even lost track of time. They were consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast non-stop every day. Their bodies, unknowingly, gradually started to change.

For example, Lin Fei's skin became more and more tender and resilient. Even if one cut it with a sharp saber, it could not cut Lin Fei's skin. Moreover, Lin Fei's body seemed to be slowly exuding a faint, almost unnoticeable, exotic fragrance.

Skin as delicate as a baby, body exuding a unique fragrance.

Lin Fei thought of the words that were used to describe physical perfection. His body was increasingly in line with the characteristics of physical perfection. Moreover, when Lin Fei reached out his hand. The tiny dust in the cave fell, surprisingly, none of it stuck to Lin Fei's hand.

Untouched by dust! Or could say, pure and clean!

"Skin as delicate as a baby, body exuding a unique fragrance, untouched by dust... It's increasingly like physical perfection. But it seems to be missing something. It seems the body never went through a metamorphosis."

Lin Fei frowned. He had consumed so much of the exotic beast's flesh and blood, and so had Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin.

"System."

Lin Fei called out the system to check.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Martial Arts Grand Master

True Intention Scroll: Perfection

Saber Intention: Perfection (5% progress)

Fist Intention: Mastery (81% progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (50% progress)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (0% progress)

Refining The Golden Body: (99% progress)

The progress of refining the golden body stopped at 99%.

"Is the flesh and blood of the exotic beast still not enough?"

Lin Fei frowned.

"Huh?"

Suddenly, Lin Fei felt a pain in his heart. He seemed as if he was going to suffocate. He covered his heart with his hand.

"Thump."

The next moment, Lin Fei collapsed. His heart had stopped.

"Lin Fei!"

"Brother Lin!"

Immediately, Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin came to Lin Fei's side. Shen Lianxin touched Lin Fei's heart. His face instantly changed.

"How...how did Brother Lin's heart stop?"

When the heart stopped, whether it was a martial artist or a Qi cultivator, there was only one possibility, death!

"Could it be, the flesh and blood of the exotic beast we consumed is poisonous?"

Liu Yibai also turned pale. This situation seemed to be unrecorded in the Hidden Sword Sect's archives. Just as the two of them were uncertain, suddenly, their expressions changed dramatically. They both looked as if they were in pain.

"Thump."

Then, the two of them clutched their chests. With painful expressions, they fell to the ground. Their hearts, too, had stopped beating.

For a moment, the entire cave fell silent. All that remained were the three motionless "bodies" on the ground.

A note from RighteousEgg

The end. MC died ;D

More than 45 chapters on my Patreon.

166. Physical Perfection

The cave was very quiet. Three "corpses" quietly lay on the ground.

One hour, two hours, three hours... No one knew how long it had been.

Suddenly, Lin Fei's "corpse" trembled slightly.

"Thump thump thump."

A deep sound came from Lin Fei's body. It sounded like a heartbeat. At first, it was very faint. But as time passed, the sound of the beating grew louder.

"Swoosh."

One could feel, after the heart started beating, a large amount of Qi and blood flowing in the veins with a "booming" sound, making a huge rushing sound.

At the same time, Lin Fei's skin also began to crack.

"Crack."

The skin cracked open, just like an eggshell, revealing a layer of fair, delicate skin inside, glistening with a faint luster.

"Swoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei opened his eyes. He quickly held his chest. He could feel the strong beat of his heart and even hear the sound of his heart beating.

Lin Fei stretched out his hand. There were many cracks on the skin of his arm. A numb and tingling sensation made him feel uncomfortable.

Lin Fei grabbed the cracked skin on his arm and pulled hard.

The next moment, Lin Fei's cracked skin was torn off directly, exposing skin as delicate as a baby's.

Moreover, a unique fragrance emanated from his body. It was somewhat similar to the scent of sandalwood. It was faint, but very clear.

Lin Fei abruptly stood up. He could feel his whole body was full of strength.

His Qi and blood, muscles, skin, etc seemed to be completely renewed.

"Rebirth!"

Lin Fei thought of a word.

"System."

Lin Fei directly called out the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Martial Arts Grand Master

True Intention Scroll: Perfection

Saber Intent: Perfection (5% progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (81% progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (50% progress)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (0% progress)

Refining The Gold Body: Physical Perfection

Seeing the words "Physical perfection" after the Refining The Gold Body, Lin Fei completely understood.

"So, to achieve physical perfection, one needs to be reborn. Consuming the flesh and blood of the exotic beast is subtly refining and changing one's body. At this moment, my internal organs, Qi and blood, etc., are probably completely different from before. Even, some characteristics of the exotic beast have been integrated."

Lin Fei murmured softly. His eyes were shining with a glint of light. No matter what he had fully achieved physical perfection.

Looking at his current characteristics. Skin like a baby, body emitting a unique fragrance, pure and dust-free.

Even more, Lin Fei's body was now impervious to swords and spears, unaffected by water or fire, and never sinking in the water! This was physical perfection.

Vaguely, it was a bit beyond ordinary people, equivalent to a complete rebirth. Only with such a body can one withstand the "Foundation Establishment". Otherwise, what to build the foundation with?

After all, martial artists and Qi cultivators were different.

A martial artist's strength resided within their own body. All the power was on their own. Therefore, a martial artist's body must be strong. So, to build the foundation, the body must achieve perfection and undergo rebirth.

Lin Fei's heart had previously fallen into stagnation. In fact, it wasn't real death but "rebirth".

Rebirth, just like a newborn baby, was equivalent to gaining a "new life". Not only Lin Fei, but Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin were the same.

"Thump thump thump."

Sure enough, with Lin Fei's awakening. Liu Yibai, and Shen Lianxin, their hearts also started to beat one after another. The two of them abruptly opened their eyes. After seeing Lin Fei, they looked at each other again.

"Did we... undergo rebirth?"

Obviously, they also knew what had happened. For a moment, they widened their eyes. Looking up and down their bodies.

It was really a rebirth! Moreover, all the characteristics of physical perfection had them all!

"Physical perfection, this is physical perfection! This physical perfection can be called a true rebirth, not just a transformation of Qi, blood, muscles, and skin, even the meridians inside the body also transform.

This way, it allows us to burst out with even stronger Innate True Qi at once. Even, it makes the quantity of our Innate True Qi continue to increase. Our strength can naturally continue to improve!"

Both of them were very excited. They were already martial arts Grand Masters. Their strength was almost impossible to improve further unless they built their foundation!

But at this moment, after achieving physical perfection, they found that they still had room for improvement.

Of course, this bit of improvement was not really important. Because, physical perfection, represented they could build their foundation!

"Can we... can we really build our foundation?"

Shen Lianxin was very excited. He kept looking at his own white, tender hands, which were like the skin of a baby. He had mixed feelings.

Many years had passed, from being full of enthusiasm to despair, and then to a glimmer of hope. And now, he could finally build his foundation. He felt a bit unreal.

Liu Yibai, on the other hand, seemed very calm. He was a martial arts Grand Master of the Hidden Sword Sect. The Hidden Sword Sect had a very detailed description of "physical perfection".

Therefore, Liu Yibai nodded heavily and said, "Yes, with physical perfection, we can build our foundation. However, typically, to build a foundation, one must achieve physical perfection, True Qi perfection, and Martial Dao True Intent perfection, to have great hope.

But it's just a great hope. It's not absolutely foolproof. In our Hidden Sword Sect's ancient records, some martial artists who achieved physical perfection tried to build their foundation but still failed.

Building a foundation is simple to say, but it's difficult to do. It requires a martial artist to continuously compress their own Innate True Qi. From gaseous Innate True Qi, compress into liquid True Essence. This process will cause a huge impact on the body, equivalent to refining it through many trials. Those without physical perfection can never bear it.

Once the True Essence appears, it means that the foundation has been successfully built! With True Essence nourishing our body's Qi, blood, muscles, and skin, our body will continue to improve. Our lifespan will increase, not inferior to those Foundation Establishment cultivators!"

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin felt a little stir in their hearts.

"Compressing True Qi into True Essence, huh? Thanks for the guidance, Brother Liu."

Shen Lianxin also made a fist salute to Liu Yibai. He was a solitary practitioner. If it weren't for Liu Yibai telling him these things, he would probably have had to go through a lot of trouble to know the secrets of foundation building.

"This process requires a large amount of support from the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth. Therefore, it's best to have some formations that gather Spiritual Qi, or simply be in a place with abundant Spiritual Qi.

The entire north region is actually not suitable for building a foundation. I will return to the Hidden Sword Sect and prepare properly before building my foundation."

Lin Fei nodded. Building a foundation, of course, needed to be cautious. It's impossible to rush to build a foundation.

"But Brother Shen, you are a solitary practitioner. If you want to build your foundation and don't have a suitable place with Spiritual Qi, I'm afraid..."

Liu Yibai intended to rope in Shen Lianxin. But Shen Lianxin smiled and said, "Brother Liu, you don't have to worry about that. As Brother Lin knows, I accidentally found a ruin of an ancient martial arts sect. That ruin has plenty of Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth, I believe it's enough for me to build my foundation."

The three of them looked at each other.

"In that case, let's set off and go back."

The hearts of the three were burning with anticipation. They wished they could go back right away to prepare well and build their foundation as soon as possible and achieve the status of Martial Saint!

"Let's go."

With one step, Lin Fei left. He went straight out of the cave. In a few leaps, the three of them disappeared without a trace.

167. Nine Profound Sect is in danger

Chang City, the Imperial Palace Garden.

At this moment, outside the garden, many martial artists and Qi cultivators had already knelt down. There was even a middle-aged man in dragon robes. He was the Emperor of Great Chang.

But now, this supreme sovereign actually knelt down in the garden. Behind him were Qi cultivators, martial artists, princes, etc. All were the core of the royal family.

"Ancestor, what will we do when you're gone?"

"Yes, Ancestor. Now the world is filled with the smoke of war, the situation is shaking, I'm afraid our Great Chang's nine hundred years of reign is in danger!"

"Ancestor..."

These people all knelt down in the garden. This was because the royal family's Supreme Elder had informed the emperor and others tonight was the time when his lifespan would come to an end.

The Supreme Elder, at this moment, was already full of silver hair. Even his originally rosy face, at this time, gradually became pale. He was sitting cross-legged in the middle of the garden.

Looking at the descendants who had knelt down in front of him, he couldn't help but shake his head slightly and said, "When I was born, the Great Chang was already shaking. It was me, who built the foundation and became a True Person. I continued the fate of Great Chang for more than four hundred years!

But, after four hundred years, even if I'm a Foundation Establishment True Person, I also have a lifespan. Great Chang has been established for nine hundred years, which is long enough. Even the founding emperor said that descendants will have their own blessings.

Wishing for the reign to last forever is impossible. After my death, those immortal sects will surely cause trouble. If you want to keep Great Chang, with your abilities, I'm afraid it's impossible.

So, let nature take its course, even the strongest dynasty has its day of collapse. It's a pity that I don't have the courage of the first emperor, daring to go out to sea alone in search of the Dao. Now, it's too late to regret..."

After speaking, the royal family's Supreme Elder slowly closed his eyes. Then, he gradually lowered his head. The last trace of vitality in his body was completely cut off.

"Ancestor..."

Seeing this scene, everyone knew the ancestor was dead! The sky of the royal family collapsed! From now on, the royal family of Great Chang no longer had a Foundation Establishment True Person to suppress the world. The entire world, collapsing and disintegrating, may only be a matter of time.

With the passing of the royal family's Supreme Elder, the array that originally covered the entire palace gradually disappeared. The array of this palace was always maintained by the Supreme Elder. Without the Supreme Elder, other Qi cultivators of the royal family, even if they were top-notch Qi cultivators, would not expect to maintain it.

The Emperor still wanted to keep it a secret. However, the array of the palace disappeared. This could not be kept secret.

Moreover, in today's Chang City, there are various immortal sects and factions. Openly and secretly.

How many spies were there? How could the death of the royal Supreme Elder be concealed? For a time, the spies of various forces quickly spread the news.

In the main hall of Guardian Primordial Mountain. The Grand Elder, who had reached the perfection of the twelfth level of Qi Condensation, had just received the news. His gaze swept over, and with a hint of excitement in his eyes, he slowly said, "I just received the news, the old man of the royal family has passed away!"

This news immediately exploded the entire hall.

"What, the royal supreme elder is dead?"

"He lived for a full five hundred years and suppressed the world for hundreds of years."

"The royal supreme elder is finally dead, the mountain pressing on our immortal sects has finally disappeared."

"Hahaha, I'm afraid the prosperous age of our immortal sects is coming!"

Basically, the Qi cultivators in the hall were very excited.

That supreme elder of the royal family was the one who made all the immortal sects gasp for breath. Strictly speaking, he was even more ruthless than the Great Chang Founding Emperor!

After all, not long after the Great Chang Founding Emperor established the Great Chang, it seemed that in less than a hundred years, he went out to sea alone in search of the Dao.

But the royal supreme elder was different. He suppressed the world for more than four hundred years. He also suppressed all the major immortal sects for more than four hundred years.

Now, the royal ancestor was dead. Of course, everyone at Guardian Primordial Mountain was happy.

"Humph."

Suddenly, the Grand Elder at the perfection of the twelfth level of Qi Condensation seemed very dissatisfied. He snorted coldly and the entire hall became quiet.

"I have finally refined another batch of Foundation Establishment Pills, and I will try to build the foundation again soon. This time, there shouldn't be any problems, I should be able to succeed in building the foundation. But there is one thing that bothers me.

That is the death of Yuan Gangzi. The last time he joined forces with the top Qi Condensation cultivators from He Mountain Dao and others was to kill Lin Fei. What's the result? They all died!

If Lin Fei and Nine Profound Sect are not removed, where is the prestige of our Guardian Primordial Mountain? To deal with the Nine Profound Sect, there is no need for me to build the foundation successfully before making a move.

Yuan Xingzi, Yuan Chenzi. You two bring the two magic treasures 'Heavenly Thunder' and 'Earthly Evil' of our sect, go and level the Nine Profound Sect, and kill Lin Fei! I hope to hear the good news of you wiping out the Nine Profound Sect when I finish building the foundation!"

"Yes, Grand Elder!"

So, Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi immediately went down to get the two treasures. These were the treasured items of Guardian Primordial Mountain!

To be able to be called a magical treasure, it must be of the Foundation Establishment level.

With these two magical treasures, leveling the Nine Profound Sect would be easy. It's also because there was no deterrent from the royal supreme elder, Guardian Primordial Mountain would be so unscrupulous.

Not only Guardian Primordial Mountain. At this moment, He Mountain Dao also received the news from Chang City.

"Hahaha, the old bastard of the royal family is finally dead! We, He Mountain Dao, closed the mountain because of the old bastard. Humph, we have become a laughingstock of the immortal sects, all because of Lin Fei and the Nine Profound Sect.

"He Yuanzi, I command you to take our He Mountain Dao's treasure, the magical treasure Mountain River Seal, to destroy the Nine Profound Sect and kill Lin Fei!"

"Yes, master!"

He Yuanzi took the command and left. He was a top-notch Qi Condensation cultivator of the eleventh level. Plus, he had the Mountain River Seal bestowed by He Mountain Dao. Below the Foundation Establishment level, it was hard to meet an opponent. To kill a mere martial arts Master and destroy the Nine Profound Sect, wasn't that easy?

So, He Yuanzi, with a group of disciples from He Mountain Dao, carrying the magical treasure of the Mountain River Seal, descended the mountain in a grand manner.

......

Bibo River.

The river was calm, with blue water and blue sky. Occasionally, fish would jump out of the water. Lin Fei was standing on the bank at this moment.

"Crossing Bibo River, it's not far from Nine Profound Sect. Bibo River has no ferry, if it was in the past, it would require a detour. But I need to return to the Nine Profound Sect and prepare for the Foundation Establishment as soon as possible. I have to save a little time. It seems that I have to walk on the water directly and cross the Bibo River."

Lin Fei had the ability to walk on water with Saber Qi. Lin Fei had gone to Saber City using Saber Qi to walk on the water. However, that would consume too much Saber Qi.

But at that time, Saber City was not far away. It wouldn't consume too much Saber Qi. But crossing the Bibo River, it's not easy.

But, today's Lin Fei is much different from when he went to Saber City. Now, Lin Fei's Saber Qi had reached great perfection!

What's more important, Lin Fei's physical body had also reached perfection. He was impervious to saber and gun and immune to fire and water.

What's more, those who reached perfection in their physical body could walk on water without sinking!

"Swoosh".

Lin Fei took a step forward. He wanted to see what it was like to walk on water. So, Lin Fei's foot directly stepped on the water's surface.

This time, Lin Fei did not use his Saber Qi. When his feet stepped on the water's surface, a miraculous thing happened.

Lin Fei's legs felt as if they were stepping on soft cotton, they didn't sink. Even Lin Fei was shocked by this.

One step, two steps, three steps...

Soon, Lin Fei was striding forward. On the river surface, he was striding along briskly.

"This...this is walking on water... It's incredible. Once the physical body reaches perfection, it will display all kinds of incredible abilities."

Lin Fei step by step, walked on the water surface. It immediately drew a lot of attention.

Many ignorant people, even started kneeling and praying by the river bank, thinking they had encountered a deity.

Lin Fei shook his head. He couldn't really blame these people for being ignorant. Weren't his current skills the same as the gods in the legends?

"Martial arts can lead to divinity..."

Lin Fei thought of a phrase. It seemed to describe his current state quite aptly. Soon, Lin Fei crossed the Bibo River and arrived at the opposite bank.

At this time, a dozen knights appeared on the opposite bank. Each one of them looked at Lin Fei, their faces showing a trace of astonishment.

After all, Lin Fei crossed the river as if he was strolling in a courtyard. This was extremely shocking for anyone.

However, the leader still asked loudly, "May I ask if you are 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Master Lin Fei?"

"Hmm? You know me?"

Lin Fei looked at their attire. He knew they were people from the Great Chang court.

"Master Lin, we are the secret guards of the South King Mansion. Ordered by the princess, we came to wait for you near the Nine Profound Sect. Here is a letter from the princess. Master Lin Fei will know once you see it."

Then, these secret guards respectfully handed over a letter to Lin Fei. Lin Fei opened it and read it. The letter was indeed written by Princess Ling Yao. There was only one simple sentence on it.

"The Supreme Elder is dead, Nine Profound Sect is in danger, leave quickly!"

Few words, but they contained a lot of information.

"Swoosh".

Lin Fei suddenly raised his head.

"Nine Profound Sect is in danger! Tell me, what happened to Nine Profound Sect?"

Lin Fei's eyes were fixed on these secret guards. Since they were stationed at the foot of the Nine Profound Sect, they must know what happened to the Nine Profound Sect.

"Master Lin Fei, Qi cultivator disciples from He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, carrying the treasures of their sects, are rushing towards Nine Profound Sect. If you go back to Nine Profound Sect now, I'm afraid..."

The secret guard didn't finish his sentence. Obviously, going back to Nine Profound Sect now was not a wise choice.

"He Mountain Dao, Guardian Primordial Mountain. I'll go up the mountain and wait for them!"

In the next moment, Lin Fei's saber energy exploded. The entire person, like a phantom, instantly burst out dozens of meters, rushing towards Nine Profound Sect.

168. The Saber Light that Pierces Through Heaven and Earth

In the Nine Profound Sect, the ground was littered with bodies. At this moment, countless disciples had gathered together. Their eyes filled with a hint of hatred, staring intensely at the two groups of people in front of them.

One group was Qi Condensation disciples from the Guardian Primordial Mountain, led by Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi. Each of them held a magical weapon in their hands, "Heavenly Thunder" and "Earthly Evil".

The Heavenly Thunder was invincible, sharp, and unstoppable, even mountains could be collapsed. The Earthly Evil would cover the sky and earth once it came out, whoever touches it would die. Forget about martial artists, even Qi Condensation disciples would keep as far away as possible.

The other group was Qi Condensation disciples from He Mountain Dao led by He Yuanzi, holding a magical weapon "Mountain River Seal".

Once it was unleashed, the Mountain River Seal seemed to carry the weight of a mountain and river, mighty and overwhelming. Once it strikes down, whether martial arts Masters or Qi Condensation disciples, all would be smashed into a pulp.

Any defense of the Nine Profound Sect, in front of the Mountain River Seal, all seemed so fragile.

At this moment, all martial artists of the Nine Profound Sect, including the three martial arts Masters, were all gathered together now. The Nine Profound Sect only had three martial arts Masters in total. Among them, Grand Elder Zhao Kongming was the strongest.

After all, Zhao Kongming had already comprehended the Sword Intent. Zhao Kongming's Sword Intent, when dealing with some high-level Qi Condensation disciples, could still be somewhat effective. But against top-level Qi Condensation disciples like He Yuanzi, Yuan Xingzi, and Yuan Chenzi, it was of no use.

"Zhao Kongming, Lin Fei is your disciple, hand him over. Otherwise, the Nine Profound Sect will not escape destruction."

He Yuanzi spoke indifferently. Even though he had killed his way to the Nine Profound Sect, so far, he had not seen Lin Fei. He thought that the Nine Profound Sect might have "hidden" Lin Fei. After all, Lin Fei had great potential. It's possible for the Nine Profound Sect to protect Lin Fei.

"That's right, Zhao Kongming, if you don't hand over Lin Fei, are you intending to have the entire Nine Profound Sect be buried with Lin Fei?"

Yuan Xingzi also spoke. He and He Mountain Dao's He Yuanzi actually did not have prior contact. But He Yuanzi arrived before the Guardian Primordial Mountain.

Moreover, they had also sent top-level Qi Condensation disciples to surround and kill Lin Fei last time. So they were familiar with each other.

Besides, this time, their goal was the same. Not only to kill Lin Fei but also to destroy the entire Nine Profound Sect. So they simply teamed up.

Before finding Lin Fei, Guardian Primordial Mountain, and He Mountain Dao were not in such a hurry to destroy Nine Profound Sect, they even had it all planned out.

If Lin Fei is not here, then they would use the Nine Profound Sect as a threat, and let Lin Fei return to the Nine Profound Sect himself. In short, they had many means.

Without the check and balances of the Great Chang royal family, without the royal family's supreme elder suppressing the world, these immortal sect Qi Condensation disciples were completely unscrupulous. They held an absolute advantage, they had plenty of ways to deal with Lin Fei.

Zhao Kongming glanced at the two Grand Elders by his side.

He chuckled and said, "Old Li, Old Bai, after so many years, I didn't expect that we three old fellows would have to fight shoulder to shoulder again."

"Haha, Zhao Kongming, when you were young, you made a name for yourself as 'Empty Abyss Sword' in the martial world. Back then, your temper was quite hot. How come you have become so motherly now that you're old?"

"That's right, Old Zhao, since our ancestor founded the sect when has our Nine Profound Sect ever bowed its head? We, as martial artists, fight against heaven and earth, and die without regret!"

"Even if we die, as long as there is a disciple of Nine Profound Sect, our sect can still be rebuilt!"

"Remembering the past, our founder was invincible in the world. You Qi cultivators from the immortal sects, how dare you be so presumptuous?"

"Hahaha, indeed. Forget about our founder, even Elder Lin Fei can kill Qi Condensation disciples as easily as killing chickens!"

The three Grand Elders, martial arts Masters at this moment, showed no fear. Instead, they openly mocked.

"How presumptuous! You're nearing death and still dare to be stubborn! Good, then I'll smash each of you into a pulp, then deal with Lin Fei. Mountain River Seal, kill!"

He Yuanzi was extremely furious. Whenever Lin Fei was mentioned, He Mountain Dao was the most furious. Because, time and again, Lin Fei had killed too many disciples of He Mountain Dao.

In fact, Lin Fei's reputation as the "Immortal Slayer Saber" was built on the bodies of He Mountain Dao's disciples, and became famous in Great Chang. This was simply a great disgrace to He Mountain Dao.

"Hum".

He Yuanzi directly threw a small seal from his hand into the air and spiritual power surged into it.

"Whoosh".

The Mountain River Seal expanded with the wind, emitting a grayish glow. In the blink of an eye, it went from a small seal to a covering the sky and earth, like a mountain, hovering in the air.

Of course, it wasn't as heavy as a real mountain. But even so, this was already extremely astonishing. This was a magical treasure! It could change size as desired and had all sorts of incredible powers. It was many times stronger than magical artifacts. Once a Qi cultivator possessed a magical treasure, their strength would be vastly different from before.

Looking at the Mountain River Seal in the air, Zhao Kongming and the three innate elders glanced at each other. They could all see the determination in each other's eyes!

"Under my Mountain River Seal, who in your Nine Profound Sect can resist? Martial artists, in the end, are merely nobodies, unable to withstand a single blow! You were born to be stepped under our Qi cultivators' feet!"

He Yuanzi's body stirred with spiritual power. His robes fluttered, moving without wind. His aura was incredibly strong. Especially with the Mountain River Seal enhancing his aura.

In front of such a magical treasure, martial artists, even innate martial artists were indeed very insignificant. Like ants.

"Whoosh".

Zhao Kongming made his move. His fierce sword intent surged to the sky. A terrifying sword light viciously slashed toward He Yuanzi. He knew that he could not shake the Mountain River Seal. But He Yuanzi was different. He Yuanzi was just a Qi Condensation cultivator. He wasn't at the Foundation Establishment stage. His sword could injure him.

"Futile struggle. Mountain River Seal, fall!"

He Yuanzi didn't even glance at Zhao Kongming. He directly controlled the Mountain River Seal to fall toward Zhao Kongming.

"Boom".

Instantly, the Mountain River Seal fell directly. Zhao Kongming's sword light dissipated inch by inch. He could only watch the Mountain River Seal, as big as a mountain, fall onto his head. All the Nine Profound Sect disciples had bloodshot eyes.

"Hahaha, Old Zhao, you can't go before us. Let's go together!"

Instantly, the two Grand Elders also burst out with Innate True Qi. They directly rushed to Zhao Kongming's side, raised their fists, and viciously smashed towards the Mountain River Seal overhead.

"Bang".

However, the two innate martial artists were simply unable to shake the Mountain River Seal.

"The three of us, let's die together."

The three martial arts Masters looked at each other. They also showed a trace of a smile on their faces, quietly waiting for the Mountain River Seal to fall.

"Whoosh".

Suddenly, from the corner of Zhao Kongming's eye, seemed to see a familiar saber light. That saber light shook the heavens as if it pierced through the sky and earth. It stretched across the void and fierce aura swept across the entire sky.

"That's..."

Zhao Kongming's eyes slowly widened as if he had thought of something. His expression showed a hint of joy.

169. Saber Breaks the Magic Treasure

Saber energy!

One thousand meters high saber energy!

And, it was emanating an extremely familiar aura.

He's back!

Lin Fei is back!

At this moment, all the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect were overjoyed to tears.

"It's Grand Elder Lin, it must be Grand Elder Lin returning!"

"Saber energy, this is Grand Elder Lin's unique saber energy!"

"Grand Elder Lin's saber energy is too terrifying. It pierces through the sky and earth. The saber intent it emits makes me feel like I'm suffocating."

"A one thousand meters high saber energy, Grand Elder Lin has become stronger again!"

At this moment, not just Zhao Kongming, in fact, even the ordinary disciples of the Nine Profound Sect knew that Lin Fei had returned.

Lin Fei's signature saber energy pierces through the heavens and earth, vast and overwhelming, rolling in. That was impossible to hide. Moreover, Lin Fei seemed to have no intention of hiding his figure.

"Hm? Lin Fei..."

He Yuanzi felt a terrifying force behind him. A terrifying saber intent directly rolling towards him. That terrifying power even made him feel like his body was being cut into pieces. That was the feeling of death! It made He Yuanzi's scalp numb. His whole body shivering.

"Mountain River Seal!"

He Yuanzi immediately withdrew the Mountain River Seal. Although, as long as his Mountain River Seal was pressed down, it could definitely crush Zhao Kongming and the other two.

But what's the point?

Just three innate martial artists. As long as Lin Fei was dealt with, he could kill these three innate martial artists at any time. For these three innate martial artists, he would have to face the risk of being killed by Lin Fei. Of course, He Yuanzi wouldn't be so unwise!

"Whoosh".

The next moment, He Yuanzi turned around abruptly. At the same time, the Mountain River Seal also quickly turned into a stream of light. Overwhelmingly, it howled towards the saber light that pierced through the sky and earth behind him.

At this moment, under that saber light that pierced through the sky and earth, there indeed was a figure, with every step spanning dozens of meters, step by step, he walked towards the gate of the Nine Profound Sect. The Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei finally returned!

Lin Fei looked at the Mountain River Seal that was howling towards him, looking like a small mountain. He had a vague understanding. This was not a magical artifact but a magic treasure!

However, what if it was a magic treasure?

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

The next moment, Lin Fei replaced his hand with a saber and slashed fiercely toward the Mountain River Seal.

"Boom".

In the void, the one thousand meters high saber energy instantly descended from the sky, carrying the momentum of heaven's collapse. One slash landed on the Mountain River Seal and collided fiercely with this treasure of the He Mountain Dao.

"Bang".

Immediately, the two forces collided. The terrifying shockwave swept in all directions. Endless saber energy, wherever it passed, everything was leveled!

The huge Mountain River Seal was actually sent flying back by this one slash from Lin Fei. Even He Yuanzi couldn't help but shudder.

The spiritual power in his body was constantly surging as if he had been backlashed. He clapped his hands together and use spiritual power to stabilize the Mountain River Seal.

"What an 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei!"

He Yuanzi's eyes narrowed slightly. He looked somewhat uncertainly at a figure in the distance.

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei!

This name was now well-known. Not only in the martial arts world. In the Immortal Sects as well, it was also well-known.

Even top Qi Condensation cultivators like He Yuanzi actually felt quite wary of Lin Fei. This was the deterrence of "reputation" or "infamous reputation".

"Hmph, so what if you are the 'Immortal Slayer Saber'? Last time, the Five Directions Killing Array couldn't kill you. But this time, the headmaster has bestowed upon me the magic treasure Mountain River Seal!

The magic treasure is Foundation Establishment level power, you are just a martial artist, even if the founder of the Nine Profound Sect were to reincarnate, what about it?

You can't do anything to me. Under the Mountain River Seal, I don't know how many Martial Grand Masters have been crushed to death. Today, not only will I kill you, but I will also level the entire Nine Profound Sect!"

He Yuanzi was high-spirited. Even though the previous strike, the Mountain River Seal failed to crush Lin Fei's saber energy. But how many saber energies could Lin Fei have? He believed that with the Mountain River Seal in hand, he was invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm!

However, as his words fell. He Yuanzi realized something seemed a bit off.

Lin Fei's eyes were extremely calm. He just stood quietly on the spot. His gaze seemed as if he was looking at a cold corpse and the gazes of the others around him also carried a hint of fear.

"Senior Brother He Yuanzi, quickly look at the... the Mountain River Seal, it seems to have cracked...."

A disciple's face was full of horror and he was reminding He Yuanzi aloud.

"Huh?"

Only then did He Yuanzi take a closer look. He looked at the Mountain River Seal.

At this moment, there were countless patterns on the Mountain River Seal, dense and covering the entire Mountain River Seal.

Those were runes!

Each rune was very mysterious. It was inscribed by a Foundation Establishment True Person by hand.

It was these runes that allowed the Mountain River Seal to possess the terrifying power of a large mountain.

But now, those mysterious runes had actually begun to crack and the number of cracks was increasing. Densely packed, like a spider web.

In an instant, He Yuanzi's face turned deathly white.

"It's impossible, the Mountain River Seal is a magic treasure, it was refined by a Foundation Establishment True Person, comparable to the power of Foundation Establishment.

Without reaching the level of Foundation Establishment power, how could it possibly break a magic treasure? Our He Mountain Dao's Mountain River Seal is not just any Foundation Establishment magic treasure..."

He Yuanzi immediately mobilized the spiritual power within his body. Handprint after handprint, he crazily imprinted onto the Mountain River Seal, trying to stimulate the power of the Mountain River Seal.

"Crack".

But the next moment, the Mountain River Seal finally couldn't hold on anymore.

"Crack, crack".

One after another, cracks appeared on the Mountain River Seal. Each one was larger than the last, shocking to the eye. Even the aura of the Mountain River Seal was flickering continuously, fading in and out, gradually becoming dim and lightless as if in the next moment, the aura would completely disappear.

"No..."

He Yuanzi's spiritual power erupted completely, trying to save the Mountain River Seal. But it was already too late.

From the moment he activated the Mountain River Seal and forcefully collided head-on with Lin Fei's one thousand meters high saber energy, the fate of the Mountain River Seal was already sealed.

"Boom".

When the last strand of aura from the Mountain River Seal disappeared, the enormous Mountain River Seal instantly collapsed, transforming into piece after piece of rock, falling to the ground.

"Boom".

The Mountain River Seal itself was refined from a mountain peak. It was the Foundation Establishment True Person of He Mountain Dao, who used his heaven and earth penetrating spiritual power to summon a mountain peak, exhausting endless effort, to finally refine this treasure. But now, this magic treasure shattered into pieces and completely collapsed!

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei strongly returned to the Nine Profound Sect. One thousand meters high saber energy. One slash shattered the Treasure Mountain River Seal!

For a time, the entire Nine Profound Sect was silent. Whether it was martial artists from the Nine Profound Sect, or cultivators from He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, were silent, as if they couldn't believe what was happening before their eyes.

"One slash shatters a magic treasure. Lin Fei, have you reached the Saint-level?"

Zhao Kongming looked at Lin Fei with fiery eyes. His expression was filled with a trace of shock that was hard to believe!

170. Immune to all poisons, impervious to all spells

Martial Saint!

At this moment, these two words appeared in everyone's minds and Zhao Kongming, couldn't help but ask.

Everyone knew a magic treasure was equivalent to the power of the Foundation Establishment.

Below Foundation Establishment, let alone shattering a magic treasure with a single saber strike, even if someone could resist a single strike from a magic treasure would be worth recording. Even the founder of Nine Profound Sect and the top Qi Condensation realm cultivator, couldn't handle a magic treasure.

However, Lin Fei had done it. That huge one thousand meters high saber energy, hovering in the void. It was much stronger than the previous hundreds of meters high saber energy. It had already exceeded the limit of a Martial Arts Grandmaster. Therefore, Zhao Kongming asked this question.

Everyone's eyes were on Lin Fei. Especially the Qi cultivators of He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain. All of them looked at Lin Fei in disbelief.

Martial Master and Martial Saint.

Although both were martial artists, these were two different concepts. Once a martial artist reached Foundation Establishment and became a Martial Saint, he would be even more terrifying than a typical Foundation Establishment True Person!

"Martial Saint?"

Lin Fei shook his head and said calmly, "I haven't reached Foundation Establishment, nor have I become a Martial Saint. However, dealing with these Qi Condensation stage cultivators shouldn't be a problem.

He Mountain Dao, Guardian Primordial Mountain, you were looking for me, right? I am here now. Today, my saber will begin its slaughter!"

Lin Fei exuded a cold killing intent. His heart was also filled with vast killing intent. If he had returned just a few hours later, perhaps the Nine Profound Sect would have ceased to exist.

How could Lin Fei not be terrified? How could he not have a killing intent?

"Lin Fei, you destroyed the magic treasure of my He Mountain Dao. Not only will you die, but Nine Profound Sect, and your Lin family, will also all die! All disciples of He Mountain Dao, form the formation!"

He Yuanzi gritted his teeth. His body was also filled with killing intent. The Mountain River Seal shattered. That was the magic treasure of He Mountain Dao! It was even more precious than him. But now it had been destroyed by Lin Fei.

If Lin Fei didn't die, if Nine Profound Sect didn't perish, how would he explain to He Mountain Dao? Therefore, the current He Yuanzi wished he could slash Lin Fei a thousand times!

Thus, the many disciples of He Mountain Dao quickly formed a formation.

Without the Mountain River Seal, there were still many disciples of He Mountain Dao and there was He Yuanzi, a top Qi Condensation realm cultivator.

Once they formed a formation, they might have the power to fight against Lin Fei! Of course, He Yuanzi was very clear Lin Fei was the "Immortal Slayer Saber" and he could shatter the Mountain River Seal.

If it was just the disciples of He Mountain Dao, he wouldn't be so tough. He might turn around and run. However, there were people from Guardian Primordial Mountain here, and there were two magic treasures from Guardian Primordial Mountain!

"Dao friends Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Gangzi. You have also seen it, this Lin Fei can shatter even the Mountain River Seal. If Lin Fei is not eliminated, he will surely leave endless troubles!

Do we have to wait for a Foundation Establishment True Person to make a move? If our two Immortal sects join hands, we can definitely kill Lin Fei!"

He Yuanzi loudly said to the people of Guardian Primordial Mountain. Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi looked at each other.

Just now, Lin Fei had shattered He Mountain Dao's Mountain River Seal with a single saber, which really scared them a bit. Being able to shatter a magic treasure with a single saber, wasn't that a Martial Saint?

However, Lin Fei later denied it himself. Lin Fei was not a Martial Saint!

Moreover, the whole Great Chang was now devoid of exotic beasts. All top Qi Condensation cultivators knew this.

No martial artist could reach Foundation Establishment and become a Martial Saint.

Lin Fei, with the body of a Martial Master, shattered He Mountain Dao's magic treasure, the Mountain River Seal. This was truly astonishing.

Just as He Yuanzi said, if Lin Fei was not eliminated, endless troubles would ensue in the future!

Besides, they brought two magic treasures from Guardian Primordial Mountain down the mountain.

If they returned without any achievements, once the Grand Elder succeeded in Foundation Establishment, wouldn't they be punished?

Even more so, their magic treasures weren't like the Mountain River Seal of He Mountain Dao. They didn't need to confront Lin Fei head-on.

"Take action!"

In the next moment, Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Gangzi had made up their minds. Moreover, the two top Qi Condensation cultivators took action together.

When they were dealing with the Nine Profound Sect before, they were watching the show. They basically wouldn't take action.

Even if they did, it was just a casual shot from one person. But now, the two of them took action together. They directly activated the two magic treasures.

This showed how much they valued Lin Fei. After all, the reputation of the "Immortal Slayer Saber" wasn't just for show. It was earned through killing!

"Heavenly Thunder."

A blue bead appeared in Yuan Xingzi's hand. It didn't look very impressive. However, when his spiritual power poured into the blue bead, a thunderbolt condensed in the void.

"Boom."

Lightning struck, aiming unerringly for Lin Fei.

Not just Yuan Xingzi but also Yuan Chenzi produced a white porcelain bottle, twisting off the cap.

From within seeped a wisp of greyish-black mist, Yuan Chenzi channeled his spiritual power and blew hard against the escaping greyish-black mist from the bottle.

Instantaneously, the greyish-black mist shot out of the bottle, increasing in volume, and it spread throughout the void. This was the "Earthly Evil."

Upon contact with the human body, it would corrode flesh and bone. In the blink of an eye, it could reduce the human body to a heap of bleached bones. Even the Innate True Qi of a martial arts Master would find it hard to resist.

Two magical treasures. Heavenly Thunder and Earthly Evil, attacking simultaneously.

He Yuanzi also arranged his He Mountain disciples in a formation, pooling the spiritual power of dozens of Qi Condensation disciples. He released a series of talismanic scrolls. The scrolls pulsated with spiritual power, subtly forming a great net.

The net continuously contracted, attempting to trap Lin Fei within.

Three methods, three top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, and two magical treasures, simultaneously attacking Lin Fei!

It seemed Lin Fei had nowhere to escape, no means to evade!

However, Lin Fei stood his ground, entirely unmoving. He raised his head, seeing the Heavenly Thunder descend.

"Is it true Heavenly Thunder? That is the power of the natural world. How could a Qi Condensation cultivator, a single magical treasure hope to control it?

It is nothing but a strand of thunderous energy. And this talismanic net, does it hope to ensnare me?"

Lin Fei took a deep breath. The Saber Qi within his body no longer held back. It exploded in full force.

"Boom."

In the void, Lin Fei's saber energy formed a sky-high saber reaching one thousand meters. Furthermore, an invisible "saber momentum" shrouded all the Qi Condensation cultivators.

This was the momentum of the Heavenly Saber! Though it could not match the true saber momentum, even if it could suppress the opponent's strength by ten or twenty percent, it was utterly terrifying!

"What sort of power is this?"

For a moment, shock colored the faces of He Yuanzi, Yuan Xingzi, and Yuan Chenzi. They felt as if they were being oppressed by an invisible force. This was beyond their comprehension. Neither saber energy nor saber intent seemed to possess such power.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

The next moment, at Lin Fei's mental command, the one thousand meters high saber energy slashed downwards in a grand display.

The sky-high saber in the void finally moved. As the Heavenly Saber congealed, they only felt an awe-inspiring heavenly majesty. But once the Heavenly Saber slashed down, in these Qi cultivators' eyes, it seemed as if the sky was collapsing!

Their senses, seemed to discard everything else, leaving only the Heavenly Saber in the void. The saber carried with the momentum of the heavens falling, slicing down relentlessly!

"Boom."

The immense Heavenly Thunder was severed directly by Lin Fei's massive saber energy. The endless saber energy constantly entwined and clashed with the remaining force of the Heavenly Thunder. The Heavenly Thunder had yet to reach Lin Fei but was already obliterated by the saber energy.

"Crash."

At last, the heavenly saber plummeted. He Yuanzi along with dozens of disciples formed a rune-script web, and it directly clashed with the heavenly saber...

Even though nearly half of the saber energy of the heavenly saber had been consumed by the heavenly thunder, could it really be stopped by the mere rune-script web?

"Thwack."

In an instant, the rune-script web shattered. The heavenly saber ferociously plummeted. Saber energy surged mightily. Countless Qi Condensation disciples wanted to use their spiritual power against the saber energy, which seemed to have no effect at all. Their bodies were torn apart by the saber energy in a flash.

Only three of the topmost Qi cultivators, leveraging their abundant spiritual power, could slightly resist. Yet, even so, they were exceedingly disheveled.

"Crack."

The heavenly saber fell. The saber energy dissipated. The ground was cleaved, a gigantic rift left behind, as if it would split the entire land into two.

He Yuanzi, Yuan Xingzi, and Yuan Chenzi, at this moment, exchanged glances. From the other's gaze, they saw fear and shock.

Was this the power of a martial artist? Was this the power of a martial arts master?

It was even more terrifying than their magic treasures.

"Ssst."

However, Yuan Chenzi's face suddenly lit up with joy.

"It's done! Hahaha, my 'Earthly Evil Qi' has stealthily risen from beneath the ground, binding itself to Lin Fei. The Earthly Evil Qi corrodes bones and souls, Lin Fei will undoubtedly die!"

Everyone was slightly taken aback. Then, there was ecstatic jubilation. Yes, the Heavenly Thunder was broken, the rune-script web was broken. Lin Fei's saber energy was indeed formidable and able to annihilate heavenly thunder and sever the rune-script web.

Yet, it could not eradicate the Earthly Evil Qi. After all, the Earthly Evil Qi was inherently gaseous. It could even sneak into the ground, making it impossible to guard against.

"Whoosh."

Everyone immediately looked toward Lin Fei. Sure enough, in the spot where Lin Fei stood, from the ground, a cloud of gray-black gas erupted, quickly enveloping Lin Fei.

Lin Fei's Saber Qi was rapidly corroding. Saber Qi, a form of Innate True Qi, which could not resist the Earthly Evil Qi. After all, the Earthly Evil Qi was a particularly toxic force. Once afflicted with the Earthly Evil Qi, flesh and blood couldn't resist, death was inevitable!

"Sssst."

Lin Fei's saber energy was quickly corroded by the Earthly Evil Qi. The Earthly Evil Qi, finally covered Lin Fei entirely, starting to corrode Lin Fei's skin.

Lin Fei, however, remained unmoved. He even stretched out his hand. His own fair hand was covered in gray-black Earthly Evil Qi. It looked exceedingly ferocious and unsightly.

"So, this is Earthly Evil Qi?"

Lin Fei, step by step, slowly walked toward He Yuanzi and the others. From his body, there emerged a faint golden glow.

At the same time, a peculiar, refreshing fragrance emanated from Lin Fei's body. This sight had everyone wide-eyed as if they couldn't believe what was happening. Why wasn't the Earthly Evil Qi affecting Lin Fei?

"Body emanates a fragrance, pure and dust-free, skin like a baby's... This is a sign of physical perfection! Physical perfection, also known as the Golden Body! Immune to all poisons, impervious to all spells. Even the Earthly Evil Qi can't harm those with physical perfection. But, Great Chang no longer has any exotic beasts. How could you attain physical perfection?"

He Yuanzi, seeing this scene, had a flash of inspiration. It seemed he thought of something, staring at Lin Fei with a face full of shock!

Physical perfection was a requirement that a martial artist must meet to build a foundation. And Lin Fei was now physically perfected.

Didn't this mean, Lin Fei was about to build the foundation?

Thinking of this, for a moment, the three topmost Qi Condensation disciples, had a blank mind, their spirits trembling.

Because this meant the Nine Profound Sect was about to birth a Martial Saint! Great Chang was about to birth a Martial Saint! The martial arts were about to prosper!

---------------------

Immune to all poisons, impervious to all spells. It's exaggerated.

171. Preparing for Foundation Establishment

"Disperse!"

With a mere thought, Lin Fei's muscles and skin incessantly trembled. Subsequently, the layer of greenish-black Earthly Evil Qi encompassing his body was directly shattered by him.

Only at this moment did Lin Fei truly comprehend the significance of purity, and imperviousness to a myriad of poisons. Indeed, the perfection of the physical body was not as straightforward as he had imagined. The perfection of the physical body, in itself, was a lofty achievement.

Rebirth from the old, was this an insignificant feat?

Almost since the commencement of perfecting the physical body, the life strata of a martial artist became fundamentally different from those of common folk, or even Qi Condensation cultivators.

"Retreat!"

Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi exchanged glances, and without any hesitation, they immediately retreated, fleeing in a frenzy.

Lin Fei had already attained physical perfection. Moreover, his combat power was terrifyingly potent. He hadn't yet built his foundation to become a Martial Saint, yet he could already unleash power rivaling those who had.

Even if they were currently wielding magic treasures, they were no match for Lin Fei. They must report back to the Grand Elder.

Once the Grand Elder established his foundation, they must annihilate the Nine Profound Sect and behead Lin Fei with swift unerring might. Otherwise, once Lin Fei became a Martial Saint, that would truly sow the seeds for endless calamity!

However, the first to flee were not Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi but He Yuanzi who earlier had become furiously indignant.

Even with murderous intent surging to the heavens, pledging to behead Lin Fei, He Yuanzi was the first to retreat. He Yuanzi, surprisingly, retreated even before Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi.

Regardless of the numerous disciples of the He Mountain Dao Sect still present, he spurred on his magical artifact. In a blink of an eye, he had retreated dozens of meters away.

"Escaping? It's too late!"

Lin Fei's gaze was icy cold. Instantly, the momentum of Heavenly Saber was fully unleashed. Within a radius of hundreds of meters, all fell under the dominance of his Heavenly Saber.

"Boom."

Being enveloped by the Heavenly Saber's momentum, it was as if they were suddenly shouldering a huge mountain. He Yuanzi, Yuan Xingzi, and Yuan Chenzi, among others, paused in their tracks. Their speed drastically reduced. Although it didn't come to a complete halt, their speed had slowed significantly. That was enough!

"Heavenly Saber!"

Lin Fei waved his hand. The sky full of saber energy instantly came slashing down. To deal with these top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, there was no need for one thousand meters of saber energy, even dozens of meters of saber energy, these top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators couldn't withstand.

"No......"

With a slash of saber energy, the first to perish was He Yuanzi. How could he withstand Lin Fei's saber energy without his Mountain River Seal magic treasure?

Therefore, saber energy instantaneously broke through He Yuanzi's protective magical artifact. He Yuanzi was cleaved in half, his body falling to the ground.

Then, it was Yuan Chenzi's turn. His "Earthly Evil" magic treasure was indeed venomous, but it was not essentially a defensive magic treasure after all.

When the Earthly Evil Qi failed against Lin Fei, Yuan Chenzi was left without any other means. He fell instantly under Lin Fei's saber energy, meeting the same end.

Finally, it was Yuan Xingzi's turn. His magic treasure "Heavenly Thunder" could invoke a hint of thunder energy, transforming it into the utmost yang and unyielding Heavenly Thunder.

It was indeed able to counter Lin Fei's saber energy. Therefore, he managed to escape a certain distance. However, after Lin Fei had dealt with Yuan Chenzi and He Yuanzi, his huge saber energy immediately coalesced. One thousand meters of saber energy reappeared.

"Slash!"

When one thousand meters of saber energy descended from the sky, all Yuan Xingzi could do was let out a miserable cry. He was instantaneously ground to a pulp by Lin Fei's saber energy, turning into a pool of blood and flesh.

As for the disciples of the He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, they were all slain by Lin Fei's saber energy.

In just a short time, not a single Qi cultivator from the He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain escaped, all were beheaded by Lin Fei!

Looking at the corpses strewn about, each disciple of the Nine Profound Sect seemed to be in a dream.

"A Martial Saint... is just so..."

Many murmured softly, looking at Lin Fei's figure, only one term appeared in their minds.

Peerless brilliance!

Wasn't Lin Fei's performance at this moment a display of peerless brilliance?

Killing immortal masters as if slaughtering chickens. Even top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators, even those with magic treasures, were no match for Lin Fei.

"Hahaha, with Elder Lin in our Nine Profound Sect, we shall flourish!"

"The fortune of the Nine Profound Sect, the fortune of the Great Chang Martial Dao!"

The master of the Nine Profound Sect was extremely excited at this moment, as were Zhao Kongming and the other three elders.

Their excitement and exhilaration were not solely because Lin Fei had displayed his mighty prowess, slaying three top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators and defeating the invading enemies. Rather, it was due to Lin Fei's state at this moment.

Skin as soft as a baby's, emitting a unique fragrance, pure and untainted, impervious to myriad poisons, immune to all techniques...

All in all, a myriad of extraordinary characteristics. And these characteristics all indicated one thing.

Physical perfection!

Lin Fei had already achieved physical perfection!

Only the Sect Master and the three Grand Elders understood what physical perfection represented.

It was the most crucial requirement for a martial artist to establish a foundation and become a Martial Saint!

Now that Lin Fei had achieved physical perfection, it implied that Lin Fei could attempt a foundation establishment. There was a high hope that he might become a Martial Saint!

Once Lin Fei became a Martial Saint, he would be the first Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect. In fact, he might even be the only Martial Saint in Great Chang at the moment!

Lin Fei took a step forward, arriving beside the corpses of Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi.

Although Yuan Xingzi's body had turned into a puddle of mud, Lin Fei had still retained some saber energy, without completely destroying the magic treasure "Heavenly Thunder."

Thus, with a swipe of his big hand, he grasped both the "Heavenly Thunder" and "Earthly Evil" magic treasures in his hand.

After all, even if he couldn't use two magic treasures, for Qi Condensation cultivators, they were precious items they would want to get at any cost.

It was just a pity about the Mountain River Seal. In fact, this seal was even better, especially in situations of group attack. The Mountain River Seal would have been more effective.

For instance, on the battlefield, once one applied the Mountain River Seal, regardless of whether hundreds of thousands of soldiers or even more troops, they wouldn't be able to withstand such terrifying power.

Magic treasures represent the power of the Foundation Establishment level. Only True Persons who have built their foundations could refine them. This was not a power of the mundane world.

Lin Fei put away the "Heavenly Thunder" and "Earthly Evil" magic treasures. At this point, Zhao Kongming, the Sect Master, and others had also rushed over.

"Lin Fei did you... did you really achieve physical perfection?"

Zhao Kongming was the first to ask. The other two Grand Elders and the Sect Master all focused their attention on Lin Fei with a hint of anticipation in their eyes. Although they felt that he should have achieved physical perfection, they still wanted to hear Lin Fei's answer personally.

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Yes, I have achieved physical perfection."

"Boom."

In the minds of the three Grand Elders and the Sect Master, it was as if a thunderous explosion had occurred.

Excitement!

Too much excitement!

"Hahaha, my disciple, my good disciple. You have fulfilled the wish that our founder failed to achieve. With physical perfection, you're only a step away from becoming a Martial Saint after building your foundation!"

Zhao Kongming couldn't help but laugh out loud. The Nine Profound Sect was finally going to birth a Martial Saint!

In the past, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect passed away with regret, sitting in loneliness on Ancestral Master Peak.

And now, Lin Fei, a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, finally had the opportunity to make up for the regret of the founder.

"Elder Lin, the supreme elder of the royal family has passed away. Now, the world is about to fall into chaos. Those Immortal Sects can no longer contain themselves. As for the He Mountain Dao, it's not a concern, as they won't be able to produce a Foundation Establishment True Person in a short time.

But the Guardian Primordial Mountain is different. I heard that the Grand Elder of the Guardian Primordial Mountain is currently taking Foundation Establishment Pills.

There's a high possibility that he will successfully build his foundation in the near future and become a Foundation Establishment True Person. When the Guardian Primordial Mountain makes a move then, it will definitely be a Foundation Establishment True Person."

The Sect Master spoke solemnly. He was reminding Lin Fei. Lin Fei must build his foundation and become a Martial Saint as soon as possible.

Lin Fei nodded, and calmly said, "I came back this time to prepare for Foundation Establishment. Foundation Establishment requires the spiritual qi of heaven and earth. The most spiritual qi is found on Ancestral Master Peak. Lin Miao, go and set up Spirit Gathering Formations on Ancestral Master Peak, the more the better.

Master, Sect Master, I will head to Ancestral Master Peak immediately to start it. No one is allowed to disturb me on Ancestral Master Peak until I come down voluntarily."

Lin Fei was also swift and decisive. The situation was pressing now. He couldn't afford to slowly build his foundation.

Given the current situation, only by building his foundation and becoming a Martial Saint could he protect the Nine Profound Sect!

Having given his instructions, Lin Fei's figure flashed, and he took a step, spanning tens of meters. Step by step, he walked towards Ancestral Master Peak. In a blink of an eye, he disappeared from sight.

"You must succeed in foundation establishment! Our Nine Profound Sect will definitely produce a Martial Saint!"

Zhao Kongming and others, looking in the direction of Ancestral Master Peak, had a hint of hope in their eyes.

172. Compressing Saber Qi, Birth of Saber Essence!

On Ancestral Master Peak, Lin Fei stood once again beneath the stele. The turmoil of the Nine Profound Sect did not disturb Lin Fei.

There was only Lin Fei at the peak. Lin Miao, after setting up the Spirit Gathering Formations, left Ancestral Master Peak.

On the entire Ancestral Master Peak, a total of ten Spirit Gathering Formations were set up. Hence, the spiritual qi of heaven and earth was very abundant. It almost gathered all the spiritual qi of the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei did not immediately start the foundation establishment. Instead, he quietly looked at this stele. He seemed to see in a trance that the founder of the Nine Profound Sect, under this stele, was lonely and desolate and eventually died in meditation.

The founder of the Nine Profound Sect was unable to build a foundation to become a Martial Saint leaving behind this stele. This was the regret of the founder of the Nine Profound Sect.

"Founder, your disciple will not leave any regrets!" Lin Fei said, sitting cross-legged in front of the stele.

"Let's begin..."

Lin Fei's spirit quickly immersed within his body.

True Intention Scroll!

Lin Fei rarely operated the True Intention Scroll. In general, the True Intention Scroll would operate automatically. But now, Lin Fei actively operated the True Intention Scroll.

"Hum."

The next moment, a massive amount of spiritual qi from heaven and earth surged into his meridians from the Ren and Du meridians, also known as the bridge of heaven and earth.

A large amount of spiritual qi from heaven and earth was crazily trying to transform into Innate True Qi. This process was very smooth.

Lin Fei's saber intent merged again with the Innate True Qi, transforming into Saber Qi. This was also very smooth.

In the past, Lin Fei's body had already reached its limit. Therefore, no matter how much spiritual qi he absorbed, no matter how much it transformed into Saber Qi, it couldn't increase the Saber Qi in his body by a fraction.

But now it was different. Lin Fei's fleshly body has reached perfection. His body underwent a complete transformation. Therefore, both the meridians and the limit of the body have been further enhanced. So, the Saber Qi in Lin Fei's body could still continue to increase.

Lin Fei did not rashly attempt the foundation establishment. Instead, he first raised everything within his body to the peak limit.

Time passed bit by bit. Several hours later, the Saber Qi in Lin Fei's body had increased by about another thirty percent.

With Lin Fei's current volume of Saber Qi, an increase of thirty percent was extremely terrifying.

For instance, if Lin Fei now fully utilized his Saber Qi, the condensed saber energy would likely not just be one thousand meters but closer to one thousand and five hundred meters!

Of course, that was not important. Without foundation establishment, there could never be immortality. A hundred years later, it was all just a handful of dust.

Whether it was a martial foundation establishment or an immortal foundation establishment, they were all for the purpose of achieving immortality.

Lin Fei never forgot his goal of practicing martial arts.

Immortality!

Martial arts started simple but become increasingly difficult. In comparison, immortal cultivation was tough from the beginning. After all, immortal cultivation required talent. Without talent, there's no point in discussing it.

Martial arts and immortal cultivation each had their own advantages and disadvantages.

For example, Qi cultivators could initially overpower martial artists. However, there were far fewer Qi cultivators than martial artists. And not everyone could become a Qi cultivator. Talent selection had already eliminated over ninety percent of people.

While martial artists, although initially far inferior to Qi cultivators, had the advantage of sheer numbers. No matter who, regardless of talent, could practice martial arts. Numbers were the greatest advantage of martial arts.

However, whether it was martial arts or immortal cultivation, once foundation establishment was achieved, everything became "equal".

Immortal foundation establishment results in becoming a True Person, transcending the mundane, and being above others! Martial foundation establishment results in becoming a Martial Saint, beyond the ordinary with immeasurable divine abilities!

Thus, different paths lead to the same goal. Martial arts and immortal cultivation, once foundation establishment was achieved, starting from the same line.

And, the lifespan would range from three hundred to five hundred years. As Lin Fei's Saber Qi within his body reached its limit and could no longer increase, Lin Fei began compressing his Saber Qi.

He used his saber intent, bit by bit, continuously compressed his Saber Qi. Lin Fei's Saber Qi was already very strong. Now that he wanted to compress it, the difficulty was naturally higher.

However, Lin Fei was not in a hurry. He compressed it bit by bit. Each time, he compressed only a little bit of Saber Qi.

For example, Lin Fei was now compressing about one percent of his Saber Qi. With such a small amount of Saber Qi, Lin Fei's saber intent could forcefully suppress it.

As time passed bit by bit. A wisp of Saber Qi was compressed to one-tenth of its original size. Yet, it was still Saber Qi. The more it was compressed, the harder it was to compress towards the end.

For instance, after a wisp of Saber Qi was reduced to one-tenth of its original size, it became very difficult to compress. One needed to withstand a huge backlash.

Moreover, during this compression process, Lin Fei's meridians would also be severely impacted. If his physical body hadn't reached perfection, undergone a complete transformation, and had his meridians strengthened countless times, even this slight compression of Saber Qi could have irreversible effects on his meridians.

This was just the beginning of the foundation establishment and the pressure on the meridians had been so great. If the physical body wasn't perfect, how could one build the foundation?

Lin Fei compressed a wisp of Saber Qi down to one-tenth of its original size, however, no True Essence was born. But Lin Fei was not discouraged at all. Instead, he was very patient, continuing to compress this wisp of Saber Qi bit by bit.

One-twentieth, one-thirtieth, one-fortieth, one-fiftieth...

He didn't know how long it had passed. When Lin Fei felt that this wisp of Saber Qi had been compressed to about one percent of its original size even the wisp of Saber Qi had almost become invisible, at this moment, there was a slight tremor in Lin Fei's meridians. Immediately following, that wisp of Saber Qi actually made a "ding" sound in his meridians.

"Is this... the sound of a water droplet?"

Lin Fei focused his mind. Suddenly, he saw it. In his Dantian, there was faintly a droplet, crystal clear, about the size of a hair.

This droplet was really too small, it was almost imperceptible. Only Lin Fei's perception could sense this droplet.

However, this one droplet made Lin Fei incredibly excited.

Because this was liquid Saber Qi! When Saber Qi became liquid, it transformed from Saber Qi into Saber Essence.

This was stronger than the True Essence of ordinary Martial Saints. Because within the Saber Essence, Lin Fei's perfection-level saber intent was contained!

With the first droplet of Saber Essence, there would definitely be a second droplet of Saber Essence.

So, Lin Fei continued to compress Saber Qi. Gradually, the second droplet of Saber Essence was born.

The third droplet, the fourth droplet, the fifth droplet, the sixth droplet, the seventh droplet, the eighth droplet...

Each droplet of Saber Essence was crystal clear and looked beautiful. When countless droplets of Saber Essence came together, they formed a stream.

When the quantity of Saber Essence surpassed that of Saber Qi, the Saber Essence began to devour the remaining Saber Qi. Countless Saber Qi were devoured by the Saber Essence.

Suddenly, the amount of Saber Essence within Lin Fei's body surged. Moreover, during the process of devouring, the Saber Essence faintly formed a vortex. Not only devouring Saber Qi but also devouring the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth.

"Boom."

The entire Spiritual Qi of the Ancestral Master Peak seemed to shake. Countless martial artists paying attention to the Ancestral Master Peak at this moment felt a slight abnormality.

However, the acquired martial artists didn't know what was happening.

Only the three Martial Masters of the Nine Profound Sect could see the giant Spiritual Qi vortex forming in the sky above the Ancestral Master Peak.

Countless Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth were being devoured by the giant Spiritual Qi vortex. Not only did it involve the Nine Profound Sect, but it also drew in the elemental energy of the heavens and earth for miles around, which was rushing madly towards the peak.

"What a terrifying vortex, it can actually devour so much Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth."

"Even a hundred Martial Masters couldn't absorb so much Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth."

"It seems that Elder Lin is about to succeed!"

The three Grand Elders all looked serious, staring fixedly at the situation on Ancestral Master Peak.

Although there was a great commotion, the larger the commotion, the more settled they felt in their hearts.

Building the foundation to become a Martial Saint was a breakthrough in bodily shackles, an upgrade of life. As the condensers of Qi put it, it was seizing the natural resources of heaven and earth, reversing Yin and Yang, and breaching life and death.

How could there be no commotion?

No one dared to disturb Lin Fei, they could only wait quietly at the foot of the peak.

---------------

Dantian: A place to store energy, near the belly.

173. Remolding the Dao Body, Achieving Martial Saint! Walking in the air!

One day, two days, three days...

The Spiritual Qi vortex on Ancestral Master Peak had persisted for a full three days.

In these three days, Lin Fei devoured countless Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth. Was it equivalent to the Spiritual Qi absorbed by hundreds of Martial Masters? Or even the Spiritual Qi of thousands of Martial Masters? Lin Fei himself wasn't clear.

But he could feel that as the Saber Essence in his body kept expanding, his body underwent another transformation. Yes, it was still a transformation of the flesh. And it was a second rebirth!

The first rebirth was when Lin Fei's physical body reached perfection. And now, the second rebirth was Lin Fei's Saber Essence.

Countless Saber Essence, along with the meridians, actually permeated into the blood, muscles, bones, and every inch of the body.

Lin Fei's blood was no longer merely bright red, but bright red with a hint of silver. That was the color of the Saber Essence. Saber Essence was silver-white.

With the infiltration of the Saber Essence, Lin Fei felt that this body's transformation was even greater than the last time. Moreover, he could clearly feel the rich life aura starting to emit from within his body.

In the dark, Lin Fei felt that perhaps, that was the lifespan! Life aura represented lifespan. Once the foundation was successfully built, it would break the shackles of life, and lifespan would increase. Foundation Establishment True Persons and Martial Saints could live for five hundred years!

However, this was not the end. Lin Fei quietly experienced the continuous "remodeling" of his body by the Saber Essence inside his body.

Back in the Northern Territory, Liu Yibai also mentioned that Foundation Establishment was very important. What was built was the foundation of the Martial Dao!

And the infiltration of True Essence or Saber Essence into the body was actually a process of remolding the body.

The human body, usually during gestation in the mother's womb, forms the body. How a person's body was formed at that time was closely related to their parents. But this was uncontrollable.

Foundation Establishment, however, was actually the second remolding of the body. This time, the remolding of the body was controllable.

What did the True Essence look like? What did Martial Dao True Intent look like? This affected the direction of body remolding, making it completely compatible with one's True Essence and Martial Dao True Intent. This would allow the True Essence to explode with its strongest power!

The direction of body remolding was closely related to the direction of the Saber Essence. It could fully accommodate the explosion of Saber Essence. This process of remolding the body was called Remolding the Dao Body!

Whether it was Qi Cultivators building their foundations or Martial Artists doing so, the process was actually the same. Qi Cultivators build their foundations and what they remold was their Magic Body. Martial Artists build their foundations and what they remold was their Dao Body.

This process could be fast or slow and varies from person to person. It was precisely because of the need to remold the Dao Body that Lin Fei absorbs so much Spiritual Qi from heaven and earth, converted it into Saber Essence, and then integrated it into his body.

Time gradually passed. Lin Fei didn't know how long it had been.

"Swish."

Lin Fei suddenly opened his eyes. He found that the Saber Essence in his body could no longer be integrated. The Spiritual Qi vortex in the sky gradually disappeared. Everything calmed down.

"Did I make it?"

Lin Fei stretched out his hand. His hand was still fair and tender, with skin like a baby's. However, when he gently clenched his fist, an unimaginable sense of power rose in him.

Lin Fei then slowly opened his palm and lightly imprinted it on a giant stone next to him. Even without using any power from the Saber Essence, just a slight exertion of force, his palm seemed to embed into the giant stone as if it were a piece of tofu.

"That's not tofu, it's a hard giant rock! So, the problem isn't with the giant rock, it's with my hand! My hand seems to have become as sharp as a saber blade. Even without using Saber Essence, just with the Dao Body alone, I can easily blow up a Martial Grand Master!"

Lin Fei clenched his fist and smashed it into the ground.

"Boom."

The ground violently shook. It seemed as if the entire Ancestral Master Peak was shaking.

"I understand now, remolding the Dao Body is actually making the body more closely matched with the energy inside. The energy in my body is Saber Essence, which has the sharp characteristics of a saber.

Therefore, the Dao Body that I remolded subtly has the characteristics of a saber. In other words, my current Dao Body is equivalent to a peerless treasure saber..."

Lin Fei finally understood what the Dao Body was all about. Even though Liu Yibai had talked about it before, how could it be as clear as experiencing it firsthand?

Moreover, Lin Fei faintly recalled the challenge he faced against the Royal Family's Supreme Elder in the garden,

He gave it his all at the time, unleashing a terrifying two hundred and fifty meters of saber energy. But his previously unbeatable saber energy only made the Supreme Elder casually flip his palm and easily extinguished it.

At that time, there were hardly any spiritual power fluctuations on Supreme Elder. Lin Fei was utterly puzzled at the time. The Supreme Elder just explained that this was the difference between Foundation Establishment and others.

Now, Lin Fei finally understood. Even if the Supreme Elder had explained it at that time, Lin Fei probably wouldn't have understood.

The reason why the Supreme Elder was able to control the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth in the void and directly extinguished Lin Fei's saber energy without much use of his spiritual power was simple.

It was because of the Magic Body that Foundation Establishment True Person remolded!

The Magic Bodies of Foundation Establishment True Person probably had a natural affinity with the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth. Their control over the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth far exceeds the imagination of ordinary people.

At least controlling the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth in a small range was not very difficult for them. That was the function of the Magic Body.

On the other hand, martial artists condense their Dao Bodies. The Dao Body cannot control the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth, but it has incredible abilities.

For example, the Dao Body that Lin Fei was currently remolding was almost like a peerless treasure saber.

His Dao Body was the deadliest weapon. And not only that, Lin Fei also vaguely felt as if his body was very light as if he could walk in the void.

Yes, walking in the void!

Lin Fei took a deep breath, then, slowly stood up, lifted his foot, and took a step towards the void.

Lin Fei immediately felt a difference with this step. He didn't feel like he was stepping on land but stepping on air. It was as if stepping on cotton, very soft.

However, he did not step into the empty space. The Saber Essence in his body almost instinctively converged into Lin Fei's legs and it was just a part of the Saber Essence that converged into the legs. But it didn't go through the body. That is to say, it hardly consumed any Saber Essence.

"Rise!"

Lin Fei shouted lowly. Instantly, Lin Fei step by step, as if there were steps under his feet, walked into the void. The higher he walked, the smoother he walked. It was almost like instinct.

"This is the Dao Body! This is Martial Saint! Today, I have successfully built my foundation and have become a Martial Saint!"

Even though Lin Fei has always been very calm and composed, at this moment, he couldn't help but howl towards the sky. His howling sound instantly spread throughout the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei's gaze naturally could see down below all the people under the Ancestral Master Peak at a glance.

Lin Fei took step by step, walking in the air, stepping into the void. He walked down from the sky.

Under the Ancestral Master Peak, hearing Lin Fei's long howl, Zhao Kongming and the sect master, among others, immediately awakened. They looked in the direction of the Ancestral Master Peak abruptly.

But at this sight, even martial artists like Zhao Kongming and the sect master who have seen and known a lot, widened their eyes. There was a look of disbelief in their eyes.

What did they see?

Lin Fei, surprisingly, walked down the void step by step as if there were invisible stairs in the void. But, how could there be stairs in the void?

At this moment, it seemed as if their cognition was overturned. Only Zhao Kongming had a flash of insight in his mind as if he had thought of something.

"Walking in the air, stepping in the void. This is a characteristic of a Martial Saint! A martial artist builds his foundation, becomes a Martial Saint, and has all kinds of incredible means. Among them, walking in the air and stepping in the void are the most basic means! Lin Fei has become a Martial Saint!"

Zhao Kongming's body began to tremble from excitement.

A Martial Saint! The Nine Profound Sect had finally given birth to a real Martial Saint! The Great Chang had also once again given birth to a Martial Saint!

The Nine Profound Sect was going to rise! The martial arts were going to rise!

174. Desire to Slash the Foundation Establishment, Cast the Martial Saint's Reputation!

"Master, sect master."

Lin Fei stepped into the void, descending from the air. He carried an aura of faint oppression. It was as if it came from the soul, causing an unconscious pressure.

This was the pressure of life level. Upon foundation building, the life level is different. Building a foundation was transcending the ordinary, completely different from ordinary life.

"Lin Fei, have you successfully built the foundation?"

Even though everyone had their suspicions. They still wanted to hear it from Lin Fei himself.

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Master, your disciple has been successful in building the foundation and achieving the status of a Martial Saint!"

As Lin Fei's words fell, everyone's mind seemed to go blank. Excitement, jubilation, and a hint of complexity in their eyes. Various emotions churned in their hearts.

A Martial Saint!

This was a realm that countless martial artists dream of. Even the founder of the Nine Profound Sect had not taken this step. But now, Lin Fei had become a Martial Saint. This had surpassed the founder and surpassed all the predecessors of the Nine Profound Sect.

"It's the fortune of our Nine Profound Sect!"

Zhao Kongming was very excited, and so were the others. A Martial Saint's life span ranged from three hundred to five hundred years. And now, Lin Fei was still very young. Not even twenty years old.

With Lin Fei stationed at the Nine Profound Sect, the Nine Profound Sect would have a prosperous period of hundreds of years. At that time, what would the Nine Profound Sect develop into? The Grand Elders could hardly imagine.

"What's the reaction of He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain?"

Lin Fei asked calmly. He hadn't forgotten that Guardian Primordial Mountain and He Mountain Dao, these two immortal sects had attacked the Nine Profound Sect, even planning to annihilate the entire Nine Profound Sect!

"Elder Lin. He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain have made no move, which seems strange," The sect master said, frowning.

"It's not strange that He Mountain Dao has made no move. With He Yuanzi carrying the precious Mountain River Seal, it is almost the strongest force He Mountain Dao can put forth. But He Yuanzi is no match for me, He Mountain Dao has to swallow their anger! They are helpless. But it should not be the case that Guardian Primordial Mountain is silent because they are helpless.

I'm afraid the Qi Condensation perfection elder of Guardian Primordial Mountain is building his foundation. Guardian Primordial Mountain probably wants to wait for the elder to successfully build his foundation before personally taking action against our Nine Profound Sect."

Lin Fei said calmly. In just a few words, he analyzed the situation and intentions of He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain.

"Elder Lin, what do you plan to do?" The sect master asked.

Since Lin Fei said so. He must have a plan.

"Wait! He Mountain Dao, Guardian Primordial Mountain, these immortal sects with thousands of years of heritage, even the founding Emperor of the Great Chang, who swept all directions and suppressed the world, could not break the gates of these immortal sects.

This shows that these immortal sects have large formations guarding them, and even powerful magic treasures suppressing them that even a Martial Saint would find it hard to break through.

Yet, having suffered such a tremendous loss, the Guardian Primordial Mountain will not rest. Once the elders of the Guardian Primordial Mountain attain the perfection of Qi condensation and successfully establish their foundation, they will undoubtedly seek retribution.

More likely than not, the Foundation Establishment cultivator of the Guardian Primordial Mountain will personally descend from the mountain to annihilate the Nine Profound Sect! This is my opportunity.

I may not be able to breach the mountain gates of those immortal sects, but who says I can't cut down a Foundation Establishment cultivator? Hence, the news of my successful Foundation Establishment and attainment of the Martial Saint status must be immediately sealed, and no information shall be divulged. Then, we shall quietly await the arrival of the Foundation Establishment cultivator from the Guardian Primordial Mountain."

Lin Fei spoke calmly. Yet, within the hearts of Zhao Kongming, the Sect Master, and others, a storm of astonishment surged. Lin Fei's words were spoken with a tranquil demeanor, seemingly ordinary. But the content was far from it.

What does Lin Fei want to do?

He aimed to cut down a Foundation Establishment cultivator! Even as a Martial Saint, one cannot casually claim to be able to do so, can they?

If Foundation Establishment cultivators were so easily slain, the founding emperor of the beginning could have eradicated all Foundation Establishment cultivators in the past.

Yet, in truth, Foundation Establishment cultivators might not rival Martial Saints, but slaying a Foundation Establishment cultivator was a challenging task.

Furthermore, Lin Fei had only just attained Martial Saint status. How dare he make such bold claims of slaying a Foundation Establishment cultivator?

"Elder Lin, you have just established your foundation to become a Martial Saint. If you are not confident, perhaps it would be better to tread more cautiously..."

The Sect Master subtly reminded Lin Fei, that lest the Foundation Establishment cultivator from the Guardian Primordial Mountain truly arrives, only for Lin Fei had to prove not up to the challenge. That would pose a significant problem.

"Sect Master, I am well aware of the situation. In recent times, the Nine Profound Sect should refrain from any action. We merely have to wait!" Lin Fei spoke indifferently.

"We shall abide by Elder Lin's orders!" The Sect Master responded with reverence.

Now, Lin Fei was more than just a Grand Elder. He was also the first Martial Saint in the history of the Nine Profound Sect! Lin Fei's words were law within the Nine Profound Sect. He, as the Sect Master, dare not defy them.

"Master, fellow elders, I need to return to Ancestral Master Peak to consolidate my cultivation and prepare for a battle against the Foundation Establishment cultivator of the Guardian Primordial Mountain. So, forgive me I shall not linger here."

After speaking, Lin Fei turned around, Step by step, he traversed the void, returning to the Ancestral Master Peak, he vanished without a trace.

"Martial Saint..."

The Sect Master murmured under his breath, his spirit greatly composed.

"Fellows, our Nine Profound Sect is on the cusp of a prosperous era spanning several centuries. This is indeed our Nine Profound Sect's great fortune!

However, we must first resolve the issue with the Guardian Primordial Mountain. As Elder Lin suggested, we must lure the Foundation Establishment cultivator of the Guardian Primordial Mountain to the Nine Profound Sect.

Since Elder Lin has attained the Martial Saint status, let's solidify his name with the fresh blood of a Foundation Establishment cultivator!"

The Sect Master's eyes also held a flicker of fiery fervor.

Slaying a Foundation Establishment! Should Lin Fei truly achieve this feat, his prestige would undeniably skyrocket. The Nine Profound Sect would likewise gain renown throughout the world!

In these chaotic times, nothing was more shocking to the heart than the slaying of a Foundation Establishment cultivator!

...

Within the secret chamber of the Guardian Primordial Mountain.

"Hum."

Suddenly, a rich whirlpool of Spiritual Qi materialized in the air above the secret chamber. Moreover, this vortex was gushing forth copious amounts of Qi from the heavens. Even the grand Spiritual Qi gathering array surrounding the entire secret chamber began fervently accumulating Spiritual Qi.

The commotion was considerable. All the Qi condensation cultivators could see the enormous whirlpool of Spiritual Qi in the void. They all knew that direction was where the Grand Elder secluded himself, striving to establish his foundation.

"He's succeeded, he must have succeeded!"

"The Grand Elder is about to successfully establish his foundation."

"Hahaha, finally, our Guardian Primordial Mountain will witness the birth of another Foundation Establishment cultivator!"

Many Qi Condensation cultivators of the Guardian Primordial Mountain were all tremendously excited. Especially the high-level and top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators were well aware of what the birth of a Foundation Establishment cultivator signifies.

The Guardian Primordial Mountain was a thousand-year-old immortal sect. In its history, several Foundation Establishment cultivators have been born. Only a Foundation Establishment cultivator, possessed the qualification to seize sufficient benefits in these turbulent times, ensuring the prosperity of the Guardian Primordial Mountain for hundreds if not thousands of years!

The Spiritual Qi vortex in the sky lasted for three full hours.

"Boom."

The next moment, a terrifying surge of spiritual power shot skywards. The Spiritual Qi vortex in the void was instantaneously scattered.

"Rumble."

The stone door of the secret chamber opened. The Grand Elder of the Guardian Primordial Mountain slowly emerged. His gaze swept across, exuding an invisible pressure from his body, causing many Qi condensation cultivators to avert their eyes.

"Congratulations, Grand Elder, on successfully establishing your foundation and attaining the title of True Person!"

For a time, countless Qi Condensation cultivators knelt on the ground, offering their congratulations to the Grand Elder.

The Grand Elder's face showed neither joy nor sorrow but appeared very calm. He calmly stated, "Today, I have achieved true enlightenment, becoming a Foundation Establishment cultivator, I shall shelter the Guardian Primordial Mountain for hundreds of years. Where are Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi?"

The Grand Elder asked indifferently. However, there was no response from below.

"Hmm? Sect Master, where are Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi?"

The Grand Elder's face fell, his gaze fixed intently on the Sect Master. The Sect Master felt immense pressure. The Grand Elder had successfully established his foundation. Just a single look made him feel somewhat unbearable.

The Sect Master hurriedly reported, "Elder, Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi took the two treasures 'Heavenly Thunder' and 'Earthly Evil' to the Nine Profound Sect to slay Lin Fei.

However, it seems something went wrong. Both of them have not returned yet. Moreover, I also heard that He Mountain Dao had Heyuanzi with the 'Mountain River Seal' to the Nine Profound Sect, who also has not returned. I'm afraid the odds are not in our favor."

Upon hearing this, the Grand Elder became furious.

"Yuan Xingzi and Yuan Chenzi, carrying two of Guardian Primordial Mountain's magic treasures, could they actually fail? Does that Nine Profound Sect have a Martial Saint? Or did the founder of the Nine Profound Sect leave something behind for the Nine Profound Sect?"

The Grand Elder was aware of the prestige of the Founder of the Nine Profound Sect. However, no one below responded. They dared not respond. If they were to anger the Grand Elder, it would lead to big trouble.

"Forget it, since I have established my foundation, it's time for the world to know the prestige of Guardian Primordial Mountain! Now the world is in chaos, the time for Immortal Sects to take over the secular world has come.

Only by spreading the fame of Guardian Primordial Mountain can we gain enough benefits in this chaos. I will personally go down the mountain to flatten the Nine Profound Sect and spread the fame of Guardian Primordial Mountain!"

"May we follow the Grand Elder's decree!"

A group of Qi Condensation cultivators were very excited. The Grand Elder was going down the mountain. How could the Nine Profound Sect not be destroyed with a Foundation Establishment cultivator coming in person?

Finally, Guardian Primordial Mountain could flatten the Nine Profound Sect to declare to the world the prestige of Guardian Primordial Mountain!

175. Hundreds of Saber Techniques

Atop the Ancestral Master Peak, Lin Fei sat cross-legged quietly. The Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth formed a gigantic pillar that was poured into Lin Fei's body.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes. He gently shook his head and slowly said, "Too slow, the conversion efficiency of the Saber Essence is too slow. Without a Martial Saint level technique, I can only operate the Saber Essence myself, capturing the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth, and transforming it into Saber Essence.

But this efficiency is too slow! And even with such a slow efficiency, it still requires a massive amount of Spiritual Qi from heaven and earth. The amount of Spiritual Qi in the Nine Profound Sect is too little, not enough to support the cultivation of a Martial Saint."

After achieving the Martial Saint level, Lin Fei discovered it turned out that the demand for Spiritual Qi by a Martial Saint was so massive.

The location of this Nine Profound Sect was relatively good. The Spiritual Qi was abundant. However, it was not enough to satisfy Lin Fei's daily cultivation.

This was due to Lin Fei's own cultivation. He didn't practice for very long each day. If he found a Martial Saint-level technique in the future, then practicing the technique every day, every moment required a vast amount of Spiritual Qi from heaven and earth. At that time, Lin Fei was afraid the Spiritual Qi of the Nine Profound Sect would be even less sufficient.

Of course, now Lin Fei was just consolidating his Martial Saint cultivation. He hadn't thought so much yet. After all, a Martial Saint-level technique was not so easy to obtain.

"System."

Lin Fei had a thought in his heart and called up the system to check his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

Saber Intent: Perfection (Progress 5%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei's realm was still in the early stage of Martial Saint. The True Intention Scroll had disappeared. Because the True Intention Scroll was just an innate level technique. What it cultivated was also Saber Qi.

Now Lin Fei had achieved Martial Saint. What he cultivated was Saber Essence. He absorbed Spiritual Qi from heaven and earth, one step at a time, directly transforming it into Saber Essence.

The Saber Essence needed to accumulate over a long period and it took an unknown amount of Saber Essence to reach the mid-stage of Martial Saint and advance Lin Fei's martial arts cultivation.

Of course, Lin Fei wasn't too concerned about improving his cultivation right now. This was not something that could be improved in a short time. After all, he didn't even have a Martial Saint-level technique.

As for saber techniques, fist techniques, lightness techniques, etc. They could also be used with Saber Essence. This point was not affected at all. Moreover, deploying the Saber Essence, power would be even more terrifying.

After all, Saber Qi and Saber Essence were actually the same kinds of power. With the same properties, the Saber Essence was just Saber Qi that had been compressed continuously. It only formed a kind of high-density energy in the end.

"I wonder if Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai have also succeeded in establishing their foundations and have become Martial Saints?"

Lin Fei lifted his head, looking at the void outside the Nine Profound Sect. Back then, he, Liu Yibai, and Shen Lianxin went to the Northern Territory together. They killed an exotic beast together and reached physical perfection together.

If there were no accidents, Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin should have also achieved Martial Saint. If the other two had become Martial Saints, then, their saber intent and sword intent would be pretty much the same. Even if Lin Fei's saber intent was a bit stronger, there wouldn't be a qualitative difference. Unless Lin Fei's saber intent could transform into saber momentum. However, that's very difficult.

Lin Fei's current saber intent had only reached cultivation progress of 5%. To reach cultivation progress of 100%, it could then be transformed into saber momentum. Therefore, Lin Fei's only advantage was the Saber Essence. Lin Fei's Saber Essence came from the accumulation of inner power, True Qi, and Saber Qi. Each step was much stronger than martial artists of the same level. So this step-by-step accumulation had reached the present.

Therefore, Lin Fei's current Saber Essence and the True Essence of other Martial Saints might already be a huge difference. Even when Lin Fei was building his foundation, the Dao Body he remodeled also became stronger because it was close to the Saber Essence. The Dao Body and Saber Essence were Lin Fei's current advantages.

"Foundation Establishment...I wonder if my saber can cut through Foundation Establishment cultivators?"

Lin Fei murmured in a low voice. His tone was very calm. He wasn't sure of victory.

After all, the only time he competed with a real Foundation Establishment cultivator was when the Supreme Elder of the royal family had not passed away. What's more, at that time, the Supreme Elder of the royal family did not go all out and Lin Fei hadn't become a Martial Saint. Therefore, how strong a Foundation Establishment cultivator was, Lin Fei was not clear.

Now, Lin Fei's strength growth was very slow. Relying on the Saber Essence, it was unknown how long it will take to accumulate more Saber Essence. But if Lin Fei wanted to improve his strength in a short time, relying on the Saber Essence was not enough.

"Saber intent, saber momentum. Only by transforming saber intent into saber momentum. Only then can it be called a true saber saint! In three hundred years, that sword saint of the Hidden Sword Sect has definitely not cultivated sword momentum. Actually, he cannot be considered a true sword saint."

A gleam flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He was now a Martial Saint. But Lin Fei didn't just want to be a Martial Saint. He wanted to be a Saber Saint!

However, only by understanding saber momentum could he be considered a Saber Saint.

But saber momentum, how difficult is it?

So far, Lin Fei's saber intent had only increased to 5%. Afterward, there was no movement at all.

"Initially, the Heavenly Saber Art absorbed other perfection-level saber techniques, which improved its cultivation progress. The improvement of saber intent is actually the improvement of the realm of saber technique.

As long as the saber technique is stronger, the foundation of the saber technique is more profound, then the saber intent should be able to improve.

With my current realm of saber technique, I should be able to learn any saber technique at a glance. Especially with body refining and acquired level saber techniques, reaching perfection should not be a problem. Perhaps, it's time to try the Martial Arts Pavilion."

Lin Fei thought for a moment and immediately made a decision in his heart. If he wanted to challenge a Foundation Establishment cultivator, he shouldn't be here in bitter guard. He still needed to find a way to improve his strength. A martial artist wanted to improve his strength, he could only rely on various martial arts.

Therefore, Lin Fei got up. He directly walked through the air and descended from Ancestral Master Peak step by step.

Soon, Lin Fei arrived at the Martial Arts Pavilion. The Martial Arts Pavilion was still guarded by that acquired third-level elder.

Upon seeing Lin Fei, the elder immediately stood up, his expression showing a hint of excitement, he respectfully said, "Greetings Grand Elder, may I ask what martial arts you need?"

Lin Fei glanced at the elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion, nodded, and said, "Send all the saber techniques, whether they are body refining saber techniques, acquired saber techniques, or innate saber techniques, all into the training room."

"All?"

The elder was somewhat surprised. But he still promptly complied.

Lin Fei was the Grand Elder. Moreover, he had heard some rumors. It seemed that the Grand Elder in front of him was very likely to have become a Martial Saint!

The only Martial Saint in the Nine Profound Sect, even in the whole Great Chang now!

Therefore, the elder was so respectful. Lin Fei went directly to the training room.

About half an hour later. The elder had brought all the saber techniques that could be found in the Martial Arts Pavilion.

Around Lin Fei, various martial arts secrets were almost piled up like a mountain. These martial arts were all saber techniques. Among them, body refining and acquired-level saber techniques were the most especially the body refining level. It didn't involve the circulation of inner power. They were just some saber techniques. The number was as many as hundreds!

Then there were the acquired level saber techniques. The number was also huge. At least more than two hundred!

The least was the innate level saber techniques. Only a scant twenty or so.

So many saber technique secrets. Even if one wanted to read them all, it would take a lot of time. Maybe he wouldn't be able to finish reading them in a few days. However, Lin Fei did not intend to read them himself.

"Boom".

In the next moment, Lin Fei's saber intent erupted. His saber intent enveloped all the saber technique secrets in the room. At the same time, Lin Fei pointed with his finger.

A wisp of saber essence that condensed into form and condensed into a Heavenly Saber. With the appearance of the Heavenly Saber, the power of the Heavenly Saber also appeared.

Saber intent, saber essence, the momentum of the Heavenly Saber. Three forces that were closely related to the saber, at this moment, all filled this small room.

Lin Fei's gaze was calm, looking at these hundreds of saber technique secrets. At this moment, these saber technique secrets, in his eyes, were as if they were no longer rigid books and texts but a living "life".

Lin Fei and these saber technique secrets were equal. Therefore, Lin Fei also word by word, spoke to these saber technique secrets, "I have just become a Martial Saint and wish to evolve my saber intent into saber momentum. I need countless saber techniques to enhance the foundation of the saber technique. Would you like to help me evolve saber momentum?

If the saber momentum is achieved, I will be a Saber Saint! All saber techniques will be engraved in my supreme Saber Dao! By then, you will no longer be ordinary saber techniques. Instead, you will be the cornerstone of my supreme Saber Dao! If anyone is willing, they can reach perfection on their own and integrate into my saber intent."

After Lin Fei finished speaking, he did not say anything else. What should be said, he had said. And now, he could only wait quietly. Waiting for the choice of these saber techniques.

After all, no matter how strong a saber technique was, it might be lost, damaged, or incomplete.

However, once it became the cornerstone of Lin Fei's Saber Dao, then these saber techniques would exist forever in another way. Because no matter what, the Saber Dao would never be destroyed!

176. Heavenly Fire Crossing the Sky

Time passed by minute by minute. The whole room was filled with saber intent, saber essence, and the momentum of the Heavenly Saber. And around Lin Fei, hundreds of saber technique secrets, one by one were incredibly quiet, without the slightest movement.

Lin Fei himself wasn't sure whether these saber techniques would be stimulated by him After all, Lin Fei's request was to let these saber techniques self-practice to perfection, then integrate into the saber intent, help him evolve saber momentum. This was simply getting something for nothing.

Lin Fei just moved his lips. But, Lin Fei believed his proposal was also attractive to these saber techniques.

Saber techniques would last forever! The Saber Dao will never perish!

Not many saber techniques could resist such a temptation. However, the everlasting saber technique and the unperishing Saber Dao were also just based on Lin Fei's words.

Right now, Lin Fei couldn't possibly achieve the everlasting saber technique, the unperishing Saber Dao. So, Lin Fei was waiting.

The entire secret room was very quiet. Lin Fei closed his eyes. His heart was also very calm. Waiting quietly. No one knows how long it had passed. Suddenly, a voice rang out in Lin Fei's mind.

"Perfection-level Blinking Saber Technique, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved."

"Perfection-level Spring Wind Saber Technique, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved."

"Perfection-level Empty Saber Technique, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

Finally, one saber technique after another began to merge into Lin Fei's saber intent, and they were all at the perfection level.

Of course, these saber techniques were at best Body Refining level or Acquired level saber techniques. The increase in the cultivation progress of saber intent was actually not much. Even if there were dozens of saber techniques, it would be hard to say whether they could increase the cultivation progress of saber intent by 1%.

However, it was visible to the naked eye that Lin Fei's saber intent cultivation progress was indeed improving bit by bit. And Lin Fei could clearly feel, in his mind, there were more perfection-level saber techniques. These saber techniques seemed to be all under Lin Fei's control.

Ten, twenty, thirty, fifty, a hundred...

Countless saber techniques were all integrated into Lin Fei's saber intent, increasing Lin Fei's foundation. And Lin Fei's saber intent was also improving bit by bit.

6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...

Although the increase was slow. A perfection-level Body Refining saber technique, the increase in saber intent cultivation progress was almost not countable.

However, there were a lot of Body Refining level saber techniques. There were five or six hundred Body Refining level saber techniques and there were also acquired level saber techniques.

Of course, what Lin Fei cared most about was the innate level saber techniques. Once the innate-level saber technique was integrated into the saber intent, the increase in the foundation of the saber technique would definitely be extremely terrifying.

"Perfection-level Broken Saber Flow, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved by 3%."

"Perfection-level Mountain-Cleaving Chop, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved by 3%."

Lin Fei's eyes lit up.

Innate-level saber techniques!

Broken Saber Flow and Mountain-Cleaving Chop were both innate-level saber techniques. They actually took the initiative to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent. Moreover, the increase in the cultivation progress of the saber intent was far beyond the comparison of Acquired saber techniques and Body Refining saber techniques.

However, Lin Fei was still waiting.

These two innate-level saber techniques were not the strongest innate saber techniques of the Nine Profound Sect. Even among the innate level saber techniques, there were superior and inferior ones. Once integrated into the saber intent, the increase in the foundation was also different. Soon, in Lin Fei's mind, the voice of the system echoed again.

"Perfection-level Three Abyssal Sabers, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved by 5%."

"Perfection-level Twenty-Three Sabers, willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress has improved by 5%."

Sure enough, Three Abyssal Sabers and Twenty-Three Sabers, second only to the Heavenly Saber Art, also chose to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent.

Within a short hour, in the room, most of the hundreds of saber techniques chose to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent. Of course, this was not compulsory. Therefore, there were still quite a few saber techniques unwilling to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent.

Lin Fei didn't mind.

"System."

Lin Fei muttered in his heart, calling out to the system panel to check his martial arts status.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Stage Martial Saint

Saber Intent: Perfection (Progress 55%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei saw it on the system panel. The cultivation progress of the saber intent had increased directly from 5% to 55%. The saber intent had been enhanced more than ten times! The strength of Lin Fei's saber intent now was incredible.

However, saber intent had not yet transformed in the end. But saber intent could enhance saber techniques. Once Lin Fei performed the Heavenly Saber Art again, the power might be multiplied several times!

Moreover, most importantly, this time he merged hundreds of saber techniques.

The saber intent increased by 50%. This made Lin Fei see the direction of the saber intent evolving into saber momentum.

That was "deception." "Deceive" the saber techniques.

Let those saber techniques actively integrate into their own saber intent without having to work hard to practice saber techniques themselves. Of course, this is only useful for low-level saber techniques. If it were the Martial Saint level saber techniques, their pride was high, Lin Fei couldn't "deceive" them.

Forget about Martial Saint level saber techniques, even innate level saber techniques, Lin Fei might not be able to "deceive." But anyway, this was a direction.

Now, it was just the saber techniques of the Nine Profound Sect that had merged into Lin Fei's saber intent. And it had enhanced the saber intent so much. What if he collected all the saber techniques in the world? Or, Lin Fei didn't even need to collect all the saber techniques in the world. Just a trip to Chang City, to the royal family's martial arts secret chamber.

Most of the lower-level saber techniques like body refining saber techniques and acquired saber techniques might be a lot of repetition. It was estimated that the royal family's lower-level saber techniques were not much different from the Nine Profound Sect's. But what about innate saber techniques? There must be differences.

By then, Lin Fei would integrate some innate-level saber techniques. It was not impossible to evolve saber intent into saber momentum!

If the royal family's saber techniques were not enough, Lin Fei could go to Shen Lianxin and let him take him to the ruins of the ancient martial arts sects. There must be a lot of saber techniques there.

In short, Lin Fei had found the direction to evolve saber momentum. He was one step closer to becoming a "Saber Saint"! And for Martial Saints, saber momentum was equivalent to the significance of saber intent to an innate martial artist.

Martial Saints with or without saber momentum were on two different levels. They were not to be mentioned in the same breath.

"If I go to Chang City now, I wonder if it's too late? Has that elder at the perfection stage of Qi Condensation in Guardian Primordial Mountain successfully built his foundation? If I leave, once the Guardian Primordial Mountain Foundation Establishment cultivator comes down, the consequences would be unthinkable."

Many thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind. If he evolved saber momentum, then cutting down a Foundation Establishment True Person with a saber shouldn't be much of a problem. Having saber momentum also gave him more confidence.

However, if Lin Fei were to leave, Guardian Primordial Mountain's Foundation Establishment True Person comes down, and the Nine Profound Sect definitely couldn't resist. At that time, the consequences would be serious.

Lin Fei thought about it and decided to have the sect master send someone to go to the vicinity of Guardian Primordial Mountain and scout around again.

"Buzz."

Suddenly, the entire Nine Profound Sect slightly trembled. Many people felt a sense of being "isolated." Then, in the sky above the Nine Profound Sect, there was an endless Spiritual Qi gathering. It faintly formed a huge vortex.

However, this Spiritual Qi vortex was not just pure Spiritual Qi, but it was filled with fire attributes. It faintly turned into a fiery red color. It actually turned into a burning fire cloud. Like heavenly fire, it hovered in the sky above the Nine Profound Sect.

For a moment, everyone in the Nine Profound Sect had a feeling of impending disaster, as if the end of the world was coming.

"Nine Profound Sect has offended Guardian Primordial Mountain, offended the Immortal Dao. Today, this true person will personally descend the mountain, and with the 'Heavenly Fire Technique,' wipe out all the people of the Nine Profound Sect. From now on, martial artists who disrespect Qi cultivators and Immortal Dao should be killed without mercy!"

A vast and mighty voice came from the void, echoing throughout the Nine Profound Sect. The Nine Profound Sect was in an uproar.

"A True Person, this is a Foundation Establishment True Person!"

"Guardian Primordial Mountain has truly given birth to a Foundation Establishment True Person!"

"Now, the True Person himself is taking action, executing the Heavenly Punishment, and wants to exterminate all of us in the Nine Profound Sect."

"What do we do? Even if the ancestor were to resurrect, he would not be a match for the True Person!"

For a moment, the Nine Profound Sect was in a state of anxiety. After all, only a few knew that Lin Fei had become a Martial Saint. Most of the disciples and sect members didn't know that the Nine Profound Sect had given birth to a Martial Saint. They all felt that this was the time when the sky was falling, and the Nine Profound Sect was going to be destroyed!

"Swish".

Lin Fei raised his head, looking at the void.

"Finally here. No matter, even without saber momentum, I can cut you down!"

A hint of coldness flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

"Swoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei's figure flashed. He had already left the room.

177. Martial Saint Lin Fei

Foundation Establishment True Person! The Foundation Establishment True Person of Guardian Primordial Mountain, Yuan Kongzi, stood in the void. His spiritual power was unabashedly radiating pressure. His gaze overlooked all beings, looking down at the Nine Profound Sect below.

In his eyes, no matter how brilliant the history of the Nine Profound Sect was, or how many astonishingly talented martial artists had been born, if one did not achieve Foundation Establishment, one was still a mere ant! Not to mention the current Nine Profound Sect, even if the founder of the Nine Profound Sect, the innate perfection Martial Grand Master, was resurrected.

So what?

In the eyes of a Foundation Establishment True Person, he was still an ant!

This was the true thought in Yuan Kongzi's heart. He even once thought it was a bit exaggerated. But now, after he became a Foundation Establishment True Person, he discovered it was not exaggerated at all.

Whether it was a Martial Grand Master or a top Qi Condensation cultivator, as long as they had not achieved Foundation Establishment, in front of the True Persons, they were not much stronger than ants.

Just like now, the Nine Profound Sect had thousands of disciples, and even a few Martial Masters exist. Even the top Qi Condensation cultivators, carrying magic treasures, would have to put in quite an effort to level the Nine Profound Sect to the ground.

But what about Yuan Kongzi, the Foundation Establishment True Person himself?

Just one Heavenly Fire Technique. An ordinary Heavenly Fire Technique, many ordinary Condensation cultivators could perform this spell. But, could those ordinary Condensation cultivators' Heavenly Fire Techniques be as terrifying as the Heavenly Fire Technique performed by Yuan Kongzi?

Heavenly Fire across the sky, forming a giant cloud of fire, hovering above the Nine Profound Sect! Once it fell, it would be like a meteor, Heavenly Fire descending. Not to mention the Nine Profound Sect, even a city would be turned into ashes by the Heavenly Fire. This was the terrifying aspect of a Foundation Establishment True Person.

For Qi Condensation cultivators, even the top Qi Condensation cultivators, when casting spells, could only mobilize their own spiritual power and use their own spiritual power to cast spells.

But what about a Foundation Establishment True Person? Once they shed their mortal body and reforge their Magic body, they could leverage the Spiritual Qi between heaven and earth.

The spiritual power of a Qi Condensation cultivator was limited, but the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth was infinite. Therefore, even though it was only a small Heavenly Fire Technique when cast by a Foundation Establishment True Person, it was a world of difference. It was like the flame of destruction. Very terrifying.

Looking at the panicked expressions of the Nine Profound Sect people, Yuan Kongzi felt it was boring. How could just this group of martial artists have caused Yuan Xing Zi and Yuan Chen Zi to fail?

No matter, he didn't bother to think about how Yuan Xing Zi and Yuan Chen Zi failed. Because, under his Heavenly Fire Technique, nothing else matters. The Nine Profound Sect was destined to be reduced to ashes.

"Heavenly Fire, fall!"

The next moment, Yuan Kongzi's mind moved. The Spiritual Qi between heaven and earth exploded. In the void, the giant fire cloud suddenly fell down.

"Whoosh".

Just at the moment when the fire cloud was falling, from somewhere within the Nine Profound Sect below, a beam of saber light instantly flew out.

The saber light shone. In an instant, it flew into the void. This saber light was a saber formed by the condensation of countless saber essence.

The saber was not large, just a mere thirty meters. Facing the Heavenly Fire cloud covering the entire Nine Profound Sect, the thirty meters seemed so tiny. However, it was this tiny saber light that slashed on the Heavenly Fire cloud.

"Boom".

The saber light slashed on the giant Heavenly Fire cloud. Suddenly, a violent and sharp energy erupted from this saber light in an instant. Endless saber edge instantly cut the giant Heavenly Fire cloud.

"Sizzle".

The Heavenly Fire cloud was split in half by this saber light. Then, it completely collapsed. The sky returned to calm. It was no longer the fiery red like a burning cloud.

"Whoosh".

Yuan Kongzi's gaze instantly became sharp. He shouted loudly: "Who is it?"

That saber light just now was definitely not something that an innate martial artist could slash out. No matter how strong an innate martial artist was, how could a saber light break his Heavenly Fire Technique?

Even if it was just his ordinary Heavenly Fire Technique, that level of power already surpassed the innate martial artist and Qi Condensation cultivators and reached the Foundation Establishment level. That was not the power of the "mortal".

Soon, Yuan Kongzi's eyes narrowed slightly. He saw a figure.

It was a young martial artist. From the Nine Profound Sect below, step by step, as if climbing the ladder of the void.

"Crossing the void, walking in the air, this... this is a Martial Saint?"

Yuan Kongzi's pupils contracted. He was extremely shocked in his heart!

Martial Saint!

He had never seen a Martial Saint. After all, the last Martial Saint of Great Chang had also passed away three hundred years ago. It was a Martial Saint from the Hidden Sword Sect.

Yuan Kongzi only learned about some characteristics of a Martial Saint from the sect's classics. He only glanced at it casually at the time. After all, Martial Saints and Foundation Establishment True Persons were at the same level.

It was clearly recorded in the secrets. Once martial artists achieved the Martial Saint stage, they would rebuild their Dao Bodies and possess a variety of incredible abilities.

Among them, crossing the void and walking in the air was the most obvious characteristic of a Martial Saint. And now, Yuan Kongzi saw such a martial artist. Crossing the void, walking in the air, and even capable of breaking his Heavenly Fire Technique with a single saber light.

If that was not a Martial Saint, what was it?

Lin Fei, step by step, as if strolling in a leisurely courtyard, slowly walked into the void. He did not hide his figure. Therefore, all the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect could also see Lin Fei's figure in the void.

Seeing Lin Fei's figure in the void, all the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect couldn't help but shudder. Their hearts were stirred up like a raging storm.

"That... That's Grand Elder Lin Fei?"

"It must be Elder Lin. So young, there's absolutely no mistake."

"Elder Lin has reached the void without any use of Innate True Qi, and there's even no power fluctuation on his body?"

"Crossing the void, walking in the air. If the legends are correct, it can only mean one thing. Elder Lin has become a Martial Saint!"

"Martial Saint, it must be a Martial Saint! Only a Martial Saint would have such great power!"

"People always say that Elder Lin is an extraordinary talent, his martial arts talent is as good as the founder of our sect. But now it seems that he is not only as good as the founder, but he has surpassed him! After all, even the founder did not become a Martial Saint!"

"Our Nine Profound Sect has finally produced a Martial Saint! Hahaha, even if the Foundation Establishment True Person from the Guardian Primordial Mountain comes, we in the Nine Profound Sect can sleep without worries!"

Countless disciples were fervently looking at the figure of Lin Fei in the void.

Most ordinary disciples knew what a Martial Saint represented. It represented the pinnacle of martial arts! It represented transcendence! It represented the ability to contend with a Foundation Establishment True Person, even to be superior!

Lin Fei, step by step, finally arrived not far from Yuan Kongzi. The two were only a hundred meters apart. Both could clearly see the other's appearance.

Yuan Kongzi took a deep breath and asked solemnly: "Who are you?"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, and said calmly: "Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei."

178. Battle Between the Martial Saint and Foundation Establishment True Person!

"You are 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei?"

Yuan Kongzi's eyes slightly narrowed, and a look of disbelief appeared in his eyes.

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei. His name was well-known throughout Great Chang. He was aware of Lin Fei. After all, Lin Fei had slain top Qi cultivators from Guardian Primordial Mountain.

According to Yuan Kongzi's understanding, Lin Fei joined the Nine Profound Sect just four years ago, but for the first three years, Lin Fei did nothing notable, he did not display any talent. But in the past year, he made rapid progress. He went from the fourth level of Body Refining all the way to becoming a Martial Master.

Moreover, he even slew many Qi cultivators. He made a great name for himself in the martial world as the "Immortal Slayer Saber". And now, Lin Fei had actually become a Martial Saint? This was too shocking!

"Impossible! Exotic beasts in Great Chang have gone extinct. Without the flesh and blood of exotic beasts, how can martial artists reach physical perfection? If you can't achieve physical perfection, you martial artists can't possibly build a foundation to become a Martial Saint. The path of martial artists has been cut off!"

Yuan Kongzi stared at Lin Fei intensely. It seemed that he wanted to find Lin Fei's "flaw". Or rather, he wanted to find some evidence that Lin Fei was not a Martial Saint. However, no matter how he looked, it seemed that Lin Fei was a Martial Saint!

"Whether or not I am a Martial Saint, wouldn't True Person know if you tried? I have a saber strike. If the True Person can take it, you can leave safely. If you can't take it, then I will step over your body and ascend to the pinnacle of martial arts!"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, speaking calmly.

"Arrogant! Even if you are a Martial Saint, so what? My Guardian Primordial Mountain has been passing down the Taoist lineage for thousands of years. How can a mere Martial Saint like you shake it? To kill this True Person is simply wishful thinking. Very well, today this True Person has succeeded in building a foundation. I will get rid of you to proclaim the supreme name of this True Person!"

Yuan Kongzi was greatly angered. But there was not a shred of fear in his heart. The might of Martial Saints seemed to have disappeared from people's memories. Even the strongest Martial Saint was only a thing of three hundred years ago. There had always only been Qi cultivators slaying martial artists. When did it ever happen that martial artists stood above Qi cultivators? Even if they were Martial Saints, it wouldn't work!

Moreover, this time Yuan Kongzi did not come empty-handed. He was prepared! Guardian Primordial Mountain, with a thousand-year lineage, had a deep foundation. Among them, there were not a few magic treasures. This time, Yuan Kongzi also came bearing magic treasures.

Above Yuan Kongzi's head, a bead the size of a baby's fist suddenly appeared, floating in the air. The bead revolved around Yuan Kongzi, continuously spinning.

"Sea-Stablizing Pearl!"

Yuan Kongzi's eyes were cold. This Sea-Stablizing Pearl was a magic treasure of the Guardian Primordial Mountain's successive generations of True Persons. According to legend, it was a replica made from a remarkable magic treasure.

The Sea-Stablizing Pearl itself was made from the inner core of a special exotic beast from the sea. Although this one was just a fake one, it was not to be trifled with. It had a natural strong control over water. It was filled with a large amount of water. Once it was deployed, it would certainly be earth-shaking. It could be called the first magic treasure of the Guardian Primordial Mountain for attack! Even the "Heavenly Thunder" and "Earthly Evil" were far inferior to the Sea-Stablizing Pearl.

"Whoosh."

The Sea-Stablizing Pearl instantly turned into a stream of light and it was smashed towards Lin Fei. Lin Fei raised his hand and threw a punch.

"Immeasurable Fist!"

Lin Fei threw out a punch. The saber essence instantly covered his whole body. On his arm and fist, the saber essence also burst out instantly. Immediately, this punch blasted out. The void seemed to be trembling.

"Bang."

Lin Fei's fist hit the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. Immediately, he felt a strong force coming from the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. It sent him flying. However, his punch also directly bounced the Sea-Stablizing Pearl away.

This scene left Yuan Kongzi stunned. His face was full of shock. He knew how terrifying the Sea-Stablizing Pearl was. With just a casual strike, a mountain peak could be easily smashed through.

And now?

Lin Fei actually used his flesh and blood fist to hard clash with the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. Moreover, he even sent the Sea-Stablizing Pearl flying. How terrifying was this power?

"The power belongs to oneself, is this a Martial Saint?"

Yuan Kongzi muttered to himself. In the world, a Martial Saint hadn't been seen in three hundred years. Many people had forgotten the terror of a Martial Saint.

Little did they know, the physical body of a Martial Saint was the most terrifying weapon. Lin Fei's Dao Body was infinitely close to an unparalleled treasure saber.

Therefore, he wasn't using his flesh and blood to hard clash with the Sea-Stablizing Pearl but an unparalleled treasure saber with saber essence.

"Bang, bang, bang."

Lin Fei's punches became more and more fierce, constantly clashing hard with the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. The void was violently trembling, leaving the people below staring in amazement. Because, Lin Fei with a casual punch, sent the Sea-Stablizing Pearl flying.

The Sea-Stablizing Pearl fell onto the mountain peak of the Nine Profound Sect, instantly collapsing the mountain. Or, Lin Fei threw a punch across the air. The mountain on the other side would even be shattered.

Many disciples of the Nine Profound Sect scattered away. Their eyes were filled with fervor.

"The power of a Martial Saint shakes the heavens and the earth!"

"So, practicing martial arts to the level of Martial Saint also has earth-shaking power."

"Martial Arts, not inferior to the Immortal Dao!"

Especially for innate martial artists like Zhao Kongming, the shock in their hearts was even greater. They were staring hard at the battle between Lin Fei and Yuan Kongzi.

The battle between a Martial Saint and a Foundation Establishment True Person. No matter what era, that's hard to encounter. The power of a Martial Saint, at this moment, was being displayed in front of everyone in its full glory.

Yuan Kongzi's face was somewhat ugly. He had even used the Sea-Stablizing Pearl, but he was still unable to handle Lin Fei. His eyes flashed with a sharp light.

"We Qi cultivators are not just good at controlling magic treasures. This True Person also has talismans and spells!"

Spiritual power surged in Yuan Kongzi's body. While he was controlling the magic treasure, he was also drawing talismans in the void with spiritual power.

"Mountain Moving Talisman, Mountain Come!"

Yuan Kongzi drew a talisman in the void. Immediately, spiritual power operated. The talisman radiated bursts of golden light. Soon, the talisman disappeared. The next moment, outside the Nine Profound Sect, a small mountain peak actually began to shake violently.

"Rumble."

Following that, the small mountain peak was directly uprooted as if it was lifted by an invisible force. With a lightning-fast force, it howled and smashed hard toward Lin Fei.

"Bang."

The next moment, Lin Fei's body shook. His body was directly sent flying by the mountain. The Sea-Stablizing Pearl took advantage of this opportunity and smashed toward Lin Fei's head again.

Mountain peaks, the Sea-Stablizing Pearl, spells, talismans, magic treasures. These were the methods of Qi cultivators! Especially when performed by a True Person, it's even more miraculous.

Like this kind of "Mountain Moving Technique", Qi cultivators below the Foundation Establishment stage simply cannot perform it. The amount of spiritual power that it consumes was unimaginable.

Even Yuan Kongzi, also felt a wave of weakness in his body as if his spiritual power had been drained. Such a spell required an amount of spiritual power that even a True Person who had built their foundation must carefully execute.

However, Yuan Kongzi acted decisively. The effect of the Mountain Moving Technique was very good. It directly sent Lin Fei flying. Even more so, the Sea-Stablizing Pearl took advantage of the situation to rise again. Once it hit Lin Fei's head, Lin Fei would undoubtedly die!

"You have magic treasures, you have spells. But, I also have a saber! This one saber will cleave your Sea-Stablizing Pearl!"

Lin Fei's voice came from the void. The next moment, a dazzling saber light shot up into the sky.

179. The Fall of the Foundation Establishment

The saber light reappeared! Only, this saber was not merely thirty meters long but three hundred! And it was accompanied by Lin Fei's voice.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

It was only a three hundred meters saber light, compared with Lin Fei's previous one thousand saber energy, it seemed not worth mentioning. However, the two couldn't be compared at all.

This three hundred meters saber light was composed of saber essence. Saber energy was compressed hundreds of times, which produced such a bit of saber essence.

A saber essence of roughly the same size compared to saber energy was almost a hundred times saber energy! And the power was more concentrated.

Once the power explodes, it was not just a hundred times that simple. More importantly, Lin Fei's saber intent was also stronger. He had integrated hundreds of saber techniques. When the Heavenly Saber Art was slashed out, it seemed as if there were countless shadows of saber techniques.

As this saber slashed out, the three-hundred meters saber light cut through the void. In everyone's eyes, there seemed to be only this one saber light. This saber was too beautiful. This saber seemed to be able to slash everything! Where the saber light passed, the void seemed to have a little bit of black silk. That's the crack in the void.

Only, it was fleeting, making it difficult for people to notice. This is enough to prove. The power of this saber had reached a terrifying level.

"Boom".

Finally, this saber slashed on the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. Two terrible forces collided fiercely. The saber light was also smashed and dissipated by the Sea-Stablizing Pearl in an instant. Only, the Sea-Stablizing Pearl also stopped.

Yuan Kongzi opened his eyes wide. At the moment when the Sea-Stablizing Pearl collided with the saber light, his mind was greatly shaken!

"Puffing".

Yuan Kongzi spat out a mouthful of blood. But he didn't care at all. His gaze was fixed on the Sea-Stablizing Pearl. A look of shock appeared in his eyes.

"Crack".

As expected, the Sea-Stablizing Pearl cracked open.

"Boom".

The next moment, the Sea-Stablizing Pearl shattered. A large amount of water fell into the Nine Profound Sect. Fortunately, the Nine Profound Sect is all mountains. Otherwise, so much water might be enough to cause a flood.

"How can this be?"

Yuan Kongzi seemed to not believe his own eyes.

Shattered! The Sea-Stablizing Pearl actually shattered! This is a treasure passed down by the Guardian Primordial Mountain. How could it shatter? And, it was slashed by Lin Fei.

Lin Fei's eyes were icy cold. He glanced at his own palm. There was no more Saber Qi. But his Saber Essence was even more terrifying. The power had increased by more than a hundred times!

A saber was swung out, which was simply earth-shattering. Even a magic treasure like the Sea-Stablizing Pearl couldn't withstand Lin Fei's single saber.

"Wind Summoning Technique, Wind come!"

Yuan Kongzi gritted his teeth. Suddenly, a bone-chilling wind, seemed to blow into the bones, instantly filling the void.

"Go!"

Yuan Kongzi used the Wind Summoning Technique. He wasn't prepared to defeat Lin Fei with the Wind Summoning Technique. But to escape!

Immediately, Yuan Kongzi turned into a fleeing light. The speed was incredible. In this regard, martial artists were far inferior to Foundation Establishment True Person. After all, a True Person could perform escape techniques. If they couldn't beat a Martial Saint, they could directly perform escape techniques to escape. The Martial Saint could do nothing about it.

"Hmph, Heaven Saber Momentum!"

Lin Fei seemed to have anticipated it. In the void, the Heavenly Saber condensed again. At the same time, the momentum of the Heavenly Saber quickly spread within a radius of thousands of meters.

Yuan Kongzi, who had turned into a fleeing light and was preparing to escape, was enveloped in it. The momentum of the Heavenly Saber, although not real saber momentum, already possessed a bit of the power of the saber momentum.

Especially Lin Fei's saber intent increased significantly. It made the power of the Heavenly Saber Momentum stronger. Therefore, it could also have a certain impact on the Foundation Establishment True Persons.

"Hm?"

Yuan Kongzi's speed dropped significantly. He had to reveal his figure through the escape technique. If it was said that True Persons had escape techniques far superior to martial artists, then martial artists also had corresponding means to cope with it. That's saber momentum!

Once a martial artist evolved the saber momentum, cultivators who wanted to escape would be suppressed by the saber momentum.

Only, a typical Martial Saint was just hard to comprehend saber momentum. Lin Fei didn't have real saber momentum, but he had the momentum of the Heavenly Saber. He caught Yuan Kongzi off guard, even the escape technique was interrupted.

"Now's the time!"

Lin Fei's whole body was enveloped by the "Wind Summoning Technique". However, Lin Fei's Dao Body was strong enough. And, it was also covered with a layer of saber essence letting the cold wind blow on his body couldn't cause any harm to him.

Lin Fei leaped up.

Close Yet Distant!

Even in the void, Lin Fei could also use Close Yet Distant. And, a leap was tens of meters. In the blink of an eye, he arrived in front of Yuan Kongzi.

Lin Fei's eyes were icy cold. He didn't erupt with saber essence again. Because, when using the Heavenly Saber Art, Lin Fei's saber essence was almost exhausted.

However, it doesn't matter. The strongest means of a Martial Saint, apart from the true essence in the body, is their own Dao Body. Once a True Person was approached by a Martial Saint, that's pretty much a death sentence.

Lin Fei extended his hand. With palm substitutes saber directly downward with his palm. A harsh chop, no saber essence, just a flesh and blood hand.

However, Yuan Kongzi was like facing a great enemy as if he had encountered the most terrifying thing. A shield defending a magical artifact was immediately placed in front of him.

"Crisp sound".

However, it had no effect. The shield magical artifact, under Lin Fei's palm, was like paper, instantly cut open. Then a defensive spell layer appeared.

Lin Fei's hand, with almost no obstruction, directly cut open this defensive spell layer. Magical artifact, spell. Two layers of defense, in front of Lin Fei's Dao Body were of no use.

This was the Dao Body of a Martial Saint! Even without any saber essence and saber energy in the body, the Dao Body of a Martial Saint was still the most terrifying lethal weapon!

Yuan Kongzi saw this scene. Finally, a trace of fear appeared in his eyes. Because he felt the threat of death.

"No, I just built the foundation, standing at the pinnacle of the world, and can live for five hundred years, how can I die here? Lin Fei, you are a Martial Saint, I am a Foundation Establishment True Person, how can we fight to the death for these ants? I cannot die..."

Yuan Kongzi's voice became sharp. However, Lin Fei's hand did not show any signs of stopping.

"Bang".

Lin Fei chopped down with a hand. It did not cut open Yuan Kongzi's law body. He directly blasted Yuan Kongzi's head. Immediately, blood from Yuan Kongzi's body spurted out, sprinkling in the void. A rich smell of blood drifted into Lin Fei's nose. Yuan Kongzi's head was blasted, and even a Foundation Establishment True Person was undoubtedly dead.

"Thump".

The corpse fell from the sky and hit the ground and smashed into a pile of meat.

For a while, the entire Nine Profound Sect was silent. Everyone's mouth was wide open as if they couldn't believe what was happening in front of them.

Because a Foundation Establishment True Person had fallen! A dignified True Person had fallen! Moreover, he was killed on the spot by Lin Fei, witnessed by thousands of disciples of the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei killed Yuan Kongzi head-on. Killed the only Foundation Establishment True Person of the Guardian Primordial Mountain!

Step by step, Lin Fei walked down from the void and came to Zhao Kongming and others. Seeing the crowd still in shock, not coming back to their senses, Lin Fei calmly said: "Sect Master, go clean up and spread the news of today. Let the whole Great Chang know I've become a Martial Saint and killed the Guardian Primordial Mountain's True Person!"

At this time, Lin Fei was very clear. There's no need to keep a low profile. On the contrary, it needed to be high-profile! Let everyone know Nine Profound Sect had a Martial Saint who could kill a Foundation Establishment True Person. With such a reputation, any force, before dealing with the Nine Profound Sect, needed to weigh it carefully!

"Respect the Saint's decree!"

The Sect Master was shaking all over, his voice trembling with excitement. Lin Fei, killed the Foundation Establishment True Person. The entire Great Chang would definitely be shocked beyond measure! The Nine Profound Sect, of course, would rise with the tide. It could be compared with the first-class immortal gates of the present world!

......

The thirteenth year of Yongqing in Great Chang, early April.

Yuan Kongzi, a Foundation Establishment True Person from Guardian Primordial Mountain, with the magic treasure the Sea-Stablizing Pearl, attacked the Nine Profound Sect, intending to exterminate the entire Nine Profound Sect. Lin Fei, the Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect, appeared out of nowhere. With his saber, he cut down Yuan Kongzi! The True Person fell!

The news spread out. The martial world was shocked! The immortal sects were shocked! The entire world was shocked!

181. Lin Fei's Decision

In the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei sat cross-legged in his cave dwelling.

"Reporting to the grand elder."

Suddenly, the sect master arrived. Now, even when the sect master came to Lin Fei's cave dwelling, he had to announce his arrival. After all, Lin Fei's status was now different from before. He was now regarded by all martial artists throughout the Great Chang, and throughout the entire world, as a godlike figure. He was also currently the stabilizing force of the Nine Profound Sect!

Lin Fei's prestige had long since surpassed the ordinary scope of a Grand Elder. In fact, if Lin Fei wished to take the position of sect master at this moment, it would be as easy as a common occurrence.

"Sect master, come in."

The voice of Lin Fei came from inside the cave dwelling. The sect master respectfully entered Lin Fei's dwelling. Upon seeing Lin Fei sitting cross-legged on the ground, the sect master respectfully greeted, "Greetings, grand elder!"

"Sect master, what brings you here?"

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

The sect master respectfully said, "Grand Elder, I have been closely monitoring the movements of He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain. After He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain learned that the grand elder has become a Martial Saint and slain Yuan Kongzi with a saber stroke. Both of these immortal sects immediately declared a lockdown, activating their mountain protection arrays. It seems that they have no intention of involving themselves with the world any longer."

In reality, when He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain learned that Lin Fei had killed Yuan Kongzi, they initially refused to believe it. After carefully investigating the news and discovering that it was indeed true, they didn't hesitate any longer. They promptly secluded themselves from the world. Once they closed off their mountains, it meant that they would not venture down, and everything in the mortal world became irrelevant to them.

The only exceptions might be the occasional recruitment of disciples, which might necessitate a descent from the mountain. But only a handful of people would venture down and they wouldn't make a big fuss about it. They were truly afraid.

Even though a Foundation Establishment cultivator from Guardian Primordial Mountain was slain by Lin Fei, the Guardian Primordial Mountain did not dare to retaliate. Instead, they worried that Lin Fei might flatten the Guardian Primordial Mountain. Therefore, they promptly closed off their mountain and activated their grand array.

These immortal sects, which have existed for over a thousand years, had experience with such matters. Back when the founding emperor of Great Chang swept across the four corners of the world with his Martial Saint prowess, subduing the world. Knowing they couldn't compete, these immortal sects did exactly this.

They closed off their mountains, secluded themselves from the world, and endured hardship. They continued to endure until the founding emperor of Great Chang disappeared. Only then did these immortal sects start stirring up trouble again.

Fortunately, a Foundation Establishment True Person was born within the royal family. Although the Supreme Elder did not possess the might of the founding emperor of Great Chang, he was still a top Foundation Establishment True Person. He was able to keep other immortal sects from taking rash actions, leaving them with no choice but to seclude themselves. This lasted for over four hundred years until the royal supreme elder's lifespan ended and passed away in meditation, they began to stir up trouble again, attempting to take control of the world's power.

Now, with Lin Fei's power growing, other immortal sects might not necessarily fear him. However, He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, these two great immortal sects, currently had no Foundation Establishment True Person. How could they dare to involve themselves in worldly affairs?

They had no choice but to seclude themselves by closing off their mountains. They would wait until their sects produce another Foundation Establishment True Person, or until Lin Fei dies. It's estimated that He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain would only dare to reopen their mountains then.

This was the survival strategy of these immortal sects. If there were powerful enemies that cannot be defeated, could they not hide?

He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain were both immortal sects with a thousand-year-old heritage. They possessed treasure that stabilizes their sects. Their mountain protection arrays were so powerful that even a Martial Saint with a manifested saber momentum cannot break through them.

Otherwise, the founding emperor of Great Chang would have flattened those immortal sects long ago. How could there be room for the existence of those immortal sects?

Now it was the same with Lin Fei. He didn't think that he was stronger than the founding emperor of Great Chang at the moment. After all, the founding emperor of Great Chang had managed to master "momentum", and Lin Fei had yet to do so.

If even the founding emperor of Great Chang couldn't break through the mountain protection arrays of those immortal sects, naturally, Lin Fei wouldn't be able to break through them either. He could only let those immortal sects close off their mountains.

However, as long as he was present, He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain would have to obediently close off their mountains, not daring to take any rash actions. This was the deterrent power of Lin Fei, the Martial Saint!

"I understand. Is there anything else?"

Lin Fei looked at the sect master, who seemed to be hesitant, seemed there was more to be said.

The sect master hesitated for a moment, but eventually took out a letter from his bosom, "Grand Elder, the secret guards of the South King, on behalf of the South King's daughter, hope that the grand elder can make a trip to Chang City. This is a letter from Princess Ling Yao, please have a look, grand elder."

Lin Fei raised his head. He took the letter from the sect master's hand. Upon opening the letter, he saw the familiar handwriting. It was indeed from Ling Yao.

The content of the letter was also very simple. First, it congratulated Lin Fei on achieving the status of Martial Saint, reaching the peak of martial arts, and shaking the world with his might! Second, it hoped that Lin Fei could make a trip to Chang City.

After putting down the letter, Lin Fei did not speak, falling silent.

The sect master finally couldn't help but say, "Grand Elder, the situation in Great Chang is unstable now, and the Great Chang dynasty is in danger. Although our Nine Profound Sect has a good relationship with the Great Chang royal family, we need to think carefully about such important matters. Chang City is now a whirlpool. Once you step into the whirlpool, it will be difficult to extricate yourself!

Although you, grand elder, are now a Martial Saint, there are more than just He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain among the immortal sects in the world. Some Foundation Establishment True Persons have been practicing for hundreds of years, their depth is unfathomable, far beyond what Yuan Kongzi can compare to. I hope grand elder will think thrice!"

Lin Fei understood what the sect master was saying. He was hoping that Lin Fei would not go to Chang City to avoid stirring the troubled waters of the royal family.

If anything happened to Lin Fei, Nine Profound Sect would be in danger. The current Lin Fei wasn't just himself alone. It was the entire Nine Profound Sect behind him.

Lin Fei looked at the sect master and said indifferently, "The reason why the world is so chaotic now, I believe is clear. Behind it all are those immortal sects, coveting control of the world's power. If we truly go back to the time before Great Chang was established when those immortal sects held power. Do you think the Nine Profound Sect could stay out of it? Even if I, a Martial Saint, am sitting here, can Nine Profound Sect rest easy?"

The sect master didn't speak anymore. What was it like before the establishment of Great Chang? Some ancient texts briefly mention it. Back then, there were mortal nations. But they were divided into many nations, constantly warring with each other. And behind these nations all, were those immortal sects.

The immortal sects, high above, controlled everything. They didn't care about how many mortal people died or were injured. Holding power and controlling all kinds of spiritual resources in the world was all they cared for. Mortals were just people who served them generation after generation. If one generation died, another would grow. Moreover, ordinary people are without talent. In their eyes, they didn't even count as the same kind. This kind of high and mighty mentality was not the same as martial artists. After all, martial artists were also "ordinary people" in the eyes of Qi cultivators. Anyone could become a martial artist. Even if a martial artist became a Martial Saint, he wouldn't have this kind of high and mighty mentality.

Martial artists and Qi cultivators. To say they are born enemies was a bit of an exaggeration. But once the immortal sects control the world's power, martial arts would inevitably be suppressed. By then, let alone Martial Saints, even a martial arts Master, probably could only become a servant to be dispatched at will by the Qi cultivators.

"Moreover, what the founding emperor of Great Chang was able to do, I can do too!"

A sharp light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes! The sect master shuddered in his heart. He already knew Lin Fei's determination.

"Tell the secret guards that I will certainly go to Chang City."

"Yes, grand elder!"

The sect master did not try to persuade him further. Instead, he respectfully withdrew.

182. Ling Yao's Decision

Chang City, South King Mansion.

Ling Yao was handling a large amount of business every day. Mostly military affairs and logistics. The army on the front lines was putting down rebellions, but it was not going smoothly. Therefore, various resources need to be continuously transported to the front lines.

War, like a gold-consuming beast, all the resources are swallowed up. However, there was no sign of any improvement now. It was like a bottomless pit, making Ling Yao feel exhausted.

However, at this time, Ling Yao showed a firm will. She couldn't fall! She now was not just one person anymore. Centered on her, behind her, there were already tens of thousands of people involved.

She was a huge force. If she fell, there would be countless people falling with her. However, she was inherently weak. She also wished someone could help her. At this moment, in her mind, she couldn't help but imagine a figure.

"Will he...come?"

Ling Yao hadn't received any news from the secret guards. After all, it took time for the secret guards to pass on messages. A breeze blew past. The candlelight in the room flickered slightly.

"Hmm?"

Ling Yao suddenly looked up. She saw that in the room, she didn't know when an additional figure appeared.

"Lin Fei!"

Ling Yao widened her eyes. She even felt like she was hallucinating. However, this familiar figure was now quietly standing in front of her.

"Senior Sister Ling."

Lin Fei spoke. The familiar voice let Ling Yao know this was not a hallucination. It was Lin Fei, he really came! For a moment, Ling Yao was overjoyed. Lin Fei was a Martial Saint famous all over the world. His status had already far surpassed her, a princess.

Ling Yao looked complicated, with a slight smile on her face, "I haven't congratulated you yet, for finally achieving Martial Saint, standing at the pinnacle of martial arts, and achieving your initial goal."

When Lin Fei said he wanted to become a Martial Saint, Ling Yao just shook her head slightly. She didn't believe it at all. But now, Lin Fei was standing in front of her as a Martial Saint. She couldn't help but believe it.

"Yes, the goal I set casually at the beginning has been achieved. But this is far from being the pinnacle of martial arts."

After a pause, Lin Fei looked directly at Ling Yao and said word by word, "Senior Sister Ling, when I left Chang City, I gave you a choice...Now, you should have made a decision. Tell me, what is your decision?"

Ling Yao was taken aback. She of course knew what Lin Fei was talking about. Originally, before Lin Fei left, he gave her a choice.

Martial arts or power!

If she chose martial arts, Lin Fei would help her become an innate martial artist with all his might. But the road after that would have to be taken by Ling Yao herself. If she chose power. Even if she wanted to become an empress, Lin Fei would help her.

The words from the past were still vivid in her memory as if it was just yesterday. But now, Lin Fei had returned. She had to make a choice.

Ling Yao sighed deeply and said quietly, "With my talent, becoming innate is the limit. But, an innate martial artist is just a fleeting hundred years. To become a Martial Saint? How easy could it be?"

Lin Fei closed his eyes. Ling Yao also remained silent. He knew that Ling Yao had made her choice.

Lin Fei was not disappointed. On the contrary, he was very calm. It seemed that he had known Ling Yao's choice a long time ago. After all, not everyone is willing to risk everything to reach the peak of martial arts! In the mortal world, glory and wealth, power to dominate a lifetime, isn't it beautiful?

If martial arts cannot become a Martial Saint, it would be like the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. Such a brilliant and peerless top powerhouse, in the end, could only sit withered on the peak of the founder. Alone, dying in loneliness and desolation.

"Lin Fei, there is a rebellion in the south now, and behind it are the Fairy Crane Sect and Water Moon Sect..."

Before Ling Yao could finish her sentence, she was interrupted by Lin Fei.

"Senior Sister Ling, I understand what you mean. But feelings are feelings, and trades are trades. The royal family has to offer something that satisfies me. Then I will make a move! This matter, you can't decide, I will personally meet the Great Chang Emperor and the elders of the royal family."

So, Lin Fei turned around. He had no intention of staying in South King Mansion. Since Ling Yao made her choice, Lin Fei knew that the last thread of affection between him and Ling Yao had come to an end.

"Lin Fei..."

Ling Yao called out.

"Whoosh".

But Lin Fei's figure had already disappeared. However, although Lin Fei left, his voice still echoed in Ling Yao's ears.

"Sister Ling, since you have made your choice, let it be as you wish..."

Ling Yao suddenly widened her eyes. But outside the window, Lin Fei's figure was nowhere to be seen. Before long, Lin Fei arrived at the palace. He went straight to see the emperor.

The Great Chang Emperor was a middle-aged man. His eyes were dark and lifeless. His body didn't seem too good. This was the result of indulging in pleasure and emptying his body.

"Who?"

Seeing Lin Fei's figure, the emperor was startled.

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back and said lightly, "Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei! Emperor, call the elders of the royal family, there are some things that the emperor might not be able to decide."

Lin Fei's words were a bit overbearing, even somewhat "rebellious". But the emperor sobered up at this moment.

Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei! Now this name was resounding throughout the world! Because Lin Fei was a Martial Saint!

The emperor immediately called for the elders.

The emperor seemed to be the supreme figure. But in fact, when it really came to the life and death of the royal family, he couldn't make the decision either. The elders of the royal family must step forward.

Soon, the elders of the royal family came. Among them, there were some "acquaintances" of Lin Fei. At this moment, after these elders of the royal family saw Lin Fei, all of them were taken aback. They immediately stepped forward, bowed respectfully, and said, "Greetings, Martial Saint!"

Now, Lin Fei was already a Martial Saint, equivalent to a Foundation Establishment True Person. Even if they were of royal blood. They also had to pay their respects to Lin Fei.

"The current predicament of Great Chang, I have learned about. There is rebellion in the South and even support from the immortals behind it. I can take action, quell the rebellion, and even flatten the immortal sect behind the rebel army! But there are two conditions."

The emperor and the elders were overjoyed. They were now in a mess because of the rebellion in the South. The death of the supreme elder caused the royal family to no longer had the power to suppress those immortal sects.

If they did not suppress it in time, given time, the world would definitely be in turmoil. By then, the royal family would be helpless. But if this Martial Saint, Lin Fei, was willing to make a move, then it must be able to suppress the rebellion!

After all, Lin Fei was the only Martial Saint who could slash the Foundation Establishment True Person with a saber, and the only Martial Saint in Great Chang!

"Martial Saint, if you have any instructions, please feel free to tell."

"First, proclaim Princess Ling Yao as the royal princess, and she will ascend to the throne in the future and become the Empress of Great Chang! Second, the secret collection of royal martial arts needs to be open to me."

The second condition, of course, was not a problem. As for the first condition, in fact, it was just that the emperor was not very willing. But the elders of the royal family didn't care who became the emperor. As long as it is the royal bloodline, there is no problem. Now, the world was in turmoil. The key was to preserve the royal family and protect Great Chang!

"Good, we agree to the conditions of the Martial Saint!"

Lin Fei was not surprised. With these two conditions, the royal family had no choice but to agree.

"Let's go, take me to the place of the royal martial arts secret collection now."

"Yes, Martial Saint."

So, an elder led Lin Fei to the place of the royal martial arts secret collection. Lin Fei walked in alone. He needed a lot of saber techniques to evolve his saber momentum, especially the saber techniques at the innate level.

Lin Fei came to a row of saber technique bookshelves. He closed his eyes. In his mind, he thought of Ling Yao. Today, he helped Ling Yao become the Royal Princess. This was equivalent to severing the emotional bond between him and Ling Yao.

"Shush."

Lin Fei's emotions gradually calmed down.

"Now that the emotional bond is severed, it's time for me to evolve my saber momentum! Let's begin."

Lin Fei's gaze became calm again.

183. Integrating Royal Saber Techniques, Saber Intent Transformation

Where Lin Fei's gaze fell were rows of bookshelves. Saber techniques, sword techniques, fist techniques, etc. Body refining level, acquired level, and innate level were all included. As for the quantity, it's at least ten times more than the Nine Profound Sect. This is the foundation of the Great Chang royal family.

After establishing the Great Chang dynasty, the founder of the Great Chang began to collect martial arts techniques from all over the world. Many martial arts were collected by the founder of the Great Chang. They were put into the secret collection of royal martial arts. Therefore, there were so many saber techniques here.

Lin Fei didn't intend to examine the secret books one by one. He took a deep breath. Then, he released all his saber intent.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber intent enveloped the entire secret martial arts collection.

Now Lin Fei's saber intent was not just perfection anymore but it had surpassed perfection. The cultivation progress had reached 55%. That is to say, Lin Fei's saber intent only needed to increase the cultivation progress by another 45%, then he could evolve the saber momentum. Like the innate level saber techniques such as the Three Abyssal Sabers, and Twenty-Three Sabers, only ten were needed!

"I wish to evolve the saber momentum. If you want to exist forever, then voluntarily integrate into my saber intent at the perfection level, and help me evolve the saber momentum. By then, you will all become the cornerstone of my Saber Dao. In the future, if my saber path transcends, you can also exist forever!"

Lin Fei said calmly. He was doing the same as he did in the Nine Profound Sect Martial Arts Pavilion. Using the method of "drawing a big pie", he "bamboozled" these saber techniques. Of course, it's not entirely a bamboozle. These saber techniques, once integrated into Lin Fei's saber intent then evolved the saber momentum. These saber techniques could indeed exist forever.

However, it was very difficult.

Now, Lin Fei had only comprehended the saber intent. He hadn't even evolved the saber momentum yet. What if he got killed halfway through? Then the so-called Saber Dao will naturally become empty talk.

However, for these saber techniques, whether they were willing or not, it was all voluntary. Some saber techniques were willing to gather dust on the bookshelves, unknown for a lifetime. But some saber techniques were willing to make a big splash, to stand out.

Therefore, Lin Fei's words were voluntary on both sides, not forced. If there were those who were willing to integrate into his saber intent and become the cornerstone of his Saber Dao, he would naturally be happy.

Lin Fei showed a pure saber essence, emitting a terrifyingly sharp edge. If Lin Fei wanted these saber techniques to voluntarily integrate into his saber intent at the perfection state, he naturally needed to demonstrate some characteristics worth following for these saber techniques.

For instance, his saber essence, which was like a real treasured saber, was invincible. Moreover, his saber intent integrated the saber intent of pulling the saber and the heavenly saber, which was very special.

Martial artists choose martial arts. But why wouldn't martial arts have a choice to choose martial artists? Now, it's time for these saber techniques to choose Lin Fei.

"The Ripple Saber Technique at the perfection stage is willing to integrate into your saber intent to increase the foundation of saber intent."

"The Shadow Saber Technique at the perfection stage is willing to integrate into your saber intent to increase the foundation of saber intent."

"The Swallow Saber Technique at the perfection stage is willing to integrate into your saber intent to increase the foundation of saber intent."

In Lin Fei's mind, the system's voices sounded one after another. These were all saber techniques that voluntarily integrated into his saber intent.

However, these saber techniques were all acquired-level. So far, at least, none of the innate-level saber techniques were willing to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent.

These acquired saber techniques might be numerous. However, without the integration of innate saber techniques, it was too difficult for Lin Fei to evolve the saber momentum.

Even though the royal family had a deep foundation and many acquired saber techniques, most acquired saber techniques were similar to the Nine Profound Sect's acquired saber techniques. They couldn't increase the cultivation progress of saber intent by much.

Lin Fei's saber intent cultivation progress was slowly improving.

56%, 57%, 58%, 59%, 60%......

Indeed, it was very slow.

Gradually, Lin Fei didn't even know how many acquired saber techniques he had integrated. Finally, the cultivation progress of his saber intent also stopped. It finally froze at the number 78%. Compared to the previous 55%, it had only increased by 23%. However, there was still a gap from 78% to 100%.

"Not a single innate saber technique is willing to integrate into my saber intent?"

Lin Fei frowned. Back at the Nine Profound Sect, even saber techniques like the Three Abyssal Sabers, Twenty-Three Sabers, and so on, all voluntarily integrated into his saber intent. But in the secret martial arts collection of the royal family, it seemed that these innate-level saber techniques were all very aloof. They were unwilling to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent.

"If I evolve the saber momentum. All innate-level saber techniques will be independently presented in my saber momentum. You will no longer be ordinary. You will all become unique saber techniques!"

Lin Fei spoke again. The next moment, Lin Fei clearly felt it. It was as if a surge of extremely sharp breaths suddenly awakened.

The so-called saber momentum, in fact, was the martial artist who integrated all the saber techniques learned into a powerful suppressing force.

In the saber momentum, there could be individual saber techniques present. Even some saber techniques carry unique saber intents, all could be presented in the saber momentum.

That is to say, once covered by the saber momentum, the enemy might face attacks from countless kinds of saber techniques and saber intents. This was the terrifying aspect of saber momentum!

Of course, many martial artists integrated saber intent and saber techniques completely. But Lin Fei made a promise he would retain these saber techniques in the saber momentum. He did not believe those innate-level saber techniques would remain indifferent to his words.

The next moment, in Lin Fei's mind, the system's voice indeed sounded.

"The Perfection Stage Eternal Night Saber Technique is willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress increased by 5%."

"The Perfection Stage Samsara Saber Technique is willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress increased by 5%."

"The Perfection Stage God Slaying Saber Technique is willing to integrate into your saber intent, increasing the foundation of saber intent."

"Your saber intent cultivation progress increased by 5%."

With the fall of Lin Fei's words, one after another saber techniques were willing to integrate into Lin Fei's saber intent actively. Moreover, they all could improve the cultivation progress of saber intent by 5% in one go. This indicated that these saber techniques were all innate-level saber techniques.

Moreover, they were almost comparable to the Three Abyssal Sabers, Twenty-Three Sabers among the innate-level ones. They could be considered top-notch saber techniques!

Lin Fei's saber intent was making rapid progress all the way.

83%, 88%, 93%, 98%......

"Boom."

Lin Fei's mind was booming. Finally, when Lin Fei's saber intent cultivation progress reached 100%, his saber intent began its metamorphosis!

184. Evolving Saber Momentum, I Am the Saber Saint!

Saber intent, invisible and intangible! It's purely a force that cannot be seen or touched but could be sensed, closely relate to the spirit and will.

But now, as Lin Fei's saber intent began to metamorphose.

Gradually, above Lin Fei's head, the entire royal martial arts secret treasury, a layer of translucent light appeared faintly, as if shrouded in mid-air.

A terrifying pressure arrived instantly! If it was an acquired martial artist, or even a Qi Condensation cultivator, stepping into this translucent light, even moving was probably a luxury.

Saber Momentum!

Lin Fei was overjoyed. He immediately understood his saber intent was finally starting to evolve into saber momentum! And this was just the beginning of the evolution.

Saber momentum, not completely materialized, was between tangible and intangible. It was translucent. This also meant saber momentum could interfere with a little bit of reality. No longer was it an empty and void force but a visible and tangible peculiar power.

At this moment, within Lin Fei's saber momentum, there seemed to be countless types of saber intents. There were sky saber intent, plucking saber intent, abyss saber intent, etc. And there were countless types of saber techniques.

As long as Lin Fei is willing,

"Whoosh."

the next moment, a strand of saber energy flew out and transformed into several large sabers. Suddenly, these large sabers automatically executed some profound innate-level saber techniques. It's as if there were countless saber masters hiding in the saber momentum.

Lin Fei was shocked. This is the terrifying aspect of saber momentum. Once a martial artist's saber intent evolved into saber momentum, the number no longer had any significance.

Moreover, under the coverage of saber momentum, to those who were weaker than oneself, it's completely crushing.

Even for those at the same level, for example, other Martial Saints, or other Foundation Establishment True Persons, Lin Fei's saber momentum would have a clear advantage.

With the blessing of saber momentum, the power of any saber technique would be extremely terrifying. Therefore, once a Martial Saint understood saber momentum, there would be another name. Saber Saint!

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei pointed out. A strand of saber essence erupted instantly. This was a saber technique that Lin Fei had never used before. The Three Abyssal Sabers!

"Whoosh."

Another strand of saber essence flew out. This was also a saber technique that Lin Fei had never used before. The Twenty-Three Sabers! There were also the Eternal Night Saber Technique, the Samsara Saber Technique, the God Slaying Saber Technique, and so on.

Strand after strand of saber energy flew out one after another. What they were executing were different saber techniques. As long as they were under the cover of saber momentum, these saber essences were as if they had "come alive."

With the support of saber momentum, saber essence could even fight on its own! Moreover, because Lin Fei's saber essence was closely related to saber momentum, when saber essence fought within the saber momentum, the scattered saber essence would also be re-collected by saber momentum aside from the necessary loss, continuing to converge into other saber essences to fight. This greatly reduced the combat consumption of saber energy.

"No wonder only the Martial Saints who have realized saber momentum have the qualifications to be called Saber Saints! In the hands of saber saints, flying flowers and leaves are all profound saber techniques. Just a casual strand of saber essence is a mysterious saber technique."

Lin Fei was also shocked. If it was said that becoming a Martial Saint would have various "non-human" means. And now, with the evolution of saber momentum, Lin Fei found saber saint's various means were even more beyond the understanding of ordinary people, even other martial artists, martial arts masters, and grandmasters, Lin Fei was afraid it was hard to understand. These were two completely different levels of power and means.

"After building the foundation, life is elevated and fundamentally different from ordinary life. Realizing saber momentum, saber technique can be said to be reborn. Even, as long as I am willing, within the saber momentum, I can easily deduce many innate-level saber techniques. I can even comprehend saber intent of them..."

Lin Fei closed his eyes. The whole body was shrouded in saber momentum. Countless saber technique inspirations erupted in his mind. Just, it was meaningless. Lin Fei had already evolved saber momentum. No matter how strong the innate-level saber technique was, it was useless for him. Moreover, now, even if he integrated more innate-level saber techniques, it would no longer improve any bit of Lin Fei's saber momentum cultivation progress.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system panel to check his current martial arts situation.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Stage Martial Saint

Saber Momentum: Beginner (Progress 0%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

"Saber momentum, progress at 0. Innate saber techniques have no effect on saber momentum anymore."

Lin Fei stood up. This time, he was very satisfied he successfully evolved saber momentum. The terror of this saber momentum exceeds many people's expectations. Especially, there was only a Martial Saint three hundred years ago. Three hundred years ago, Although the Martial Saint of the Hidden Sword Sect was known as the Sword Saint, he didn't realize the Sword Momentum.

Since the founding emperor of Great Chang, there had been some more Martial Saints born one after another. However, without exception, all of them did not realize Momentum. Only the founding Emperor of Great Chang realized the Momentum, So, he was invincible at his time.

The improvement of Lin Fei's strength by this saber momentum was not one or two times but a tenfold increase! In terms of combat, the role was incalculable! However, Lin Fei still did not forget what is the root of Martial Saint. That was still the level of cultivation. Now, Lin Fei didn't have Martial Saint martial arts. Saber momentum couldn't be improved. It almost reached the limit of strength.

Lin Fei looked at it in the martial arts secret stash. There were no Martial Saint martial arts. Presumably, the founding Emperor of Great Chang became a Martial Saint at the beginning. But there were no Martial Saint martial arts. However, Lin Fei was not in a hurry about this. So, he stood up and left the martial arts secret stash.

"Martial Saint, you are out."

Outside were some people from the royal family, who had been guarding the stash. Seeing Lin Fei come out, their faces showed respect. However, there was a hint of urgency in their eyes.

"What happened?" Lin Fei asked.

"Martial Saint, you've been in the stash for three days. Two days ago, there was an urgent report. The situation in the south has worsened, and two rebel forces have captured several prefectures. The court's rebel suppression army was disastrously defeated and almost completely lost. Now, in Chang City, the people are in fear. The court urgently needs a big victory to stabilize the people's minds."

Lin Fei looked at the other party. He should be from the royal family as well. Not some kind of eunuch. Otherwise, he wouldn't know so much about the situation.

At this moment, there was a dense sound of footsteps outside. Several elderly members of the royal family came. Upon seeing Lin Fei, the elderly members of the royal family quickly approached. And, they bowed deeply and said, "Martial Saint Lin, the emperor has decreed and conferred Ling Yao as the imperial princess. Can the Martial Saint set off now? The situation is worsening, if the rebellion is not quelled soon, I'm afraid..."

Lin Fei's eyes were deep. He said calmly, "Well. Since you have all met my conditions, then I shall depart. By the way, the Fairy Crane Sect and Water Moon Water Sect are behind this rebellion, right?"

"Yes, the Fairy Crane Sect and Water Moon Sect. Although they are not millennia-old immortal sects and have not produced Foundation Establishment True Persons in the past, their strength should not be underestimated."

Lin Fei remained noncommittal. He took a step and his figure shot dozens of feet away, only leaving behind a sentence echoing in everyone's ears.

"Within seven days, I will quell the southern rebellion! Stamp out the Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Water Sect's mountain gate!"

Having said that, Lin Fei's figure disappeared from everyone's sight.

For a moment, the royal family looked at each other. They were not surprised that Lin Fei could quell the Southern rebellion. However, stamping out the Crane Gate and the Moon Sect's mountain gate was another matter. After all, that's the lineage of the immortal sects.

Ordinary Foundation Establishment True Persons dare not claim they can stamp out these two great immortal sects even without the suppressing treasure of the sect. Is it really that easy to extinguish?

185. Nine Hundred Years Later, Saber Momentum Reappears!

Yuan Province, outside Green Dragon Prefecture. A massive Imperial army meant to quell the rebellion, but at this moment, it had been utterly defeated. Bodies were strewn everywhere, piled up like mountains. The thick smell of blood was nauseating.

The Imperial army of 150,000 intended to suppress the rebellion almost all were lost in this battle! The soldiers who escaped with the commander were even fewer than ten thousand left.

The commander, South Mountain Marquis, wanted to commit suicide with his own sword. Fortunately, his personal soldiers desperately stopped him, but the South Mountain Marquis was already disheartened.

The elite soldiers of the court were lost in this battle under his command. Even if he returned to the court, he would be thrown into the celestial prison. As for whether he would die or not, that would depend on his luck.

"Marquis, this battle was not our fault!"

"Yes, Marquis. Those immortal sect demons used spells, causing our army's food and morale to be destroyed. They even used the technique of turning beans into soldiers, causing our army to panic. "

"Not to mention an army of 150,000. Even an army of 300,000 would have to be defeated!"

"If the court does not send top immortals with the army, no matter how large the army is, it will be defeated!"

The subordinates of South Mountain Marquis were persuading him. They dared not let South Mountain Marquis commit suicide. Once South Mountain Marquis committed suicide, all of his subordinates, none of them could escape death. After all, the commander of the army committed suicide and they were still alive. How could that be possible? Therefore, they must desperately protect South Mountain Marquis. As long as South Mountain Marquis did not die, then they would still have hope.

"Immortals... Now where does the court have any top immortals to accompany the army?"

South Mountain Marquis sighed. When a country was about to perish, there must be demons! This "demon", South Mountain Marquis understood now. Those were the hidden immortal sects! But these immortal sects, each of them had vast and boundless spiritual power. The court was helpless, what more could he, a South Mountain Marquis, do?

"Report. Commander, there is a martial artist blocking our retreat ahead."

A scout reported.

"A martial artist, blocking our retreat?"

South Mountain Marquis furrowed his brows.

"South Mountain Marquis, the army was defeated, you cannot escape the blame. Now there is only one way, defeat the rebels, and suppress the rebellion. Only then can the merits offset the demerits."

At this time, a figure appeared to take slow steps. But each step seemed to span dozens of meters. In the blink of an eye, he had arrived in front of South Mountain Marquis. South Mountain Marquis was not an ignorant man. He immediately knew that this person was a master!

"Please enlighten me, master!"

South Mountain Marquis bowed respectfully.

"I have promised the royal family to come and suppress the rebellion. You gather the defeated soldiers and wait quietly." Lin Fei said indifferently.

"Even if I gather the defeated soldiers, how can they fight against those rebels? Those rebels have tens of thousands of troops. Even if the master is strong. But how can one man's power resist a huge army?"

South Mountain Marquis looked at Lin Fei with suspicion.

"No worries, you all wait here and prepare to take over Green Dragon Prefecture. I will suffice alone!"

"May I ask for your respected name?"

"Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei!"

After Lin Fei finished speaking, his entire person had already disappeared from everyone's sight. Upon hearing the name "Lin Fei", South Mountain Marquis was shocked. A look of disbelief appeared on his face.

"He... He is the Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect! The only Martial Saint of Great Chang!"

South Mountain Marquis was thrilled. The Martial Saint of Nine Profound Sect! His saber cut down a Foundation Establishment cultivator of Guardian Primordial Mountain! This matter had already shocked the world. How could South Mountain Marquis not know?

"With the Martial Saint here, success is guaranteed. Even if there is only one Martial Saint, those rebels will definitely be defeated! Immediately gather the troops, follow behind the Martial Saint, and return to Green Dragon Prefecture!"

South Mountain Marquis swept away his previous desolation. He became vigorous and spirited again.

At this moment, inside the prefect's Yamen of Green Dragon Prefecture. The leader of the rebels respectfully stood in front of several Daoists dressed in Daoist robes. Don't look at him as the leader of the rebels, however, the real decision-makers were these Daoists. Or rather, the immortal sects behind these Daoists!

Here, the Daoists were divided into two groups. One group was from Water Moon Sect. The other group was from Fairy Crane Sect. At this moment, Daoists from Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect were all beaming with joy.

"This time the Imperial army was utterly defeated, with the entire 150,000 army wiped out in a single day."

"Presumably, it will be difficult for the court to gather a large army in a short period."

"We can take this opportunity to continue attacking cities and taking territory, at least first occupy Yuan Province."

"Now that the royal supreme elder has passed away, the royal family is powerless to suppress the world."

"Not only Yuan Province, but also Xia Province must be occupied."

"We Fairy Crane Sect only want Yuan Province. You, Water Moon Sect, can occupy Xia Province."

"Our two sects, serving as each other's horns, will be enough to occupy the lands of the two provinces."

"As for other provinces, we can't reach out, there are other immortal sects."

The Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect both seemed to be looking forward to occupying Yuan Province and Xia Province. By then, their sects would be high above. With the people of the two provinces providing for the sect, that would truly be a heavenly life.

"But we must be cautious. Great Chang has a history of nine hundred years after all. What if that old man really left something for the royal family? Or if Great Chang's founder left something behind, then we might be in trouble."

The Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect Sect had not completely let down their guard. Therefore, even at the beginning of the rebellion, they were all tentatively testing the waters. It wasn't until the court had suffered defeat time and time again that they prepared to occupy the lands of the two provinces.

"Report! Leader, and all Immortal Masters. There is a martial artist outside Green Dragon Prefecture, who is walking towards here alone."

"A martial artist? Just one?"

The leader and all the Immortal Masters were somewhat surprised.

"Yes, just one person!"

The several Immortal Masters looked at each other. Their eyes were full of doubt.

"Let's go and see, who this person really is?"

So, a group of people went to the city wall of Green Dragon Prefecture. They came to the city wall. Looking into the distance, there really was a martial artist.

This martial artist was step by step, walking towards Green Dragon Prefecture. However, it seemed like a step. But one step was dozens of meters. Moreover, as he got closer and closer to Green Dragon Prefecture, his body, astonishingly step by step, walked into the air.

Crossing the air, walking in the void!

Seeing this scene, the Immortal Masters on the city wall, one by one, their faces changed drastically.

"Martial Saint! He is the Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect, 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei!"

A person's name can cast a long shadow.

Just hearing the name "Lin Fei", these high-level and top Qi Condensation cultivators trembled slightly. They even wished they could run away right now!

It's not their fault for being scared. The notorious "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei was just too infamous. When Lin Fei first became a Martial Saint, he killed the Foundation Establishment True Person Yuankongzi of the Guardian Primordial Mountain. This matter was even more earth-shattering. Everyone knew about it, it was well-known. Since then, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei had become a real and matchless fearsome figure in the eyes of all Qi cultivators! Absolutely not to be provoked!

"Retreat!"

At this time, a top Qi cultivator from the Fairy Crane Sect gritted his teeth and said.

"Retreat, abandon Green Dragon Prefecture! Martial Saint Lin Fei is coming, this person is not to be trifled with. We can only retreat! We'll leave first."

"Lin Fei is a martial artist, and also from the secular world, he shouldn't massacre ordinary soldiers."

"As for you, run if you can, may fortune be with you."

Without a word. the Qi cultivators of the Water Moon Sect Sect and the Fairy Crane Sect immediately urged their magical artifacts and fled frantically backward.

Lin Fei didn't even arrive in person yet. He was merely recognized and scared off tens of thousands of troops. In the eyes of ordinary people, the immortal masters, who were high above and omnipotent, even just hearing Lin Fei's name, were scared and fled in panic.

This scene stunned the troops of the court who were suppressing the rebellion outside Green Dragon Prefecture. They couldn't believe the scene before them.

Lin Fei alone, without even saying a word, scared off tens of thousands of troops! Even when the founder of Great Chang was sweeping the world and was invincible, it wasn't this exaggerated!

At this moment, even Lin Fei in the void was slightly stunned.

"They ran away?"

Lin Fei seemed a little surprised too. Those Qi cultivators were so decisive. Seeing him, without a hint of hesitation, they even immediately abandoned tens of thousands of troops and turned around to run! If it was before, Lin Fei really had no solution. But now, Lin Fei was not the same Lin Fei as before.

"Can you escape?"

A sharp light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

"Boom."

With Lin Fei as the center, a terrifying momentum burst forth.

Saber momentum!

Nine hundred years later, saber momentum reappeared!

186. The Arrival of the Martial Saint, Thousands of Troops Kneel Down

Lin Fei stood in the void. At this moment, his saber momentum exploded, like a large net, instantly covering the sky above Green Dragon Prefecture, suddenly enveloping the entire prefecture.

Immediately, the entire Green Dragon Prefecture seemed to be enveloped by a faint white light. Moreover, everyone seemed to suddenly fall into a quagmire. It was difficult to move! It seemed there was heavy pressure on them as if they were carrying a mountain.

"What... what's going on?"

"I... I can't seem to stand up."

"Such a heavy pressure, I can't even stand up."

For a moment, many ordinary soldiers, their hearts were filled with fear. Under the suppression of the saber momentum, whether they had a saber or not, it didn't matter. They all were suppressed.

Lin Fei took a step forward.

"Plop".

Tens of thousands of rebel soldiers, at this moment, couldn't bear the heavy pressure. They actually all fell to their knees. Whether they were ordinary soldiers or body refining martial artists, or even acquired martial artists at this moment, all fell to their knees as if greeting a deity.

This scene was very shocking. And Lin Fei was step by step, slowly moving to the sky above Green Dragon Prefecture's city wall. He looked down and saw the densely packed rebels on the ground and some ordinary people. Now they were all kneeling on the ground.

A single person suppressed tens of thousands of troops! This is a Saber Saint! Even a Martial Saint couldn't do this, only the Saber Saint who had evolved "saber momentum" could reach this level.

By now, in the eyes of ordinary people, Lin Fei was actually no different from a deity! However, in Green Dragon Prefecture, there were still some people struggling. For example, those few Qi cultivators.

When Lin Fei's saber momentum descended, the Qi cultivators activated their magical artifacts and turned into a streak of light. When they tried to escape, they found their bodies shook. Then, they all fell to the ground as if carrying a mountain on their bodies, making them unable to move.

"Impossible, this... what on earth is going on?"

"A Martial Saint couldn't possibly have this kind of power. Even if it's saber intent, no matter how strong the saber intent is, no matter how strong the Martial Dao True Intent is, it wouldn't make it impossible for us to even move an inch."

"Move, move!"

"Lin Fei hasn't even made a move. What is this method?"

Some Qi cultivators hadn't fallen to their knees. They were only suppressed on the ground. Their spiritual power was surging and their magical artifacts were shaking. There was a faint struggle that was resisting Lin Fei's saber momentum.

Lin Fei came to the top of these Qi cultivators. His eyes coldly looked at them. When had Qi cultivators ever been so embarrassed?

"Kneel down!"

Lin Fei's voice was calm. Yet it was like thunder, ringing in the ears of the Qi cultivators. Suddenly, the saber momentum pressed down again.

"Plop".

These few Qi cultivators finally knelt down as well. Like the other rebels, they all knelt on the ground. Their knees seemed to have grown roots, firmly stuck to the ground. These Qi cultivators felt as if they were going to suffocate. All of them looked at Lin Fei in the void with horrified expressions.

Is this the Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect who cut down the Foundation Establishment stage with a saber?

Their hearts were already filled with shock. In their sects, in fact, there were also records of some methods of the Martial Saints. However, although the Martial Saints were strong, they were not strong enough to this extent. They hadn't even made a move yet, they were immobilized by the mere pressure. Of course, they didn't know about the existence of saber momentum. Only some ancient Immortal Sects could know about the existence of "momentum".

They just felt that Lin Fei's pressure was too terrifying. So much so that they couldn't even lift their heads. These Qi cultivators felt suffocated. They felt extremely suffocated in their hearts.

As a respectable Qi cultivator, apart from the elders of their sect. When had they ever knelt to someone? Especially, to kneel to a martial artist! Even if Lin Fei was a Martial Saint, so what? They were the lofty Qi cultivators! They were Immortal Masters!

But now, all their pride had been shattered. They had knelt down right in front of Lin Fei. And no matter what they tried to do, it was wishful thinking even to stand up. Lin Fei just stood quietly in the void.

At this moment, it was quiet in Green Dragon Prefecture. Tens of thousands of rebels had knelt down. Even the lofty Immortal Masters were kneeling on the ground. This scene was witnessed by the distant imperial armies assigned to suppress the rebellion. The imperial armies seemed unable to believe the scene before them.

What was this? A miracle?

Lin Fei was just one person, even if he was a Martial Saint. He had only ascended above Green Dragon Prefecture. There was no sign of him taking action. And yet, an army of ten thousand had knelt! Even those arrogant, lofty Immortal Masters, too obediently knelt on the ground.

"Is this the power of a Martial Saint?"

This thought unconsciously flashed through many people's minds. The power of a Martial Saint was terrifying! When a Martial Saint arrived, ten thousand soldiers knelt!

For a moment, the morale of the imperial armies surged. With such an invincible Martial Saint, what couldn't they conquer?

Lin Fei didn't care if the morale of the imperial forces surged. To him, whether the morale of the army was high or not, it didn't matter much. When his saber momentum was released, whether it was an army of one hundred thousand or several hundred thousand, it didn't matter, even the slightest movement was wishful thinking. Sure enough, a Martial Saint with or without saber momentum was a completely different concept!

Lin Fei had been silent the whole time. The Qi cultivators below couldn't bear it any longer.

One of the top Qi condensation cultivators gritted his teeth and said loudly, "Martial Saint, you are a lofty Martial Saint. We, the Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect admit that we have never troubled any member of the Nine Profound Sect. We dare not provoke you, Martial Saint. Now, the entire world is suffering due to the incompetence of the royal family, causing the people to rise up and resist. We only hope to end the war as soon as possible and provide a stable environment for the people, because we cannot bear to see the people suffer from the saber and soldiers. Where is our wrongdoing?"

Lin Fei looked coldly at this Qi cultivator. Everyone knew the real reason these Qi cultivators supported the rebels. It was for the benefit of their sects. Arguing was meaningless, so Lin Fei wouldn't argue.

"Whether there is a mistake or not, I'm too lazy to think about it. You rebelled and supported the rebels. I don't allow it. If I don't allow it, then it's a serious crime! And furthermore, the crime is unforgivable and must be punished!"

With those words, a strand of saber essence flew out from his body.

"Whoosh".

The saber essence instantly transformed into a big saber, directly chopped down at the top Qi Condensation cultivator. Suddenly, this top Qi condensation cultivator let out a scream. But he couldn't move at all. He could only watch as the saber essence cut into his own head.

"Thump".

This top Qi Condensation cultivator was directly split into two halves by the saber essence. His body fell to the ground. The other Qi Condensation cultivators' faces turned pale, even their bodies were trembling.

"Not only are you guilty, but the Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect are also guilty. I will personally pay a visit to the Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect and sever their lineage as a warning!"

Lin Fei's tone was calm. But the content made several Qi cultivators' faces change instantly. In their hearts, they couldn't help but feel a sense of fear.

187. Great Chang Has No Immortals

"No, no one can destroy our two great sects. Even a Martial Saint can't..."

Several Qi cultivators were utterly terrified.

Destroy the sect! Exterminate the lineage!

These were things they would not even think about under normal circumstances. But now, Lin Fei, this Martial Saint, said he wanted to destroy their sect. The words of a Martial Saint especially one who could slash a Foundation Establishment True Person with his saber were indeed quite intimidating.

For a moment, all these Qi cultivators became terrified. Lin Fei was indifferent. Regardless of whether he could destroy the two sects or not, he would not let these people go.

Thus, Lin Fei extended his hand. Then, he flicked his finger.

"Whoosh whoosh whoosh".

Next, strands of saber essence flew out. In an instant, they struck these Qi cultivators.

"Splash".

For a moment, the ground was covered in blood. Several Qi cultivators from the Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect were all killed by Lin Fei.

"Next up, Fairy Crane Sect!"

Lin Fei's gaze looked at the distant void. Fairy Crane Sect and Water Moon Sect. The royal family naturally had the locations of the two sects. The locations of all the sects in the world were all under the control of the royal family. When leaving Chang City, Lin Fei had already received the map. He knew the specific locations of the two sects.

Soon, the South Mountain Marquis's army entered Qinglong Prefecture. They completely controlled Qinglong Prefecture. Some of the high-ranking members and leaders of the rebels were all controlled by the suppressive forces.

The remaining regions didn't even need to bother. Because there weren't many rebels in those places. They were all a group of disorganized mobs. Without the Qi cultivators, even if only ten thousand men remained in the suppressive forces, they could easily crush them.

"Marquis of South Mountain, I'll leave this place to you. I still have to go and destroy the sects of the Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect."

After finishing his words, Lin Fei took a step out. In a few leaps and bounds, he disappeared from sight. However, when the Marquis of South Mountain heard Lin Fei's voice, he seemed not to have come back to his senses. What had he just heard? Lin Fei was going to destroy the sects of the Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect?

How could that be possible? Those were Immortal Sects! Lofty Immortal Sects!

In the realm of Great Chang, there existed numerous secluded immortal sects. They had persisted for over a millennium, some even for several millennia, witnesses to the cyclic rise and fall of dynasties. Even the Great Chang Founding Emperor was powerless against them. Perhaps only those who could decimate Foundation Establishment True Persons could do that!

In fact, such feats had occurred. Once, the Great Chang Founding Emperor had slain many a Foundation Establishment True Person. The original royal supreme elder, when suppressing the world, had likewise slain many Foundation Establishment True Persons. Yet, to slay a Foundation Establishment True Person was an entirely different concept from eradicating the immortal sect's lineage.

"Great Chang is on the brink of significant upheaval…" the Marquis murmured in a low voice.

...

Seeking Immortal Town.

Initially, this place harbored no settlement. However, centuries prior, rumors spread of an immortal residing here. Thus, gradually, many were drawn here in an attempt to find the immortal or to try their luck, hoping to gain an immortal's favor. So, this place gradually buzzed with a lot more activity. Eventually, a town formed and named Seeking Immortal Town!

At this moment, two young men arrived in Seeking Immortal Town.

"Here we are, Seeking Immortal Town. But all our inquiries have only yielded that to find an immortal, we must venture into the mountains beyond the town. Those immortals sometimes appear in the mountains. If we're lucky, they might accept us as disciples."

"What are we waiting for? Let's go! No matter what, we must find an immortal and become immortal disciples!"

These two young men traversed a thousand miles to reach Seeking Immortal Town in pursuit of an immortal. Or rather, hoping for an immortal's favor. They had once seen an immortal in their hometown. A figure of elegance and charm, idly wandering among the mortals. A sight that kindled their envy.

Of course, what was most critical was that their closest relatives were of great age. They hoped to find some immortal elixir for their loved ones. Perhaps it might extend their years.

The two young men, resolved and undeterred, immediately left Seeking Immortal Town for the mountains. The mountains were fraught with wolves and leopards, a realm of great peril, most would dare not venture within. But for the young men seeking the immortal, they paid no heed to the danger.

They wandered in the mountains for several hours and even encountered danger en route. If they had not been armed with beast-repelling powder, they would have likely perished within this woodland. Let alone the immortal, they didn't even glimpse a shadow of one.

"Alas, it seems we are not destined for the immortal's favor. Immortals place great importance on this destiny. Without this destiny, even if an immortal were before us, we would not see. Perhaps this mountain is indeed haunted by immortals. But the immortals refuse to see us. Even if we waited ten days, a month, or even a year, we would likely never find an immortal."

The two young men felt a bitter disappointment. They had been seeking immortals for such a long time, And naturally knew that immortals valued "destiny."

With destiny, they could encounter immortals wherever they went. Without destiny, even if an immortal were before them, they would not recognize it.

Just as their spirits were dampened and they were preparing to leave, suddenly, one of the young men widened his eyes abruptly, looking into the far-off void.

"Ah... An immortal! It's really immortal! Have we finally encountered an immortal?"

The two young men watched a silhouette materialize in the void. One step at a time, it descended from the void, landing at the foot of the nearby mountain. For a moment, the two young men were overcome with excitement.

"Hurry, let's go ask the immortal to take us as disciples!"

The two young men decisively, immediately sprinted towards the "immortal's" silhouette in the distance. Soon, they saw the "immortal" standing at the foot of the mountain, seemingly inspecting the grand mountain.

The two young men gathered their courage and immediately approached. With a thud, the two young men fell to their knees, and reverently they said, "Oh, esteemed immortal, please accept our obeisance! We were able to see you, which surely signifies our destined bond. We hope for your mercy to accept us as disciples!"

Without further ado, the two young men prostrated themselves. However, just as they were about to bow, They felt a sudden tightening around them and found they could not move at all, let alone bow their heads.

"No need for prostration. Moreover, I am not immortal."

Lin Fei spoke indifferently. The two young men were just ordinary people. He had noticed them long ago. He just didn't expect that these two young men would mistake him for an immortal.

"Ah? Not an immortal?"

The two young men had seen Lin Fei descend from the sky. Such a divine technique, even if he was not immortal, he must not be far from it. Thinking this, the two young men immediately said, "Even if you are not immortal, you must be nearly one. We wish to become your disciples!"

Lin Fei turned to look at the two young men.

"I am a martial artist, not an immortal. Furthermore, there are no immortals here," Lin Fei spoke indifferently.

"A martial artist?"

The two young men were taken aback. They naturally knew of martial artists, those strong and formidable wanderers. But, the gap with the "immortal" before them was too vast. How could he be a martial artist?

"We came from the Seeking Immortal Town. The people there all said that this place is frequently visited by immortals."

"Indeed, for hundreds of years, it's been said that immortals haunt this place. How can there be no immortals?"

The two young men were somewhat disbelieving of Lin Fei's words.

"This is the mountain of the Fairy Crane Sect. It's merely the ordinary disciples of the Fairy Crane Sect that appear here. Their occasional appearances have led many people to mistakenly believe that there are immortals here. Those disciples of the Fairy Crane Sect are just Qi Condensation cultivators. They are like you, only with a lifespan of a hundred or so years. How dare these mere Qi Condensation cultivators dare to call themselves immortals?"

"Ah? Qi Condensation cultivators..."

The two young men were having their eyes opened today. They hadn't expected that this "martial artist" would say that there were no immortals here at all. Only Qi Condensation cultivators!

"Alright, you should leave. There will be a great battle today. I intend to destroy the mountain gate of the Fairy Crane Sect to avoid involving you."

With a wave of Lin Fei's hand, A strand of his saber essence directly took the two young men several hundred meters away. The two young men were astounded. Such a technique was no different from that of an immortal. As to whether he was immortal or not, what difference would it make?

"May we ask, senior, to which martial arts sect do you belong?"

"We also want to become powerful martial artists like you!"

The two young men shouted.

"If you wish to practice martial arts, go to the Nine Profound Sect! Remember, Great Chang has no immortals. Do these mere sects even deserve to be called immortals? Today, I shall trample the Fairy Crane Sect to the ground!"

Lin Fei's words echoed in the ears of the two young men. The next moment, they saw Lin Fei, step by step, walking in mid-air, as though treading on the void!

"Fairy Crane Sect, your crimes of rebelling and causing the lives of innocents to suffer are unforgivable! Today, I will destroy the Fairy Crane Sect as a warning to others!"

Lin Fei's voice, resounding and mighty, echoed through the void.

188. Martial Saint Lin Fei Destroys Two Major Immortal Sects in a Single Day! The World is Shocked!

"Fairy Crane Sect? This martial artist wants to destroy the Fairy Crane Sect? But where is the Fairy Crane Sect?"

Both of the young men had remembered the Nine Profound Sect. Weren't they seeking the Immortals in order to gain powerful strength, like that of the Immortals? However, when Lin Fei said he would trample the Fairy Crane Sect, the two young men didn't want to leave.

How could they miss such an exciting battle? Although they were nearly several hundred meters away from Lin Fei, they were quite clever and felt that it was still unsafe. So they retreated further and further until they were a considerable distance away. Only then did they hide behind a big tree to watch.

"Is there really a Fairy Crane Sect?"

The two young men were somewhat puzzled. They looked at the desolate peak in the distance. Where is the Fairy Crane Sect?

Lin Fei stood in the void. He stood with his hands behind his back, gazing at the void in front of him. Without any response. His words fell, and there was no response from the Fairy Crane Sect.

The Fairy Crane Sect, after all, was a sect of Immortal Dao. There must be a mountain-protecting formation that ordinary people simply could not find it.

Even innate martial artists, martial arts Grand Masters, if the Fairy Crane Sect didn't open the mountain gate, martial arts Grand Masters would be just as unable to find it.

However, Martial Saints are different!

In Lin Fei's eyes, everything about the Fairy Crane Sect was clear at a glance. Since the Fairy Crane Sect did not come out, then Lin Fei didn't bother waiting.

"Buzz."

The next moment, Lin Fei exerted his saber momentum. Suddenly, a layer of semi-transparent light enveloped the void in front of him. The originally empty void, under the cover of the semi-transparent light, actually sent out ripples, just like the ripples of water. Then, the semi-transparent light rapidly extended. Layer upon layer of ripples, constantly stirring. Then, buildings appeared in the void. Even the towering mountain peak disappeared.

Instead, countless mountain peaks appeared. Various pavilions and towers, even the sound of cranes could be heard. And in the void, there were also countless Daoists standing in the air.

"Immortals?"

The eyes of the two young boys nearly bulged out. Such a heavenly landscape, if not immortals, then what else could it be?

However, the "immortals" that the two young men saw at this moment had faces full of terror. They looked at Lin Fei from a distance, and spoke loudly, "We were unaware of the arrival of the Martial Saint, and the Fairy Crane Sect has failed to greet you properly! But isn't the Martial Saint a bit too aggressive? If the Martial Saint is dissatisfied with our Fairy Crane Sect supporting the rebels, we can just withdraw. Moreover, we can promise not to support the rebels in the future, okay? Even, the Fairy Crane Sect can follow the example of He Mountain Dao, close the mountain for a hundred years, and ignore worldly affairs. Would the Martial Saint be satisfied?"

The sect master of the Fairy Crane Sect, a top-tier Qi Condensation cultivator at the eleventh level, stated the decision of the Fairy Crane Sect. In fact, this was also a condition. Even in the old times when the royal supreme elder was in power, they said the same to him. And of course, they acted accordingly. Being able to proactively concede to Lin Fei even actively closing the mountain gate was already the greatest concession that the Fairy Crane Sect could make.

Lin Fei's gaze was calm. He looked down from a high position, looking down at the group of Qi cultivators from the Fairy Crane Sect below. Even if they conceded, in their eyes, there seemed to be no trace of fear.

Perhaps, they were still thinking after several hundred years, the closure of the mountain would end. Or, the Fairy Crane Sect would give birth to a Foundation Establishment True Person and they could re-enter the world again.

Those thousand-year-old immortal sects are like this.

Even with a heritage of several thousands of years, when a powerful enemy appears, they would close the mountain gate, and could even close it for several hundred years. Avoiding and not coming out. Wait until the end of the powerful enemy's life, or after they disappear, then those immortal sects would come out one after another, re-enter the world and compete for worldly power.

"Immortal sects..." Lin Fei's eyes were cold, and he asked indifferently, "He Mountain Dao, Guardian Primordial Mountain, both have powerful magic treasures of the sect and mountain-protection formations. They can protect the sect and are not subject to the attacks of Martial Saints and Foundation Establishment True Persons. What does your Fairy Crane Sect have? It seems that you still don't understand your own situation. Now, let me help you understand better. Even if it's an immortal sect, there are differences. In front of me, you don't have the qualifications to negotiate terms!"

"Boom."

In the next moment, Lin Fei's saber momentum burst out in full force. Almost instantly, the entire gate of the Fairy Crane Sect was enveloped within it. Many Qi cultivators from the Fairy Crane Sect felt as if they were carrying a mountain on their backs and their bodies unable to move.

"Activate the mountain protection formation!"

The Fairy Crane Sect did not dare to delay. The mountain protection formation was activated instantly. With the opening of the formation, it isolated Lin Fei's saber momentum. However, Lin Fei just stretched out his hand. The next moment, infinite saber essence exploded from within his body. Gradually in the void, it condensed into a saber! A saber that was solid as reality and was several hundreds of meters high!

It was this saber that spanned across the void. Even through the mountain-protection formation, it caused numerous Qi cultivators to feel indescribably terrified.

"Slash!"

Lin Fei's hand waved lightly. Immediately, the several-hundred-meter-tall saber fell from the void, bringing the might to overturn heaven and earth. It fiercely slashed on the mountain protection formation.

"Crackle."

The earth-shattering collision that was expected did not happen at all. All the people of the Fairy Crane Sect seemed to have frozen in place all of a sudden. The mountain-protection formation that they had high hopes for actually couldn't withstand even for an instant.

"Crack, crack."

"Boom, boom, boom."

This mountain-protection formation was composed of six magic treasures. It could be called the strongest measure of the Fairy Crane Sect! Even a general Foundation Establishment True Person definitely wouldn't be able to break it. But now, these six magic treasures were all instantly shattered. The mountain-protection formation was instantly cut open by Lin Fei's hundred-meter heavenly saber.

"Rumble."

The several hundred meters heavenly saber fiercely descended, directly cleaving a mountain peak of the Fairy Crane Sect. Suddenly, the sky collapsed and the earth sank. Countless Qi cultivators from the Fairy Crane Sect tried to escape, but they couldn't.

Without the mountain-protection formation, Lin Fei's saber momentum instantly suppressed the entire Fairy Crane Sect.

"Kill!"

Lin Fei shouted in a low voice. The heavenly saber that had originally condensed, its saber energy had already dissipated. However, under the saber momentum, these saber energies actually re-condensed again. The heavenly saber was instantly divided into thousands of strands of saber energy. These strands of saber energy were as if they had grown eyes, flying towards the disciples of the Fairy Crane Sect who were suppressed by the saber momentum.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

Each strand of saber energy instantly pierced through the heads of a disciple from the Fairy Crane Sect. The Fairy Crane Sect had hundreds of disciples, but in less than a quarter of an hour, the entire Fairy Crane Sect had become dead silent. A thick smell of blood permeated the entire sect.

Lin Fei took one last look at the Fairy Crane Sect. In the void, countless saber energies converged once more.

"Heavenly Saber Art, Slash!"

The next moment, the several-hundred-meter tall heavenly saber in the void instantly fell.

"Rumble."

Countless mountain peaks of the Fairy Crane Sect were cut off by the heavenly saber. Rocks and mountains collapsed just like an earthquake. In the blink of an eye, the huge Fairy Crane Sect was completely buried in a pile of rubble. The Fairy Crane Sect was extinguished! Not a single disciple managed to escape. Even the lineage was completely cut off!

"Next, the Water Moon Sect."

Lin Fei did not even look at the Fairy Crane Sect. His figure disappeared in an instant, leaving behind two young men with stunned expressions and shocked faces. They had witnessed with their own eyes the destruction of the Fairy Crane Sect. That was the "Immortal Sect" in their hearts. However, such a prestigious Immortal Sect had ended up like this.

"I think we should go to the Nine Profound Sect to practice martial arts."

"These immortals are so weak, it's better not to seek the Dao of immortality!"

"Good, let's go to the Nine Profound Sect!"

The two young men also had the idea of practicing martial arts in their hearts. So, they quickly left the Fairy Crane Sect and rushed towards the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei didn't care about the thoughts of the two young men. He made another trip to the Water Moon Sect.

As before, the Water Moon Sect was even worse than the Fairy Crane Sect. Similarly, Lin Fei broke the mountain protection formation with one saber. He slaughtered everyone in the Water Moon Sect. And this time, many people outside the Water Moon Sect witnessed this scene. The Water Moon Sect was eradicated. News spread like wildfire.

In the thirteenth year of Yongqing of Great Chang, on the eighteenth day of the fourth month.

Martial Saint Lin Fei, with supreme power, in one day, successively eradicated the Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect, two major Immortal Sects!

The two major Immortal Sects, their lineage was severed, and everyone in the Immortal Sect was slaughtered to extinction!

When the news came out, the Immortal Sects were greatly shocked! The martial arts world was greatly shocked! The world was greatly shocked!

189. Two Martial Saints

Hidden Sword Sect, the world's number one swordsman, Liu Yibai, had been in seclusion for many days. The higher-ups of the Hidden Sword Sect were all anxiously waiting. They knew that Liu Yibai was in seclusion to break through to the Foundation Establishment stage and become a Martial Saint. Once successful, the Hidden Sword Sect would have a Martial Saint presiding over it again. This was of utmost importance for the Hidden Sword Sect!

However, so many days had passed, and there was no sign of movement. For a time, some of the innate elders of the Hidden Sword Sect were a little restless.

"Could it be..."

Some elders were worried in their hearts. They were about to speak to the sect master.

"Boom."

Suddenly, a huge Spiritual Qi vortex appeared in the void. A terrifying pressure emanated from the mountain.

"This is..."

Everyone's expressions were shocked, but there was a hint of joy in their eyes. That direction was the mountain where Liu Yibai was. Many people knew what was going on in their hearts. They all had a bold guess, but no one said it out loud.

Time passed little by little. About four hours later, the Spiritual Qi vortex disappeared.

"Clang."

A dazzling sword light flew out from the mountain and instantly rushed to the sky. At the same time, a vast momentum swept across the entire Hidden Sword Sect!

"Whoosh."

Everyone's eyes were fixed on the direction where Liu Yibai was. Then, they saw a figure. Liu Yibai!

Liu Yibai indeed appeared. He took step by step, incredibly crossing the air, walking in the void. He came to everyone's front.

Everyone was excited in their hearts. They were all martial arts masters of the Hidden Sword Sect. Naturally, they knew the significance of crossing the air and walking in the void.

"Elder Liu, have...have you taken that step?" An elder couldn't help but ask.

Liu Yibai nodded and said, "Yes, I have successfully built the foundation and stepped into the realm of Martial Saint!"

Liu Yibai's words made everyone in the Hidden Sword Sect incredibly excited.

The Hidden Sword Sect had a history of over a thousand years. It's not because they had many martial artists neither their swordsmanship was exquisite, but because of the Martial Saints!

Martial Saints born within the Hidden Sword Sect were not just one or two. The birth of each Martial Saint could preside over the Hidden Sword Sect for hundreds of years. That almost guaranteed the brilliance of the Hidden Sword Sect for hundreds of years.

Several Martial Saints had come out of the Hidden Sword Sect. Each Martial Saint could guard the Hidden Sword Sect for three hundred to five hundred years. Several Martial Saints could last for a thousand years. This was the essence of the Hidden Sword Sect!

What extreme devotion to the sword, what the number one sword in the world, what harsher on oneself, all of these were useless. The Martial Saint was the guarantee of the Hidden Sword Sect!

Since three hundred years ago, when the Martial Saint of the Hidden Sword Sect passed away, the power of the Hidden Sword Sect had been declining day by day. Facing the aggressive immortal sects, the Hidden Sword Sect was in constant retreat. It totally lost the spirit of being the number one martial arts sect. Even the Martial Arts Alliance. In fact, it was established by the Hidden Sword Sect. And the result? It was messed up by a Guardian Primordial Mountain.

Now, the Hidden Sword Sect finally gave birth to a Martial Saint. They could finally hold their heads high. They no longer feared those immortal sects.

"A Martial Saint, it's really a Martial Saint!"

"Hahaha, our Hidden Sword Sect finally has a Martial Saint again!"

"With a Martial Saint presiding, our Hidden Sword Sect can ensure hundreds of years of glory!"

For a time, many elders and martial arts masters were extremely excited. Liu Yibai's eyes also carried a hint of pride.

"Now, I am finally not inferior to others. I, the Number One Sword Under Heaven, should not be inferior to the Number One Saber Under Heaven. As for the conflict between the saber and the sword, I do want to spar with Lin Fei again."

Liu Yibai also had pride in his heart. Originally, he was the number one sword in the world and he was a martial arts Grand Master early on.

And the result?

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei emerged. Later, he became the Number One Saber Under Heaven. In the world, the number of saber users kept increasing. On the other hand, the number of swordsmen was decreasing. It was impossible for Liu Yibai to not have any thoughts about this.

All were martial artists. How could they be willing to lag behind?

His sword had not shown its edge in the world for thirty years. And now, it was time to show his sword! Once he made a move, it would be the Sword of the Martial Saint!

"Uh..."

Compared to Liu Yibai's ambition and warlike spirit even thinking of sparring with Lin Fei the Number One Saber Under Heaven, the sect master and many elders had somewhat unnatural expressions on their faces.

"Elder Liu, Lin Fei the Martial Saint of Nine Profound Sect, cut down Foundation Establishment True Person Yuankong Zi with his saber, his strength is unfathomable. Even though Elder Liu has become a Martial Saint, he has not yet consolidated his power. If you rashly take action, I'm afraid..."

The sect master hesitated to say. Liu Yibai was not an ordinary martial artist. He was the number one sword in the world! He represented the Hidden Sword Sect.

If he really competed with Lin Fei, in case he lost, the one who would be damaged would only be the Hidden Sword Sect. This was the burden of reputation.

Liu Yibai frowned. He wanted to say something more. Suddenly, a disciple of the Hidden Sword Sect flew to the front of the crowd.

"Report! The Martial Saint of Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei, in one day, successively wiped out the Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect, two major immortal sects! The two major immortal sects' lineage was severed, and all members of the immortal sects were slaughtered to the last man!"

As soon as the disciple's words fell, the elders, the sect master of the Hidden Sword Sect, and even Liu Yibai were all shocked. Deep inside, they were stirred with shock and horror.

Lin Fei's cutting down of the Foundation Establishment True Person, although shocking enough, some Martial Saints had done it before. However, destroying two major immortal sects and severing their lineages was truly too shocking! After all, those immortal sects' mountain-protecting formations were not so easy to break through.

As soon as Liu Yibai heard, he understood the gap between him and Lin Fei. So, Liu Yibai sighed deeply and said with a bitter smile, "I originally thought that after I became a Martial Saint, I could compete with Lin Fei. But now it seems, not only is the gap not closing, but it seems to be getting bigger and bigger..."

Liu Yibai knew very well. A martial artist like Lin Fei, with his unparalleled talent, once surpassed, would be too difficult for Liu Yibai to catch up again.

"However, slaughtering two major immortal sects, this is no small matter. Especially in the current situation, those ancient immortal sects will not sit idly by. Our Hidden Sword Sect is also a major martial arts sect, we can't just stand by. Perhaps, I'll have to draw my sword this time. Hiding the sword for thirty years, today I show it to you. Hahaha, I'm off..."

Liu Yibai, one man, one sword, laughing heartily as he flew out of the Hidden Sword Sect, heading straight for the Nine Profound Sect.

...

"Boom."

In a deserted mountain, in the void, a huge Spiritual Qi vortex suddenly appeared. A massive amount of heaven and earth Spiritual Qi poured down. Several hours later, a long howl sounded from the deserted mountain.

"Hahaha, I have succeeded in building my foundation, today I finally become a Martial Saint!"

Following this, a heaven-reaching and earth-piercing saber light, emitting unparalleled dominance and sharpness, instantly erupted from the desolate mountain, breaking through the void. Even the Spiritual Qi vortex in the sky was instantly split apart by this saber light.

Shen Lianxin, step by step, traversed the air, walking in the void.

Martial Saint!

Shen Lianxin had also finally achieved Martial Saint!

"Brother Lin, I have finally not lagged too far behind you. I wonder, whose saber is sharper now? Or even, who is the real Number One Saber Under Heaven?"

A glint flashed in Shen Lianxin's eyes. In literature, there is no first place, but in martial arts, there is no second place! He was also a saber practitioner. His heart was also very proud. In the beginning, he lost to Lin Fei. And now, he had finally become a Martial Saint. Naturally, Shen Lianxin also wanted to try whose saber was the real Number One Saber Under Heaven.

"Swoosh."

In the next moment, Shen Lianxin did not want to delay even for a moment. Stepping the void, he headed toward the direction of the Nine Profound Sect.

190. Immortal Sects' Decision

Inside the East Palace of Chang City, Crown Princess Ling Yao was dealing with a pile of complex official affairs.

"Report! Lin Fei, the Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect, in a single day, successively trampled over the Fairy Crane Sect and Water Moon Sect, two major immortal sects! Both major immortal sects had their lineage cut off, and everyone in the immortal sects was slaughtered!"

"Thump."

The pen in Ling Yao's hand fell to the ground.

"He really... destroyed the immortal sects..."

Ling Yao's expression was complicated. Not a single word Lin Fei had said seemed to be false. Every single word he said came true. Even the fact that she is now the Crown Princess, occupying the East Palace. She was already the next heir to the throne. Her status was incredibly prestigious.

But Ling Yao knew all she had now was all fought for her by Lin Fei. Without Lin Fei, she wouldn't even be a princess, let alone a Crown Princess. Back then, Lin Fei gave her two choices. Martial Dao or power. She chose power. She even carefully considered if she chose the Martial Dao, maybe with Lin Fei's help, she could achieve innate.

But what about becoming an innate martial artist?

If she did not become a Martial Saint, it would all be in vain. Even if Lin Fei would do everything he could to help her build her foundation.

But how much hope is there?

It's minuscule.

However, now seeing Lin Fei trampling over the immortal sects, she didn't know why there was a slight stir in Ling Yao's heart.

"Was I wrong?"

Ling Yao murmured softly.

......

In the towering Sky-Reaching Tower, one could not see its end at first glance. The Sky-Reaching Sect! One of the oldest immortal sects in Great Chang. At this moment, many top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators gathered within the Sky-Reaching Sect.

No one knew the current generation of the Sky-Reaching Sect actually had three Foundation Establishment True Persons! These three Foundation Establishment True Persons were always waiting for the right time. It was only when the supreme elder of the royal family reached his limit and passed away, the Sky-Reaching Sect began its layout. Their goal was to control at least half of the world's power.

However, they encountered a problem now. The three Foundation Establishment True Persons were sitting at the head. Below them were two rows of Qi Condensation cultivators.

"Dao fellows, the world is now in great chaos, and the people are suffering. The Great Chang royal family has lost its authority, and the world is vying for it! Our Sky-Reaching Sect, after hiding for hundreds of years, is now time for us to emerge.

However, recent news has emerged. The Fairy Crane Sect and the Water Moon Sect have been trampled and destroyed by Lin Fei, the newly promoted Martial Saint of the Nine Profound Sect. Everyone in the two major immortal sects has been slaughtered to the last, and their lineage has thus been severed.

When Lin Fei started to rise, he successively slew many Qi Condensation cultivators, respectively killed those from He Mountain Dao, and Guardian Primordial Mountain, and earned the title of 'Immortal Slayer Saber'.

Later, Lin Fei became a Martial Saint. He even used his saber to cut down the Foundation Establishment True Person Yuan Kongzi from the Guardian Primordial Mountain. Now, Lin Fei has trampled over the Water Moon Sect and the Fairy Crane Sect, acting recklessly.

Compared with the founder of the Great Chang from nine hundred years ago, he probably would not be outdone. With him around, the world of Great Chang cannot be extinguished."

Hearing the words of the Foundation Establishment True Person, many Qi Condensation cultivators also started to discuss. The Sky-Reaching Sect had been hidden for too long. Ever since the royal family's supreme elder suppressed the world, the Sky-Reaching Sect had been hidden for hundreds of years.

Unexpectedly, just as they wanted to emerge, vying for power in the world, and restore the glory of the Sky-Reaching Sect, there was a new Martial Saint Lin Fei! Moreover, all three Foundation Establishment True Persons of the Sky-Reaching Sect unanimously believed Lin Fei was probably not inferior to the founder of Great Chang. Even if he was not as good, he was almost there.

"If we let Lin Fei suppress all the immortal sects in the world. Wouldn't our Sky-Reaching Sect have to hide for another hundreds of years?"

"Lin Fei has just built his foundation to become a Martial Saint. In terms of age, he is younger than the three True Persons, and he could sit in Great Chang for hundreds of years. We can't wait that long!"

"Now is not the same as when the founder of Great Chang rose to power. We, the immortal sects, have been hiding for hundreds of years, and our accumulations are not ordinary. If it wasn't that the old man of the royal family had reached his limit, with our current strength, we might not have feared him."

"To ask us to endure for another hundreds of years, how is that possible?"

"Endure, endure, always endure! When will it end? We, the dignified Qi cultivators, have to bow down to those martial artists, how frustrating is that? Even Martial Saints, during our glorious days of the immortal sects, were nothing more than a pawn we could command at will. How dare they act against us as they do now?"

"Martial Saint Lin Fei must be eliminated!"

For a moment, many of the elders had a very firm attitude. They simply did not want to endure. They couldn't bear it any longer.

Lin Fei had just become a Martial Saint, and his lifespan was hundreds of years. If they really had to wait it out, not one of them could outlast Lin Fei.

In the end, they couldn't wear out Lin Fei, they would all have to die. As for whether the Sky-Reaching Sect could produce as many Foundation Establishment True Persons in the future. Or, whether they could be even more glorious than they are now. Who knew? It's not always the case that sealing the mountain would make them continuously strong.

The three Foundation Establishment True Persons looked at each other. In fact, they had a pretty good guess about these Qi cultivators' attitudes. Moreover, they didn't want to endure either.

It was not easy to achieve the Foundation Establishment stage. It was not easy to outlast the supreme elder of the royal family. Now another Martial Saint appeared and they were supposed to keep waiting? They couldn't take it anymore!

"It seems that all the elders have a unanimous opinion. That is to kill Martial Saint Lin Fei! Only with Lin Fei dead, can the world be ours, the immortal sects'. However, this matter cannot be accomplished by our Sky-Reaching Sect alone. We also need to inform the other immortal sects.

The Foundation Establishment of other immortal sects must also be unbearable now. Back then, the founder of Great Chang defeated each of our immortal sects individually. This time, we cannot repeat the same mistake. If we don't take action, that's fine, but once we do.

We must gather all our strength, and with the momentum of thunder and lightning, we will kill Lin Fei in one fell swoop! By then, the power of the world will fall into the hands of our immortal sects... Those martial artists can only be driven by us! Even to prevent things like the founder of Great Chang from happening again, we can even enact Martial Prohibition. All martial arts above innate will be completely abolished and destroyed! By then, no matter how many martial artists there are, if they can't even reach the innate level, how can they compete with our immortal sects?"

So, the Sky-Reaching Sect made a decision and immediately sent a message to the other immortal sects to join hands to deal with Lin Fei of the Nine Profound Sect. If they didn't take action, that was fine. Once they took action, they must kill Lin Fei!

...

Nine Profound Sect, in Lin Fei's cave dwelling, the sect master respectfully came into the cave.

"Elder Lin. Recently, all the major immortal sects have been very quiet. He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain have already sealed their mountains. Even those previously active hidden immortal sects have also stopped supporting the local rebels. It seems that they have all suddenly gone quiet."

Lin Fei slowly opened his eyes. It seemed that he didn't find it surprising. He spoke in a calm tone, "If there is no movement, then a storm may be brewing! Back then, the supreme elder of the royal family suppressed the major immortal sects for hundreds of years. At the same time, these immortal sects have also accumulated power for hundreds of years. Now the supreme elder of the royal family has passed away, but I have appeared. Sect Master, do you think those immortal sects will continue to endure?"

"This..."

The sect master questioned himself. If it were him, he definitely couldn't endure it. After all, Lin Fei is too young. Having become a Martial Saint, he can suppress the world for hundreds of years.

Those foundation establishment cultivators, not one of them could outlast Lin Fei. If they didn't make a move on Lin Fei now, then they would have even less chance in the future. Under such circumstances, how could the immortal sects remain indifferent?

"Martial Dao, Immortal Dao..."

Lin Fei murmured quietly. In fact, Martial Dao and Immortal Dao do not have much conflict. The resources each has are actually quite different. But why were the martial artists and Qi cultivators of Great Chang so tense in their relationship?

There's only one reason. Great Chang was too small. The whole "world" was also too small. It couldn't accommodate both the Martial Dao and immortal sects.

"Elder Lin, you are just one person. But there are dozens of immortal sects. Even the hidden immortal sects that have been passed down for thousands of years are more than ten. Once they really join forces, Elder Lin, how can you resist?"

The sect master asked with concern. Ever since Lin Fei destroyed the mountain gates of the Water Moon Sect and Fairy Crane Sect, he had completely broken with the immortal sects, there was no possibility of any reconciliation.

"I have my own plans, you may go..." Lin Fei said indifferently.

"Yes, Elder."

The sect master respectfully left the cave dwelling. However, he was still worried.

Can Lin Fei hold on?

191. The Arrival of Ten Foundation Establishment Stages

Inside his cave dwelling, Lin Fei sat alone on the ground.

"System."

Lin Fei called up the system panel. He checked his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

Saber Momentum: Beginner (Progress 0%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

In these few days, Lin Fei's fame spread throughout Great Chang. However, Lin Fei's martial arts had not improved at all. The progress of saber momentum remains at 0. No matter how many saber techniques Lin Fei integrated, they had no effect at all.

As for the martial arts realm, it was still in the early stage of Martial Saint. He didn't have the cultivation method of Martial Saint and could only rely on the saber essence accumulating little by little on his own.

The speed was too slow. At this rate, Lin Fei was afraid it would take hundreds of years to reach the middle stage of Martial Saint. That is to say, Lin Fei was truly stuck in a bottleneck now. It's not that he didn't work hard on his martial arts, but there's no way.

"According to the supreme elder from the royal family, back then, the founder of Great Chang, swept all directions, suppressed the immortal sects of the world, and established Great Chang. He didn't die of old age. He chose to leave Great Chang. Where he went, no one knows. Maybe he went out to sea. Maybe he disappeared to the south. Or even went to the north..."

Lin Fei murmured quietly. The more he knew, the more Lin Fei understood the feelings of the founder of Great Chang back then.

Probably, the situation of the founder of Great Chang back then was not much different from Lin Fei's situation now. He had become a Martial Saint and even comprehended saber momentum, sweeping invincibly, suppressing the world.

But what use was it? He couldn't make any more progress.

In Great Chang, this is the pinnacle of martial arts!

So, the founder of Great Chang didn't even want to be the emperor. He resolutely left Great Chang. Perhaps, he went to find the Dao. Martial arts is also a Dao! The founder of Great Chang might have gone to seek a stronger martial Dao.

However, no one knew whether the founder of Great Chang succeeded or not, whether he was alive or dead. After all, it has been nine hundred years. If the founder of Great Chang couldn't make any further progress in martial arts, he probably would have reached his life limit and died a long time ago. After all, Martial Saints just have a lifespan of five hundred years.

Lin Fei closed his eyes. The idea of leaving had already formed in his mind.

However, how to leave? And where to go? What would happen to the Nine Profound Sect after he left? What about his family? What about the situation in the world?

All of these matters need to be dealt with. However, of all these matters, actually, the most important and crucial thing was only one, the immortal sects!

If the immortal sects were not handled well, even if Lin Fei wanted to leave, he wouldn't be able to nor would he be at ease.

Back then, the founder of Great Chang suppressed the world and made all the major immortal sects seal their mountains. He probably had the same worries as Lin Fei does now. That is, he was wary of the immortal sects.

"The immortal sects are not all the same. What really left the founder of Great Chang helpless were actually only the top ten immortal sects. He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain are two of the top ten immortal sects. These immortal sects have a heritage of over a thousand years.

The mountain-protecting formation is guarded by powerful magic treasures. Even the founder of Great Chang back then couldn't break the mountain-protecting formation of those immortal sects. So, he couldn't truly sweep the immortal sects completely. He could only use another method to suppress the immortal sects to prevent them from causing trouble in a short period of time."

Lin Fei thought for a while. He probably could only use this method as well.

Among the top ten immortal sects, not everyone had a Foundation Establishment True Person. For example, He Mountain Dao did not. Although Guardian Primordial Mountain gave birth to a Foundation Establishment True Person, he was cut down by Lin Fei's saber. Therefore, it didn't have one either. Then, only the remaining eight major immortal sects were left.

"If the Foundation Establishment stages of the eight major immortal sects are all killed. Even if I can't break the gates of those immortal sects, at least I can make them dormant for several decades or even hundreds of years. By then, it should be enough time for me to go out and seek the Dao."

Lin Fei had a vague plan in his heart.

However, it would be very difficult to completely kill the Foundation Establishment stages of the eight major immortal sects.

However, now there was an opportunity. Lin Fei had destroyed the Water Moon Sect and the Fairy Crane Sect. This would certainly shake those immortal sects.

Now, the eight major immortal sects were quiet. But Lin Fei knew they were brewing a major event that would shake the world. Once the eight major immortal sects made a move, it would definitely not be a small matter.

Moreover, the eight major immortal sects were most likely to target Lin Fei. Unless the eight major immortal sects wanted to be like them during the time of the founder of Great Chang, being suppressed by the founder of Great Chang to the point of sealing their mountains. Otherwise, the immortal sects would definitely try to eliminate Lin Fei.

What Lin Fei was facing next might be eight, or even ten Foundation Establishment cultivators! After all, who said there could only be one Foundation Establishment stage in the immortal sects? Those immortal sects had been in seclusion for hundreds of years. How many Foundation Establishment True Persons have been born?

If Lin Fei faced them alone, this battle would indeed be very difficult! To face eight or even ten Foundation Establishment True Persons, even if Lin Fei was a Martial Saint, and has even comprehended the saber momentum, those Foundation Establishment True Persons also had powerful magic treasures passed down from the immortal sects a thousand years ago.

"However, I am not alone..."

A hint of a smile appeared at the corner of Lin Fei's mouth. He had sent out letters to the Hidden Sword Sect and the small town where Shen Lianxin was.

Although there was no reply yet, Lin Fei believed, at least, Shen Lianxin would definitely come! Because Shen Lianxin still owed Lin Fei a life! As for whether Liu Yibai would come, Lin Fei was not sure. After all, Shen Lianxin was a loner, a wanderer in the martial arts world. But Liu Yibai was different. Behind Liu Yibai, there is the Hidden Sword Sect. Every move of Liu Yibai represents the Hidden Sword Sect.

However, whether Liu Yibai comes or not. Lin Fei must win this battle!

"The founder of Great Chang was able to sweep invincibly and suppress the immortal sects, so can I!"

Lin Fei closed his eyes. He was slowly adjusting his state, adjusting his mood.

At this time, thinking about improving one's strength was simply impossible. Moreover, what preparation, what scheme, under the power at this level, actually had no effect at all. At this time, it was a competition of true strength!

Time passed bit by bit. Lin Fei kept his eyes closed. Nobody disturbed him. His state of mind, too, had completely fallen into a calm state.

"Whoosh".

Suddenly, Lin Fei opened his eyes. Just now, in that extreme state of mind, he sensed a slight fluctuation in the Spiritual Qi of the Nine Profound Sect. Although this fluctuation did not appear in the Nine Profound Sect and it was very faint, it was eventually caught by Lin Fei.

"Finally here?"

Lin Fei's eyes were calm. He then stood up and took a step forward.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei had arrived outside the cave mansion. Step by step, he walked through the air and arrived in the void.

"Since you're here, show yourself!"

Lin Fei's voice echoed in the void.

"What a Nine Profound Sect Martial Saint! We just arrived and you've already noticed. But noticing us doesn't mean anything, this time we came with a straightforward attitude to completely crush you!"

With the sound of the voice in the void, above the Nine Profound Sect, one figure after another had appeared. One, two, three, four, five...

Lin Fei swept his gaze over.

"Ten Foundation Establishment True Persons. You really think highly of me. I'm afraid that even the founder of Great Chang didn't have the treatment of being besieged by ten Foundation Establishment True Persons!"

Lin Fei looked at the ten figures in the void and said calmly.

195. Saber Momentum Mastery, Slaying Ten Foundation Establishments!

However, the evolution of the five saber techniques was still a lack of opportunity! As for what the opportunity was, Lin Fei already had a rough idea.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei's gaze was on the five Foundation Establishment True Persons. The five saber techniques were entangling with the five Foundation Establishment True Persons. In the end, it was just entanglement. To slay the five Foundation Establishment True Persons, Lin Fei's five saber techniques or Lin Fei's five saber essence was still not enough!

Lin Fei didn't hesitate anymore. He no longer had any reservations.

"Boom."

The saber essence in Lin Fei's body erupted in an instant. Strands of saber essence flew out from Lin Fei's body. Lin Fei almost erupted more than 90% of the saber essence in his body all at once.

Immediately, the five saber essence suddenly increased dramatically! The momentum of the five saber techniques also reached the peak all at once. The five Foundation Establishment True Persons had a chill in their hearts. But Lin Fei had already shouted in a low voice: "Slash!"

"Whoosh."

The five saber essence, the saber light surged and, moreover, it carried the terrifying oppressive power of saber momentum. He gave a fierce slash at the five Foundation Establishment True Persons.

"Boom."

The five Foundation Establishment True Persons let out a scream. Then, the entire void quieted down. They were dead! The five Foundation Establishment True Persons all had fallen! For a moment, the void was filled with a strong smell of blood.

"Your Three Abyssal Sabers have successfully comprehended and evolved the Killing Saber Momentum!"

"Your Twenty-Three Saber has successfully comprehended and evolved Fast Saber Momentum!"

"Your Eternal Night Saber Technique has successfully comprehended and evolved the Eternal Night Saber Momentum!"

"Your Samsara Saber Technique has successfully comprehended and evolved the Samsara Saber Momentum!"

"Your God Slaying Saber Technique has successfully comprehended and evolved the God Slaying Saber Momentum!"

"Shoo, shoo, shoo."

The five saber essence instantly came to Lin Fei's front. All of them emitted a kind of saber momentum. It's no longer saber intent but the real saber momentum!

"Take it!"

Lin Fei took the five saber essence into his body.

"Your Killing Saber Momentum merges with Heaven Saber Momentum."

"Your progress in training saber momentum has increased by 20%."

"Your Fast Saber Momentum merges with Heaven Saber Momentum."

"Your progress in training saber momentum has increased by 20%."

The system's voice sounded again in Lin Fei's mind.

Five types of saber momentum fused with Lin Fei's original saber momentum. Moreover, each saber momentum increased Lin Fei's progress in practicing saber momentum by 20%. Five types of saber momentum, that's 100%.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber momentum began to metamorphose.

"Your saber momentum training progress has reached 100%."

"Your saber momentum has broken through to Mastery!"

Lin Fei's saber momentum, from beginner, finally broke through to Mastery. The saber momentum was also undergoing earth-shaking changes. Bursts of terrifying pressure descended on everyone in the saber momentum.

At this moment, of the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons, only four Foundation Establishment True Persons were left. They saw Lin Fei slash five Foundation Establishment True Persons with one saber. Their hearts were filled with immense fear.

Who dared to fight anymore?

So, they all used their escape techniques, transforming into a light of escape, wanting to run away.

"Want to leave? It's too late!"

A sharp light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

Although the beginner-level saber momentum could suppress the Foundation Establishment True Persons, if they were determined to leave, they might really be able to escape. But Lin Fei's saber momentum had already reached Mastery. The power of saber momentum at the Mastery level increased several times.

"Suppress!"

Lin Fei let out a low shout.

Immediately, the saber essence in Lin Fei's body instantly merged into the saber momentum.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

Immediately, a large amount of saber essence, like raindrops, instantly pierced through the bodies of the four Foundation Establishment True Persons.

"Ah..."

The four Foundation Establishment True Persons screamed. Their bodies were pierced by the saber essence, pockmarked. It looked horrendous.

"Plop."

They all fell from the void, turned into a pile of mush. They were dead!

All Foundation Establishment True Persons had fallen. These were the top ten Foundation Establishment True Persons! They were strong enough to sweep across the entire Great Chang.

Seeing this scene, Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin were silent. The disciples and elders of the Nine Profound Sect, at this moment, couldn't believe their own eyes. They had seen the whole process of the fight. Ten Foundation Establishment True Persons were slain by Lin Fei alone. This was simply one man ruling the world! Even the founder of Great Chang probably couldn't do this, right? In fact, the founder of Great Chang was even inferior to Lin Fei!

Shen Lianxin looked deeply at Lin Fei. He slowly said, "Brother Lin, it seems that even if we hadn't come, you would have been able to slay these ten cultivators. Originally, when I succeeded in foundation building and achieved the status of a martial saint, I wanted to come to the Nine Profound Sect and compete with Brother Lin in saber arts again, to see who is the Number One Saber Under Heaven. However, it seems now that there's no need for competition."

Shen Lianxin was self-aware Lin Fei had evolved the saber momentum. If he were to fight with Lin Fei, in front of Lin Fei, he might not even have the qualification to unsheath his saber.

The saber momentum might only be oppressive to others, but for a saberist, even for a martial saint saberist, as long as he didn't evolve the saber momentum, it's impossible to unsheath the saber under the cover of the saber momentum.

This is the domineering nature of the saber momentum!

Liu Yibai also looked deeply at Lin Fei. He said in a deep voice, "Saber momentum, ah... In the history of my Hidden Sword Sect, many martial saints were born, but none of them could comprehend the sword momentum. The only martial artist I know who has evolved the momentum is the founder of Great Chang. I didn't expect that Brother Lin would also comprehend the momentum, and it's even the saber momentum!"

Liu Yibai was a member of the Hidden Sword Sect. Naturally, he understood the power of "saber momentum".

The saber momentum for a martial saint is just like the saber intent for an innate martial artist. A martial saint with and without the saber momentum are completely two different levels. A typical martial saint can deal with a Foundation Establishment cultivator, or he can suppress a Foundation Establishment True Person. But if a martial saint evolves the saber momentum, he can suppress four or five or even more Foundation Establishment True Persons. And that's by using his own power to suppress!

Like Lin Fei, a martial saint with exceptional talent, once comprehend the saber momentum, that's just like now, easily suppressed the top ten Foundation Establishment True Persons With his own power!

The strength shown by Lin Fei can already be described as invincible! At least, after this battle, the whole Great Chang would spread the name of Lin Fei as "invincible"!

"I must thank Brother Liu and Brother Shen for coming to the Nine Profound Sect this time to lend me a hand."

Lin Fei didn't forget Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin. After all, they came to the Nine Profound Sect and fought alongside him.

"Both of you, please stay in my Nine Profound Sect for some time. We can exchange views and discuss sword and saber techniques. Especially, the saber momentum. I will share everything I know."

Lin Fei invited Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai. For martial saints like Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai, what was the most attractive thing? It's probably Lin Fei's saber momentum!

Lin Fei was now the only one in the Great Chang who had evolved the saber momentum. Even, he was the second martial saint who had comprehended the saber momentum after the founder of Great Chang. Lin Fei was undoubtedly the saber saint!

If they discussed and exchanged views with Lin Fei, they would surely understand "momentum" more deeply. They might even find the direction to evolve "momentum". The two of them were naturally very interested.

However, Liu Yibai suddenly spoke, "Brother Lin, you have slain the ten Foundation Establishment cultivators, and your fame shakes the world. But this does not mean that you can rest easy. Foundation Establishment True Persons, when they die, they die. But as long as the immortal sects exist, there will be a constant stream of Foundation Establishment True Persons being born. The Immortal Sects are the fundamental issue!"

As Liu Yibai's words fell, everyone was silent. They naturally knew that the Immortal Sects were the fundamental issue. No matter how much damage the Immortal Sects suffered, as long as they close the mountain for a period of time, short as several decades, long as several centuries, they could recover.

Without destroying the Immortal Sects, the Great Chang martial artists and Qi Condensation cultivators would inevitably wage war again.

"Since the Immortal Sects are the fundamental issue, then I will shatter the Immortal Sects!"

There was a glint in Lin Fei's eyes.

...

In the thirteenth year of Yongqing in Great Chang, April 23rd.

The ten Foundation Establishment True Persons of the Immortal Sects set up a trap and attacked the Nine Profound Sect. The Saber Saint Lin Fei evolved the saber momentum and killed the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons!

When the news spread. The Immortal Sects were greatly shocked! The martial arts world was greatly shocked! The whole world was greatly shocked!

196. Unrivaled in the world

Chang City, the palace.

Ever since Ling Yao became the Crown Princess, the emperor even actively delegated some powers to Ling Yao. Therefore, Ling Yao was busy every day.

"Report! Internal strife has occurred among the rebels in Dong Province. The rebel leader was beheaded, his head sent to the imperial army's camp, and the rebels have surrendered!"

"Report! The rebel leader in Lu Province killed several of his confidants in one day. He led the rebels to surrender to the court, asking the court for judgment!"

"Report! Internal strife erupted among the rebels in Xia Province, several factions of rebels fought each other, the majority of the rebels were wiped out in the internal strife, and the remaining rebels were also defeated by our imperial army!"

With one report after another, Ling Yao felt something was not right. These should all be good news. But why is there a series of such good news?

One must know, Dong Province, Lu Province, and Xia Province were all breeding grounds for rebellion. Previously, they were causing chaos. It's just that they didn't make as much noise as the South. But if the court was not powerful enough to suppress the rebellion, given time, the rebels would definitely grow stronger.

But now, these rebels were either having internal strife or surrendering. It seemed that overnight, the whole Great Chang had become peaceful again.

But is this possible?

Ling Yao knew very well. Behind those rebels represented a number of immortal sects! As long as the immortal sects were not extinguished, the rebels would continue to appear.

"Go, investigate thoroughly what exactly has happened. Focus on the news about those immortal sects," Ling Yao immediately ordered.

About a few hours later, Ling Yao's subordinate hurried over. Even, his face had a hint of joy!

"Report! Crown Princess, the matter has been investigated. Just yesterday, the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons of the immortal sects set up a trap and attacked the Nine Profound Sect. The Saber Saint Lin Fei evolved the saber momentum and killed the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons! Now, led by the Sky Reaching Sect, the ten major immortal sects have announced that they are sealing the mountain!"

"Whoosh".

Ling Yao stood up abruptly. She was greatly shocked!

"As expected, it has to do with Lin Fei. Killing the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons of the immortal sects. All the major immortal sects have announced that they are sealing the mountain. They are scared. Even the founding emperor back then was no more than this..."

Ling Yao understood. She understood everything. In various places in Great Chang, the rebels were having internal strife or surrendering. Actually, it was because the immortal sects behind them had sealed their mountains.

The immortal sects no longer support the rebels. Without the support of the immortal sects, those rebels were just a mob. How could they last long? Therefore, internal strife occurred. And Lin Fei, with his own strength, suppressed the immortal sects!

The founding emperor of Great Chang, with his supreme power, swept across all directions, unstoppable. Finally, he established the Great Chang, forcing the major immortal sects to close their gates. This brought about long-lasting peace in the world.

"Killing the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons, Lin Fei is already invincible....."

Ling Yao murmured in a low voice. In the end, she fell silent. How much time has passed since Lin Fei said that he wanted to reach the peak of the martial dao? Ling Yao was still immersed in mundane matters, but Lin Fei had quietly achieved his initial dream. Unrivaled in the world! For a martial artist, this is the highest achievement!

Now, Lin Fei's words could determine the world. Even the Great Chang royal family had to look at Lin Fei's face. This was what Lin Fei said.

When martial arts is practiced to the extreme, one can control fate! Even, not only can one control their own fate, but also the fate of countless people.

"The path, after all, is chosen by me. Besides, it's already impossible..."

Ling Yao shook her head. She had chosen power. From then on, Lin Fei and she were people on two different paths. There were no more possibilities. It was her own choice!

......

In the main hall of the Sky Reaching Sect, everyone was silent. In the entire Sky Reaching Sect, there was only one Foundation Establishment True Person left. Because the two Foundation Establishment True Persons, True Person Tongxuan and True Person Tongguang, went down the mountain, and both were killed by the Saber Saint Lin Fei at the Nine Profound Sect!

"True Person, it seems that Great Chang can still have a few hundred years of national luck."

"Yes, who would have thought that a Saber Saint Lin Fei would emerge?"

"With his own strength, he killed ten Foundation Establishment True Persons, I'm afraid even the founding emperor of Great Chang was no more than this, right?"

"Lin Fei is truly the Saber Saint, evolving the saber momentum. Under the saber momentum, even Foundation Establishment True Persons have to weaken their strength by several times, even if they have precious treasures, they can only be slaughtered."

"I have to admit, the current Lin Fei is truly unrivaled in the world!"

"Unrivaled, just like the founder of Great Chang, truly unrivaled..."

Many Qi Condensation cultivators began to speak. When they received the news from the Nine Profound Sect, they even thought it was a tall tale.

A total of ten Foundation Establishment True Persons! The ten Foundation Establishment True Persons working together could sweep the entire Great Chang. But they were killed by Lin Fei with his own power. This seemed like a tall tale no matter how they look at it.

However, when they learned from other hidden immortal sects that those Foundation Establishment True Persons did not return and more and more news came in, they finally believed the ten Foundation Establishment True Persons were really killed by Lin Fei!

"Unrivaled..."

True Person Tongyuan, the only Foundation Establishment True Person in the Sky Reaching Sect, also sighed slightly, "Yes, Saber Saint Lin Fei is now unrivaled in the world. Just like the founder of Great Chang. Sweeping all directions, invincible, and dominating! Faced with such an opponent, our Sky Reaching Sect has only one choice, and that is to seal the mountain! As long as Lin Fei is there for a day, our Sky Reaching Sect will never come out! Although it's a bit suffocating, this is the way of survival for our immortal sects.

We have a mountain protection formation, at the Foundation Establishment level, which no one can break. As long as we endure until Lin Fei dies, or disappears like the first emperor of Great Chang. That will be our opportunity for the immortal sects! Didn't our Sky Reaching Sect survive in this way for a thousand years?"

The Qi cultivators of the Sky Reaching Sect also nodded one after another. The so-called immortal sects are like iron, and the dynasties are like flowing water.

The inheritance of the immortal sect lasts for hundreds of years, even for several thousands of years. No matter how many strong people are born in the outside world, as long as the mountain gate is sealed, the immortal sect is then cut off from the world. No one can do anything about it. As for the existence of an invincible power in the world, just let him be invincible. After hundreds of years, the immortal sect is still the immortal sect, but the invincible power in the world will die.

Thus, the Sky Reaching Sect announced the closure of the mountain. Not only the Sky Reaching Sect, but other hidden immortal sects also announced the closure of the mountain. As a result, almost all the immortal sects in the world have closed their mountains.

The entire Great Chang seemed to have fallen into peace. And the name of Saber Saint Lin Fei's invincibility also instantly spread all over the country.

Everyone knew Saber Saint Lin Fei, with his own power, suppressed all the immortal sects in the world. He was already like the founder of Great Chang. Unrivaled in the world!

197. The strongest saber and the strongest sect in the world

"Invincible..."

On the Ancestral Master Peak of the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei raised his head, looking at Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin. It was Liu Yibai who just mentioned that the entire Great Chang had been spreading Lin Fei's name of Invincibility recently.

"What kind of invincible am I? I haven't even been able to transcend saber momentum. Maybe I'm invincible in Great Chang, but on the road of martial arts, it is far from being invincible..."

Lin Fei shook his head. Compared to being invincible, he was more eager to continue to enhance his saber momentum. He was even more eager to continue to improve his cultivation.

In recent days, Lin Fei had been exchanging martial arts insights with Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin. Lin Fei was generous with his advice. He shared his understanding of saber momentum with the two of them. After all, the only martial artists in the entire Great Chang who were qualified to exchange ideas with Lin Fei now were Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin.

Moreover, Lin Fei also figured out that, if he wanted to evolve saber momentum, he needed to meet certain conditions. It must be top-tier innate saber techniques that could cultivate saber intent. Otherwise, it would be impossible to evolve saber momentum.

Moreover, these saber techniques must be used to defeat powerful enemies, even kill powerful enemies. For example, a Foundation Establishment True Person!

However, the first condition was actually quite difficult. How rare is it to have a saber technique that can cultivate saber intent?

The Broken Saber Flow and the Mountain Cleaving Slash could actually be considered top-tier innate saber techniques, but they couldn't cultivate saber intent. Naturally, it is impossible to evolve saber momentum.

Lin Fei also exchanged some saber techniques with Shen Lianxin. Shen Lianxin had obtained one saber technique from the ruins of the ancient martial arts sect. The Mountain-River Saber. And after countless years of practicing the saber, Shen Lianxin summarized numerous saber techniques into one saber, the Ultimate Saber Slash.

These two saber techniques had been integrated into Lin Fei's saber momentum. Just waiting to kill the Foundation Establishment True Person, perhaps it could evolve into saber momentum again. At that time, it would be integrated into Lin Fei's Heavenly Saber Momentum. It would continue to enhance Lin Fei's saber momentum, and even give the saber momentum hope to reach transcendence.

However, in the whole world of Great Chang, the saber techniques that can cultivate saber intent are very few. After all, the secret treasures of the Nine Profound Sect and the royal family almost collected all the saber techniques in the world. It's too hard to find pearls in the sea. And, cultivation techniques are also a big problem.

Lin Fei asked Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin. Neither of them had cultivation techniques at the Martial Saint level.

"Brother Liu, have the predecessors of the Martial Saints in the Hidden Sword Sect not recorded anything outside of Great Chang?" Lin Fei suddenly asked.

"Outside of Great Chang?" Liu Yibai looked deeply at Lin Fei. He slowly said, "Of course they have recorded. But, the predecessors also didn't know much. The Martial Saints of my Hidden Sword Sect, just know that if you want to leave Great Chang, you can only go to sea. But, what will happen when you go to sea, no one knows. Those who go to sea, whether they are Foundation Establishment True People or Martial Saints, none of them have ever come back. Maybe, going to sea is a dead end!"

Liu Yibai's words made Lin Fei fall silent. He raised his head, looking intently at Liu Yibai, and said, "Brother Liu, whether going to sea is a dead end, I don't know. But if we can't even find the cultivation techniques of Martial Saints in Great Chang, our martial arts will not make any progress. At most in five hundred years, like the supreme elder of the Great Chang royal family, our life limit will come and we will die. We can all feel it. Martial Saint is not the peak of martial arts! If we want to pursue the peak of martial arts, maybe, we can only leave Great Chang."

In terms of martial arts, Lin Fei was the strongest in the world and number one in the world of Great Chang!

But so what? A Martial Saint only has a lifespan of five hundred years.

Lin Fei had never forgotten what he was pursuing. His goal was longevity! Practicing martial arts can achieve longevity. So, he embarked on the path of martial arts. But, his longevity was not just a mere five hundred years lifespan. He hadn't reached the peak of martial arts yet.

Therefore, Lin Fei would continue to move forward. No matter how difficult it was, he would continue!

"If one day, I want to go to sea to seek the Dao. Brother Liu, Brother Shen, what are your plans?"

Lin Fei's gaze looked at Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin.

Without hesitation, Shen Lianxin immediately said, "I'm all alone in this life, and my dream is to reach the peak of martial arts! In Great Chang, I feel that I can no longer make any progress. Even if I exchange ideas with Brother Lin, it is very difficult for me to evolve saber momentum. But martial arts is not just about saber momentum. I can also practice martial arts techniques. I have other choices, other paths. So, if Brother Lin goes to sea to seek the Dao, please take me with you!"

Liu Yibai, however, was silent. He didn't speak at all.

Lin Fei slightly smiled and said, "It's okay, it's too early to talk about going to sea to seek the Dao. Besides, even if I want to go to sea, I have to take care of some things first. Like, the Immortal Sects!

These Immortal Sects, seal their mountains, living for hundreds of years, and then produce Foundation Establishment True Person. Then they come out of the mountain, causing chaos in the world, and vying for power.

This cycle repeats over and over again. If I leave, the Immortal Sects will reopen their mountains. By then, not only the Nine Profound Sect will be in danger, but even the martial arts of Great Chang will be in danger!

There is only one way to completely solve the Immortal Sects. That is, to destroy the mountains of these Immortal Sects!"

Lin Fei's words were filled with a murderous aura. In fact, how easy is it to destroy the mountains of those Immortal Sects?

Liu Yibai shook his head and said, "About those Immortal Sects' mountains, actually, the predecessors of the Martial Saints in my Hidden Sword Sect also mentioned them. These Immortal Sects, especially the top ten Immortal Sects, all have special magic treasures, connected to the earth's veins.

They connect the protective array of the mountain with the entire earth vein. If you want to destroy the mountains of these Immortal Sects, unless, you have the power to break the treasured objects of the Immortal Sects all at once. Or, destroy the earth veins of those Immortal Sects."

But, both of these methods are not very realistic. The founding emperor of Great Chang, who was also a Martial Saint, and who also understood momentum, couldn't break open the mountains of those Immortal Sects.

As for destroying the earth's veins, that's even harder. The earth veins of the top ten Immortal Sects, connect the entire mountain range, extending for thousands of miles. There's no way to destroy the earth's veins.

So, those Immortal Sects can sleep without any worries. The top ten Immortal Sects have already sealed their mountains early, intending to temporarily avoid your sharp edge, Brother Lin. To destroy the mountains of these Immortal Sects, it's difficult, too difficult!"

Liu Yibai felt that it was almost impossible. Lin Fei was also very clear. If the mountains of the Immortal Sects were so easy to destroy, how could they have been passed down for a thousand years?

The oldest Immortal Sects had a history of thousands of years, or even longer.

"It's okay, why not give it a try? Among the top ten Immortal Sects, which is the most powerful one?" Lin Fei asked.

"Sky Reaching Sect!" Liu Yibai immediately said.

"Sky Reaching Sect? Brother Liu, could you please take me to the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect."

Liu Yibai nodded and said, "What's so difficult about that?"

Shen Lianxin also said, "The strongest saber in the world, and the strongest mountain gate, are rare encounters! I have to see it too."

"Alright, let's go together! Let's see if my saber is sharper, or the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect is harder?"

Lin Fei stood up. With Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai also stepped into the air and disappeared into the horizon in the blink of an eye.

198. Six Sabers Fusion

The Sky Reaching Sect had already sealed their mountain. Just a while ago, after hiding from the world for hundreds of years, they were ready to come out and make big plans.

However, they were "scared" back by Lin Fei, the Saber Saint. Now, they were once again in a state of sealing their mountain.

The so-called sealing of the mountain is to let the protective array of the mountain run continuously. Moreover, the mountain gate is hidden. Ordinary people can't find it or see it.

If they need to open the mountain gate and enter the world, then the mountain gate will appear. Ordinary people can see and find it. This is what is known as "immortal fate."

Some people here can find the Immortal Sect and even join it. But some people, even if they dig three feet into the ground, can't find the Immortal Sect. It's because the Immortal Sect has sealed the mountain gate.

At this moment, three figures were walking in the air. They came directly to this mountain range.

"Brother Lin, this mountain range is known as the Sky Reaching Mountain Range because of the Sky Reaching Sect. There is a Sky Reaching Peak here that soars into the clouds. Even, the Sky Reaching Sect has an ancient magic treasure, the Sky Reaching Tower.

It's said that the Sky Reaching Tower is very magical, with all kinds of incredible abilities. The protective array of the Sky Reaching Sect is suppressed by the Sky Reaching Tower. For thousands of years, no one has been able to break the gate of the Sky Reaching Sect."

"Sky Reaching Tower..." Lin Fei looked up. He couldn't see the Sky Reaching Tower. In fact, let alone the Sky Reaching Tower, he couldn't even see the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect.

However, all three of them were Martial Saints. They were extremely sensitive to the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth. Therefore, they could clearly feel there was a rich Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth here.

The Immortal Sect could indeed hide from the world. It could restrain its aura and make it invisible to people. But it couldn't hide the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth.

Within the Immortal Sect, a large number of formations gathered together. The Spiritual Qi was like a tide. Even if there were blessed lands, it would be the same. After all, it's impossible for every disciple to practice in the blessed lands. They still had to rely on the Spiritual Qi of the outside world. Where there was an Immortal Sect. the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth would inevitably be rich.

"Brother Lin, for the task of 'greeting', it's better for me to do it."

At this time, Shen Lianxin spoke. His saber was already becoming impatient.

"Alright, then I'll leave it to Brother Shen!"

Shen Lianxin looked at the empty void in front of him with cold eyes. In his eyes, he couldn't see the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect either. But he could see a large amount of Spiritual Qi gathered in this void.

"Clang."

Shen Lianxin drew his saber.

"Ultimate Saber Slash!"

A saber light one thousand meters long tore through the void like a piece of cloth, piercing the heavens and the earth. Overwhelming, it slashed into the void.

However, such a huge saber light should have landed on the ground. Just that, as Shen Lianxin slashed out this saber, it was still in the void. It seemed to be blocked by an invisible force.

"Hum."

In the void, a faint glow emerged. Then, this light continued to tremble. Like ripples in water, spiritual Qi surged continuously. The empty void could no longer hide, it revealed a series of mountain peaks and there was also a black tower, soaring into the clouds.

Sky Reaching Tower!

Seeing that tower, anyone's heart would be shaken! That was really shocking. Soaring into the clouds, one couldn't see the end at first glance. It seemed to emit an endless aura of vastness, antiquity, and mystery. And each mountain peak seemed to have mysterious runes, densely packed. They also looked very ancient and mysterious.

This was the Sky Reaching Sect! The number one Immortal Sect in the world!

"Boom."

However, when Shen Lianxin slashed out the second saber. A huge roar shook the entire Sky Reaching Sect. For a while, many disciples and elders were awakened.

"What's going on? Why is the mountain gate shaking?"

"The protective array is shaking?"

"That's...three Martial Saints?"

"They're traversing the air, walking in the air. And there's no fluctuation of spiritual power on them. No doubt, they are Martial Saints!"

"News has already come from below the mountain. There are now three Martial Saints in Great Chang, the leading one being Saber Saint Lin Fei."

"Lin Fei is here?"

"What does he want to do? Our Sky Reaching Sect has already sealed the mountain, yet he's still not letting go. Could it be that he wants to break the mountain gate?"

"Even the founder of Great Chang in the past couldn't break the mountain gate of our Sky Reaching Sect. Just based on a single Martial Saint Lin Fei?"

"Hmph, let Lin Fei attack. He can't break the mountain gate of our Sky Reaching Sect!"

The many disciples had also guessed it. Saber Saint Lin Fei was not prepared to let the Sky Reaching Sect go. He was trying to break the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect.

The only Foundation Establishment True Person of the Sky Reaching Sect, also arrived in the void at this moment, looking at Lin Fei across the void.

"I am Tongyou. Saber Saint Lin Fei, you have slain ten Foundation Establishment cultivators, we, Sky Reaching Sect, concede! Now, our Sky Reaching Sect has announced the closure of the mountain, withdrew all disciples, and no longer interferes in mundane affairs. Saber Saint, however, has made a big fuss and come to our doorstep, isn't this a bit too much?"

True Person Tongyou looked at Lin Fei with a hint of fierceness in his eyes. The Sky Reaching Tower might have sealed the mountain. But it wasn't to the point where it could be slaughtered at will.

Lin Fei looked at True Person Tongyou, speaking calmly, "Too much? So it's okay for your Sky Reaching Sect's True Persons to attack my Nine Profound Sect, but it's not okay for me to come to your Sky Reaching Sect? True Person Tongyou, since I'm here today, I have to at least give it a try. Let's see what the current number one Immortal Sect has to offer?"

True Person Tongyou also knew that Lin Fei's trip would not be called off just because of his few words. So he sneered, "Good, then I'd like to broaden my horizons. Let's see just how astonishing the saber techniques of the current Saber Saint are, that you could actually slay ten Foundation Establishment True Persons!"

True Person Tongyou had absolute confidence in his own mountain gate. With the Sky Reaching Tower suppressing the mountain gate, whether it's a Martial Saint or a Foundation Establishment level. it's simply impossible to break the mountain gate. Even the founder of Great Chang couldn't do it!

At this time, Shen Lianxin unleashed three "Ultimate Saber Slashes" in succession. The sharp saber light howled down, slashing on the protective array of the Sky Reaching Sect. However, it was just like a clay ox entering the sea. There was no response at all. Shen Lianxin knew that he could not break the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect no matter what.

"Brother Shen, let me give it a try." Lin Fei said lightly.

Shen Lianxin also put away his saber. Lin Fei stood in the void. His gaze calmly looked at True Person Tongyou. There wasn't a hint of murderous intent. But it was this kind of cold, calm gaze that made True Person Tongyou feel a little palpitations.

"Hum."

The next moment, a semi-transparent light swept out from Lin Fei's body.

"Boom."

Saber momentum!

The mastery-level saber momentum was just like an enormous mountain pressed on the entire mountain protection formation of the Sky Reaching Sect.

Suddenly, the fierce saber edge and the light of the mountain protection formation intertwined and clashed. However, the mountain protection formation remained unshaken. Lin Fei's saber momentum, even if it was mastery, it was just slightly interfering with reality.

The existence of saber intent is intended to suppress the spirit and will. Even if it evolves from saber intent to saber momentum, the actual interference and destruction of reality, naturally, is far less than the power of saber essence. If one wants to break the Sky Reaching Sect's mountain gate, relying on saber momentum alone is not enough.

However, Lin Fei seemed not surprised. The next moment, Lin Fei kept condensing his saber momentum. The smaller the range of the saber momentum, the stronger its power will be.

However, Lin Fei didn't need to use saber momentum to suppress the Sky Reaching Sect anymore, nor could he suppress it. Now Lin Fei was allowing saber momentum to return to its original "face". In other words, saber momentum was used to enhance the power of saber techniques!

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber essence exploded instantly. It was as overwhelming as a tidal wave. A large amount of saber essence emerged from Lin Fei's body. In the void, a saber gradually formed.

A heavenly saber!

Under the bolster of saber momentum, the might of the heavenly saber was even more terrifying. However, this was not the end.

"Shoo."

Another strand of saber essence also condensed into a saber.

Three Abyssal Sabers!

Under the evolution of saber momentum, the power of the Three Abyssal Sabers also reached its peak. Moreover, the Three Abyssal Sabers also evolved saber momentum.

"Buzz buzz buzz."

Then, one by one, terrifying sabers condensed in the void.

Twenty-Three Saber, Eternal Night Saber Technique, Samsara Saber Technique, God Slaying Saber Technique. A total of six saber techniques all evolved saber momentum. In the void, six sabers also formed.

"Six Sabers Fusion!"

Lin Fei wasn't in a hurry. He merged the six sabers in the void into one.

"Boom."

Instantly, the saber formed after the fusion of the six sabers, and the saber essence skyrocketed.

Ten meters, fifty meters, a hundred meters, two hundred meters, three hundred meters...

In a blink of an eye, the saber in the void exceeded one thousand meters! And this was saber essence! Each strand of saber essence was hundreds of times the saber energy.

If it were really calculated in saber energy, one thousand meters was roughly the equivalent of a Hundred thousand meters of saber energy! And it was only going up, not down!

At this moment, even the people of the Sky Reaching Sect, who were in the mountain protection formation, felt a bit threatened. Some were even restless. Even True Person Tongyou, the expression on his face was extremely serious. He stared hard at the one thousand meters saber in the void.

How could a Martial Saint condense such a terrifying saber?

Lin Fei closed his eyes. This saber not only fused six top-tier saber techniques but also combined all the saber techniques Lin Fei had learned in his life.

Moreover, under the mastery level saber momentum, power could be continuously accumulated. Therefore, how powerful this saber was, Lin Fei didn't know. This was destined to be his pinnacle saber!

"Swoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"Slash!"

With a low roar from Lin Fei, the saber essence spanned the void, reaching as high as one thousand meters, like a god saber from the heavens, cutting everything and annihilating everything! It heavily landed on the mountain protection formation of the Sky Reaching Sect.

This saber was no longer the strike in the mortal world!

199. Sky Reaching Tower Spirit

"Sky Reaching Tower!"

The next moment, True Person Tongyou's spiritual power surged. As a Foundation Establishment True Person, naturally, he can control the mountain protection formation of the Sky Reaching Sect.

Therefore, facing Lin Fei's indescribable terrifying saber, True Person Tongyou didn't hesitate. He immediately activated the Sky Reaching Tower, maximizing the power of the mountain protection formation! He had to block this saber!

Moreover, he was confident in blocking this saber. After all, the confidence passed down for thousands of years. Generations of Foundation Establishment seniors told him the mountain protection formation is absolutely unbreakable at the Foundation Establishment level. No matter how strong Lin Fei was, he was still a Martial Saint, still at the Foundation Establishment level.

The Sky Reaching Tower shone brightly. Surged Spiritual Qi poured into the mountain protection formation. The phantom of the Sky Reaching Tower expanded continually as if it had appeared in the void in a flash.

At this moment, there were no other thoughts in Lin Fei's heart. In his eyes, there was only this saber!

"Boom."

Finally, this saber fell! It struck the mountain protection formation. Instantly, ripples on the mountain protection formation spread out continuously. Ring after ring. Even the Sky Reaching Tower began to shake violently. The phantom of the Sky Reaching Tower flickered on and off as if it was about to disperse.

All disciples of the Sky Reaching Sect were looking up at the sky. There, one thousand meters tall sabers, like an enormous mountain, gave people a strong sense of oppression. It was as if the next moment, the entire Sky Reaching Sect would be split in half!

"No, impossible! Our Sky Reaching Sect's mountain protection formation, for thousands of years, no one has been able to break it. Not even the founder of Great Chang of the past, and not even the saber saint Lin Fei now!"

True Person Tongyou let out a loud roar. He felt the danger! The mountain protection formation was shaking violently at this moment. Together with the entire Sky Reaching Sect also shaking violently.

Many people looked at the saber in the void with fear. This was the first time the Sky Reaching Sect faced such a big crisis. However, was the mountain protection formation really unbreakable?

"Bang."

The next moment, the phantom of the Sky Reaching Tower suddenly shattered. With the shattering of the phantom of the Sky Reaching Tower. Next, the mountain protection formation also started to totter.

"Rumble."

Finally, the Sky Reaching Sect shook violently. The mountain protection formation hadn't been broken for thousands of years. At this moment, it finally collapsed! Instantly, the sky was filled with that boundless, terrifying to the extreme saber!

"It's broken, how could the mountain protection formation be broken? Impossible, this is impossible! Our Ten Immortal Sects inherited for thousands of years. Even the founder of Great Chang couldn't break the mountain protection formation. Could it be that Saber Saint Lin Fei is stronger than the founder of Great Chang? Today, is it the great catastrophe of our Sky Reaching Sect that hasn't happened for six thousand years?"

True Person Tongyou's soul was trembling.

A great calamity! A real life-and-death calamity! Every Immortal Sect, every Dao lineage, will face a great calamity.

Perhaps, many people didn't know how ancient the Sky Reaching Sect was. It had been passed down for six thousand years! It was arguably the oldest Immortal Sect in all of Great Chang. Without a doubt!

After six thousand years of ups and downs, the Sky Reaching Sect had weathered them all and maintained its lineage intact. Now, however, it is facing such a calamity of extermination. Once the saber in the void fell, the entire Sky Reaching Sect, they were afraid they would turn into ruins.

"No, the Sky Reaching Sect will not perish! With my spirit, awaken the spirit of the tower! Tower Spirit, please awake and save our Sky Reaching Sect!"

True Person Tongyou seemed to have performed a secret method. Suddenly, his whole body surged with spiritual power. Countless Dao marks struck the Sky Reaching Tower.

"Hum."

Suddenly, the towering Sky Reaching Tower actually began to shake violently. At the same time, it was as if a beast's roar, emanated from the void.

"Roar......"

A strange ancient being's phantom emerged from the Sky Reaching Tower.

"Who has awakened me?"

This huge phantom shook its head, seeming somewhat dazed.

"Tower Spirit, our Sky Reaching Sect is facing a crisis of extermination, someone has broken the mountain protection formation, please, tower spirit, make a move and kill the invading enemy!"

True Person Tongyou was overjoyed when he saw the tower spirit appear. He immediately reported. In fact, True Person Tongyou was just giving it a try. As for the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower, he had always thought of it as a legend. After all, the Sky Reaching Tower was just a magic treasure. How could it have a Tower Spirit?

But now, at the critical moment of life and death for the Sky Reaching Sect, True Person Tongyou could only give it a try. Unexpectedly, there really was a tower spirit awakening.

"The critical moment of life and death for the Sky Reaching Sect? How dare anyone attack the Sky Reaching Sect? Don't they know that the Sky Reaching Sect is a Golden Core Dao lineage? Don't worry, with me here, no one can exterminate the Sky Reaching Sect!"

With the awakening of the tower spirit, the Sky Reaching Tower suddenly shrank.

"Rumble."

The Sky Reaching Tower suddenly shrank from towering into the clouds to a treasure tower of tens of meters. Although it was much smaller, on the Sky Reaching Tower, precious light was abundant and colors were overflowing. It emitted a very strong spiritual pressure. Even True Person Tongyou, at this moment, felt as if he was being suppressed by the Sky Reaching Tower.

In a single moment, elation surged within his heart. A glimmer of hope revealed itself upon his countenance. The moment Tongyou awoke the Tower Spirit, the Sky Reaching Tower transformed into a splendid structure, several dozen meters tall, suspended in the ethereal void.

All of this took less than a breath's time. Yet Lin Fei harbored no hesitation. A saber essence of a thousand meters, after cleaving through the protective mountain formation, proceeded downwards, striking mercilessly upon the Sky Reaching Tower.

"Boom!"

The void resonated, vibrating abruptly.

"Ah... Damn it, what kind of saber intent is this? No, it's saber momentum! The combination of saber momentum and true essence? When did martial arts become like this, where saber momentum can be combined with true essence?"

The Tower Spirit shrieked in agony. This one strike from Lin Fei seemed to inflict on the Tower Spirit an unparalleled torment.

"Crack."

The next moment, the Sky Reaching Tower dimmed, its divine glow waning. A fissure was formed. Although it was a mere, insignificant crack and it was hardly worth mentioning in comparison to the dozens of meters tall Sky Reaching Tower, don't forget about the one thousand meters long saber! Moreover, it was saber momentum! Should this strike truly descend, the Sky Reaching Tower would surely be destroyed!

"Damn you, the old ghost of Tongming, the inheritance you left for your disciples is on the verge of being obliterated. And you expect me to be their scapegoat? Impossible! Sky Reaching Tower, retract!"

In the next moment, the Tower Spirit roared in rage. The dozens of meters tall Sky Reaching Tower astonishingly contracted. In a blink of an eye, it reduced to the size of a grain, vanishing into thin air.

At this moment, True Person Tongyou was dumbfounded. The disciples of the Sky Reaching Sect who cultivated Qi were equally flabbergasted.

The Sky Reaching Tower...had actually disappeared. The proud Tower Spirit that stood there just moments ago, thought of as the savior of the Sky Reaching Sect, was believed to be able to turn the tide.

And what was the outcome?

With a single strike, the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower had actually fled!

"Thud."

Lin Fei's one thousand meters long saber fiercely crashed into the grounds of the Sky Reaching Sect.

"No..."

The True Person Tongyou, devoid of any resistance, was engulfed by the one thousand meters long saber essence, and instantly ground into dust. Many of the disciples and elders failed to escape, most of them butchered by the vast saber essence.

"Rumble."

The peaks of the Sky Reaching Sect collapsed one after another. Even the ground below bore a colossal chasm. The Sky Reaching Sect was thoroughly reduced to ruins! A millennia-old inheritance was destroyed in a moment!

200. Obliterating the Ten Great Immortal Sects

"It's broken... Even the mountain gate of the foremost immortal sect of this era has been shattered..."

Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin exchanged glances, each seeing the shock mirrored in the other's eyes. Who could have anticipated that Lin Fei could actually break through the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect?

Especially Shen Lianxin. He had previously unleashed three saber strikes, but what was the outcome? Not even the protective mountain formation of the Sky Reaching Sect could be shaken in the slightest. Even more, he felt that even if his strength increased tenfold, he still would not be able to disrupt the mountain protection formation.

Yet now, Lin Fei had cleaved open the mountain gate of the Sky Reaching Sect with a single saber strike, even obliterating the Sky Reaching Sect entirely. A millennia-old inheritance, destroyed in a moment! The entire Sky Reaching Sect was instantaneously reduced to ruins.

"Eliminate evil thoroughly, cut the grass, and remove the roots! Saber momentum, suppress!"

Yet Lin Fei didn't let his guard down or become negligent. He stood in the void, his robe fluttering, his saber momentum expanding once again, enveloping the entirety of the Sky Reaching Sect in an instant.

Under the envelopment of the saber momentum, any Qi cultivator hidden within the Sky Reaching Sect could not evade Lin Fei's senses. Thus, Lin Fei flicked his fingers.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

His saber essence instantaneously transformed into hundreds of precious sabers, flying towards those Qi cultivators who had luckily survived with their fierce edges.

"Squelch."

Not a single Qi cultivator could withstand Lin Fei's saber essence. Perhaps this was somewhat brutal, but Lin Fei was very clear.

Eliminate evil thoroughly!

If he did not cut the grass and remove the roots, who knew when the remnants of the Sky Reaching Sect would rise from the ashes? When that time came, it would threaten the entire Nine Profound Sect!

Therefore, at this moment, Lin Fei showed not a shred of hesitation. Hundreds, even thousands of saber essences continued to slaughter within the ruins of the Sky Reaching Sect.

These saber essences were indomitable, pierced through even those hiding beneath the broken walls and ruins. A quarter of an hour later, the saber essences returned to Lin Fei's body. The air was thick with the stench of blood.

The Sky Reaching Sect, in fact, did not have many disciples, only a few hundred. But these were all Qi cultivators, several hundred Qi cultivators now all lay buried within the ruins of the Sky Reaching Sect.

"Hmm?"

Suddenly, something stirred in Lin Fei's heart, His gaze turned to a certain direction in the void.

"Want to escape? Return!"

Lin Fei seized with his large hand.

"Hum."

Immediately, a strand of saber essence flew out, instantaneously condensing into several hundred meters long heavenly saber! The terrifying edge seemed to slice through the void itself.

"Stop, don't strike, please, don't strike. If you strike again, I'll shatter..."

At this moment, a voice sounded from the void, It was none other than the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower from before. Subsequently, the originally empty void revealed the Sky Reaching Tower once again.

However, this tower was only about dozens of centimeters tall, delicately exquisite, emitting a precious glow. Yet the glow appeared somewhat dim as if it could disappear at any moment. This indicated that the Sky Reaching Tower had suffered heavy damage. Clearly, it was Lin Fei's earlier saber strike that severely damaged the Sky Reaching Tower.

"What sort of magic treasure are you? You have sentience?" Lin Fei asked with a furrowed brow.

A sentient magic treasure was simply unheard of. At least, the magical artifacts and magic treasures wielded by Qi Condensation cultivators and Foundation Establishment True Persons did not possess any form of sentience.

Yet, this Sky Reaching Tower seemed to be somewhat special.

"I'm a magic treasure that has passed through a heavenly tribulation. Isn't it normal to develop sentience? Every magic treasure that has passed through a heavenly tribulation will develop sentience, only varying degrees of wisdom. I was originally of weak sentience. But after six thousand years in the Sky Reaching Sect, my wisdom naturally grew to about the same level as you cultivators," The Tower Spirit spoke confidently.

"So you've existed for six thousand years?"

Lin Fei was somewhat astonished. Six thousand years! Even a Foundation Establishment cultivator only has a lifespan of a mere five hundred years. But the tower spirit before him had existed for six thousand years.

"Indeed, I have had sentience for six thousand years. But you needn't be so amazed. The foundation of a spirit is the magic treasure. If the magic treasure is damaged, then the spirit dies as well. Moreover, the spirit is forever trapped within the magic treasure and cannot stray far from it. In this aspect, we are far inferior to you cultivators."

Lin Fei remained silent. The Tower Spirit seemed quite fond of talking, rambling on and on.

After speaking for a while, the spirit seemed to sense that something was off. It hastily asked, "Your gaze is very dangerous. What are you planning to do? I have answered every question you've asked without the slightest concealment."

The spirit became somewhat anxious.

Lin Fei calmly stated, "You know so much, it's no different from those Foundation Establishment True Persons. You are the fundamental magic treasure of the Sky Reaching Sect. So, I was considering whether or not to destroy you."

The Tower Spirit turned pale with fright, immediately shouting, "No, please, don't! I'm merely a spirit, and the Sky Reaching Tower is just a magic treasure. Ever since that old devil, Tongming left to cross the sea, I've been staying in the Sky Reaching Sect. No one has been able to make me acknowledge them as my master. Only some seals and prohibitions left by Tongming could control me slightly. You can use those seals and prohibitions to control me too."

The will to live was strong. The Sky Reaching Tower Spirit did not want to die. Once the Sky Reaching Tower was destroyed, it would be equivalent to it dying. And Lin Fei's earlier saber strike had proven that Lin Fei was capable of destroying the Sky Reaching Tower.

"But I'm not a Qi cultivator. I don't have spiritual power. Those seals and prohibitions are of no use to me."

"There is a way, I have a way! For all these years, no one within the Sky Reaching Sect has been able to make me recognize them as my master. I am now an unowned magic treasure. I can recognize you as my master."

"I've heard that to control a magic treasure, one needs to refine it with special seals. I have no spiritual power, how am I to refine it?"

"Minor problem, it truly is a minor problem. It doesn't matter if you don't have spiritual power, just drip a drop of blood on it."

"A drop of blood?"

Lin Fei furrowed his brows. He had never heard of magical artifacts or magic treasures being controlled by dripping blood on them.

Seeing Lin Fei's doubt, the tower spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower hurriedly explained, "Ordinary magic treasures certainly can't be controlled by dripping blood on them. Even ordinary people can't control them by dripping blood. But you're a Martial Saint, and you have successfully established your Foundation, undergoing a complete transformation. Within your blood, there is a trace of the Laws of Heaven and Earth. To control a magic treasure, all you need is this trace of the Laws of Heaven and Earth."

The tower spirit was terrified that Lin Fei might be unwilling and end up destroying it. Its desire for survival was extremely strong.

Dripping blood for recognition might sound easy, but in reality, is it that simple? It required a spirit that has achieved transcendence. And the spirit should actively refine a drop of Martial Saint's blood. It's not the Martial Saint refining the magic treasure but the magic treasure refining the Martial Saint's blood. And then recognize the master in turn.

This was too humbling! The spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower would have never imagined that one day it would fall into such a state. But for the sake of survival, the Sky Reaching Tower had no other choice.

Lin Fei thought for a moment and still flicked out a drop of fresh blood. It dropped onto the body of the Sky Reaching Tower. Immediately, the tower spirit, "like a starving beast," immediately absorbed this drop of fresh blood and began to actively and rapidly "refine" this drop of Lin Fei's blood.

About half an hour later,

"Buzz."

the Sky Reaching Tower emitted a brilliant light. Lin Fei abruptly raised his head.

"Hmm?"

He had a thought and reached out his hand.

"Whoosh."

The Sky Reaching Tower had already fallen into his hand. Lin Fei could feel he could control the Sky Reaching Tower. Even, any secret within the Sky Reaching Tower, couldn't escape Lin Fei's control. This showed that the Tower Spirit had indeed recognized Lin Fei as its master.

But his control over the Sky Reaching Tower was very limited. Having no spiritual power, every time Lin Fei activated the Sky Reaching Tower, in fact, the Sky Reaching Tower was relying on its own spirit power.

This Sky Reaching Tower was indeed a marvelous magic treasure, it could be big or small. When big, it could reach into the clouds, higher than any mountain. When small, it could transform into the size of a grain of rice, like a speck of dust, hiding in the void. It was a very magical, very powerful magic treasure.

Just that, no one controlled it. The Sky Reaching Tower itself could unleash a great power that even the founder of Great Chang presumably might not match. But it just happened to meet Lin Fei. His saber essence contained true essence and saber momentum. Its power was earth-shattering even the Sky Reaching Tower couldn't withstand it. In the end, it could only out of a desperate will to live, actively recognize Lin Fei as its master, to save itself.

Lin Fei still had many questions about the Sky Reaching Tower. However, Lin Fei first put away the Sky Reaching Tower.

"Whoosh."

The Sky Reaching Tower transformed into a streak of light, flying into Lin Fei's blood. Only in the blood of a Martial Saint could the Sky Reaching Tower be nurtured.

"The Sky Reaching Sect has been destroyed. Next immortal sect."

Thus, Lin Fei, along with Shen Lianxin and Liu Yibai, tread on air and departed, swiftly flying toward the horizon.

...

In the thirteenth year of the Yongqing era of the Great Chang, on the twenty-eighth of April,

The Saber Saint, Lin Fei, crushed the ten major immortal sects! Millennium Taoist traditions were destroyed in an instant! The immortal sects were greatly shaken. The remaining immortal sects all emerged from their seclusion, coming to the Nine Profound Sect to apologize to the Saber Saint.

From then on, the immortal sects were greatly defeated. All Qi cultivators were under the control of the court. The court established the Immortal Inquiry Hall and Martial Saint Hall, opening up the secrets of Qi cultivation and martial arts to the world.

From then on, both the Immortal Dao and Martial Dao were on par, and the world was greatly stabilized!

A note from RighteousEgg

The first volume is complete! You can check out more chapters ahead of time on Patreon.

201. The glacier shatters, exotic beast reappears!

Inside the cave dwelling of Lin Fei at the Nine Profound Sect.

"You're saying that the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth is gradually decreasing? Even to the point where, in the end, the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth might become extremely scarce?"

In front of Lin Fei, the Sky Reaching Tower was hovering. Ever since he crushed the Ten Major Immortal Sects, he had been staying in the Nine Profound Sect.

Many questions about the Immortal Sects, The tower spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower could provide Lin Fei with answers.

The tower spirit replied: "Yes, although I have been asleep for most of the time and can't leave the Sky Reaching Sect. But during my six thousand years, I've also woken up many times. Each time I wake up, I feel that the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth has decreased a lot. Up to this time, I find that the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth has actually become so scarce. You must know that in the era of Tongming, the old ghost, there could be cultivators who could form a golden core. But what about now? Don't even mention the golden core, even Foundation Establishment is difficult."

Lin Fei was digesting what the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower had said.

Golden Core! That's above Foundation Establishment.

According to the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower, once the golden core is achieved, one can live for a thousand years!

As for martial arts, above Martial Saint, there is the Sovereign, the Martial Sovereign! Once a martial artist becomes a Sovereign, that's equivalent to mastering one's own "fate".

Fate is also a kind of power. The cultivation of a martial artist's body refining series is completely different from that of the Immortal Dao, but they end up in the same place.

For example, there's a saying about the golden core cultivators. Swallowing a golden core, I control my own fate, not dictated by the heavens!

Whether it's the golden core or the Sovereign, They both represent a qualitative leap. Even, it's like going through another rebirth, taking control of one's own destiny!

However, as for how a Martial Sovereign mastered his own "fate", the spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower wasn't clear.

Because, even six thousand years ago, as far as the Sky Reaching Tower knew the Martial Sovereigns were few and far between. The number was even less than that of the Golden Core cultivators.

As for the golden core, the Sky Reaching Tower knew a lot of information. For example, in order to condense a golden core, one must endure the heavenly tribulation. Only after experiencing the baptism of the heavenly tribulation can the spiritual power in one's body condense into a golden core. Otherwise, one will never be able to condense a golden core.

Below the golden core all are insignificant!

Countless Foundation Establishment True Persons attempted to cross the tribulation, But all ended up reduced to ashes.

In the six thousand years of the Sky Reaching Sect, There was only Tongming, the true person, who formed a golden core. Moreover, after achieving the golden core, Tongming hastily left, saying he was going to pursue the Great Dao. He only left behind the Taoist succession and the Sky Reaching Tower.

"You are a magic treasure that has survived the heavenly tribulation. According to your division of cultivators. You should belong to the golden core level of magic treasure. But why was a golden core level magic treasure, with the power of the golden core level, injured by my saber? Even, possibly shattered by me?"

Lin Fei coldly looked at the Sky Reaching Tower in front of him. This Sky Reaching Tower indeed was an incredibly magical treasure. Not only was it an integrated attack and defense, but most importantly, a huge internal space was inside the Sky Reaching Tower, which could store many things. This was quite fascinating.

Lin Fei destroyed the Ten Major Immortal Sects. None of the other nine major Immortal Sects had magic treasures similar to the Sky Reaching Tower.

The spirit of the Sky Reaching Tower said with a wry smile: "I have indeed survived the heavenly tribulation and possess the power at the golden core level. But I am a magic treasure. To display the power at the golden core level, certainly requires spiritual power at the golden core level. But in the Sky Reaching Sect, there is only a Foundation Establishment cultivator left. His bit of spiritual power can't even bring out one-tenth of my might.

Although I, as a spirit, can also independently operate the Sky Reaching Tower, I still can't display one hundred percent of its power, I can probably only display about twenty to thirty percent of its power. As for why you, master, could shatter me, I am also at a loss.

All I can say is, your saber essence is truly miraculous. It has integrated the saber intent, saber momentum, innate power, spiritual qi, and so on, eventually forming a completely new power.

Although this new power is not as good as the power of the golden core of a Golden Core True Person. Or not as strong as the power of a Martial Sovereign, it surpasses an average Martial Saint or Foundation Establishment True Person And I can't fully exert the power of the Sky Reaching Tower, so that's why it could be shattered by your saber essence."

Lin Fei understood. However, he was also slightly amazed in his heart. So, his saber essence is actually so miraculous? It's even only slightly inferior to the power of the golden core of a Golden Core True Person. Even a golden core level magic treasure that has survived the heavenly tribulation can be shattered.

Tongming left behind the Taoist succession and the Sky Reaching Tower. At the level of the Martial Saint and Foundation Establishment, they couldn't break the Sky Reaching Tower. This statement wasn't wrong.

But who could have thought Lin Fei possesses this peculiar power of "saber essence"? And the saber essence was cultivated from the True Intention Scroll. Initially, it was saber qi, and later transformed into saber essence. Even the founding master of the Nine Profound Sect who created the True Intention Scroll wouldn't have been aware of this.

After all, the founding master of the Nine Profound Sect was just an innate grand perfection back then. He didn't become a Martial Saint. How could he know that practicing the True Intention Scroll to the Martial Saint level would bring about such a terrifying change?

Of course, this was also because Lin Fei had comprehended the saber momentum. Without the saber momentum's saber essence, there's no way it could possess such terrifying power.

"Tower Spirit, you mentioned that True Person Tongming has left. Where did he depart from?" Lin Fei inquired further.

At present, his strength was at its zenith, advancing no further. Naturally, he needed to seek a method of departure.

"Tongming, the old ghost, seemed to have mentioned that he could only leave by sea. As for the specific reason, I'm uncertain."

"By sea?"

Lin Fei recalled the Northern Territory. That expanse of glaciers! Boundless. Back when he was still an Innate Martial Artist, even approaching the glacier posed a risk. But now, things were different. He wanted to see if he could pass through the glacier and leave the Great Chang.

Lin Fei had a hunch. There seemed to be a secret beneath that glacier.

"Store!"

Lin Fei brought the tower into his body. Afterward, without notifying anyone, he directly took a step forward. In an instant, he transformed into a streak of light, vanishing into the horizon.

A few hours later, Lin Fei arrived at Extreme North City. Having become a Martial Saint, he could walk on air. Naturally, his speed was far superior to his previous days as a Martial Master.

As long as he wished, Lin Fei could reach any part of the Great Chang in a short time.

Silently, Lin Fei flew out of the Extreme North City. Guided by the memories in his mind, he trudged on through the snowfield. This time, he successfully beheld the glacier.

"Hmm?"

Lin Fei looked down at the glacier. There lay huge footprints. Moreover, the surroundings looked as if they had been turned upside down. The flesh of the Exotic Beast he had slain before was buried underground. But now it was nowhere to be found. Seeing the entire snowfield, pitted and scarred, as if leveled.

A thought flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

This was probably not the work of Shen Lianxin or Liu Yibai. Most likely, an even more terrifying Exotic Beast had visited.

Liu Yibai had mentioned this before. Beneath the glacier lived adult Exotic Beasts. Chances were an adult Exotic Beast had been here and it had taken away the Exotic Beast's flesh.

Lin Fei didn't ponder much. His circumstances had vastly improved. Even if he encountered an adult Exotic Beast, so what? He could slay it. He arrived at the edge of the glacier. Beneath this boundless glacier was an incredibly frigid ice river. Moreover, inner power, the spiritual power of a Qi Condensation cultivator, and so forth, upon the glacier, all would freeze. This was truly a forbidden zone for life!

However, Lin Fei was now a Martial Saint. He could try his luck.

"Shoo".

Lin Fei unleashed a Saber Essence. In an instant, it flew above the glacier.

"Crack".

The Saber Essence slashed into the glacier, causing a crevice to form. The Saber Essence was not frozen.

"Indeed, Martial Saints or Established Foundation cultivator can traverse the glacier. I'm curious to see where this glacier ends."

Lin Fei's countenance was tranquil. Without any hesitation, he took a step forward.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei's footstep was on the glacier.

Cold! Unspeakably cold!

When Lin Fei stepped onto the glacier, even with the protection of his Saber Essence, even though his Dao Body was extremely robust, he could still feel the cold. The Saber Essence within his body was even somewhat impeded in its circulation. However, he could withstand it in the end.

Thus, Lin Fei quickened his pace. Now Lin Fei could cover three hundred meters distance with one step. The speed was unimaginable.

One step, two steps, three steps...

Lin Fei lost count of the steps he took. Looking back, he could no longer see the snowfield on the shore. Yet, there was still no end in sight for the glacier.

"Crack, crack".

At that moment, numerous cracks appeared on the hard glacier. Dense, like a spiderweb, as if something terrifying beneath the glacier was striking it, attempting to break out.

Lin Fei's figure ascended into the void. He coldly watched the glacier below.

"Rumble".

Finally, the glacier broke open. A terrifying beast, more than three hundred meters tall, burst out from beneath the ice river. Its formidable aura rushed toward Lin Fei like a tidal wave.

Upon seeing this Exotic Beast, Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly.

Familiar. This Exotic Beast was too familiar!

Its appearance was almost identical to the Exotic Beast that Lin Fei, Shen Lianxin, and Liu Yibai had killed previously. The only difference was this Exotic Beast was several times larger than the previous one. It looked even more terrifying.

"Adult Exotic Beast!"

A thought flashed through Lin Fei's mind. He had a rough guess about this Exotic Beast's identity. Most likely, it was the parent of the Exotic Beast that helped him achieve his Martial Saint status. This was a truly mature Exotic Beast on par with a Foundation Establishment cultivator.

202. The Empress Ascends to the Throne, Proclaiming to the World!

"Roar..."

The exotic beast roared furiously at Lin Fei. Incredibly, its massive body even leaped into the sky. Opening its huge maw, it wanted to swallow Lin Fei in one gulp.

Lin Fei's expression remained indifferent. He didn't even show any intention of using martial arts.

Lin Fei extended his fair hand. With a thought, a small exquisite pagoda quickly emerged in the palm of his hand.

"Sky Reaching Tower, suppress!"

Lin Fei threw the Sky Reaching Tower into the void. Instantly, the Sky Reaching Tower grew with the wind. In an instant, it towered several hundred meters high. Moreover, it continued to grow wildly, reaching a height of thousands of meters. The mighty Sky Reaching Tower descended from the heavens, directly landing on the massive exotic beast.

"Boom".

The gigantic exotic beast was directly pushed down by the Sky Reaching Tower, falling onto the glacier. Although the glacier had just been shattered by the exotic beast, it quickly reformed and became incredibly sturdy.

The exotic beast fell heavily onto the glacier, causing the glacier to crack. Despite the exotic beast's furious roars, yet, the Sky Reaching Tower was like a true mountain, firmly suppressing the exotic beast.

The Sky Reaching Tower might seem like it couldn't take a single blow in front of Lin Fei. But in reality, this was a genuine Golden Core level magic treasure. Even if it was manipulated by the spirit, it could only unleash two to three-tenths of its power. Yet even this two to three-tenths of power was enough to suppress an exotic beast. There was no problem at all.

Lin Fei looked at the exotic beast, speaking in a calm tone: "Perhaps, you are one of the few remaining exotic beasts in the Great Chang. I was able to build my foundation and become a Martial Saint, and the exotic beasts contributed greatly. I won't kill you, go."

Lin Fei extended his hand, directly taking back the Sky Reaching Tower. Now, in Lin Fei's eyes, this exotic beast seemed too weak, just the Sky Reaching Tower was enough to suppress it. If Lin Fei were to make a move, a single saber could slay the exotic beast!

Yet in the end, Lin Fei did not slay this exotic beast. There were now too few exotic beasts in the Great Chang. Killing one meant one less. To achieve Martial Saint status in the future, how difficult would it be? Therefore, Lin Fei didn't want to senselessly slaughter these exotic beasts.

"Roar......"

Exotic beasts were intelligent. Ultimately, they were fundamentally different from wild beasts, knowing that it was no match for Lin Fei. So, it let out a low growl, quickly breaking through the glacier and diving into the ice river.

Lin Fei didn't pay any attention to the exotic beast. He continued to walk forward on the glacier, step by step. Every step spaned hundreds of meters. His speed getting faster and faster.

One hour, two hours, three hours...

Lin Fei didn't know how long he had been walking. Even when night fell, he continued to move forward. But the glacier seemed to have no end.

One day, two days, three days...

With Lin Fei's speed, he didn't know how far he could travel in three days. However, the glacier in front of him still seemed endless.

Suddenly, Lin Fei stopped. He lowered his head, seeing traces of blood on the glacier ahead. Although it had turned into ice, it was still very clear. The ice contained fresh blood.

"I've been here before..."

Lin Fei's eyes hardened. This blood, wasn't it left behind by the exotic beast when he suppressed it with the Sky Reaching Tower? And now it appeared here again!

Lin Fei remembered he had been walking forward all the time. But unexpectedly, he had circled back. In fact, he might have been walking in circles all this time in the last three days.

"Formation!"

Lin Fei immediately thought it might be a formation.

The formations were laid by Qi cultivators. Had such means. They could make people feel like they're moving forward. But in reality, they're just going in circles.

However, with Lin Fei's current strength, how could he not detect it was a formation? Yet now, he didn't have the slightest hint of it.

"Let me see what secrets are hidden beneath this glacier."

Lin Fei was too lazy to continue walking. He directly flew up into the void.

Lin Fei's saber momentum burst forth. Doing everything he could to expand the range of his saber momentum. Then, Lin Fei's saber essence also burst forth, covering every part of his saber momentum.

"Fall!"

In the next moment, countless saber essence fell. Like raindrops, the surrounding glacier was instantly cut open by the fierce saber essence, shattering one after another.

"Boom."

As far as the eye could see, the endless glacier was all slashed apart by Lin Fei's saber energy. The ice river immediately surfaced in front of Lin Fei's eyes. But still, it was boundless. There was no change at all. After a while, the ice river froze again. The boundless glacier appeared again!

Lin Fei was silent. He knew there was a problem with this glacier. However, with his current abilities. He couldn't figure out the reason.

"Go south!"

Lin Fei didn't continue to stay on the glacier. Instead, he went to the South again. The south was a lush forest, mountains, stretching endlessly, there was no end in sight.

Lin Fei still kept flying forward. However, the experience was the same as with the glacier. After flying for several days, he returned to the original place.

Lin Fei then went to the west of Great Chang. That was an endless desert. In the desert, Lin Fei also kept flying. However, he still returned to the original place.

For half a month, Lin Fei had been rushing to the north, south, and west of Great Chang. However, without exception, he couldn't get out. No matter how he walked, eventually, he would return to the original place.

At this moment, anyone would know that there must be a problem here. It was as if the whole Great Chang was "trapped". No matter how he walked, he couldn't get out.

Lin Fei returned to the Nine Profound Sect. Now, the only place he hadn't been to was the East. Because there was an ocean. The ocean was boundless.

According to the records of the Hidden Sword Sect and the statement of the Sky Reaching Tower's spirit. If so many Foundation Establishment and even Golden Core cultivators really left Great Chang, the north, south, and west were all unable to leave. Then there was only one direction to leave, the east.

Go to sea!

However, once at sea, if he could really leave, then Lin Fei definitely wouldn't return to Great Chang in a short time.

Lin Fei was still considering.

"System."

Lin Fei summoned the system panel, checking the martial arts on the panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

Saber Momentum: Mastery (Progress 10%)

Fist intent: Mastery (Progress 81%)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (Progress 50%)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

The progress of saber momentum reached 10%. This was because Lin Fei had evolved the Mountain River Saber and Ultimate Saber Slash into saber momentum. Therefore, the progress of saber momentum practice improved. But each saber technique only added 5% to Lin Fei's practice progress.

To know, when Lin Fei's saber momentum wasn't at mastery, a saber technique evolved into saber momentum could increase the practice progress by 20%.

According to this progress, to make saber momentum transcendence needed 20 top-notch innate saber techniques that could cultivate saber intent and evolve into saber momentum, only then was it possible for saber momentum to transcend.

However, Lin Fei searched all over the world, but he didn't find more top-notch saber techniques. So, whether it was in terms of techniques or saber momentum, he had now reached a dead end. He reached a bottleneck!

"It seems I really have to leave. Great Chang can't make my martial arts go any further. If I want to be immortal, I can only leave Great Chang and pursue the highest realm of martial arts..."

Lin Fei gradually made up his mind. However, before leaving, there was always a figure in Lin Fei's mind.

"One last time..."

Lin Fei's figure flashed and turned into a streak of light, disappearing in the Nine Profound Sect.

Chang City, within the palace. Now, the entire palace was full of joy. Tomorrow, Emperor Yongqing was going to hold a ceremony to abdicate. He would pass the throne to the Crown Princess Ling Yao. Therefore, the entire palace was very busy.

As for why the emperor would abdicate, that naturally was the decision of the royal family. Moreover, everyone knew it must be related to Lin Fei, the saber saint who was now popular.

After all, there were rumors the saber saint Lin Fei had a deep relationship with the crown princess Ling Yao. However, this could only be thought of privately. No one dared to discuss it rashly.

Ling Yao was now wearing a dragon robe. Because it's abdication. Therefore, there's plenty of time to tailor a suitable dragon robe for Ling Yao.

"You all go down."

Ling Yao waved her hand.

"Yes, your highness!"

So, many palace women left. The whole room was left with only Ling Yao. She was wearing a dragon robe, standing in front of a huge mirror, looking at herself in the mirror.

At this moment, Ling Yao didn't feel very happy. Instead, she felt very complicated.

"Senior Sister Ling, you finally got what you wanted. You have control of the world's power and control of your own destiny!"

Suddenly, a familiar voice came from behind Ling Yao. Ling Yao's body trembled. She saw that familiar figure in the mirror.

"Whoosh".

Ling Yao turned around abruptly.

"Lin Fei, you...you finally came!"

Ling Yao was very excited. But, she didn't know what to say. Now, the two of them had different identities.

Ling Yao, who would ascend the throne tomorrow and become the Empress of Great Chang, ruling the world!

Lin Fei, the saber saint of Great Chang, single-handedly destroyed the ten major immortal sects and the strongest person in the world!

One wanted power.

One wanted martial arts.

Now, both of them had reached the peak of their original dreams.

"Senior Sister Ling, I'm leaving."

"Leaving?"

"Yes, leave Great Chang. In Great Chang, Martial Saint is the limit, and there is no further progress. My goal is the pinnacle of martial arts, longevity. So, I have to leave."

Ling Yao's body trembled. Leave Great Chang! Lin Fei was leaving Great Chang! She knew very clearly. Perhaps Lin Fei would never come back once he left.

Lin Fei just came to Chang City to take a final look at Ling Yao. As for Ling Yao's initial choice, it didn't matter anymore.

Ling Yao had obtained what she wanted. And Lin Fei had to continue his pursuit of martial arts.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei left. He didn't say another word nor did he stay for a long time. Just like that, he resolutely turned around and left.

Ling Yao watched Lin Fei's disappearing figure. She murmured, "Should...should I regret it?"

Ling Yao didn't know whether she should regret it or not. But, no matter how much she said, it was of no use. Lin Fei had left after all.

......

Great Chang, the thirteenth year of Yongqing, May 15th.

Crown Princess Ling Yao ascended the throne and became the empress, establishing the era of Changping.

The first edict of the empress' ascension was awarded the Martial Saint Lin Fei as the Martial Saint of Great Chang who guards the nation.

The Lin family for generations, prosperity and decline with the nation.

From now on, declare it to the world!

203. Crossing the Sea, The Astonishment of the Qi Cultivator

In Great Chang, within the city of Haizhou, a sliver of sea breeze swept through, infusing the air with a touch of salinity.

"Brother Lin, Brother Shen, have you truly made up your minds?"

Liu Yibai glanced at Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin standing before him, his expression imbued with complexity.

"Brother Liu, since you've chosen to remain within the Hidden Sword Sect, we would kindly ask you to extend your protective gaze over the Nine Profound Sect and my Lin family."

Lin Fei, reciprocating with a respectful bow, had long informed Liu Yibai and Shen Lianxin of his intentions to voyage across the sea in pursuit of the Dao.

However, after deliberate contemplation, Liu Yibai declined. He chose to stay in the Hidden Sword Sect, preserving its centuries-long glory, akin to the Martial Saints of its history.

Furthermore, Liu Yibai's willingness to remain in Great Chang was indeed a boon. With this Martial Saint at the helm, Great Chang was as secure as a fortress of gold. No matter what transpired, Liu Yibai could lend his support to the Lin family.

"Rest easy, Brother Lin. Your Lin family is under the personal care of the Empress. How could it be my turn? The Martial Saint who guards the nation shares the nation's fate. The decree from the Empress is teeming with sincerity."

Liu Yibai commented, his smile teetering between sincerity and mockery.

For nine hundred years since the founding of Great Chang, there had never been a Martial Saint tasked with guarding the nation. Lin Fei was the first!

Rumors about the relationship between Lin Fei and the Empress were already circulating in the city. Liu Yibai was merely teasing Lin Fei.

Lin Fei offered no rebuttal. Following that, with a single stride, he stepped into the void.

"Until we meet again, Brother Liu! If there ever comes a day when I successfully find the Dao, I shall return to Great Chang!"

"Brother Lin, Brother Shen, may your journey be smooth!"

In an instant, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin transformed into a streak of light. Soaring out of Haizhou City, they vanished within the vast expanse of the sea.

"Pursuing the Dao... I hope there will be a day of reunion..."

Liu Yibai gazed towards the outskirts of Haizhou City, remaining still for a long while.

...

The boundless sea stretched out before them, a sight that never ceased.

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had been flying for over a month.

Finally, Lin Fei could rest assured they hadn't circled back to their starting point. Haizhou City was nowhere to be seen. This confirmed that they had truly distanced themselves from Haizhou City.

Indeed, the ocean was the only path leading away from Great Chang. However, the sea was perilous.

In the initial few days, they faced no threats. Yet, barely a fortnight later, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin encountered sea beasts, which were exotic beasts.

Great Chang was not devoid of such creatures, but they were simply found within the depths of the sea. The ordinary innate martial artist, even Grand Masters, would encounter numerous perils in the deep sea. Even Martial Saints would be at a disadvantage when facing these exotic beasts, a situation likely to end in disaster.

Shen Lianxin was acutely aware of this. In this short span of a month, they encountered seven crises. If Shen Lianxin had been alone during these seven crises, his death would have been almost certain! Fortunately, they had Lin Fei. Together, they had weathered these seven crises.

The pursuit of Dao was an arduous journey. Lin Fei even harboured suspicions that many of those who had departed - Foundation Establishment True Persons and even the Martial Saints - were likely more prone to disaster than fortune.

Take, for instance, the founding patriarch of Great Chang. Despite his comprehension of Momentum, the vast sea was riddled with peril. At any moment, a powerful sea beast could strike him down.

Yet, Lin Fei held an advantage - he possessed the Sky Reaching Tower. Within it, a world unto itself, he stored abundant fresh water and food. Although a Martial Saint could procure sustenance from the sea, the vast and treacherous waters demanded that they maintain a low profile. Their movements should be as discrete as possible.

With the Sky Reaching Tower, they could even retreat within it for rest. As such, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin were able to delve deeper into the sea with more surprises than threats.

One month, two months, three months... Time trickled by, with Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin drifting aimlessly across the sea. Several months passed, and yet they had not spotted any land or coastline. They even lost track of the way back to Great Chang.

However, both of them were Martial Saints with unyielding resolve. Even though they were "adrift" at sea and directionless, their willpower remained steadfast. After all, it had only been a few months.

Even if they were to drift at sea for years, their convictions would not waver. Becoming a Martial Saint required an indomitable spirit!

Lin Fei, hovering above the sea, glanced at Shen Lianxin. His companion was as reticent as ever. If Lin Fei did not initiate conversation, Shen Lianxin might remain silent for months, or even years. Though they journeyed together, their conversations were few and far between.

"Brother Shen, have you noticed that in recent days, the number of sea beasts we've encountered has been decreasing? Sometimes, we wouldn't encounter a single sea beast in a day or two."

"Brother Lin, what do you imply?"

"Perhaps, we are nearing land."

A gleam of anticipation shimmered in Lin Fei's eyes. The dwindling number of sea beasts could only be attributed to one reason - they had been hunted. Or, there was something in the vicinity that deterred them.

However, with the vastness of the ocean, it seemed implausible that there would be several days, even weeks, without encountering a single sea beast.

Near the land, there would be people, and where there were people, there would likely be strong martial or immortal cultivators hunting vast amounts of sea beasts. Thus, the number of sea beasts naturally decreased. Moreover, sea beasts, inclined to seek fortune and avoid calamity, would hesitate to approach land.

However, this was only a hypothesis on Lin Fei's part. As of now, they hadn't even sighted a coastline, let alone the land. He didn't know how long it would take before they could truly set eyes on dry land.

"Let's enter the Sky Reaching Tower," Lin Fei suggested, his fatigue becoming evident. "We've been on the move for so long, we could use some rest. We'll recover in the tower."

With a wave of his hand, the Sky Reaching Tower appeared in the void.

"Tower Spirit, be on guard."

"Yes, Master."

With that, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin flew straight into the Sky Reaching Tower. They would continue their journey once their bodies had fully recovered. The Sky Reaching Tower stood tall in the void, absorbing the faint Spiritual Qi from the sea to replenish Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin's internal energy.

Time slipped by unnoticed.

From the distant sea, four or five Qi Condensation cultivators appeared. These cultivators, each controlling a magical artifact, were flying above the sea as if searching for something.

"This area has been swept by Foundation Establishment True Persons, so there aren't any powerful sea beasts here. It's relatively safe," one of them commented. "But the Black Swine Beast doesn't appear in this sea area. We need to venture deeper, but the deeper we go, the greater the chance we encounter powerful sea beasts. With our current strength, such encounters will likely be disastrous."

"We have no other choice. Without catching the Black Swine Beast, when will we be able to gather enough contributions for the Foundation Establishment Pill?"

"Once we catch the Black Swine Beast, we can get at least two Foundation Establishment Pills. If one of us successfully establishes the Foundation, catching Black Swine Beasts will become much easier. Then, everyone could receive a Foundation Establishment Pill."

These Qi Condensation cultivators were all at stages ten, eleven, or even at the pinnacle stage twelve. They adventurously ventured onto the vast sea to hunt the Black Swine Beast to exchange it for a Foundation Establishment Pill.

"Huh? Look, there's a ray of treasure light ahead. Could it be a magic treasure?"

"Magic treasure?"

"Indeed, auspicious treasure light signifies the presence of a magic treasure!"

"It's rumored that beneath this sea, there are immortal dwellings. Could it be that this magic treasure came from one of those dwellings?"

"If it really is a magic treasure, perhaps we wouldn't need to risk catching the Black Swine Beast. We could sell the magic treasure and get the Foundation Establishment Pill."

For a moment, these Qi Condensation cultivators were filled with excitement.

A magic treasure in the open sea wasn't entirely impossible. There were often rumors of fortunate Qi Condensation cultivators who had accidentally fallen into the sea and found magic treasures. Some even rumored that there were ancient immortal dwellings at the bottom of the sea.

It seemed that their luck had finally turned. They "found" a magic treasure.

With that, the five Qi Condensation cultivators, each controlling their magical artifacts, quickly flew towards the treasure light.

Soon, the five cultivators arrived at the void and laid their eyes on the magic treasure. It was a tower radiating with treasure light, appearing mysterious, ancient, and emanating a powerful aura.

204. A strand of Saber Essence decimates the sea beast

"At last, human figures meet our sight…"

The voice of Lin Fei resonated in tranquility.

Unfortunately, these figures were merely Qi Condensation cultivators. As for language and scripts, they seemed akin to those of Great Chang.

Perhaps this was somewhat peculiar. But upon closer contemplation, it appeared to fall within the bounds of reason. After all, this was a world of cultivation. Possibly, ages ago, Great Chang had been connected with the outside world. Now, these were trivial concerns.

What mattered was that Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had finally encountered others. And these were Qi Condensation cultivators no less! This implied that there were places suitable for cultivation. Undeniably, these Qi Condensation cultivators wouldn't be able to cultivate on the sea.

"Retrieve."

Lin Fei withdrew the Sky ReachingTower. Simultaneously, he also pulled back the Saber Momentum. Instantly, the five Qi Condensation cultivators began to gasp for air vehemently.

The oppressive aura exerted by Lin Fei had been overwhelmingly terrifying. Could this be the legendary "Martial Saint"?

Indeed, in legend. Because for a very long time, they hadn't seen a Martial Saint. The Fairy Mist Island housed martial artists. However, the Martial Saints were nearly extinct!

"From whence do you cultivators hail?"

Lin Fei inquired.

"With due respect, senior, we are cultivators from the Zhao family of Fairy Mist Island."

"Fairy Mist Island?"

A flicker passed through Lin Fei's gaze. Judging by the name, it seemed to be an island.

The Qi Condensation cultivators exchanged glances. Subsequently, one of them gritted his teeth and cautiously queried, "Dare I ask, senior, are you a Martial Saint?"

"Hmm?"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

For a moment, even without the exhibition of the Saber Momentum, the inherent oppression of a Martial Saint was not something these Qi Condensation cultivators could match. More so, Lin Fei was no ordinary Martial Saint.

"I am indeed a Martial Saint. Are there no martial artists on your Fairy Mist Island?"

Lin Fei's question hung in the air with an aura of calm. He had just extinguished the ten immortal sects in Great Chang. The enmity between him and the Qi cultivators was far from trivial. Even before, in Great Chang, the relationship between martial artists and Qi cultivators had been fraught with tension.

If the situation on Fairy Mist Island was similar, then Lin Fei would have to consider whether to annihilate these Qi Condensation cultivators. After all, since they had encountered Qi cultivators here, it implied the proximity of Fairy Mist Island. A bit more searching, and they would certainly find it. They didn't even need these Qi cultivators to guide them.

"Senior, we do have martial artists on Fairy Mist Island. Perhaps the senior has misunderstood. On Fairy Mist Island, martial artists and Qi cultivators coexist. However, it has been a long time since a Martial Saint was born on Fairy Mist Island, hence the query. May I ask elder, have you traveled across the sea?"

"Indeed, I, Lin, have drifted in the vast sea for several months. This is the first encounter with living beings."

Lin Fei did not conceal his identity. This was something that simply couldn't be hidden. Even these Qi cultivators had discerned at a glance that Lin Fei had arrived across the sea.

Upon hearing this, the five Qi cultivators exchanged glances. A hint of shock shimmered in their eyes. He really had journeyed across the sea! Moreover, he had drifted on the sea for several months.

Several months! It should be noted, once one strayed away from the vicinity of Fairy Mist Island and slightly ventured into the outer sea, terrifying sea beasts would be encountered. Even the lofty Foundation Establishment True Persons would more likely face calamity than fortune. To have endured three days' time was deemed a feat for top-tier Foundation Establishment True Persons.

And now?

These two Martial Saints who had journeyed across the sea could actually drift for several months at sea. This was truly unimaginable!

The five Qi cultivators weren't fools, under such circumstances, it could only indicate that the two Martial Saints before them were incredibly powerful. Even beyond their imaginations.

For a moment, the hearts of the five Qi Condensation cultivators burned with excitement.

"Seniors, since you have journeyed across the sea, you must be seeking the Dao, right? Our Fairy Mist Island occasionally hosts visitors from the outer sea who are on a quest for Dao. Seniors could first come to Fairy Mist Island, rest a while, and understand the situation. And then make plans, how about it?"

The Qi cultivators took the initiative to invite Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin.

"Inviting us, what's in it for you?"

Lin Fei asked straightforwardly. After all, this was not Great Chang. For Lin Fei, everything here was unfamiliar.

"This..."

The five Qi cultivators felt a bit abrupt, but when they thought that Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had journeyed across the sea and might have encountered countless dangers, being vigilant was quite justified.

"Seniors, if we say there are no benefits, you probably wouldn't believe us. To be honest with you, both of you are Martial Saints and there are martial arts families on Fairy Mist Island, they are currently desperate for Martial Saints. If we bring the two Martial Saints back to Fairy Mist Island. Then, those martial arts families will certainly seek us out. As Qi Condensation cultivators, we desire some resources, and we believe those martial arts families will certainly give them. After all, they are all former Martial Saint families, each with deep resources."

These Qi cultivators didn't dare hide anything. They basically laid everything out on the table.

"There are Martial Saint families on Fairy Mist Island?"

"Yes, there are indeed Martial Saint families, and more than one!"

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin exchanged a glance. Now they had journeyed across the sea and had been drifting on the vast ocean for several months, wasn't it to seek the Dao and hope to make further progress in martial arts? Since there were Martial Saint families on Fairy Mist Island, it was natural to go take a look. Even if there was no breakthrough in martial arts, they would also know the direction for a breakthrough in martial arts.

"Alright, we will follow you back to Fairy Mist Island."

Lin Fei agreed.

"Great! Now, even if we can't find the Black Swine Beast, there might still be hope for our Foundation Establishment Pills. This trip wasn't in vain."

The faces of the five Qi Condensation cultivators all held a glimmer of joy.

Martial Saints! It is believed that the Martial Saint families on Fairy Mist Island would each go crazy. And those Martial Saint families, each was exceedingly wealthy. In order to meet a Martial Saint, giving them some resources was nothing.

However, just as they were about to leave,

Suddenly, someone exclaimed: "Look, the Black Swine Beast!"

"The Black Swine Beast has been found!"

"Isn't our trip out to sea for the purpose of hunting the Black Swine Beast?"

"Now that we're here, and it's so close, it would be a pity not to hunt it."

For a moment, the five Qi Condensation cultivators were somewhat hesitant.

"Seniors, our trip out to sea was specifically to hunt the Black Swine Beast. This relates to whether we can obtain the Foundation Establishment Pills. So, please wait a moment, seniors, let us hunt this Black Swine Beast first, then we'll take you back to Fairy Mist Island."

In the end, these Qi Condensation cultivators decided to hunt the Black Swine Beast first.

Lin Fei glanced at the Black Swine Beast. He had seen this kind of sea beast. Its strength was not worth mentioning. Even a Foundation Establishment cultivator could handle it.

Lin Fei was in a hurry to go to Fairy Mist Island. So, he lightly said, "You want to hunt this sea beast? Forget it, consider it as a greeting gift."

Lin Fei flicked his finger.

"Whoosh".

A wisp of saber energy flew out. In an instant, this wisp of saber energy grew with the wind and it transformed into a heavenly saber several tens of meters high.

"Slash!"

The sky saber fell instantly. It slashed on the Black Swine Beast.

"Splurt".

The Black Swine Beast let out a miserable cry. Almost without the power to resist, it was cut into two halves by the heavenly saber.

Blood dyed the surrounding seawater red. The air was filled with a rich scent of blood. The five Qi Condensation cultivators were all looking at Lin Fei with an incredibly shocked expression.

With a casual wave, He killed the Black Swine Beast. Even a Foundation Establishment True Person couldn't do it this easily and casually. And they knew, Martial Artists, especially Martial Saints, excel in close combat.

As for Lin Fei? Thousand of meters away, his true essence flew out, easily killing the Black Swine Beast. This was beyond their understanding of martial artists. They felt incredibly shocked! At this moment, perhaps they could more intuitively understand what it means to drift at sea for months.

205. Cross the Sea to Seek Dao, we are all Seekers of Dao

When Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin finally set foot on land, both of them breathed a sigh of relief as if a huge weight had been lifted off their shoulders.

Drifting at sea for months, exotic beasts lurking all around, having to be on high alert at every moment. Every moment, their minds were stretched taut. Life during those times was not easy.

"Senior, this is Fairy Mist Island. Most of the people on the island are Qi cultivators. They are connected to dozens of nearby islands, forming the Overseas Immortal Islands. There are no powerful sects here, so calling it an Immortal Island is just a name we give ourselves. In reality, on the Ancient Continent, we are called overseas loose cultivators, lacking resources, even sects are reluctant to come to us..."

Zhao Mingyu said with a bitter smile. Lin Fei knew the names of these five Qi Condensation cultivators. Among them, Zhao Mingyu was the leader.

Zhao Mingyu had reached the twelfth level of Qi Condensation, at great perfection. He had taken two Foundation Establishment Pills. Unfortunately, both attempts at Foundation Establishment failed.

In the Zhao family, once someone reached the twelfth level of Qi Condensation at great perfection, the family would grant a Foundation Establishment Pill. Some people could make it in one leap, successfully establishing their foundation. But for most people, one Foundation Establishment Pill is simply not enough for Foundation Establishment.

This was the case for Zhao Mingyu. Later, he tried all sorts of ways and used several years to finally purchase a second Foundation Establishment Pill. However, he still failed to establish his foundation. So, this time, Zhao Mingyu took the risk to hunt the Black Swine Beast at sea in exchange for a Foundation Establishment Pill.

Now it seems that Zhao Mingyu was lucky. Not only did he meet Lin Fei, he even obtained the Black Swine Beast. Perhaps, this time he could get two Foundation Establishment Pills.

"Ancient Continent? So, there's another big continent?"

"Of course, the Ancient Continent is boundless...Specifically, senior, if you stay on Fairy Mist Island for a while, you'll naturally understand."

Lin Fei nodded. Upon arriving at Fairy Mist Island, he broadened his horizons. There were so many Qi cultivators here. Almost everywhere were Qi cultivators.

Of course, there were also ordinary people. However, these ordinary people were not ordinary at all. Because they practiced martial arts. And unlike Great Chang, The Qi cultivators here seem to not have that superior attitude towards martial artists.

"Two seniors, we've arrived at the Zhao family. You two rest first, I'll go report to the family."

Lin Fei nodded. The Zhao family was a Qi cultivator family with five Foundation Establishments. In the entire Fairy Mist Island, they could be considered in the top ten.

After Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin were received by a Foundation Establishment True Person of the Zhao family. Both parties had a brief exchange.

Under the arrangement of the Zhao family, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin stayed with the Zhao family. And the two, through the Zhao family members, as well as some books and notes, gradually came to understand Fairy Mist Island and the Ancient Continent.

The Ancient Continent was a vast and boundless continent. On it, various sects stood tall. There were nations, sects, noble families, martial artists, Qi cultivators, and so on. But basically, each area was controlled by a sect. For example, the Immortal Sect and the Martial Arts Sect.

The martial arts sects here were not like those in Great Chang. These were true rulers that stand alongside the Immortal Sect!

As for Fairy Mist Island, martial arts had declined there used to be Martial Saint families. But in the past few centuries, not a single Martial Saint had emerged. Therefore, the whole of Fairy Mist Island was still dominated by Qi cultivators.

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin only understand some of these generalities. But they knew, on the Ancient Continent, there is a higher level of martial arts, and that was enough.

This indicated that their path of seeking the Dao had hope. As for specific Martial Saint techniques, or some martial arts secret books, on Fairy Mist Island, only a few Martial Saint families had them.

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin did not actively seek out those Martial Saint families. Instead, they waited quietly. After understanding some of the situations in the Ancient Continent and Fairy Mist Island, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin both understood those Martial Saint families would definitely take the initiative to find them.

A few days later.

Zhao Mingyu, with a face full of joy, came to find Lin Fei.

"Senior Lin, Senior Shen, the eight Martial Saint families of Fairy Mist Island have sent people to find me. They hope to meet the two seniors. Originally, they were all prepared to come in person. But this involves some secrets of the Martial Saint families, and it's not quite convenient in my Zhao family. So, the two seniors need to make a move and go to the Shangguan family among the Martial Saint families."

Lin Fei looked at Zhao Mingyu and said calmly, "The eight Martial Saint families are quite generous. I suppose they've given you a lot of benefits."

Zhao Mingyu did not hide anything, a smile appeared on his face, and he respectfully responded, "Thanks to the two seniors, the eight Martial Saint families have really put in a lot of effort this time. They have actually gathered two Foundation Establishment Pills. As long as I can invite the two seniors, these two Foundation Establishment Pills will be mine."

It has to be said, the eight Martial Saint families were indeed sincere. They gave the middleman Zhao Mingyu two Foundation Establishment Pills. Considering the current situation of the eight Martial Saint families, these two Foundation Establishment Pills were not easy to come by. And Zhao Mingyu also did not hide anything. His attitude was very sincere.

However, Zhao Mingyu was a smart man. He knew that Lin Fei would definitely agree. Because Lin Fei was a seeker of the Dao! He crossed thousands of miles, crossed the sea, all for the sake of seeking the Dao. Lin Fei was a Martial Saint. So naturally, he sought the martial dao! What Lin Fei wanted only the eight Martial Saint families had it.

Lin Fei looked deeply at Zhao Mingyu and nodded, "Two Foundation Establishment Pills, I hope you can succeed in your foundation establishment! Let's go, lead the way!"

Zhao Mingyu was overjoyed. So, he immediately led Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin away from the Zhao family.

Fairy Mist Island, though it was an island, was actually quite large. At least, it should be a quarter the size of Great Chang. Otherwise, it would not be able to accommodate so many Qi cultivators and ordinary people.

Soon, the three arrived at the mansion of the Shangguan family.

The Martial Saint family's mansion was also very impressive. After all, they had given birth to Martial Saints. But compared to the Zhao family, it seemed to have declined a lot. After all, the Zhao family was becoming stronger and stronger. They have five Foundation Establishment True People, and the family's power naturally grows day by day. On the other hand, Once the Martial Saint families had not given birth to a Martial Saint, they would decline.

Lin Fei was now a Martial Saint. He also gradually knew some differences between the Martial Dao and the Immortal Dao.

For example, the Immortal Dao required talent from the beginning. It excludes over 90% of people. The number of martial artists was large, and ordinary people could practice martial arts. Even the number of martial artists who had achieved innate was definitely more than that of Qi cultivators. But when it came to the stage of Martial Saint, it was difficult. The difficulty was not exotic beasts. There were many exotic beasts in the sea.

The Martial Saint families themselves were storing exotic beast flesh and blood, True Qi Perfection was not difficult. The real difficulty was Martial Dao True Intent! Martial Dao True Intent, to achieve perfection was too hard! If Martial Dao True Intent cannot achieve perfection, then one cannot establish a foundation, and cannot become a Martial Saint.

This is the same in Great Chang. In Great Chang, there were very few martial arts masters who could comprehend Martial Dao True Intent.

As soon as Lin Fei and the others stepped into the mansion of the Shangguan family,

"Swish".

dozens of gazes were focused on Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin.

Lin Fei saw the eight people in the lead. There was an exotic fragrance coming off their bodies. Their skin was like a baby's, free of dust and dirt. This is a characteristic of physical perfection!

And True Qi had achieved perfection. But there is one point, Martial Dao True Intent had not achieved perfection. Even, there were many who have not achieved the transcendence of True Intent. The worst few didn't even have Martial Dao True Intent.

Obviously, these people were all martial arts grandmasters. But they were just True Qi Perfection and physical perfection. They didn't lack exotic beast flesh and blood. For these innate martial artists, physical perfection was the easiest to achieve.

"Greetings to the two Martial Saints!"

The eight people in the lead should be the so-called representatives of the eight Martial Saint families, upon seeing Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin, all bowed respectfully.

"May I ask why the two Martial Saints have come to Fairy Mist Island?"

One of the martial arts Masters asked in a deep voice. Lin Fei glanced at the eight people and calmly said, "I crossed the sea, just to seek the Dao. Brother Shen and I are both seekers of the Dao!"

As soon as Lin Fei's words fell, the representatives of the eight Martial Saint families all showed expressions of joy.

"So, they are seekers of the Dao!"

"After so many years, we finally have seekers of the Dao again."

"Hahaha, seekers of the Dao, and Martial Saint at that, our eight families have hope again!"

For a moment, the expressions of these eight family representatives seemed to carry a hint of excitement.

206. The saber momentum erupts, intimidating the eight great aristocratic families

Seeing how the representatives of the eight great aristocratic families were so excited, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin remained calm. Because they had learned some stories about "Seekers of the Dao" during their few days on Fairy Mist Island.

Whoever could cross the sea would usually arrive at Fairy Mist Island first. Those people were either top-tier Foundation Establishment True Person or Martial Saints. They appear once every few hundred or even a thousand years. But every time they appear, they bring great changes to Fairy Mist Island. Because these seekers of the Dao, their final achievements were not small!

There were those who become Golden Core True Person and also those who have become Martial Sovereign. Even, there were those who have achieved even higher! For the eight great Martial Saint families, seekers of the Dao represented a guarantee! A guarantee that they could enter the sect!

"Senior Martial Saints, I believe you both are aware of the situation. Since you are seekers of the Dao, you are destined to climb to the pinnacle of martial arts, you must go to the martial arts sect! Such as Martial Saints like you two, those sects with profound martial arts, capable of climbing to the pinnacle of martial arts, usually don't accept. The only exception is the Ancient Origin Sect. Ancient Origin Sect's purpose is to accommodate all rivers, different paths lead to the same goal. Even if it's a Martial Saint, Ancient Origin Sect will accept. But it needs a recommendation quota.

This recommendation quota is not easy to find. Even if you two are Martial Saints, it won't be easy to get a recommendation quota. But our eight great families on Fairy Mist Island have a recommendation quota. We recommend you two Martial Saints go to Ancient Origin Sect and compete for the position of 18 outer gate elders. This is equivalent to the position of inner gate disciples. Once you become outer gate elders, each of you Martial Saints can recommend five disciples, without exams, directly entering the outer gate of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Joining hands will benefit both, going separate ways will hurt both! I wonder what you two seniors think?"

The representatives of the eight great aristocratic families did not beat around the bush but straightforwardly stated this matter. Joining hands will benefit both. Going separate ways will hurt both. Everything is out in the open.

"That is reasonable, you need Martial Saints and we need recommendation quotas. However, I have one condition. Your eight great Martial Saint families must have collected a lot of martial arts, right? I need innate-level saber techniques that can cultivate saber intent. The more the better."

Lin Fei also proposed a condition. He did not choose martial techniques of the Martial Saint level. Because there was no need. Only those major sects had techniques that could reach the level of Martial Sovereign. Besides, he wanted to enter Ancient Origin Sect. Where would he need the common techniques of these Martial Saint families?

But saber techniques were different. Each top-tier innate level saber technique, especially those that could cultivate saber intent, could increase Lin Fei's foundation in saber techniques.

Lin Fei could find ways to let these top-tier saber techniques evolve saber momentum. When Lin Fei's saber momentum achieved transcendence, its power could increase countless times. Therefore, top-tier saber techniques were very important to Lin Fei.

"Saber techniques that can cultivate saber intent? This is not a problem. Our eight great families have collected some top-tier saber techniques."

The eight great families also nodded. It was just some saber techniques. They could copy them and give them to Lin Fei.

"Two Martial Saints, there is one more thing. Although you two are seekers of the Dao, we would like to know more about your strength. After all, there are many Martial Saints who want to enter Ancient Origin Sect. If you don't have particularly strong power, it might not be easy to get into Ancient Origin Sect smoothly."

The eight great families also made a request to understand the strength of Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin.

"This request is not excessive. How would you like to know?"

"Of course, it's through a spar. Although we're not Martial Saints, we have achieved perfection in our physical bodies. And, the martial arts we have learned are not weak. Even if it's a Martial Saint, the eight of us can resist when joining forces."

The eight people finished speaking and turned their gazes to Lin Fei.

"I will only draw my saber once!"

At this time, Shen Lianxin stepped forward. He swept his gaze over the eight people.

"Thank you, senior, for your guidance!"

Therefore, the eight Martial Grandmasters also exuded a strong momentum.

"Ultimate Saber Slash!"

Shen Lianxin slashed out with his saber. Suddenly, a saber light of thousands of meters cut through the sky, like a dazzling rainbow.

The eight people were greatly shocked.

"Nine Dragons Dance!"

"Eternal Saber Slash!"

"Dragon Gate Shadow!"

One by one, the Martial Grandmasters displayed their own martial arts. True Qi burst out, and even Martial Dao True Intent also burst out. The eight people joined hands, and their momentum reached its peak. It seemed like they could really resist a Martial Saint.

"Bang."

The next moment, the saber light slashed down. The eight Grandmasters, each one of them shook. Their clothes were cut by the saber light. They looked very embarrassed.

"Clang."

Looking at Shen Lianxin again. After slashing that saber, he had already sheathed his saber. The whole person was like an indifferent iceberg, silent and reserved.

"Senior Shen is really too strong."

"Even though he is a Martial Saint, this saber, Senior Shen is even stronger than all the Martial Saints we have seen!"

"And that saber intent, it's simply reached an extreme sharpness."

"With just one saber, we couldn't resist it..."

Although the eight Grandmasters were shocked, they were very happy in their hearts. They used their recommendation quotas to send Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin to the Ancient Origin Sect. The stronger Shen Lianxin and Lin Fei were, the happier they were. If both could enter the Ancient Origin Sect, it might be the turning point for the eight great families in recent centuries.

"Senior Shen's strength is amazing, even among the Martial Saints, he is a strong one!"

The eight innate Masters from the great families recognized Shen Lianxin's strength. So, their gazes turned to Lin Fei.

"I wonder, Senior Lin..."

"Do you also want to spar with me?"

Lin Fei spoke in a calm tone. Shen Lianxin had always kept a cold face. Like an ice sculpture, he remained silent. But now, his gaze swept over the people from the eight great families. A hint of pity was revealed in his eyes.

The people from the eight great families didn't understand. They nodded and said respectfully, "We rudely ask for guidance from Senior Lin!"

Lin Fei's gaze was deep. Looking at the eight innate Masters in front of him. He spoke calmly, "A spar is fine, but don't draw your sabers. No one can draw their saber in front of me!"

Lin Fei's gaze fell on the three Masters who used sabers. Out of the eight innate Masters, there were three saber users. They had even all comprehended saber intent. However, the saber intent had only reached transcendence, far from perfection.

"Uh? Senior, although you are a Martial Saint, we haven't reached the point where we can't even draw our sabers."

The three saber users had anger on their faces. Lin Fei's words made them feel as if they were being "disrespected". So, they put their hands on the hilt of their sabers, trying to draw them.

"Hum."

But the next moment, their expressions changed slightly. The sabers in their hands actually began to tremble violently. No matter how hard they tried, they couldn't draw them. Even using their True Qi didn't change anything. The sabers seemed to be tightly sucked by their sheaths. They simply couldn't draw their sabers.

"This is..."

The eight Innate Masters suddenly looked up. Their gazes were incredibly shocked as they looked at Lin Fei.

"Boom."

The next moment, Lin Fei didn't hold back any longer. His saber momentum instantly exploded. Majestic and overwhelming, it pressed on the eight Innate Masters.

Immediately, the eight Innate Masters, not to mention making a move, even moving a single step was extremely difficult. Without becoming a Martial Saint, in the face of Lin Fei's saber momentum, even making a move was a luxury!

"Saber momentum!"

"It's actually saber momentum!"

"Hahaha, senior can actually comprehend saber momentum!"

"Dao Seeker, this is a true Dao Seeker!"

For a moment, the eight innate Masters, expressions of immense shock appeared on their faces. Even their voices began to tremble with excitement.

"Now, do we still need to spar?"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back. His gaze fell on the eight Grandmasters as he calmly asked.

207. Transformation, Saber Momentum Transcendence

Shangguan family mansion.

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had both moved in here. After all, the Zhao family was a Qi cultivator family. It wouldn't be a long-term plan to stay at Zhao's. And Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had already reached an agreement with the eight great families. The two had officially become guest elders of the eight great families. It could be said that they shared honor and disgrace now. So, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin simply moved into the Shangguan family. They quietly waited for the eight great families to arrange for their trip to the Ancient Origin Sect.

According to the arrangement of the eight great families, they first needed to build momentum for Lin Fei. Yes, build momentum. They needed to publicize Lin Fei's status as a Dao Seeker.

Becoming an elder of the Ancient Origin Sect was not easy. Not only did they need to have great strength but also needed some other factors. For example, Lin Fei being a Dao Seeker would definitely attract the attention of the high-level figures in the Ancient Origin Sect. After all, many Dao Seeker seniors have proven all Dao Seekers achieved great things in the future!

The eight great families went to build momentum while Lin Fei looked at the secret saber technique manuscripts sent by them. Although they were transcriptions, there wasn't much difference from the originals. Moreover, the number of secret saber technique manuscripts sent by the eight great families greatly exceeded Lin Fei's estimate. There were a total of twenty-four top-tier saber techniques. Almost every family contributed three top-tier saber techniques.

One should know these were not ordinary saber techniques. They were saber techniques that could cultivate saber intent. Such saber techniques were rare and very valuable no matter where.

"If I can evolve all these saber techniques into saber momentum. Then my saber momentum should be able to break through to transcendence!"

A strange light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

Saber momentum is very unique. It doesn't require accumulation over time. Often a sudden insight could comprehend saber momentum, even directly leading to saber momentum perfection. If they can't have sudden insight, even after hundreds of years of hard cultivation, the saber momentum will not improve a bit.

Lin Fei didn't need to comprehend saber momentum. His saber momentum took a different path from other martial artists.

Other martial artists, most of them comprehend a type of saber momentum. Then they constantly comprehend this type of saber momentum, continuously evolve this kind of saber momentum, hoping to evolve this saber momentum to transcendence, or even to perfection.

But Lin Fei didn't take this path. He took the path of integrating saber momentum. He wanted to integrate a large amount of saber momentum and then be inclusive of all, reaching perfection!

This method required Lin Fei to integrate various kinds of saber techniques. In order to comprehend various types of saber momentum, even the most talented martial artists had limited energy. No one could comprehend a top-tier saber technique in one or two days, or half a month, and evolved its saber momentum. That's simply impossible.

But Lin Fei could! Because he didn't need to practice himself. Even the saber techniques didn't need him to comprehend himself. His saber techniques could all cultivate and evolve saber momentum by themselves. Of course, the prerequisite was that Lin Fei could attract these saber techniques.

"Let's begin."

Lin Fei took a deep breath.

"Boom."

In the next moment, Lin Fei released his saber momentum. A semi-transparent glow erupted from his body. Suddenly, the entire room was covered by this transparent glow.

Lin Fei took a deep breath. Then he said calmly: "I need more top-tier saber techniques to evolve my saber momentum. If you can fuse your perfection state saber techniques into my saber momentum on your own. I will definitely help you successfully evolve to the saber momentum!"

Having said that, Lin Fei quietly waited. These were all top-tier innate-level saber techniques. All of them could cultivate saber intent and the saber techniques that could cultivate saber intent all wanted to evolve saber momentum. Saber momentum was almost the highest achievement for these saber techniques.

Therefore, Lin Fei didn't say much. Just these few sentences. He believed these saber techniques could all choose on their own.

Sure enough, as soon as Lin Fei finished speaking, a system voice sounded in his mind.

"Heaven-Earth One Saber Slash, self-cultivated to perfection state, wishes to integrate into your saber momentum."

"Shadow Slicing Saber, self-cultivated to perfection state, wishes to integrate into your saber momentum."

"Nine Heavens Slash, self-cultivated to perfection state, wishes to integrate into your saber momentum."

"Wind Slicing Saber, self-cultivated to perfection state, wishes to integrate into your saber momentum."

One by one, the saber techniques were all integrated into Lin Fei's saber momentum. In the blink of an eye, all twenty-four top-tier innate-level saber techniques chose to integrate into Lin Fei's saber momentum on their own.

Now, Lin Fei's saber momentum had an additional twenty-four top-tier innate-level saber techniques! Of course, this had no effect on Lin Fei's saber momentum for now.

To improve the saber momentum, he had to integrate another saber momentum. And these saber techniques just integrated into the saber momentum but had not yet evolved saber momentum.

Lin Fei also promised he would definitely help these saber techniques to evolve saber momentum. Only then could he attract so many saber techniques to integrate into his saber momentum. If Lin Fei did not fulfill his promise, then these saber techniques might go silent. They would not add any saber technique foundation to Lin Fei.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei opened his eyes. With a thought, he retracted his saber momentum. Immediately, the glow that covered the entire room also instantly returned to Lin Fei's body.

"I need to help these saber techniques evolve their saber momentum."

Lin Fei murmured in a low voice. To evolve saber momentum, the only way he knew now was to let these saber techniques fight against Foundation Establishment level powerhouses. Even, they must kill those Foundation Establishment level powerhouses.

For example, when Lin Fei's saber techniques were able to evolve saber momentum, it was because Lin Fei had destroyed the ten immortal gates, killing countless Foundation Establishment True Persons. Only then could those top-tier saber techniques evolve saber momentum. It might sound cruel, but it couldn't be more normal. And this was also the broad road! After all, sabers were inherently lethal weapons!

From the moment the saber was born, the saber was used for killing. And the saber techniques were natural for killing as well. There was never a "kind" saber technique. If the saber techniques in Lin Fei's saber momentum could each take a human form, they would definitely be ferocious and terrifying. So, if saber techniques want to improve, besides enlightenment, they must fight and kill!

"I need to kill Foundation Establishment level powerhouses..."

A thought flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

The ocean!

In the vast ocean, there was a lack of everything. But there was no shortage of Foundation Establishment level sea beasts. If he wanted to kill, go to the ocean!

Under normal circumstances, the ocean was actually very dangerous for Foundation Establishment True Persons. But for Lin Fei, he had drifted at sea for several months. What danger had he not encountered?

With the Sky Reaching Tower and saber momentum, as long as he didn't provoke some very powerful or surpassing the Foundation Establishment level sea beasts, then he wouldn't be in danger.

So, Lin Fei got up. He left the Shangguan family and turned into a streak of light, flying toward the ocean.

At this moment, the sea was surging, especially in the deep sea far away from Fairy Mist Island, there lurked many terrifying sea beasts.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber momentum exploded in an instant. In a flash, it enveloped an area of ten miles. This was not the limit of Lin Fei's saber momentum, but that was enough.

"Roar..."

Under the suppression of Lin Fei's saber momentum, one after another, sea beasts emerged, showing their huge heads. They were emanating terrifying auras, roaring furiously at Lin Fei.

"Go."

Lin Fei flicked his finger. Immediately, streaks of saber energy flew out. They quickly transformed into a giant saber. Then, the saber intent burst forth. These were the twenty-four saber techniques that Lin Fei had just integrated into his saber momentum. Now, they all transformed into heavenly sabers, fighting with those sea beasts.

One, two, three...

In the sea area of ten miles, there were actually eight sea beasts. And without exception, all were at the Foundation Establishment level.

But Lin Fei seemed very calm. His saber momentum kept suppressing these sea beasts. In the battle with the sea beasts, the saber intent of the saber techniques kept rising.

Lin Fei was using these sea beasts to temper his saber techniques. Moreover, the speed was very fast. Beginner, Mastery, Transcendence, Perfection!

When the saber intent of a saber technique reached Perfection, it could no longer be improved. Because it faced the evolution into saber momentum. Therefore, it needed an opportunity. And this opportunity was to kill sea beasts.

"Slash!"

With the suppression of Lin Fei's saber momentum, helping these saber techniques to kill sea beasts was a breeze.

"Splat."

One after another, sea beasts were killed by the saber techniques. Afterward, those saber techniques successfully evolved into saber momentum.

"Your 'Heaven-Earth One Saber Slash', excited after slaying a Foundation Establishment sea beast, has evolved into saber momentum."

"Your 'Shadow Slicing Saber', excited after slaying a Foundation Establishment sea beast, has evolved into saber momentum."

"Your 'Nine Heavens Slash', excited after slaying a Foundation Establishment sea beast, has evolved into saber momentum."

"Your 'Wind Slicing Saber', excited after slaying a Foundation Establishment sea beast, has evolved into saber momentum."

All twenty-four saber techniques had evolved into saber momentum.

"Fuse!"

The next moment, Lin Fei did not hesitate. He immediately started the fusion of saber momentum. Originally, Lin Fei's progress in cultivating saber momentum had reached 10%. And now, after fusing twenty-four saber momenta. Lin Fei's progress in cultivating saber momentum began to advance by leaps and bounds.

20%, 40%, 60%, 80%, 100%......

When the progress of cultivating saber momentum reached 100%, Lin Fei's saber momentum started shaking violently.

"Saber Momentum Transcendence!"

At this moment, Lin Fei was overjoyed. He immediately knew his saber momentum has transformed. It had finally reached Transcendence!

208. The Eight Great Families Rally, the "Dao Seeker" Shocks Ancient Origin Sect

"Transcendence!"

Lin Fei was sensing his saber momentum. Transcendent saber momentum was significantly different from the Mastery stage. The glow of the saber momentum appeared more substantial. The saber momentum might just be a process of turning from the virtual to the real. As to when it would completely "become real", Lin Fei was not sure.

Transcendent saber momentum made Lin Fei's saber essence even more terrifying. With the boost of saber momentum, the power of Lin Fei's saber essence was multiplied!

Under saber momentum, even a thread of Lin Fei's saber essence could possess the terrifying power of splitting mountains and rivers. As for the saber momentum itself, its suppression of enemies had increased several times.

Perhaps, an average Foundation Establishment True Person or an average Martial Saint could only exert half of their strength under the suppression of Lin Fei's saber momentum. It's quite possible that they couldn't even exert half of it.

This was the horror of saber momentum. A Martial Saint with and without saber momentum was on completely different levels.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Realm: Early Martial Saint

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

On Lin Fei's system panel now, things like boxing techniques and lightness techniques had disappeared. It had been extremely simplified. This was intentional on Lin Fei's part. After all, things like boxing techniques and boxing intent were not of much significance to Lin Fei after he had evolved the saber momentum. What boxing intent can do, saber momentum can do as well.

As for lightness techniques, Lin Fei had saber momentum. As long as it's within the range of his saber momentum, Lin Fei's moving and dodging would be at the top level. Lightness techniques had temporarily lost their relevance.

Besides, when he reached the Ancient Origin Sect, there would be better lightness techniques. If necessary, he would choose more powerful lightness techniques then.

What Lin Fei paid the most attention to was his saber momentum. The progress bar behind it was surprisingly at 0. In fact, Lin Fei had evolved twenty-four kinds of saber momentum. Each fusion of saber momentum increased the cultivation progress by 5%.

In theory, Lin Fei's saber momentum reaching Transcendence would only require another eighteen saber momenta. After all, Lin Fei's saber momentum already had a 10% cultivation progress. But now, after Lin Fei fused all twenty-four saber momenta, the cultivation progress remained at 0 even after his saber momentum reached Transcendence.

This could only explain one thing. After Lin Fei's saber momentum reached Transcendence, fusing with the saber momentum evolved from those top-tier innate saber techniques could no longer increase the cultivation progress.

This was just like Lin Fei integrating those basic saber techniques to increase his saber intent in the past. After enhancing the saber intent, no matter how many basic saber techniques were fused, they couldn't increase the saber foundation anymore. The same went for saber momentum.

Once saber momentum transcended, the saber momentum evolved from the innate level saber techniques might not be of much use. Unless there were some Martial Saint level saber techniques.

Lin Fei didn't think too much. He glanced at the sea area, which had a strong smell of blood. This might attract even more terrifying sea beasts. Therefore, Lin Fei didn't linger any longer.

"Let's go back."

Then, Lin Fei instantly transformed into a stream of light, heading back towards Fairy Mist Island.

...

Tianqi Country, where martial arts were supreme!

Tianqi Country had been in existence for over ten thousand years. Of course, it wasn't that Tianqi Country was special, capable of being passed down for over ten thousand years. It was because Ancient Origin Sect was backing Tianqi Country!

Ancient Origin Sect had been established for over ten thousand years as well. Unlike some other sects that directly control their territories, the Ancient Origin Sect established Tianqi Country to govern its vast territory. All the Ancient Origin Sect needed to do was control Tianqi Country.

Everyone in Tianqi Country was from Ancient Origin Sect. Even in the entire Tianqi Country, almost all martial artists had intricate connections with Ancient Origin Sect.

Although Tianqi Country didn't ban Qi cultivators, there were very few of them. After all, ambitious Qi cultivators would go to the vast Ancient Continent and other places. Those areas were controlled by immortal sects and were more convenient for immortal cultivators.

At this moment, Ancient Origin City, located at the foot of the Ancient Origin Sect mountain, had become very lively. Because Ancient Origin Sect was recruiting disciples again.

Ancient Origin Sect's philosophy was that all rivers run into the sea, leading to the same goal through different paths. Therefore, whether they were commoners, martial families, or the nobility of Tianqi Country, they all had the chance to join Ancient Origin Sect.

However, there was a special case to it. The nobility and children of martial families could use recommendation slots to directly enter the outer sect.

As for the children of commoners? They had to pass layers of assessment before they had the chance to join the outer sect. The number of disciples in the outer sect of the Ancient Origin Sect was extremely large, amounting to hundreds of thousands! A large number of disciples were eliminated from the outer sect each year. The outer sect was in competition at all times.

The path of martial arts was unlike the path of immortality. Martial arts were like rowing against the current; if you don't advance, you retreat.

Therefore, a terrifying competition must be maintained. Once an outer sect disciple reached the innate realm, they could be promoted to the inner sect and become an inner sect disciple.

As for Martial Saints, they were the true disciples! The real foundation of the Ancient Origin Sect was the true disciples. Each of them was a powerful Martial Saint. If a Martial Saint from the outside world wanted to reach the peak of martial arts, they could also join Ancient Origin Sect.

However, they would also need to compete. And it could only be done by some of the affiliated forces of the Ancient Origin Sect, using recommendation slots to participate in Ancient Origin Sect's competition.

These "beginner" Martial Saints, once selected into Ancient Origin Sect, would immediately become elders of the outer sect. Their status was only slightly lower than that of the true disciples. But that was just some difference in resource allocation.

In fact, in terms of identity, the status of outer sect elders and true disciples was equal. Even if they stayed in Ancient Origin Sect for a long time, they might become inner sect elders. Then they would truly become the core of the Ancient Origin Sect!

Lin Fei, Shen Lianxin, and Shangguan Feiyun arrived in Ancient Origin City.

In Ancient Origin City, top-notch geniuses appeared from time to time. Carrying a huge "genius" aura, they appeared in Ancient Origin City, receiving the admiration of many martial artists.

"That's Little Divine Dragon, Liu Xuan, right?"

"This Little Divine Dragon is not simple. He's only sixteen this year and has already comprehended sword intent. He's a peerless genius in swordsmanship."

"Although he's only in the acquired realm since Little Divine Dragon has understood sword intent, he's most likely going to be promoted to the inner sect, becoming an inner sect disciple!"

"Little Divine Dragon doesn't come from a big martial family. He's just an ordinary commoner, but his talent in swordsmanship is outstanding."

Many people were discussing Little Divine Dragon, Liu Xuan. Even Lin Fei, upon hearing this, took a few more looks at Liu Xuan.

Liu Xuan had a cold demeanor and remained unflustered. Although he was young, he was very calm. Under the praise of everyone, he remained calm.

Being in the acquired realm and understanding sword intent, that's absolutely top-notch genius.

Lin Fei had also understood saber intent in the acquired realm back then, which allowed him to kill high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. And Lin Fei was very clear. The reason he understood saber intent was that his saber technique was very promising. The saber technique had understood saber intent on its own.

However, Liu Xuan was different. He comprehended saber intent based on his swordsmanship talent. Moreover, he was even younger than Lin Fei when he comprehended saber intent.

Seeing Lin Fei's interest in Little Divine Dragon Liu Xuan, Shangguan Feiyun said with a smile, "Seniors, every year there are top-notch talents like Little Divine Dragon Liu Xuan. They don't hide their talents at all. On the contrary, they publicize it. Because in Ancient Origin Sect, the more talented you are, the more resources you can get. So, every time Ancient Origin Sect begins to accept disciples, a large number of geniuses emerge. It's all to get the attention of the Ancient Origin Sect. Now, seniors, you should understand why our eight major families have spent a huge price to create momentum for you, right?"

Both Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin understood. In this Ancient Continent, in this Ancient Origin Sect, things seemed to be quite different from Great Chang.

Great Chang had Qi cultivators, dynasties, and other sects. If one's talent was too dazzling, they might face various unpredictable events. But Ancient Origin Sect was different.

In Tianqi Country, Ancient Origin Sect was supreme, suppressing everything! Ancient Origin Sect hoped that more people with good martial arts talents would appear. Anyone who dared to attack the disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect would undoubtedly die!

"So, how is the momentum you created?" Lin Fei asked.

"Hehe, seniors," Shangguan Feiyun responded. "Although our eight major families have declined for a long time, some connections still exist. Moreover, you two are Dao Seekers. Just the words 'Dao Seeker' are enough to attract the attention of the Ancient Origin Sect!

However, when the mountain gate opens later, no matter what, you two must try your best to create the greatest momentum. Even better if you could create a sensation throughout the venue, and shake the Ancient Origin Sect, that would be the best! Especially Senior Lin. I believe that Senior Lin can definitely shake the entire Ancient Origin Sect!"

There was a trace of eagerness in Shangguan Feiyun's eyes as he looked at Lin Fei.

At this time, a figure suddenly appeared in the void. This figure walked step by step to the sky above Ancient Origin Sect. His gaze swept across Ancient Origin City. Then, he shouted loudly, "Where are the Dao Seekers from Fairy Mist Island?"

"Boom."

Immediately, all the martial artists in Ancient Origin City were greatly shocked.

"Dao Seekers?"

"Are there really Dao Seekers on Fairy Mist Island?"

"Seekers have not appeared for hundreds of years."

"The Seekers who appeared before were all Foundation Establishment True Persons."

"This time Dao Seeker is finally one of our martial artists. I heard it's two powerful Martial Saints!"

Shangguan Feiyun hurriedly said to Lin Fei, "Senior Lin, Senior Shen, this is the benefit of the momentum we created! Both of you go quickly."

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin looked at each other and nodded. Then they took a stride and directly arrived in the void.

209. The Saber Momentum Emerges, Hundreds of Martial Saints Suppressed Within a Ten-Mile Radius!

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin moved steadily onward, each step echoing like the silent tread of an invisible staircase. Traveling through the vast emptiness, they trod upon thin air and arrived in front of the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect.

"We two are Dao Seekers from Fairy Mist Island," Lin Fei declared with tranquility.

Even when facing the dignified Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect, he neither groveled nor acted pretentiously. After all, the figure before him was just a Martial Saint. And so was Lin Fei.

"What a good poise!" The Ancient Origin Sect's Martial Saint gave Lin Fei an appraising glance.

His aura was not something one could easily endure. Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin managed to stride toward him step by step. This was not something an ordinary Martial Saint could achieve. They were indeed the rare seekers seen only once in centuries!

"Dao Seekers are known for their steadfast spirits and wills, promising remarkable achievements in the future. However, that's all later. First, you must pass our Ancient Origin Sect's assessment, successfully join us as outer elders, and then you will have the chance to ascend to the pinnacle of martial arts!"

"What is the assessment?" Lin Fei queried further.

"No rush."

Subsequently, the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect called out to the crowd below, "Dragon Hidden Mountain, Martial Saint Lu Xuan!"

Following this, a man garbed in black emerged from the crowd, his entire demeanor chilly and detached.

"Lu Xuan pays his respects to the Envoy Gu!"

The black-robed man was none other than Lu Xuan, a Martial Saint.

Lin Fei had heard this name in the Ancient Origin City. It was said that Lu Xuan came recommended by Dragon Hidden Mountain, having once vanquished thirty-eight Martial Saints in succession, among whom were top-tier Martial Saints! This was a testament to his prowess.

Therefore, Dragon Hidden Mountain had made a show of him, ensuring the higher echelons of the Ancient Origin Sect knew of Lu Xuan. The purpose of this spectacle was exactly this—to make the Ancient Origin Sect take notice.

"Cold Water Pavilion, Ying Wuming!"

"Great Snow Mountain, Xia Zongtian."

"Red Maple Manor, Zhao Canglong."

The Ancient Origin Sect's Martial Saint called out a dozen more names, all of whom were currently enjoying considerable fame within Ancient Origin City.

In truth, all of this was merely to create a sensation. These Martial Saints' respective backers had expended immense resources and leveraged vast networks for this spectacle. Otherwise, how would the higher-ups of the Ancient Origin Sect know the names of these Martial Saints? Although the Martial Saints were powerful, they were not yet within the sights of the Ancient Origin Sect's upper echelons.

These ten Martial Saints were all eyeing each other. After all, there were limited spots within the Ancient Origin Sect. They were competitors. Of course, these were the famous ones, known to the Ancient Origin Sect's higher-ups. There were still some Martial Saints who were not known to the upper echelons of the Ancient Origin Sect, but who had recommendations. There were quite a few of them.

"I trust your backers have mentioned this. Once you create a sensation, and catch the eyes of my Ancient Origin Sect's upper echelons, then, upon passing the assessment, the upper echelons of the Ancient Origin Sect will bestow various rewards. Of course, the premise is that you have to pass the Ancient Origin Sect's assessment. Come with me."

Thus, Lin Fei and the others, following the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect, arrived at the foot of the Ancient Origin Sect's mountain.

Accompanying Lin Fei and the others were actually as many as hundreds of Martial Saints! With so many Martial Saints vying for spots, though the Ancient Origin Sect's quota was not fixed, it typically accepted only around a dozen. If the Ancient Origin Sect was unsatisfied, it would only admit a few. The most outrageous occurrence was once when none were accepted.

"Dare I ask, what is the content of this assessment?" A Martial Saint inquired.

Each time, the content of the Ancient Origin Sect's assessment was different. Thus, there wasn't any reference point. However, one thing was certain. The strength of the Martial Saints was extremely important. After all, these Martial Saints, unlike the disciples, upon joining the Ancient Origin Sect, would directly become outer elders. Naturally, the stronger they were, the better.

As for potential? Having become Martial Saints, potential no longer mattered. What mattered was strength! Hence, typically each assessment would see the strongest Martial Saints able to join the Ancient Origin Sect and become outer elders.

This was clear to all the Martial Saints. This was also the reason why people from the eight great families initially wished to spar with Lin Fei. They wanted to gauge Lin Fei's approximate strength, so they wouldn't invest heavily only to find out that the strength of Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin was too weak to join the Ancient Origin Sect. That would mean a major loss for the eight great families.

The Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect looked at Lin Fei and the others, a smile tugging at the corner of his mouth: "The content of this assessment is simple. Do you see the gate of the Ancient Origin Sect? We are currently at the foot of the Ancient Origin Sect's mountain. Your task is to reach the gate of the Ancient Origin Sect as quickly as possible! The first batch of Martial Saints to reach there will be able to join the Ancient Origin Sect smoothly and become the elders of the Ancient Origin Sect!"

"Hm? Is it that simple?"

Some of the Martial Saints seemed somewhat incredulous.

"Is it really simple?"

The Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect looked amused but didn't answer.

At this moment, a black-robed Lu Xuan coldly asked, "Can we kill?"

Lu Xuan's words tightened the hearts of the many Martial Saints. Indeed, those who first reach the gate of the Ancient Origin Sect could smoothly join it. Actually, this did not refer to speed, but to ranking. Just getting to the mountain before their opponents was enough. If they killed all the Martial Saints at the foot of the mountain, they would certainly be able to join the Ancient Origin Sect.

All present were Martial Saints. All had experienced slaughters and walked their paths through battle. Could they not understand Lu Xuan's meaning? Even Shen Lianxin was momentarily moved to kill.

However, the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect regretfully shook his head and said, "Unfortunately, you can't kill."

"Can't kill?"

"But you didn't say we can't hurt others?"

The eyes of the crowd brightened. They immediately understood the meaning of the Ancient Origin Sect's Martial Saint. Can't kill, but he didn't say they couldn't injure. Evidently, fighting was inevitable. This scene was simply too cruel.

Over a hundred Martial Saints! What a grand line-up! These hundreds of Martial Saints had to pit their wits and courage against each other, fighting amongst themselves just for a chance to join the Ancient Origin Sect.

The Ancient Origin Sect was conducting the Martial Saint assessment first. Therefore, those disciples at the foot of the mountain who wanted to join the outer or even the inner sect of the Ancient Origin Sect were also watching the scene unfold. Perhaps their hearts were shocked. Even at the Martial Saint level, they had to join the Ancient Origin Sect in such a cruel manner. Now, their chances of joining the outer sect of the Ancient Origin Sect seemed much easier than the Martial Saints'.

If they missed this opportunity, they wouldn't need to consider becoming Martial Saints and joining the Ancient Origin Sect in the future. The probability of that was infinitesimal.

"I wonder who will be the first to climb to the top of the mountain?"

"Maybe it will be Martial Saint Lu Xuan."

"These two Dao Seekers look a bit ordinary."

"They say Dao Seekers have strong willpower, but their strength might not necessarily be the strongest."

"Foundation Establishment Dao Seekers do occasionally appear. Those Dao Seekers are highly valued by the Immortal Sects."

"The Ancient Origin Sect certainly values Dao Seekers, but whether they can pass the assessment is still a big question."

Many disciples temporarily didn't need to take the assessment. So, they were all discussing these Martial Saints. After all, it was rare to see these Martial Saints fighting so fiercely for a few spots under normal circumstances.

"Brother Shen, you go first. I'll stay at the foot of the mountain to ensure everything goes smoothly."

Suddenly, Lin Fei said to Shen Lianxin. Shen Lianxin understood immediately. Lin Fei was going to stop the other Martial Saints.

Shen Lianxin understood. Naturally, the others did too. Lu Xuan, Ying Wuming, and the others remained expressionless. However, a hint of murderous intent flashed through their eyes.

Although they were not allowed to kill, it didn't mean they couldn't injure others. Injuring a Martial Saint was much easier than killing one.

When it came to the opportunity to enter the Ancient Origin Sect, they would strike against anyone who dared to obstruct them. Even the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect seemed a bit surprised. He looked up and down at Lin Fei, a hint of doubt in his eyes. However, no matter what the doubt was, he would soon know.

"Alright, let's begin."

With the order from the Ancient Origin Sect's Martial Saint, the competition started.

"Whoosh."

Without any hesitation, Shen Lianxin rushed toward the mountain almost immediately. He was well aware of Lin Fei's strength. Therefore, Shen Lianxin wouldn't distract Lin Fei. Anyway, no matter what, if Lin Fei wanted to ascend the mountain, Shen Lianxin believed that no one could stop him. So, he didn't beat around the bush. Without any hesitation, he activated the true essence within his body and rushed towards the mountain at the fastest speed.

However, as fast as Shen Lianxin was, Ying Wuming, Lu Xuan, and the other Martial Saints seemed to be even faster! They moved ahead even faster than Shen Lianxin at first.

A gleam flashed across Lin Fei's eyes.

"I didn't allow you to move!"

In the next moment, without any hesitation, Lin Fei's saber momentum exploded!

"Boom."

A circle of white light erupted from Lin Fei's body. Instantly, it covered the area beneath the mountain of the Ancient Origin Sect. Hundreds of Martial Saints, even including the martial artists who were preparing to participate in the Ancient Origin Sect outer disciple assessment, were all enveloped by Lin Fei's saber momentum.

Suddenly, whether they were ordinary martial artists or Martial Saints, they all felt as if they were stuck in a swamp, finding it difficult to move. Even those Martial Saints felt as if they were carrying mountains on their backs. The weight made their whole bodies tremble. Even the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect, who was originally high above and prepared to stand by and watch the show, at this moment, was also suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum.

The entire area beneath the mountain of the Ancient Origin Sect, within a radius of ten miles, was suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum!

For a moment, the entire area beneath the mountain fell silent, and one could hear a pin drop.

210. Transcendence Saber Momentum Suppress Martial Saints

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back. He stood quietly at the foot of the mountain. He didn't move, and neither did the others. Because of the momentum they had created, they were being noticed by the high-ranking members of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Being noticed in itself was a testament to these Martial Saints' power. Perhaps, each had their own special traits and trump cards. Every single one of them was a highly renowned individual. To rise from an ordinary martial artist to become a Martial Saint was undoubtedly extraordinary.

Even so, at this moment, under the suppression of Lin Fei's saber momentum, everyone felt as if they had fallen into a swamp. Their bodies carried the weight of heavy mountains, trembling. Even the true essence within their bodies couldn't flow smoothly. They all stopped in their tracks.

As for trying to force their way up?

Certainly, it could be done. However, it would consume an enormous amount of true essence. If their true essence was exhausted, what would they do when they encountered attacks from other Martial Saints later?

Therefore, for a while, these Martial Saints didn't move. Their eyes were all fixed on Lin Fei. They recognized Lin Fei.

Dao Seeker Lin Fei.

Now, because of the hype created by the eight major families, his name was known far and wide. Only, they hadn't expected Dao Seeker Lin Fei was actually this terrifying. He had comprehended saber momentum!

"Saber momentum, this is saber momentum!"

"Even if it's saber momentum, it won't trap me. Break!"

"Ah... Break for me!"

Among these Martial Saints, there were still some fierce characters. For example, Lu Xuan, Ying Wuming, etc. Their true essence was indeed powerful. They tried to break free from Lin Fei's saber momentum. If it were before, when he had only mastered saber momentum, Lin Fei's saber momentum might not have been able to suppress these Martial Saints.

But now, it was different. The transcendence of saber momentum wasn't a doubling or tripling of power. But a tenfold, dozens of times increase! Therefore, even if these Martial Saints tried their best to struggle, their efforts were in vain.

As for the disciples at the foot of the mountain, they were even more terrified. Looking at Lin Fei, their eyes were a hint of fear and dread.

Saber momentum, evolved from the saber intent. Not only could it interfere with reality, but it could also deter the spirit! For these acquired martial artists, being suppressed by the saber momentum, even if Lin Fei's saber momentum didn't intentionally suppress them, just a little bit of the leaked power was enough to make them feel incredibly shocked and terrified.

However, at the foot of the mountain, there was one exception. That was the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Originally, this Martial Saint was merely "supervising." Or, watching the excitement from the side. He was high above, detached from the world. But now, he was also suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum. Although there was a hint of surprise on his face, he seemed to have no fear or panic.

"Saber momentum, he actually comprehended saber momentum. Interesting. It seems the Dao Seeker truly lives up to his reputation. How could someone who managed to cross the vast sea from the other end be ordinary? But, you have saber momentum, I have fist momentum!"

At this time, the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect, a fierce light flashed in his eyes!

Perhaps, many people didn't understand his identity. He was a true disciple! In the Ancient Origin Sect, his status was higher than that of the elders.

Each direct disciple, in the outside world, could become the overlord of a region. All were terrifying Martial Saints standing tall and upright. And he was among the best of them. This time, he presided over the initiation ceremony out of interest. Unexpectedly, he encountered such an "interesting" Martial Saint like Lin Fei. As a dignified direct disciple, how could he be suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum?

"Boom."

The Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect, originally bent slightly by Lin Fei's saber momentum, now, bit by bit, slowly straightened up. His body became upright again.

At the same time, a circle of grey light radiated from the body of the Ancient Origin Sect's Martial Saint. One circle after another, exuding an overbearing, fierce, utterly rigid, and masculine aura.

Everyone seemed to "see" an incomparable fist as if it spanned across the void. This fist seemed to be able to destroy everything, crush everything!

Fist momentum!

No one expected that this Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect had actually comprehended fist momentum too!

"Fist momentum... I remember now, he is the true disciple of the Ancient Origin Sect, the Fist Saint Gu Meng!"

"What, he is Fist Saint Gu Meng? The Fist Saint Gu Meng who killed three top Martial Saints with one punch, shocking the entire Tianqi Nation?"

"Fist Saint Gu Meng, the true disciple of the Ancient Origin Sect, is actually presiding over the ceremony."

"What a terrifying fist momentum, is this the true disciple of the Ancient Origin Sect? It's simply incredible..."

"Why do I feel like Fist Saint Gu Meng's fist momentum seems a bit inferior to Dao Seeker Lin Fei's saber momentum?"

For a moment, the hearts of many people at the foot of the mountain were shocked.

A true disciple of the Ancient Origin Sect. Fist Saint Gu Meng.

The combination of these two titles made everyone look at Gu Meng with newfound awe. Even Lin Fei's gaze at Gu Meng's fist momentum held a touch of surprise. But, that was all. If he didn't move, then no one had the right to move under his saber momentum!

"Suppress!"

Lin Fei just spat out a single word. Suddenly, it seemed as if countless strands of saber intent in the void, covering the sky and the earth, pressuring towards the numerous Martial Saints.

"Thud!"

Some of the Martial Saints flew into the void, preparing to walk on air, rushing to the top of the mountain at the fastest speed, but they were directly pressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum, causing them to fall to the ground. Even after falling to the ground, they had to desperately seek support from the ground with both hands, resisting the pressure of the saber momentum.

As for Fist Saint Gu Meng, originally, he detached from the world. Even when Lin Fei displayed his saber momentum, he didn't take it seriously. He felt that once his fist momentum came out, he would be able to easily break free from Lin Fei's saber momentum.

However, the expression on Gu Meng's face had become rigid. Even the smile on his face was gradually disappearing. Because he found that when his fist momentum erupted, the circles of grey light were actually being compressed back.

Yes, bit by bit, they were compressed back. Whether it's fist momentum or saber momentum. The smaller the range, the stronger the power. Now being suppressed back could only mean one thing. His fist momentum was inferior to Lin Fei's saber momentum!

Moreover, Gu Meng himself felt even with the protection of fist momentum, under the cover of Lin Fei's saber momentum, he still felt as if he was surrounded by a mountain of sabers. Countless sabers were ready to fall at any time, cutting him into pieces!

The competition between saber momentum and fist momentum didn't tolerate any deception.

Strength is strength. Weakness is weakness.

Clearly, Gu Meng's fist momentum was inferior to Lin Fei's saber momentum. Even, far inferior! The two were not even on the same level.

"Saber momentum... Transcendence!"

Gu Meng uttered each word slowly. At this moment, his expression had become extremely solemn. He finally understood Lin Fei's saber momentum had reached transcendence.

And him?

Fist momentum at the Mastery level! Even among the true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect, Fist momentum at the Mastery level could be considered an outstanding achievement. That's why he could always appear so relaxed.

But, Lin Fei's was transcendence-level saber momentum. Only at this time did Gu Meng truly understand what "Dao Seeker" really meant. Why every Dao Seeker ultimately achieved no small feat. Just based on Lin Fei's understanding of the transcendence-level saber momentum, he could make the entire Ancient Origin Sect take him seriously!

Thinking of this, Gu Meng withdrew his fist momentum.

He said to Lin Fei, "Lin Fei, withdraw your saber momentum. Your companion has reached the top of the mountain. As for you, there's no need to compete with them for the quota. It's their misfortune to compete with you for the quota. With you here, they can't even move. Won't they be wiped out by then? You can directly enter the Ancient Origin Sect and become an outer elder!"

The other Martial Saints were also all taken aback. Their eyes were filled with shock!

Lin Fei was going to directly enter the Ancient Origin Sect. He didn't even have to take the examination!

Many Martial Saints, who were proud and arrogant, thought they were not inferior to anyone. But they were easily suppressed by this "Dao Seeker" alone. Hundreds of Martial Saints, not one could move. Their pride was shattered by Lin Fei.

This was a Dao Seeker who truly lived up to his reputation!

211. Energy billows, forming flowers

Lin Fei looked up towards the top of the mountain. Shen Lianxin had reached the top. So, Lin Fei nodded and directly withdrew his saber momentum. Once the saber momentum was withdrawn, the suppression of everyone also disappeared in an instant.

"Whoosh".

The next moment, hundreds of Martial Saints immediately rushed frantically toward the top of the mountain. Among them, the Martial Saints like Ying Wuming and Lu Xuan were the fastest.

Hundreds of Martial Saints even started to make their moves. True essence burst forth. Martial arts shocked the heavens and the earth.

It was a shocking battle. If it weren't for Lin Fei's saber momentum, suppressing everything, then this battle of hundreds of Martial Saints would have shaken the heavens and the earth.

Such a battle was something one could only come across but not seek. It made countless disciples yearn for it. However, just now Lin Fei, with his own strength, displayed saber momentum, suppressing hundreds of Martial Saints!

Looking back now, these Martial Saints were fighting passionately. It seemed to have a different taste, but it felt a little bland. Even those acquired disciples felt the same. Their gazes, from time to time, fell on Lin Fei.

Suppressing hundreds of Martial Saints with his own strength, no one dared to move. What kind of power is this? What kind of boldness? What kind of domineering attitude? They also hoped that one day they could be this domineering!

"Brother Lin, let's go up the mountain together."

Gu Meng changed the way he addressed Lin Fei. Obviously, Gu Meng had also acknowledged Lin Fei. Perhaps, other people didn't know what saber momentum transcendence meant. But Gu Meng knew very well.

All the true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect knew, for a Martial Saint, reaching the peak of cultivation wasn't difficult. The Ancient Origin Sect had various resources piled up. For a typical genius, spending some time reaching the peak of Martial Saint was also possible. But if one wanted to comprehend momentum, that was not something that could be achieved by piling up resources.

Moreover, above Martial Saints, there is the Martial Sovereign! Without comprehending momentum, there would be no breakthrough to achieve the status of Martial Sovereign. Momentum is essential!

Therefore, among the true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect, only the true disciples who had comprehended momentum could be considered Martial Sovereign seeds.

"Alright, let's go up the mountain together."

Facing the "goodwill" released by Gu Meng, Lin Fei didn't refuse. So, the two of them, step by step, crossed the void, walked in the air, and arrived at the top of the mountain.

At this moment, on the top of the mountain, many Martial Saints had already reached their destination. There were still some Martial Saints fighting. But Gu Meng didn't even look at them. He was just a supervisor. As for gathering those beginner Martial Saints, that was not his jurisdiction. Naturally, there were others in charge. Gu Meng only brought the most special one, the Dao Seeker Lin Fei!

Lin Fei looked at the Ancient Origin Sect in front of him.

The mountain gate was huge. There was no immortal qi lingering inside nor were there any precious birds or exotic beasts. Instead, there was energy rushing to the sky. Like a cloud of smoke, it rushed into the clouds.

"This is energy smoke cultivated to an extremely profound level. When you enter the Ancient Origin Sect and acquire the cultivation method, you naturally will have energy, and even cultivating to the point of energy smoke is not difficult," Gu Meng said with a smile.

Lin Fei nodded. Soon, two figures walked out from inside the Ancient Origin Sect. These two figures didn't have energy smoke, but they had an extremely strong sense of oppression! Even Lin Fei felt the pressure.

Even Gu Meng, seeing these two martial artists, immediately paid his respects: "Greetings. Two transmission elders!"

The others also paid their respects one after another. Obviously, these two transmission elders seemed to have different statuses and positions.

The two martial artists had cold gazes and serious expressions. Only when they saw Lin Fei, their expressions seemed to soften slightly, even a smile appeared.

"The examination is over, this time, a total of eleven people passed the examination, can join our Ancient Origin Sect, and become the outer elder. Dao Seeker Lin Fei, Dao Seeker Shen Lianxin, Lu Xuan, Ying Wuming..."

Then, these two transmission elders began to read out the names. Soon, all eleven names were read. Lin Fei found that there were several Martial Saints who were not those who were mentioned by Gu Meng to build momentum. Instead, they were obscure. Some of the Martial Saints who built momentum failed the examination.

"I don't accept this! I went through all kinds of hardships and expended countless efforts to reach the Ancient Origin Sect. Just a trivial examination eliminated me? If there really was a big fight, more than half of the eleven people you chose are not my matches! Why can't I enter the Ancient Origin Sect?"

Suddenly, a Martial Saint roared. His expression was ferocious. His body was full of momentum. His eyes were red. Obviously, he had reached the point of extreme anger and he was extremely unwilling to accept this.

Lin Fei also looked over. He recognized this person. Zhao Canglong! He was previously named by Gu Meng, one of the Martial Saints who greatly built momentum. But he was not selected.

It was unknown what happened at the foot of the mountain. That prevented Zhao Canglong from reaching the top of the mountain first. It must be that his movement technique was lacking.

In Lin Fei's view, this examination was full of loopholes. It wasn't even an examination. It seemed that anyone could be chosen. It was entirely up to the preferences of the two transmission elders.

Of course, if there were really good talents like Lin Fei who had comprehended momentum, the transmission elders would definitely not miss it. As for the others, it really depended on luck.

"Don't accept it? Hehe, these scattered cultivation Martial Saints from the outside world really think they've reached the peak step by step? Since you don't accept it, then die!"

One of the transmission elders stepped forward. He didn't burst out any momentum, just punched out. This punch, without any extra fancy moves, was just a straightforward punch, even the true essence in his body didn't burst out much.

It was just barely visible that this elder's body erupted with terrifying energy. This was no longer just energy smoke but rather a flower that was vaguely opening on top of his head. A flower completely condensed from energy.

The moment the flower opened, this punch arrived in front of Zhao Canglong.

"Ah..."

Zhao Canglong was as if awakening from a dream. His body's blood and true essence exploded instantly and also punched out. It seemed as if there was a faint sound of a dragon chant. It was obviously some very profound boxing method.

On the other hand, the transmission elder was just an ordinary straight punch.

"Boom".

The two fists collided hard. But the next moment, Zhao Canglong's body exploded on cue. He was directly blown up by the elder's punch and turned into a cloud of blood mist.

He died!

A Martial Saint of such prestige, even everyone could see Zhao Canglong was no ordinary Martial Saint. However, he was still blown up by this ordinary punch from the transmission elder. He didn't have any resistance at all.

This was completely crushing! Even a crushing that didn't leave any hope. Just like an adult and a baby. Worlds apart!

For a moment, the faces of all the Martial Saints present changed drastically. Those two transmission elders obviously were also just Martial Saints. Their realm was the same. Even, they didn't use any momentum, and the true essence wasn't used. Just a punch with physical strength alone instantly exploded a top Martial Saint.

Was this possible?

Even Lin Fei's pupils shrank sharply. Danger! He sensed a trace of danger from the two transmission elders. Especially when the flower made of energy appeared on the elder's head. The danger Lin Fei could sense was more intense.

"This is the Energy Flower! The elder has condensed the Energy Flower, which means that the body has reached its limit! If the three flowers gather at the top. The elder doesn't even have to make a move, just a glance can kill Zhao Canglong. The gap between Martial Saints and Martial Saints is worlds apart. How can a loose cultivation Martial Saint be compared with a Martial Saint from my Ancient Origin Sect?"

Gu Meng sneered.

"Energy Flower?"

A glimmer of surprise flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

"Brother Lin, don't be surprised. Once you enter the Ancient Origin Sect, you will naturally know. Like you, a Dao Seeker who has already comprehended saber momentum, your future achievements will definitely be extraordinary. Even the gathering of the three flowers is not impossible! By then, I'm afraid I'll have to rely on Brother Lin."

Gu Meng said with a smile. In dealing with Lin Fei, his attitude was completely different. After all, even though they were all Martial Saints, not all Martial Saints were the same.

"The eleven Martial Saints whose names were read, follow us to the Ancestral Hall for the beginner ceremony."

After saying that, the two transmission elders turned around and walked towards the mountain gate of the Ancient Origin Sect.

"Brother Lin, go ahead. After you're settled, I'll come to visit you."

Gu Meng said with a smile to Lin Fei. Lin Fei nodded. He then followed the two transmission elders and flew into the Ancient Origin Sect.

212. Martial Dao Tower

In the Outer Sect of the Ancient Origin Sect, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin had now received the clothing of the Outer Sect elders. They were Outer Sect elders and naturally had to preside over the Outer Sect. Therefore, the cave mansion they lived in was also in the Outer Sect.

The Ancient Origin Sect was very large, with the Outer Sect disciples, Inner Sect disciples, true disciples, and so on all divided into different mountain peaks. There were dense mountain peaks, stretching as far as the eye could see. Lin Fei didn't believe these mountains naturally existed.

After casually asking around, Lin Fei found out that these mountains were all moved here by some of the predecessors of the Ancient Origin Sect using their astonishing Divine Abilities.

Moving mountains!

Even though Foundation Establishment True Persons could also cast some mountain-moving spells, they could only move small mountains. The mountains of the Ancient Origin Sect, however, were all very tall and grand, clearly not ordinary mountains.

"Divine Abilities..." A gleam flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He had heard this term more than once.

Did the Martial Sovereign have Divine Abilities? He didn't know.

However, the various aspects of a Martial Saint were magical enough. It was just that Lin Fei had always been a loose martial artist, and he hadn't even acquired any Martial Saint cultivation methods.

Take a look at those two transmission elders. They were also Martial Saints, but they didn't use any momentum and still could punch out such a terrifying punch.

"Brother Shen, we are now the Outer Sect elders of the Ancient Origin Sect. Here, we can find the direction forward in martial arts. So, let's each perform our duties here and jointly step onto the pinnacle of martial arts! As for the matters of the eight major families, I will deal with them."

Shen Lianxin nodded and didn't say much. He turned around and left.

The two of them each had their own cave mansions. Lin Fei knew that Shen Lianxin was a martial fanatic and wasn't good at socializing. He could handle some trivial matters, like those of the eight major families.

Now, although both of them were Outer Sect elders, their responsibilities were different. Lin Fei was the Elder of the Enforcement Hall of the Outer Sect, and Shen Lianxin was the Elder of the Transmission Hall of the Outer Sect. Of course, there wasn't much to do as an Outer Sect elder. Besides, not all elders were the same.

Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin were both Martial Saints. What could surprise them? If it were up to elders at the Martial Saint level like Lin Fei in the Enforcement Hall of the Outer Sect to take action, what major event must have happened in the Outer Sect?

Although the Ancient Origin Sect was not very strong in the Ancient Continent, it still suppressed one side. At least in the Tianqi Country, no one dared to provoke the Ancient Origin Sect.

Lin Fei sat alone in the cave mansion. Being an Outer Sect elder of the Ancient Origin Sect certainly had some benefits. The most direct benefit was contribution points. He could get three thousand contribution points.

The source of these contribution points had two ways. One was the contribution points distributed to disciples and elders each year. For example, Lin Fei, an Outer Sect elder, would receive only a thousand contribution points per year, roughly the same as a true disciple. True disciples got slightly more, approximately 1,200 contribution points per year. As for Outer Sect disciples, they received none at all. Only Inner Sect disciples received a distribution of 300 contribution points per year.

The second source was sect missions. One could undertake some sect missions and thereby gain some contribution points. But there weren't many high-level sect missions, and even if a Martial Saint took on a mission, it entailed certain risks. Most of these missions were not within the Tianqi Country. Hence, the Ancient Origin Sect's contribution points were precious. Unlike the Nine Profound Sect, they could not be exchanged for silver. It was impossible in the Ancient Origin Sect.

"Three thousand contribution points, it's obviously for the Outer Sect elders to exchange for cultivation methods in the Martial Dao Tower," Lin Fei thought excitedly. He had traveled thousands of miles across the sea and endured great hardships, all for what? Now, he could finally get what he wished for - the cultivation method!

Moreover, joining the Ancient Origin Sect had given Lin Fei an extra benefit - an additional 3,000 contribution points! While the other ten Martial Saints received 3,000 points, Lin Fei had 6,000 points, a full double!

Clearly, this was due to his "building momentum" and understanding the "saber momentum", suppressing hundreds of Martial Saints at the foot of the mountain. In the Ancient Origin Sect, the higher-profile and more talented one was, the more benefits one got.

With his contribution points doubled, the range of martial arts Lin Fei could choose from was undoubtedly broader. Without any hesitation, he stood up, took a step, and transformed into a stream of light, rushing towards the Martial Dao Tower.

In the Ancient Origin Sect, martial arts were exchanged in the Martial Dao Tower.

Dressed in the attire of an Outer Sect elder, Lin Fei was greeted with respect by many Outer Sect disciples as he walked in. He entered the Martial Dao Tower. The first floor contained Body Refining and Acquired level martial arts. The second floor contained Innate level martial arts. The third floor had Martial Saint level martial arts. Lin Fei could only enter the third floor as the fourth was beyond his reach.

Upon reaching the third floor of the Martial Dao Tower, he found two Martial Saint elders stationed there. He handed over his elder's token to the two Martial Saint elders.

"Hmm? So you're a newly promoted Outer Sect elder. Since you were a loose martial artist before, do you know the path of a Martial Saint?" one of the elders asked.

"Please give me your guidance, elder."

"Take this and study it carefully. Make sure you understand so that you don't choose the wrong martial arts."

Lin Fei took a small booklet that contained an explanation of the Martial Saint realm. Excited, Lin Fei immediately moved aside to read it thoroughly.

According to the booklet's description, a Martial Saint who wishes to achieve the pinnacle of martial arts must cultivate three aspects: Energy, Qi, and Spirit.

Energy refers to human energies, which in fact represent the body. Qi refers to a Martial Saint's true essence. Spirit refers to Martial Dao True Intent, or a Martial Saint's momentum.

When a Martial Saint cultivates their body to the extreme, they can condense the Energy Flower. When their True Essence is cultivated to the extreme, they can condense the Qi Flower. When the saber momentum is cultivated to the extreme, the Spirit Flower can be condensed.

Only when the Three Flowers converge at the top and energy, qi, and spirit become one is there a glimmer of hope to unlock the "chains of life wheel" and manifest the life wheel. Manifestation of the life wheel means that a martial artist has taken control of their own "life". This is the pinnacle of martial arts!

A Golden Core cultivator survives the Heavenly Tribulation. Martial arts master controls the life wheel!

"Swallowing a golden core, I control my fate, not heaven!" This describes a Golden Core cultivator, and similarly, it describes a Martial Sovereign. Controlling the life wheel means controlling one's own life!

Lin Fei finally understood why his evolution of the saber momentum and reaching transcendence was taken seriously by the higher-ups of the Ancient Origin Sect. If he hadn't evolved the saber momentum, he wouldn't have been able to condense the Spirit Flower. He would never achieve the convergence of the Three Flowers, and lose the opportunity to break the chains of the life wheel.

Without the manifestation of the life wheel, one naturally cannot become a Martial Arts Sovereign. For a martial artist like this, it means losing hope. Even if he is a Martial Saint, in the eyes of the Ancient Origin Sect's higher-ups, his potential has been exhausted.

With a snap, Lin Fei closed the booklet and respectfully returned it to the two elders.

"I understand," he said.

"Good, now that you understand, go in and choose. You can't touch the martial arts inside until you've made your choice. Otherwise, if you touch it, it will trigger the prohibition and reveal the martial arts content. That would be the equivalent of choosing that martial art, and the contribution points will be deducted directly. Each martial art inside, regardless of its profundity, is at the Martial Saint level, and each one requires a thousand contribution points."

Lin Fei nodded and entered the third level. Each martial art costing a thousand contribution points was indeed very affordable. The three thousand contribution points of an Outer Sect elder could be used to choose three.

As for the profound martial arts, or slightly weaker martial arts, what's the difference? At the level of a Martial Saint, everyone knows that martial arts is not about profundity, but about what suits oneself. This is the most important thing.

Lin Fei stood before the bookshelves. Various martial arts, saber techniques, sword techniques, and so on, were all available, all at the Martial Saint level.

Now Lin Fei had to choose a cultivation method first. He saw the names of these cultivation methods:

"Star Fighting Technique: absorb the power of the stars and the moon, transform them into true essence, and use the vastness of the stars and the moon to condense the Qi Flower."

"Glutton Technique: created by observing the ancient fierce beast Glutton. You can transform various exotic beasts you devour into blood essence, increase your blood essence, and ultimately condense the Energy Flower."

"Sky Beast Blood Transformation Technique: transforms the blood essence of all beasts in the world, making it your own, increases your blood essence, and ultimately condenses the Energy Flower."

"Clouds gathering Technique: gather the rosy clouds of the world, and transform them into true essence. If you can gather extremely special rosy clouds, your cultivation can advance by leaps and bounds, and ultimately condense the Qi Flower."

Seeing these martial arts techniques, each was earth-shattering. Just reading the introductions of these techniques was enough to make his spirit tremble, demonstrating the extraordinariness of these techniques. To say these techniques are "creation-inspired" is no exaggeration.

Lin Fei calmed his emotions, then closed his eyes. He did not go to choose a martial art. Because he had long understood his own characteristics. The martial arts he needed could only be those with "fate". The so-called, destined ones, the martial arts will come naturally. Only the martial arts that choose Lin Fei on their own can be cultivated more quickly. This is Lin Fei's best choice.

So, Lin Fei spoke.

"I wish to set foot on the pinnacle of the martial path. Which supreme martial art technique would be willing to lend me a helping hand? I promise to make you famous throughout ancient times, celebrated for thousands of years!"

After finishing speaking, Lin Fei closed his eyes and quietly waited. He believed that the "destined one" would surely choose him.

213. True Intention Scroll Wants to Advance

Time passed little by little. Lin Fei was quietly waiting. He was very patient. However, an incense stick's time had passed, and it seemed there was no movement. A quarter of an hour passed, and there was still no movement.

Lin Fei couldn't help but frown slightly.

"It seems that martial arts techniques at the level of Martial Saint are indeed different. They are high-spirited and arrogant and have unique personalities. Just listening to my few words, I'm afraid they won't be persuaded..."

Lin Fei compared it to his time in Great Chang. At that time, whether Lin Fei was a Martial Master or a Martial Saint, he still had a strong appeal to some top martial arts techniques. Because, at that time, Lin Fei had a great reputation. Moreover, in the history of Great Chang, martial artists stronger than Lin Fei were few and far between!

So, at that time, as long as Lin Fei was willing, those top martial arts techniques flocked to him like moths to a flame. For instance, in the True Intention Scroll, with Lin Fei's understanding, it was difficult to even be a beginner in a short period of time. But the True Intention Scroll wanted to get out, so it simply helped Lin Fei "begin", becoming Lin Fei's martial art technique. This was almost like a "reverse charge".

Also, when Lin Fei needed some top saber techniques to increase his saber foundation, or to increase the progress of saber momentum cultivation, he needed perfection-level top saber techniques. And those top saber techniques actually integrated into Lin Fei's saber momentum in the state of "perfection-level saber techniques". That was very "proactive".

However, when he arrived in the Ancient Origin Sect, things were different. Lin Fei was just an outer sect elder. Even his cultivation was only at the early stage of Martial Saint. Therefore, it's not hard to imagine his appeal to these Martial Saint level techniques in the Ancient Origin Sect.

"It seems that if I can't attract these Martial Saint level techniques, I need to find a way."

Lin Fei pondered for a while. These techniques were all at the Martial Saint level. Moreover, almost every martial art could reach the Martial Sovereign realm. To impress such martial arts, he must have some of his own characteristics.

And what was Lin Fei's current advantage?

Lin Fei quickly had an answer. Saber momentum and Saber Essence!

Obviously, Lin Fei's biggest advantage compared to other Martial Saints was his saber momentum and saber essence. Transcendence-level saber momentum, even among the core disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect, not many could reach this level.

As for saber essence, it was also very special. The founder of the Nine Profound Sect, although only a martial arts Grand Master, not even a Martial Saint, was astonishingly talented. He actually created such an amazing technique as the True Intention Scroll which could merge saber intent into true qi.

Now that Lin Fei had become a Martial Saint, it had evolved into saber essence. Perhaps only the combination of the Spirit Flower and the Qi Flower could achieve a similar effect to the saber essence. Therefore, this saber essence of Lin Fei's was unique. Other Martial Saints simply couldn't possess it.

Thinking of this, Lin Fei took a deep breath.

"Boom."

The next moment, he released his saber momentum. The transcendence-level saber momentum enveloped the entire third floor. There were few people usually coming and going on this third floor, but there were a few Martial Saints.

At this moment, these Martial Saints felt as if they were carrying a mountain on their backs. They were all suppressed from head to toe. A hint of shock appeared on their faces.

"Huh? Is this... saber momentum?"

The two Martial Saint elders guarding the third floor raised their eyebrows and immediately looked inside the third floor. They too felt the saber momentum. Even, this saber momentum gave them a bit of pressure.

"Transcendence-level saber momentum. It seems that this newly-promoted outer sect elder is not simple."

"Being able to comprehend transcendence-level saber momentum at the early stage of Martial Saint is indeed not simple."

"But what is he doing releasing his saber momentum in the Martial Dao Tower?"

"It doesn't matter, as long as he doesn't take action and doesn't break the rules."

The two Martial Saint elders shook their heads slightly. Lin Fei had only released his saber momentum. He did not break the rules of the Martial Dao Tower. They naturally did not need to pay attention.

At this moment, in the saber momentum, Lin Fei stretched out his hand. Suddenly, a large amount of saber essence surged out of his hand. These saber essence condensed into a sharp Heavenly Saber.

Lin Fei spoke again, "I wish to reach the pinnacle of martial arts. Is there any divine technique that would lend me a hand? I will make you famous throughout the Ancient Continent and praised for eternity!"

As Lin Fei's voice fell, the entire third floor of the Martial Dao Tower became very quiet.

Time passed little by little.

"The Glutton Technique wishes to be your martial art. However, the Glutton Technique is sealed and needs the host to unseal it."

"Seal?"

Lin Fei immediately understood. It must be a restriction. On the third floor of the Martial Dao Tower. every martial art had restrictions. As long as one touched it, he could lift the restriction.

Lin Fei was not in a hurry. If the martial art chose him, then he would choose the martial art. He had seen the Glutton Technique before. It can devour the flesh and blood of exotic beasts, increase essence blood, and ultimately condense the Energy Flower. This should be a martial art for cultivating the body.

Once the Glutton Technique was chosen, Lin Fei would probably have to go and hunt exotic beasts constantly, and then swallow their flesh and blood.

Soon, a voice from the system sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"The Heavenly Blood Transformation Technique wishes to become your martial art. But the Heavenly Blood Transformation Technique is sealed and needs the host to unseal it."

"The Glutton Technique is enraged, feeling its dignity challenged by the Heavenly Blood Transformation Technique daring to compete with it."

"Thus, the Glutton Technique and the Heavenly Blood Transformation Technique started a fierce confrontation."

"The two are evenly matched, and it will take at least a few days to determine the winner, so neither can temporarily become the host's martial art."

Lin Fei listened to the system's voice in his mind. He didn't know what to say. The Glutton Technique and the Heavenly Blood Transformation Technique were fighting and thus didn't have time to become his martial arts. So, he still didn't have any martial art to choose?

"So fiercely competitive, these two martial arts are too aggressive and do not consider the overall situation. Even if I chose these two martial arts, I'm afraid they would be difficult to manage."

Lin Fei shook his head. He was very dissatisfied with the performance of these two martial arts. Even if these two martial arts were earth-shattering and wonderfully created, if they became Lin Fei's martial arts and were impulsive and inconsiderate, Lin Fei would never be able to cultivate the Energy Flower in his lifetime. That would be a big problem.

However, Lin Fei was a little curious. Why were all the martial arts he came across related to body cultivation? He displayed saber momentum and saber essence. Aren't there any martial arts for cultivating true essence?

Just then, the true essence in Lin Fei's body suddenly started to run wildly. This was the first time such a thing had happened.

Lin Fei was taken aback. Then, the voice of the system sounded in his mind.

"Your True Intention Scroll wishes for the host to give it a chance."

"The True Intention Scroll hopes that the host will unlock the seal of the Myriad Transformation Technique. The True Intention Scroll is willing to duel with the Myriad Transformation Technique, devour it, and upgrade to the Martial Saint level!"

Lin Fei was a little surprised. The True Intention Scroll wanted to duel with the Myriad Transformation Technique. Even more, it was prepared to devour the Myriad Transformation Technique and upgrade to the level of a Martial Saint Technique. However, could the True Intention Scroll succeed?

Lin Fei was a bit uncertain. The True Intention Scroll, although previously a bit willful and domineering, it had been diligent after being tamed by Lin Fei's saber intent, fulfilling its mission, allowing Lin Fei's saber qi to successfully transform into saber essence. It certainly made a considerable contribution!

Unexpectedly, the True Intention Scroll now had such grand ambitions. It even wanted to upgrade to the level of Martial Saint Techniques.

However, Lin Fei did not rashly agree. He had to first take a look. What kind of martial art is the Myriad Transformation Technique that the True Intention Scroll wanted to devour?

So, Lin Fei looked around at the bookshelf. Finally, he found the Myriad Transformation Technique and some introductions about it.

214. True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique

"Myriad Transformation Technique: transform heaven and earth, sun, moon, stars, and everything, there's nothing it can't transform! It can open up any power and integrate any power. It's hard to get started, and it requires an extraordinary genius to start practicing. After practice, everything, such as heaven and earth, sun and moon, and stars, can be transformed into energy and converted into True Essence. The more energy you transform, the more True Essence you can convert."

When Lin Fei saw this Myriad Transformation Technique, his eyes lit up. This Myriad Transformation Technique seemed really extraordinary. The phrase "transform heaven and earth, sun, moon, stars, and everything, there's nothing it can't transform" certainly wasn't ordinary.

Moreover, according to the Myriad Transformation Technique, the speed of this martial art could be fast or slow. The speed completely depended on the "transformed energy".

As long as it could transform a strong power, even if it condensed the Qi Flower in one day, there probably wouldn't be a problem. However, it was too hard to get started. This martial art did not want to become Lin Fei's martial art.

If it were before, Lin Fei really didn't have a way. After all, this martial art seemed to have "no fate" with him. But now it was different.

The True Intention Scroll wanted to duel with the Myriad Transformation Technique. Once successful, the True Intention Scroll would devour the Myriad Transformation Technique. At that time, the Myriad Transformation Technique would naturally become Lin Fei's martial art. Moreover, it could perfectly integrate with Lin Fei's saber essence.

"True Intention Scroll, I hope you won't disappoint me!"

Lin Fei didn't hesitate at all. He reached out his hand and pressed directly on the secret book of the Myriad Transformation Technique.

"Buzz".

A faint white light flashed. Then, the restriction on the secret book of the Myriad Transformation Technique on the bookshelf was also lifted.

Lin Fei picked up the secret book and began to read. The next moment, Lin Fei closed his eyes.

In Lin Fei's mind, two rays of light appeared. One was the True Intention Scroll. The other was the Myriad Transformation Technique.

However, the light of the True Intention Scroll looked much smaller than the light of the Myriad Transformation Technique, almost only one-tenth of the light of the Myriad Transformation Technique.

"Whoosh".

However, the True Intention Scroll was the first to attack, instantly charged toward the Myriad Transformation Technique. Immediately, the Myriad Transformation Technique seemed to be angered too. It also emitted a great light and went directly toward the True Intention Scroll.

"Boom".

The two martial arts made a big mess in Lin Fei's mind. The True Intention Scroll was full of fighting spirit. It seemed fearless. However, the Myriad Transformation Technique was obviously much stronger than the True Intention Scroll. Therefore, it soon became clear that the True Intention Scroll was gradually unable to hold on.

Lin Fei knew if it continued like this, the True Intention Scroll would undoubtedly lose! Naturally, Lin Fei would like the True Intention Scroll to defeat the Myriad Transformation Technique and even devour it.

Thinking of this, Lin Fei had a thought.

"Saber momentum, go, help the True Intention Scroll!"

Suddenly, another ray of light appeared in Lin Fei's mind. That was saber momentum. The transcendence saber momentum was extraordinary. It covered the Myriad Transformation Technique all at once.

The True Intention Scroll also immediately pounced on it. The Myriad Transformation Technique was expanding crazily, trying to break free from the saber momentum's restriction.

However, both the saber momentum and the True Intention Scroll were supported by Lin Fei. How could the Myriad Transformation Technique break free?

About a quarter of an hour later, under the joint slaughter of the saber momentum and the True Intention Scroll, the Myriad Transformation Technique finally couldn't hold on. The True Intention Scroll immediately incorporated the Myriad Transformation Technique into itself.

"Shh".

The next moment, Lin Fei opened his eyes. The voice of the system also came into his mind.

"Your martial art True Intention Scroll has devoured the Myriad Transformation Technique and started to advance."

"Your martial art True Intention Scroll has advanced to the Martial Saint Technique, True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique!"

Lin Fei digested the memories in his mind. The True Intention Scroll had become the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. Not only did it possess all the characteristics of the Myriad Transformation Technique, but also it could perfectly integrate with Lin Fei's saber essence.

This allowed Lin Fei to easily convert the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth directly into saber essence. Moreover, not just Spiritual Qi, there was also the energy of the sun and moon, the power of stars, and so on. Even some heavenly treasures could also be transformed. This was the terrifying part of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. Everything can be transformed!

The martial art for cultivating true essence was finally settled. However, the martial art for cultivating the body was still without a clue.

"Blood Essence Nine Transformations hopes to become your martial art. But Blood Essence Nine Transformations has been sealed and requires the host to unseal it."

The voice of the system sounded in Lin Fei's mind. By the name, it should be a martial art for cultivating the body. So, he immediately went to check out the Blood Essence Nine Transformations martial art.

Soon, Lin Fei found this martial art.

"Blood Essence Nine Transformations: the first transformation is for accumulating blood essence. The second transformation doubles, the third transformation quadruples, the fourth transformation multiplies by eight, and the fifth transformation multiplies by sixteen. So on and so forth, all the way to the ninth transformation, which multiplies by two hundred and fifty-six! With two hundred and fifty-six times the blood essence, you will surely be able to condense an Energy Flower!"

When Lin Fei saw the content of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations, he couldn't help but feel a tremor in his heart.

This martial art didn't have many fancy moves. It was purely to increase blood essence. Blood essence is the foundation of the body. As long as the blood essence increases, then the body can correspondingly increase. Therefore, this martial art aims to condense the Energy Flower as its ultimate goal.

To condense an Energy Flower, no one knows how much blood essence is needed. However, with the Blood Essence Nine Transformations, as long as he could practice the ninth transformation, the amount of blood essence would be two hundred and fifty-six times. Such a terrifying amount of blood essence can almost guarantee a hundred percent that it can condense an Essence Flower.

"Let it be Blood Essence Nine Transformations then!"

Lin Fei reached out and touched the secret book of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations. Suddenly, the restriction on the Blood Essence Nine Transformations was instantly lifted. Then, in Lin Fei's mind, an extra segment of memory appeared. That was the memory of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations. And after the Blood Essence Nine Transformations became Lin Fei's martial art, it started practicing immediately.

Blood Essence Nine Transformations was very diligent. The first step was to transform blood into blood essence in Lin Fei's body. Originally, Lin Fei was a Martial Saint with a very strong body. Therefore, now transforming into blood essence was also the accumulation of the first transformation of Blood Essence Nine Transformations. Of course, this required some time.

"I have martial arts for cultivating the body and the saber essence. Next, it's time to cultivate the saber momentum."

Lin Fei looked at the martial arts on the bookshelf. There were no martial arts that directly cultivated saber momentum. There were only martial arts for cultivating saber techniques.

To comprehend the saber intent and then evolve the saber momentum is the hardest. Many martial artists of the Ancient Origin Sect, by chance, could condense an Energy Flower or a Qi Flower. Even, both flowers bloom together. But it was the Spirit Flower that they couldn't condense.

That's because the momentum that represents the Spirit Flower was always imperfect. The biggest reason is that there is no martial art that directly cultivates momentum. Momentum completely depends on one's own comprehension!

In this regard, Lin Fei had an advantage. Because his saber momentum was already transcendent.

Lin Fei didn't need to comprehend saber momentum. His saber momentum was a fusion of various saber momentums, and then further enhances it.

The saber momentum which evolved from the innate level saber techniques could no longer improve Lin Fei's saber momentum. To bring his saber momentum to perfection, Lin Fei figured that there was only one way. That is to practice martial arts of the Martial Saint level.

To evolve their saber momentum, and then incorporate it into the saber momentum of the Heavenly Saber. By then, his saber momentum would be able to improve again.

Therefore, Lin Fei needed more than one saber technique. He needed to practice more saber techniques at the Martial Saint level as soon as possible.

"Holy Spirit Saber Technique hopes to become your martial art. But Holy Spirit Saber Technique has been sealed and requires the host to unseal it."

"Flame Burning Heaven Saber hopes to become your martial art. But Flame Burning Heaven Saber has been sealed and requires the host to unseal it."

"Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique hopes to become your martial art. But Rainbow Transformation Saber has been sealed and requires the host to unseal it."

The system's voice came out in Lin Fei's mind. Lin Fei also looked at these three saber techniques in turn. All seemed feasible. So, he chose these three saber techniques.

In fact, Lin Fei could choose more saber techniques. After all, the more saber techniques he practices, the better. However, he had already chosen five martial arts. That is five thousand contribution points. Lin Fei needed to save a thousand contribution points for emergencies.

Wait until the saber momentum was evolved to see how much one Martial Saint level saber technique could increase the cultivation progress of the saber momentum. By then, it's not too late to continue choosing saber techniques.

After choosing five martial arts, Lin Fei didn't stay on the third floor of the Martial Dao Tower. He went directly to the two elders on the third floor.

"You've chosen five martial arts, deducting five thousand contribution points."

Lin Fei nodded. Then he directly left the Martial Dao Tower. He needed to return to his seclusion for cultivation as soon as possible and wait for the first transformation of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations to complete the transformation of the blood essence in his body.

215. Who hurt you？

Lin Fei had been meditating in his cave for three days. Suddenly, Lin Fei's body shook. He felt the Blood Essence Nine Transformations pause slightly. It seemed to stop. The Blood Essence Nine Transformations was quite diligent. It's always transforming the blood essence in the body every moment.

"Your Blood Essence Nine Transformations, after three days of hard cultivation, has finally transformed all the blood essence in your body."

"Your Blood Essence Nine Transformations, cultivation progress increased by 50%."

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"Is the transformation complete?"

Lin Fei knew that his body needed to complete the first transformation of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations cultivation. That was to transform the blood in the body. He also wanted to see how much blood essence can his body now transform.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately brought up the system panel to check the cultivation situation of martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique: Early stage (Progress 3%)

Blood Essence Nine Transformations: First transformation (Progress 50%)

Holy Spirit Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress 8%)

Flame Burning Heaven Saber: Mastery (Progress 15%)

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress 10%)

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei's martial arts were increasing again. For example, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique's cultivation progress had reached 3%. Almost increasing by 1% each day.

It seemed very little. But actually, it's not.

In about a hundred days, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique's cultivation progress could reach 100% and thus break through to the middle stage. Once it broke through, Lin Fei's cultivation would also reach the middle stage of Martial Saint!

Under normal circumstances, the cultivation of a Martial Saint actually looks at "Qi". That is the situation of true essence cultivation.

Of course, Lin Fei was very clear nothing was unchangeable.

If he got a bit of heaven and earth's treasures, for example, some spiritual grasses containing abundant spiritual power, then his True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique could advance by leaps and bounds.

Next is the Blood Essence Nine Transformations. The first transformation is to accumulate blood essence.

Currently, it had transformed all the blood essence in Lin Fei's body. The cultivation progress had only reached 50%.

In other words, he could still continue accumulating to break through to the second transformation. So he had to increase his blood essence.

Typically, the augmentation of blood essence came from the blood and flesh of exotic beasts, or from elixirs made from the same. This, essentially, was a resource! As long as he had enough resources, forming the Energy Flower wouldn't be an insurmountable task.

As for the three martial saint level saber techniques, it took him a mere three days to achieve mastery in all of them. This was rather terrifying. These were martial saint level saber techniques, each unfathomably profound. It would be considered quite impressive to achieve proficiency in just one of them within three days.

As for mastery?

That was destined to be challenging for others.

However, Lin Fei was different. After all, Lin Fei had already reached the level of saber saint with his transcendence in saber momentum. His foundation in saber technique was extraordinary, surpassing the majority of martial saints.

Therefore, with such a profound foundation in saber technique, it seemed reasonable that he could master the pinnacle martial saint level saber techniques in just three days.

However, this was just about his limit. Lin Fei's foundational saber technique had been almost completely depleted. Moving forward, If he wished to enhance his saber technique further, enlightenment was his only recourse.

Lin Fei hoped that these saber techniques were "hard-working" enough to reach transcendence or even perfection soon.

To comprehend the essence of the saber, to then reach perfection. Even just hearing this sounded extremely difficult. But this was the only way for Lin Fei's saber momentum to reach perfection. Moreover, this was the only method!

The path of martial arts was challenging, this was clearly demonstrated at the martial saint level. Every step was difficult. Even if the physical body could be enhanced with resources, it required a vast amount of them. It wasn't as simple as just piling them on. Some independent martial saints couldn't amass enough in their entire lifetime.

"I have only a thousand contribution points. To use them to buy resources from the sect at the early stage of Martial Saint would be somewhat uneconomical. For the Blood Essence Nine Transformations, I just need to consume the blood and flesh of exotic beasts. The vast ocean is home to an infinite number of sea beasts. Seems I could make a trip back to Fairy Mist Island. I could hunt sea beasts and consume their blood and flesh. At the same time, I could fulfill my agreement with the eight noble families."

Lin Fei planned a return to Fairy Mist Island. After all, he had an agreement with the eight noble families. Once he and Lin Fei became outer sect elders of the Ancient Origin Sect, each of them could nominate five disciples to join the sect, without the need for an examination.

The eight noble families on Fairy Mist Island were probably yearning for Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin's attention. The reason they had not disturbed Lin Fei yet was probably because they knew he needed time to familiarize himself with the Ancient Origin Sect.

Once Lin Fei gained a foothold in the Ancient Origin Sect, people from the eight noble families would certainly come to him. Now, if Lin Fei took the initiative to go back, he could also settle the agreement with the eight noble families.

Lin Fei thought of Shen Lianxin. He had been in the Ancient Origin Sect for several days now. How was Shen Lianxin doing? Since he had to go back to Fairy Mist Island, Lin Fei naturally had to ask Shen Lianxin if he wanted to go back too. Thus, Lin Fei rose to his feet and flew towards Shen Lianxin's cave dwelling.

Lin Fei was in the Outer Enforcement Hall, and Shen Lianxin was in the Outer Transmission Hall. Their caves were not in the same place and were a distance apart.

Soon, Lin Fei arrived at Shen Lianxin's cave. Shen Lianxin was sitting cross-legged. When he saw Lin Fei, he opened his eyes. However, Lin Fei frowned.

"You're injured," Lin Fei asked coldly, "Brother Shen, who hurt you?"

Shen Lianxin and Lin Fei had journeyed together from Great Chang, struggling to find their Dao, and finally arrived at the Ancient Continent. Naturally, they had to help each other.

Seeing that Shen Lianxin had only been in the Ancient Origin Sect for a few days and had already been injured, Lin Fei felt a trace of anger. However, Shen Lianxin seemed quite calm.

"Brother Lin, it's no big deal. As you know, I'm a martial fanatic. Injuries are inevitable when sparring with others. Moreover, the injuries are not severe. I can handle this."

Lin Fei stared at Shen Lianxin. It seemed Shen Lianxin didn't want Lin Fei to interfere.

Lin Fei did not continue to inquire. In the Ancient Origin Sect, nobody dared to kill the elders. It was just an injury. Since Shen Lianxin said he could handle it, Lin Fei would not press the matter.

"Brother Shen, I am planning to go back to Fairy Mist Island. Do you need to go back?" Lin Fei asked.

Shen Lianxin shook his head and said, "I need to heal now, so I won't go back to Fairy Mist Island for the time being. As for the matter of nominating five disciples from the eight noble families, Brother Lin, I ask you to take care of it for me."

"That's natural. Brother Shen, rest assured, you take good care of your injuries. I will handle the matter with the eight noble families."

"Thank you, Brother Lin."

Lin Fei did not say much. He turned around and left the cave dwelling. Shen Lianxin's injury was a bit unexpected for Lin Fei. However, judging by Shen Lianxin's demeanor, he should be able to handle it himself.

Lin Fei did not want to interfere too much. After all, Shen Lianxin was also a Martial Saint. He and Lin Fei were friends, he was not Lin Fei's follower. Some things, Shen Lianxin could handle himself. He didn't need Lin Fei to step in.

Moreover, even in the Ancient Origin Sect, even though Lin Fei had the transcendence saber momentum, there were still others who were Martial Saints with transcendence martial arts momentum.

Even the two elders who transmitted their skills had formed the Energy Flower. Even with Lin Fei's transcendence saber momentum as pressure, Lin Fei did not feel that he was an opponent for those two transmitting elders. The three flowers of energy, qi, and spirit. Once a flower was formed, it represented a Martial Saint at the peak!

In some aspects, they had reached the limit. Compared to other Martial Saints, the difference was as great as the difference between heaven and earth! They were completely on different levels.

So, Lin Fei also had to enhance his strength as soon as possible. He didn't need to think about the saber momentum for the time being. Reaching perfection was too difficult. On the contrary, forming the Energy Flower or Qi Flower seemed to have a glimmer of hope.

"Let's go."

Lin Fei didn't stay in the Ancient Origin Sect for long. He turned into a streak of light and flew towards Fairy Mist Island.

216. Lin Fei Returns to Fairy Mist Island

Lin Fei had returned to Fairy Mist Island. In the Ancient Origin Sect, especially in Tianqi Country, everyone was a martial artist. But what about Fairy Mist Island? Almost everyone was a Qi cultivator. For a while, Lin Fei was somewhat unaccustomed.

Regardless, Fairy Mist Island was not within the sphere of influence of the Ancient Origin Sect. It didn't even belong to any force. Fairy Mist Island was a group of overseas cultivators, primarily Qi cultivators. There were also martial artists. They all lived together on these overseas islands.

However, when Lin Fei returned to Fairy Mist Island, he found that something was not quite right. Fairy Mist Island seemed to be on higher alert. Lin Fei was detected as soon as he arrived.

Fortunately, Lin Fei was now a guest elder of the eight noble families. Therefore, he had a token with him. He passed the questioning of the patrolling Qi cultivators and smoothly entered Fairy Mist Island.

The entire atmosphere of Fairy Mist Island seemed somewhat heavy. There were noticeably fewer people coming and going.

Lin Fei did not inquire. Instead, he quickly went to the Shangguan family and met Shangguan Feiyun.

"Elder Lin, you're back? That's great. Where is Elder Shen?"

When Shangguan Feiyun saw Lin Fei, he seemed somewhat surprised. A smile appeared on his face.

"Brother Shen is busy cultivating and can't spare the time. This time I came back, I plan to take away ten juniors from the eight noble families to fulfill our agreement. Have the eight noble families settled on the people?" Lin Fei asked.

Together, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin could recommend a total of ten people. There were only eight noble families. Each family could nominate one person, leaving two vacancies. Everyone wanted these two spots. Therefore, this definitely involved some wrangling among the eight noble families.

However, Lin Fei didn't care at all. This was an internal matter of the eight noble families. They could handle it themselves. He just needed to take ten people to the Ancient Origin Sect.

"Elder Lin, we have already arranged the spots. You can take them away anytime."

Lin Fei nodded. Shangguan Feiyun was preparing to notify the eight noble families.

Lin Fei then asked, "By the way, has something happened on Fairy Mist Island recently? A lot of Qi cultivators are on patrol. Also, the atmosphere on the island seems quite tense."

When it came to this matter, Shangguan Feiyun's expression also became solemn. He said in a deep voice, "Elder Lin, there have indeed been some changes on the island recently. Our Fairy Mist Island has many islands, three of which were raided by pirates a while ago. These pirates looted three islands and then fled. The defensive formations on the islands couldn't hold for long. By the time the Foundation Establishment True Persons arrived, it was already too late. Three islands were wiped clean. Therefore, all the islands of Fairy Mist Island are currently tense, preparing for the pirates' next attack."

"Pirates?"

Lin Fei thoughtfully considered this. Shangguan Feiyun explained in detail. Originally, the people of Fairy Mist Island were uncared for by both heaven and earth. Being overseas, they seemed to command the vast sea.

But in reality? The place was actually quite barren. Neither martial arts sects nor immortal sects cared about them. Therefore, though Fairy Mist Island was home to many people, including Qi cultivators and martial artists, no large forces intervened. Though this gave them some freedom, it also brought increased risks.

For instance, pirates. These pirates consisted of martial artists and Qi cultivators. They had fallen into piracy for various reasons, specializing in looting.

In places like Fairy Mist Island, which lacked the backing of a large force, these pirates acted without restraint. Occasional raids on several islands were commonplace. This was not the first time such a thing had happened.

The pirates came and left without a trace. Even if the Foundation Establishment True Persons of Fairy Mist Island set up ambushes, once the pirates began to flee, the True Persons would not dare to chase after them.

Because pirates were desperadoes. They could venture into the open sea. But Foundation Establishment True Persons? They dared not!

The open sea was incredibly dangerous. Although it seemed that Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin who had sailed across the sea and survived several months of drifting in the open sea didn't face much danger.

In fact, they had encountered numerous perils. Luckily, they had the Sky Reaching Tower. After all, it was a magic treasure at the Golden Core level. It had a trace of heavenly thunder aura. This could deter some sea beasts. Thus, Lin Fei and Shen Lianxin were able to survive and reach Fairy Mist Island.

As for other Foundation Establishment True Persons and Martial Saints, venturing into the open sea would truly be a gamble with their lives. The pirates, too, often ended up in the bellies of sea beasts. But they were desperadoes. They could pay any price. Therefore, Fairy Mist Island was helpless against these pirates. They could only do their best to defend themselves.

Having understood the ins and outs of the situation, Lin Fei then quietly waited in the Shangguan family. Soon, the other noble families also arrived. Upon seeing Lin Fei, they all paid their respects. Lin Fei was no longer an ordinary Martial Saint. He was an outer sect elder of the Ancient Origin Sect. His status was revered.

"Greetings to Elder Lin."

"All right, you can leave the people here," Lin Fei responded indifferently.

Soon, the eight great families left behind ten family disciples. There were seven males and three females in total. They were all in their teens the right time to build their foundation. Moreover, all of them had strong martial arts talents. Once they were sent to the Ancient Origin Sect, they would likely make rapid progress and quickly reach the acquired level. They might even have a chance to reach the innate level! From the outer sect to the innate level, they could become inner disciples. Only then could they be truly carefree. Otherwise, as outer disciples, they could be expelled from the Ancient Origin Sect at any time.

"Elder Lin, please take good care of them," Shangguan Feiyun once again bowed in salute.

"The rules of the Ancient Origin Sect are clearer to you than to me," Lin Fei said calmly. "Whether they can stand out or not is up to them!"

The competition in the outer sect of the Ancient Origin Sect was extremely fierce. Lin Fei estimated that it would be good if half of these ten individuals could stay in the Ancient Origin Sect. If a third of them could advance to become inner disciples, that would be considered a great success. As an elder of the outer sect, his ability to help was quite limited.

"We are well aware of that. Thank you in advance, Elder Lin!"

The people from the eight great families also showed great respect for Lin Fei. Although their relationship with Lin Fei was essentially a transaction and it was now over, their relationship still was unusual. After all, Lin Fei was an elder of the outer sect of the Ancient Origin Sect. If he really wanted to help, he could. Now, it was not Lin Fei who needed the eight great families, but the eight great families that needed Lin Fei.

The people from the eight great families took their leave, and the ten disciples were left behind. Lin Fei did not immediately take the ten disciples back to the Ancient Origin Sect. Instead, he said to Shangguan Feiyun, "This trip down the mountain is not only for taking the disciples from your eight great families to the Ancient Origin Sect. I also need to kill sea beasts to aid my cultivation. So, I need to go to the open sea. Please let these ten disciples stay at Shangguan's house. After I come back, I'll take them to the Ancient Origin Sect."

Hearing that Lin Fei was going to the open sea, Shangguan Feiyun's face changed slightly. He said softly, "Elder Lin, it's not safe to go to the open sea at this time. There have been pirate invasions on Fairy Mist Island recently. And those pirates are drifting in the open sea. If you encounter them, wouldn't it be dangerous?"

Lin Fei's face remained calm as he said, "The open sea is vast, and the pirates are just a drop in the ocean. It's not that easy to encounter them. Besides, even if I do encounter them, I have my ways of escaping. If I can't even deal with pirates, how could I have crossed the sea?"

Although Lin Fei seemed a bit overconfident, when Shangguan Feiyun thought about it, Lin Fei was no ordinary Martial Saint. He was an enquirer who had comprehended the reverse side. He had drifted in the open sea for several months in the past. What kind of danger hadn't he faced? Lin Fei surely had some reliance.

"Regardless, Elder Lin, it's better to be cautious. If you encounter pirates, try to return to Fairy Mist Island. No matter how rampant the pirates are, they wouldn't dare to attack Fairy Mist Island," Shangguan Feiyun advised.

Lin Fei nodded. Then, he took a step forward, turned into a streak of light, and flew out of Fairy Mist Island, heading towards the vast sea.

217. Encountering Old Acquaintances at Sea

The sea was vast, with waves rolling. Smelling the saltiness in the air, Lin Fei felt a sense of "familiarity." He had been drifting on the sea for several months. Even though his will was strong, he couldn't help but feel a little lost. Now, having finally found the Ancient Continent and his martial path forward, he once again came to the sea. However, this time, Lin Fei came to the sea for cultivation.

Fairy Mist Island divided the sea into the near sea and the open sea. The near sea was the sea area near Fairy Mist Island. This was a relatively safe area, with not many powerful sea beasts. After all, sometimes some Foundation Establishment True Persons would patrol the near sea. But once one left the near sea and reaches the open sea, there are many more sea beasts.

Lin Fei flew all the way and quickly arrived at the open sea. He didn't have to wait long before he sensed a sea beast.

"Saber momentum, suppress!"

Lin Fei unleashed his saber momentum. Immediately, it enveloped the sea beast. The transcendent saber momentum instantly suppressed the sea beast, rendering it unable to move.

"Shoo."

Next, Lin Fei flicked a finger. A thread of saber essence flew out, turning into a heavenly saber, directly beheaded the sea beast. For a moment, blood filled the air.

"Sky Reaching Tower, collect!"

For Lin Fei, killing a Foundation Establishment level sea beast was too easy. Saber momentum plus saber essence, it couldn't be easier.

"Hmm? There's another sea beast?"

Under Lin Fei's saber momentum, he discovered another sea beast. This sea beast seemed slightly stronger than the one Lin Fei had just killed.

Suddenly, Lin Fei thought of the three Saint-level saber techniques he had just practiced. These saber techniques, Lin Fei wanted to practice these all the way to transcendence, and perfection, giving birth to saber intent, and finally evolving into saber momentum.

Saber techniques were all for battle, only battle could improve saber techniques. So, Lin Fei had an idea. He flicked his finger.

"Shoo."

A thread of saber essence flew out. This thread of saber essence actually turned into a rainbow light. Its speed was too fast. It was actually the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique that Lin Fei had recently mastered.

"Plurt."

The next moment, the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique instantly severed the head of the sea beast. The sea beast didn't even have a chance to resist.

"So strong! The Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique, even in the mastery realm, is so mysterious and powerful. And when combined with my saber essence, it makes the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique invincible."

Lin Fei felt a chill in his heart. A Saint-level saber technique was indeed extraordinary. Of course, there was also the support of his transcendence saber momentum. Externally, saber momentum could suppress enemies. Internally, it could support saber techniques.

The role of saber momentum for saber practitioners was just too great. Martial Saints with and without saber momentum were on completely different levels.

"Your Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique has slain a Foundation Establishment sea beast, and in its excitement, it has fallen into enlightenment."

"Enlightenment?"

Lin Fei was somewhat surprised. He hadn't expected that merely using the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique to slay a sea beast would trigger enlightenment of the technique. It seemed that the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique had a pretty good aptitude for understanding.

Lin Fei had long known that the martial arts he possessed each had different characters. Even their aptitude for comprehension was different. The Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique slayed a Foundation Establishment sea beast and fell into enlightenment. But other saber techniques might not necessarily do the same.

Every saber technique had its own opportunities. They couldn't all be treated the same way. However, the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique didn't stay enlightened for long.

"Your Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique's enlightenment is over. By virtue of its extraordinary understanding, it has comprehended the realm of transforming into a rainbow, and the progress of cultivation has increased by 100%."

"Your Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique has broken through to the transcendence realm!"

In Lin Fei's mind, the system's voice sounded again. The Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique had indeed broken through. It had directly broken through from mastery to transcendence!

Lin Fei tasted the sweetness of success. He then caught a few more sea beasts. Unfortunately, aside from the Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique's enlightenment and breakthrough to transcendence, the other two saber techniques, Holy Spirit Saber Technique and Flame Burning Heaven Saber, did not fall into enlightenment. They merely made some progress in cultivation, but they didn't break through to transcendence. And after killing the sea beasts multiple times, the improvement to his saber techniques was limited.

Seeing that his saber techniques were no longer improving, Lin Fei stopped killing sea beasts.

"Let's first try out the flesh and blood of these sea beasts."

Lin Fei didn't return to Fairy Mist Island. He just wanted to give it a try. It was troublesome to go back and forth. So, with a flash, he directly entered the Sky Reaching Tower.

Inside the Sky Reaching Tower, several sea beasts were piled up. A large amount of fresh blood permeated the air. Lin Fei took a deep breath.

"Let's begin."

With that, Lin Fei began to consume the flesh and blood of the exotic beasts. After his body had undergone a rebirth, consuming some exotic beast's flesh and blood was absolutely normal. Large amounts of exotic beast flesh and blood were consumed by Lin Fei.

At the same time, the Blood Essence Nine Transformations within Lin Fei's body also started operating on their own. Clearly, it was stimulated by a large amount of exotic beast flesh and blood. Therefore, the cultivation speed of the Blood Essence Nine Transformations also started to rapidly increase.

50%, 60%, 70%, 80%, 90%......

As Lin Fei consumed a large amount of exotic beast flesh and blood, the transformation, quickly converted into blood essence in his body. Lin Fei's physical body, at a speed visible to the naked eye, was rapidly improving. And Blood Essence Nine Transformations was also undergoing a momentous transformation.

"Boom."

The blood essence in Lin Fei's body directly doubled. Equivalent to twice the original amount. Moreover, Blood Essence Nine Transformations had broken through from the first transformation to the second at this moment.

"As expected, consuming the flesh and blood of exotic beasts is effective. Can I keep consuming the flesh and blood of exotic beasts until Blood Essence Nine Transformations forms the Energy Flower?"

A glint of sharpness flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. So, he continued to consume the flesh and blood of the exotic beasts. However, as soon as he consumed more, Lin Fei immediately felt a change.

Slow!

The speed of Blood Essence Nine Transformations transforming blood essence had slowed down. Or rather, it wasn't that the efficiency had become slower. But rather, Lin Fei needed more of them. So, it appeared to be slowing down in converting blood essence. However, blood essence was still increasing. That was enough. So, Lin Fei continued to consume the flesh and blood of sea beasts and convert blood essence within the Sky Reaching Tower.

At this moment, on the sea surface, a rainbow light was frantically fleeing towards Fairy Mist Island. However, behind him, there were a full three rainbow lights. Their speed was even faster.

In the rainbow light, Zhao Mingyu's face was flushed red. The aura on his body had become extremely chaotic. Even his Magic Body had been severely injured.

Zhao Mingyu had actually reached the Foundation Establishment stage! He relied on two Foundation Establishment pills and then exhausted all he had to buy another Foundation Establishment pill. Therefore, he had gathered a total of three Foundation Establishment pills.

After taking three Foundation Establishment pills, Zhao Mingyu successfully reached the Foundation Establishment stage and became a Foundation Establishment True Person!

According to the rules of the Zhao family, upon being promoted to Foundation Establishment True Person, one could obtain an island.

The Zhao family owned numerous islands. Each island had some resources. Zhao Mingyu was assigned to Liuli Island. He didn't expect to encounter pirates before he'd even stayed on Liuli Island for long. The pirates attacked Liuli Island. Even with Zhao Mingyu, a Foundation Establishment True Person, in charge, Liuli Island was still captured.

Zhao Mingyu fought as if his life depended on it. He self-detonated a magic treasure only then did he manage to escape narrowly. However, in the vast sea, there were three Foundation Establishment True Persons from the pirates chasing after him.

"Damn it, I've just established my foundation and I have hundreds of years of life left, how can I die? Moreover, these pirates must have a big conspiracy. I must go back and tell my family, tell everyone on Fairy Mist Island. I can't die, I absolutely can't die here..."

Zhao Mingyu gritted his teeth. He once again forcefully maintained his stance. He performed a spell. Immediately, his injuries worsened once again.

"You can't escape. Why not join us, with your aptitude, it's hard for you to reach the mid-stage of the Foundation Establishment in your lifetime. But if you join us, you might even reach the mid-stage of the Foundation Establishment or even the later stage! Isn't it much better than staying in the small Fairy Mist Island?"

Three Foundation Establishment True Persons from the pirates tried to confuse Zhao Mingyu's mind. But in reality, how could they possibly really accept Zhao Mingyu? If Zhao Mingyu really stopped, they would immediately destroy him.

"Black Blood Needle, go!"

One of the pirates, a flash of black light in his hand, disappeared in a flash. Inaudibly, it pierced through Zhao Mingyu's protective spell in an instant. And, it pierced through Zhao Mingyu's body.

"Crack."

Cracks had appeared on Zhao Mingyu's body. Clearly, it was not far from collapsing.

"Pfft."

Zhao Mingyu even spat out a mouthful of blood. The whole person fell towards the sea below.

"Splash."

Zhao Mingyu fell into the sea.

"My life is over."

Zhao Mingyu knew that he had no hope. There was no doubt he would die!

However, when he fell into the sea, from the corner of his eye, he vaguely saw a hint of treasure light. And this strand of treasure light was very familiar. He took a closer look. On the sea surface, there was actually a tower floating. This tower, Zhao Mingyu was too familiar with it. It was because of this tower Zhao Mingyu changed his fate and became a Foundation Establishment True Person.

"Is... is it Senior? It must be Senior Lin! I heard that Senior Lin has become an Outer Sect Elder of the Ancient Origin Sect. He's back? Senior, save me, I am Zhao Mingyu, please save me!"

Zhao Mingyu staked his last bit of spiritual power and quickly approached the tower. The three Foundation Establishment True Persons from the pirates also saw that tower.

"Is there someone else?"

"That's a tower, is it a magic treasure?"

"This Zhao Mingyu is shouting for help, could it be that there is a powerful Foundation Establishment True Person nearby?"

"Hmph, maybe Zhao Mingyu doesn't know this tower at all. He just wants to drag others down."

"Anyway, first kill Zhao Mingyu, then see what this tower is all about."

The three Foundation Establishers looked at each other. They made a decision immediately.

"Shoo."

Immediately, the Black Blood Needle flew out again. This needle against the now desperate, severely injured Zhao Mingyu. It would surely kill with one blow!

"Senior, save me..."

Zhao Mingyu's eyes were wide open. He saw the Black Blood Needle, but he was powerless to resist now. He could only shout desperately towards the tower. However, the tower seemed to have no response and the Black Blood Needle was already close at hand.

"Suppress!"

Suddenly, a cold voice sounded. Immediately afterward, that Black Blood Needle stopped two inches away from Zhao Mingyu. The Black Blood Needle was shaking violently. However, it had been suppressed. It was a luxury to even move a little.

218. Killing a Foundation Establishment is as easy as killing a chicken

"What?"

The Foundation Establishment cultivator who controlled the Black Blood Needle had an inexplicably horrified look on his face. He was frantically urging his spiritual power, displaying his seal. However, it was useless. His Black Blood Needle seemed to be firmly suppressed. It couldn't move at all.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei stepped out of the Sky Reaching Tower.

"Senior, it really is you, please save me..."

Seeing Lin Fei, Zhao Mingyu was overjoyed. This was simply a narrow escape.

"Zhao Mingyu..."

Of course, Lin Fei recognized Zhao Mingyu. Just didn't expect that Zhao Mingyu had already established his foundation. As for the three Foundation Establishments that were pursuing Zhao Mingyu, Lin Fei had also heard Zhao Mingyu's words.

Pirates! These three Foundation Establishment True Persons were all pirates.

Lin Fei had a thought. The Sky Reaching Tower instantly flew into his body. At the same time, he moved. With one step, he arrived in front of Zhao Mingyu. In front of Zhao Mingyu, the Black Blood Needle was still trembling. However, it was suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum, unable to move.

Lin Fei stretched out his fair hand and directly reached for the Black Blood Needle.

"Hmm? He's courting death! Flesh and blood body dare to touch my Black Blood Needle. Even if you're a Martial Saint, the Black Blood Needle can instantly pierce through your palm covered with True Essence."

Seeing Lin Fei actually trying to grab the Black Blood Needle directly. The owner of the Black Blood Needle couldn't help but sneer in his heart. They had already seen Lin Fei was a Martial Saint.

After all, the difference between a Martial Saint and a Foundation Establishment True Person was too great. The vitality of a Martial Saint was incredibly powerful, like a blazing sun. It was too conspicuous.

His Black Blood Needle specialized in breaking flesh and blood. There had been several Martial Saints died from the Black Blood Needle before. However, when Lin Fei's hand grabbed the Black Blood Needle, he gave it a hard pinch.

"Crack."

The Black Blood Needle broke! The spiritual light flickered, and then completely disappeared. Lin Fei casually threw the Black Blood Needle into the sea.

"The magical treasure is not bad, but it's too weak."

Lin Fei said in a calm tone. He really didn't use much strength just now. This time, Lin Fei just wanted to test how strong his physical body was now. After all, he had consumed so many sea beasts this time. The blood essence accumulated in Lin Fei's body was already unimaginably large. Although it was still far from condensing the Energy Flower, compared to his previous body, it was at least ten times stronger!

So, with a casual pinch of his physical body, Lin Fei found that the magic treasure was even more fragile than he had imagined, and it broke directly.

Now Lin Fei understood, why back then, Zhao Canglong, facing the elder who had condensed an Energy Flower, exploded with one punch.

Perhaps, the elder who had condensed an Energy Flower back then didn't even use ten percent of his strength.

Once Martial Saints started cultivating their physical body and reached the point of condensing an Energy Flower, that would be indestructible and incredibly powerful. Even the magic treasure of a Foundation Establishment True Person would be easily crushed.

"Not good, his physical body is too powerful, and he's probably not far from condensing the Energy Flower."

"We're no match for a Martial Saint like him."

"Retreat quickly!"

Seeing this scene, the three Foundation Establishments were greatly shocked, knowing that the Martial Saint in front of them was probably not easy to provoke!

Those who could crush magic treasures barehanded, even if they hadn't condensed an Energy Flower, were not far off. This was a top-tier Martial Saint!

Such a Martial Saint is very terrifying. Impervious to swords and spears, immune to fire and water, indestructible. Even magic treasures can be easily crushed.

They were just at the early stage of the Foundation Establishment, and they didn't have powerful magic treasures in their hands. Facing such a top-tier Martial Saint, how could they take advantage? Moreover, they were pirates!

Therefore, without any hesitation, the three Foundation Establishment cultivators made a decision and ran away. Even the owner of the Black Blood Needle, at this moment, was forcibly enduring the pain of backlash and quickly fleeing.

"Hum?"

But just as they wanted to leave, a vast saber momentum enveloped them, instantly trapping them inside.

"Suppress!"

Lin Fei uttered a single word.

"Boom."

The saber momentum was suppressed with all its might. The three Foundation Establishments were like they were stuck in the mud. They were finding it difficult to move. Even the circulation of spiritual power in their bodies became somewhat difficult.

"Saber momentum? How can there be such a terrifying saber momentum, who are you?"

The faces of the three Foundation Establishment cultivators changed dramatically. Even if Lin Fei was about to condense an Energy Flower, they could still escape. But with a Martial Saint with saber momentum, their chances of escape were slim to none. There was only one way. That was to kill the opponent!

"Spare no effort, kill him!"

The three Foundation Establishment True Persons were very decisive. Knowing that Lin Fei had a saber momentum, they could not escape. Therefore, they made a prompt decision. Their internal spiritual power surged. They used their magic treasures and spells again, bombarding Lin Fei.

Lin Fei's saber momentum was indeed strong. It could suppress some of the power of a Foundation Establishment True Person. But it wasn't to the point of completely suppressing the other party, making them immobile.

The three Foundation Establishments were very decisive when they started, they exerted their magic bodies. In the void, a large amount of Spiritual Qi was gathered. The entire saber momentum was filled with storms, flames, etc. These were all spells. There were even magic treasures!

The Black Blood Needle could be suppressed by the saber momentum, but that was because the Black Blood Needle was not very powerful. For other magic treasures, Lin Fei's saber momentum might not be able to suppress them.

Seeing the three's fierce counterattack, Zhao Mingyu couldn't help but tremble in his heart. However, Lin Fei was as calm as ever. In his view, this was a true Foundation Establishment True Person!

The Foundation Establishments he had killed before were too weak. Whether in will or strength, both were weak. As for the sea beasts, although they were also at the Foundation Establishment level, they had no magic treasures, only some innate abilities. Compared to Foundation Establishment, they were somewhat inferior. And these three Foundation Establishment True Persons were all pirates. Being able to fall into piracy, apart from anything else, their combat experience was definitely very rich.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei reached out his hand. There wasn't much movement. He simply flicked his finger. Three strands of saber essence flew out instantly, condensing into three large sabers.

"Boom."

As soon as these three large sabers appeared, they immediately erupted with an earth-shattering momentum. One of the large sabers swung out. It was like a brilliant sun. Moreover, it seemed to burn the void. This was Flame Burning Heaven Saber. One saber swung out, burned the sky, and boiled the sea!

There was also a large saber turned into a rainbow light. This was the Rainbow Transformation Saber. Its speed was as fast as a startled swan.

There was another saber, holy, grand, magnificent. One saber swung out like a god coming down from the heavens, possessing infinite power. This was the Holy Spirit Saber Technique.

Three great saber techniques were all top-tier saber techniques at the Martial Saint level.

"You..."

They felt Lin Fei was so bold that he didn't make a move and he only used a strand of true essence. Of course, they didn't know about saber essence. They just took saber essence as the true essence of a Martial Saint.

Even if Lin Fei had saber momentum, the three Foundation Establishment True Persons felt insulted. Just a strand of true essence, and he wanted to defeat them? It was a fantasy. They were also dignified Foundation Establishment True Persons! And they were even notorious pirates!

"Puff."

However, the Rainbow Transformation Saber vanished in a flash. Then, a Foundation Establishment True Person widened his eyes as if he couldn't believe it. From his head, a line of blood emerged. With a "plop", the body of a Foundation Establishment True Person fell into the sea. He was dead! The Rainbow Transformation Saber was like a rainbow. Against the enemy, it always took only one slash!

"Boom."

Next was the Holy Spirit Saber Technique. Upright and open-minded, with one slash, the other party's magic treasure was directly shattered.

"Crack."

The magic treasure shattered. The saber essence instantly turned his law body into minced meat. The second Foundation Establishment was also dead. Only the last Foundation Establishment True Person was left. His soul was in great fear. How would he dare to make a move?

The Flame Burning Heaven Saber seemed to carry a sky full of flames. One slash swung out. The flames were rampant, and instantly engulfed the last Foundation Establishment True Person. In an instant, he was burned to ashes. He was dead!

Three Foundation Establishment True Persons had been chasing Zhao Mingyu before. Now, Lin Fei killed them all with a flick of his finger and a strand of saber essence.

Moreover, in the entire process, those three Foundation Establishment True Persons had no power to fight back.

"Killing Foundation Establishment is like killing a chicken..."

This sentence emerged in Zhao Mingyu's mind. At this moment, wasn't Lin Fei's method of killing the Foundation Establishment like killing a chicken?

Zhao Mingyu thought that he had succeeded in Foundation Establishment and he was a dignified Foundation Establishment True Person, feeling that he might not be far behind Lin Fei.

But what was the result? The further he went and the higher he stood, the more terrifying he found Lin Fei was. That was far beyond his imagination.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei turned around, standing with his hands behind his back, looking calmly at Zhao Mingyu. But it made Zhao Mingyu feel his scalp tingle. His whole body felt like it had fallen into an ice cellar, the pressure was immense.

"Zhao Mingyu, what exactly happened?"

After a while, Lin Fei slowly asked.

219. Lin Fei's Fury

The scrutiny in Lin Fei's gaze had placed a significant amount of stress on Zhao Mingyu just moments prior.

Hearing Lin Fei's inquiry now, Zhao Mingyu felt slightly relieved and promptly responded, "Senior, thanks to your blessings, I gathered three Foundation Establishment Pills, successfully established my foundation, and was assigned by my family to oversee the Liuli Island. Unexpectedly, pirates invaded and shattered the protective array of Liuli Island. The entire Liuli Island was pillaged.

I escaped in the ensuing chaos, only to be pursued relentlessly by these pirates. Fortunately, I encountered you, senior. Otherwise, I fear I would not have survived."

Even now, Zhao Mingyu felt a chill of fear at the memory.

"A horde of pirates, pillaging as their primary objective. Why did they specifically target you? Moreover, they dispatched three Foundation Establishment level experts to pursue you relentlessly. This does not match the usual behavior of pirates," Lin Fei calmly analyzed, his gaze fixed on Zhao Mingyu.

He knew that there was more to Zhao Mingyu's story than he had disclosed.

As expected, Zhao Mingyu gritted his teeth and revealed, "Senior, you are no outsider. When I was escaping from Liuli Island, I overheard some information from the pirates. It turned out that the pirates' purpose was not merely to pillage. They intended to completely conquer Fairy Mist Island. Our Fairy Mist Island has no major power to intervene. This has inadvertently become the pirates' ideal target. Senior, I must rush to convey this information back to Fairy Mist Island. Once there, the various powers on Fairy Mist Island will be prepared for the upcoming threat."

Lin Fei nodded in understanding. So that was the case. Those pirates were quite audacious indeed. However, upon closer consideration, it seemed plausible.

Fairy Mist Island had no major powers, only minor families of Qi cultivators and small organizations. If it were to fall, it would merely fade into obscurity. Once the pirates took control of this place, they might abandon their pirate status.

After all, given a choice, who would willingly choose the pirate life?

However, Zhao Mingyu's escape and his potential to relay this information back to Fairy Mist Island would allow the various powers there to prepare in advance.

"Alright, return and deliver your message," Lin Fei stated, showing no intention of getting involved.

Having existed for such a long time, Fairy Mist Island and its families of Qi cultivators surely had some means to resist. If they were truly helpless, the pirates would have conquered them long ago. They wouldn't probe Fairy Mist Island's strengths and weaknesses in such a manner.

The intermittent harassment from pirates who dared not launch a direct attack on Fairy Mist Island was actually an attempt to discern the true strength of Fairy Mist Island. This suggested that the pirates were somewhat wary of Fairy Mist Island.

Zhao Mingyu left. He needed to hurry back to Fairy Mist Island with the information. Lin Fei didn't give the matter much thought. Once the message reached Fairy Mist Island, the numerous Foundation Establishment True Persons there would naturally devise a solution.

"System," Lin Fei summoned his system panel, checking his martial arts progress.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique: Early Stage (Progress: 6%)

Blood Essence Nine Transformations: Seventh Transformation (Progress: 12%)

Holy Spirit Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress: 58%)

Flame Burning Heaven Saber: Mastery (Progress: 65%)

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique: Transcendence (Progress: 10%)

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress: 0%)

Lin Fei had spent approximately three days at sea. In this triad of days, his practice of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique progressed steadily at a rate of 1% per day. By now, he had escalated from 3% to a whopping 6%. Each of his three martial arts saber techniques, each hailing from the level of a Martial Saint, had also made appreciable advancements. Naturally, the centerpiece of his focus was the Blood Essence Nine Transformations.

Over these three days, Lin Fei consumed the flesh and blood of sea beasts without ceasing. Hence, each passing moment saw an increase in the essence of blood circulating within him. At present, Lin Fei's Blood Essence Nine Transformations had escalated from the first transformation to the astounding seventh transformation.

Seven transformations implied a sixty-four-fold increase in Lin Fei's blood essence - a truly terrifying magnitude. In such circumstances, he could even attempt to condense an Energy Flower.

However, Lin Fei was not one to rush. The condensation of an Energy Flower was not a task to be taken lightly. A failed attempt would deplete his blood essence, leading to its decay and even a slight erosion of his foundation. A long period of recovery would be needed.

Thus, without absolute certainty, Lin Fei would not risk condensing an Energy Flower. The Blood Essence Nine Transformations had made it clear: once the nine transformations were achieved, his blood essence could multiply to a horrifying two hundred and fifty-six fold! At that time, with the blood essence multiplied two hundred and fifty-six times, the condensation of an Energy Flower would be a sure success.

This was a significant reason why Lin Fei chose the path of Blood Essence Nine Transformations. Mastering it to the highest realm would allow for the condensation of the Energy Flower.

However, Lin Fei found that his current consumption of ordinary sea beast flesh and blood no longer provided any substantial benefits.

The progress of his Blood Essence Nine Transformations had noticeably slowed. He had a fair idea as to why. After all, he had already achieved seven transformations, and the total volume of blood essence in his body had grown exceptionally large. How much blood essence could ordinary sea beasts provide?

If he were to keep slaughtering one beast after another, Lin Fei feared that it would take three to five years of relentless killing to advance to the eighth transformation.

And then, perhaps a decade or even several decades of slaughtering and consuming the flesh and blood of sea beasts daily might finally bring him to the Blood Essence Nine Transformations.

Perhaps for other Martial Saints, a mere decade or several decades to condense an Energy Flower would be a cause for jubilation and unparalleled exhilaration.

But for Lin Fei, it was far too lengthy. With his martial arts pursuits so arduous, he must naturally provide them with the best resources, not resort to inefficient, cumbersome methods.

Moreover, the ocean held its share of dangers.

Constant slaughter by Lin Fei and his sustained presence in the outer seas could potentially provoke a mighty sea beast, one comparable to a Martial Sovereign or Golden Elixir, thereby putting him in danger.

Even if he survived smoothly in the outer seas for ten years, a single day of danger could nullify all his decade-long efforts.

"Better to return to the Ancient Origin Sect. If I can obtain more potent exotic beast flesh and blood..."

Lin Fei had made up his mind.

As an external elder of the Ancient Origin Sect, and a Martial Saint among the major factions, he ought to fully utilize this relationship, rather than behaving like an independent martial artist, killing sea beasts relentlessly.

Now that his Blood Essence Nine Transformations had reached seven transformations, he was quite close to his goal.

Thus, Lin Fei set a course for Fairy Mist Island.

Soon, he arrived back at Fairy Mist Island and headed straight to the Shangguan household.

At the moment, Shangguan Feiyun seemed quite agitated.

On seeing Lin Fei, his face brightened.

Shangguan Feiyun hurried forward, "Elder, you're finally back. Fairy Mist Island is in grave danger. News has emerged that a group of sea pirates plans to capture Fairy Mist Island. The whole island is in a state of anxiety."

However, Lin Fei was not surprised. Instead, he calmly replied, "I am aware. Therefore, I have returned to bring people back to the Ancient Origin Sect."

"You're leaving?" Shangguan Feiyun's countenance changed slightly.

"Do you eight great families think I'll stay on Fairy Mist Island to guard you all? What transpires between us is merely a transaction. The ten external disciple quotas I promised will be delivered. But beyond that, it has nothing to do with me."

Having said this, Lin Fei ignored the complex expression on Shangguan Feiyun's face, and with a wave of his hand, he lifted the ten geniuses from the eight great families with his saber essence.

"Let's go!"

With his companions, Lin Fei rose into the air and disappeared into the horizon in the blink of an eye.

Shangguan Feiyun wore a complex expression, muttering softly, "Yes, it's just a transaction between us...But after all, Elder Lin has some ties of kindness with our eight great families. If anything happens in the future, we can still seek Elder Lin's help. As for the affairs of Fairy Mist Island, let those of the Foundation Establishment True Person and Qi cultivator families worry about it. Our eight martial art families haven't had a Martial Saint for too long, we've been in decline..."

Lin Fei paid no heed to the thoughts of the eight great families.

He returned to the Ancient Origin Sect with the ten disciples of the eight great families and immediately exercised his privilege as an outer sect elder, admitting five of them as outer disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect. However, the remaining five required the recommendation of Shen Lianxin. Thus, Lin Fei made his way to Shen Lianxin's cave abode.

"Hmm?"

As he stepped into Shen Lianxin's abode, Lin Fei's eyes narrowed as he fixated his gaze upon Shen Lianxin.

"Brother Shen, you're injured again! Tell me, who inflicted this upon you? And with such a ruthless hand at that. With injuries like these, you'll need at least a year to recuperate!"

Upon seeing Shen Lianxin's condition, a glint of cold fury flashed across Lin Fei's eyes. Such injuries were clearly inflicted deliberately!

220. A Challenge Letter, Storm Brewing in Ancient Origin Sect

"True disciple, Ao Yunxiao!"

Shen Lianxin finally uttered a name.

"Ao Yunxiao?"

Lin Fei frowned. He had not heard of this name before.

"Brother Shen, have you offended him?" Lin Fei asked.

"No, in fact, I didn't even know him before."

"So why did he injure you?"

Shen Lianxin looked up at Lin Fei, speaking word by word: "For momentum! Ao Yunxiao ranks well among the true disciples, both in physical strength and true essence." He's not far from condensing his Energy Flower or Qi Flower. But he hasn't comprehended any momentum. So, he practiced a special martial art. As long as he can defeat opponents of the same level one by one, he can successfully comprehend momentum!

Among the true disciples, except for those who have condensed their Energy Flower or Qi Flower, he has challenged almost all of them. Without exception, he has won. Even a true disciple who has understood the momentum of transcendence martial arts fell under his fist.

We might not be true disciples, but we are 'Dao Seekers', well-known. Especially Brother Lin, with your supreme saber momentum, suppressing hundreds of Martial Saints. Although not a true disciple, your reputation and popularity even overshadow many true disciples. Ao Yunxiao came to me, seeking a duel. And as you know, the result. I am not afraid of any challenge. I fought him and lost."

Lin Fei understood. Shen Lianxin was injured by Ao Yunxiao.

"But, after losing the last time, why did he injure you again?" Lin Fei asked.

Ao Yunxiao just wanted to challenge, to build up momentum. He did not have any deep hatred for Shen Lianxin. It wouldn't warrant a second attack.

Shen Lianxin spoke with a complex expression: "Two days ago, Ao Yunxiao was going to find you. But he couldn't find you, so he came to me to inquire about your whereabouts. I naturally ignored him. He was not happy with my response, and he injured me again."

Shen Lianxin was succinct, explaining the reason. Lin Fei understood. Shen Lianxin was injured for the second time on his behalf. Ao Yunxiao's target was Lin Fei. But Lin Fei had just happened to go down the mountain, back to Fairy Mist Island. So, in the absence of Lin Fei, Ao Yunxiao found Shen Lianxin.

There was some verbal conflict between them. A fight was inevitable. That's why Shen Lianxin got injured this time. And the injuries were very serious. Because this time, Ao Yunxiao was full of anger. He vented all his anger on Shen Lianxin. If it weren't for the Ancient Origin Sect's prohibition against disciple killing, Ao Yunxiao might have wanted to kill Shen Lianxin.

"Ao Yunxiao..."

Lin Fei's gaze was growing colder and colder. In the Ancient Origin Sect, he didn't really have any friends. Lin Fei only had one real friend, Shen Lianxin!

Shen Lianxin was usually quiet and reticent. Even when they were drifting on the sea for months, they hardly spoke. But as friends, they understood each other. Lin Fei was very clear about this. If there was a need, Shen Lianxin would help him at all costs. Even if it meant giving up his life! He and Shen Lianxin were truly friends who had shared life and death together!

However, Lin Fei's anger did not show. He simply said calmly, "Brother Shen, I brought back ten disciples from the eight major families from Fairy Mist Island. I have recommended five disciples. And another five disciples need your recommendation."

Shen Lianxin nodded.

"Brother Shen, rest well. I'll come to see you in a few days."

Lin Fei didn't say much more. He turned around and prepared to leave. As Lin Fei reached the entrance of the cave, Shen Lianxin spoke: "Brother Lin, hit him hard!"

Lin Fei paused slightly but didn't look back. A smile appeared at the corner of his mouth.

"The one who knows me is Brother Shen!"

With that, Lin Fei strode away. Even though he didn't say anything, Shen Lianxin knew Lin Fei would definitely go to find Ao Yunxiao!

Shen Lianxin might be quiet and reticent, but he was not ignorant. On the contrary, Shen Lianxin understood everything. Between him and Lin Fei, there was no need to say much. A single look was all it took to understand!

Lin Fei left Shen Lianxin's cave dwelling. He did not directly go to find Ao Yunxiao. Didn't Ao Yunxiao want to accumulate momentum? Wanting to defeat Martial Saints at the same level and then comprehend the momentum of martial arts?

Lin Fei did not want to let Ao Yunxiao get his wish. He wanted to publicly fight Ao Yunxiao, and completely defeat Ao Yunxiao. Let all the momentum that Ao Yunxiao had accumulated before dissipate!

So, Lin Fei didn't need to find Ao Yunxiao. A challenge letter would be enough!

...

The mountain peak of the true disciples. This area was off-limits to inner disciples. Only some elders at the Martial Saint level and true disciples could enter this area. This was the core of the entire Ancient Origin Sect! After all, each true disciple was a hope for the future of the Ancient Origin Sect. There were even many seeds of Martial Sovereign.

Of course, they were only seeds. True disciples had come and gone in waves. But who had become a Martial Sovereign? Few and far between! Scarce! So-called seeds of Martial Sovereign, maybe, would always remain seeds, never growing into towering trees!

Inside Ao Yunxiao's cave dwelling, several true disciples gathered. Although Ao Yunxiao was not a seed of Martial Sovereign, even the seeds of Martial Sovereign feared Ao Yunxiao. Because, apart from not having comprehended momentum, his physical body and true essence were about to condense into Energy Flower and Qi Flower. By then, with both flowers blooming, even if he hadn't comprehended momentum, Ao Yunxiao would still be a top-tier Martial Saint!

Such a person, no matter how much emphasis was placed on him was not excessive. Even if he didn't become a Martial Sovereign, he would dominate one side in the future. Therefore, around Ao Yunxiao, there would be some true disciples who took the initiative to befriend him.

"Brother Ao, the momentum you've accumulated should be almost enough, right? Could it be that you still haven't comprehended momentum? Almost all the true disciples at the same level as Brother Ao have been defeated by you. Only those brothers who have condensed the Energy Flower and Qi Flower have not been challenged. But for those who have condensed the Energy Flower and Qi Flower, the gap is too big, and the challenge is also useless."

Many true disciples hoped that Ao Yunxiao could comprehend momentum. Because, in that case, once Ao Yunxiao comprehends momentum, he might even have the chance to be listed as a seed of Martial Sovereign. By then, Ao Yunxiao's identity and status in the Ancient Origin Sect will be greatly different.

"I'm just one short! Defeat him and I can comprehend momentum!"

Ao Yunxiao had been waiting all along, waiting for that person to appear.

"Brother Ao, you're referring to the 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei, aren't you? I heard he comprehended the saber momentum, and he was in the limelight for a while in the beginner stage. But he seems to have gone down the mountain."

"Going down the mountain at this time is probably to avoid Brother Ao."

"Yes, Lin Fei definitely doesn't dare to fight with Brother Ao. After all, Brother Ao is famous and invincible among the true disciples. If he accepts the challenge, wouldn't it be a humiliation for himself?"

Everyone knew who Ao Yunxiao was referring to.

Dao Seeker Lin Fei!

Although he was not a true disciple but an outer elder, his status as a "Dao Seeker" made him a prominent figure in the Ancient Origin Sect. Ao Yunxiao wanted to accumulate momentum, and he definitely couldn't do it without Lin Fei.

"He will appear. I purposely injured Shen Lianxin to show him. As long as he is still a martial artist and has a bit of arrogance, he won't be able to resist! If he can't resist, I can defeat him. By then, my martial momentum will be achieved!"

Ao Yunxiao said faintly. His tone was filled with unwavering conviction.

"Report! Master, the outer elder, 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei has issued a challenge letter to the master, requesting the master to fight him on the Sect's stage in three days!"

"Whoosh."

Suddenly, a glint flashed in Ao Yunxiao's eyes. The many true disciples were also somewhat surprised. They didn't expect that Ao Yunxiao's prediction would come true. Lin Fei indeed couldn't resist, and even took the initiative to issue a challenge! However, this was exactly what Ao Yunxiao intended.

"I accept the challenge! Junior brothers, please return. I need to adjust my condition. In three days, I will defeat Lin Fei and fully comprehend the martial momentum! See the guests out!"

Ao Yunxiao waved his hand. Many true disciples also got up one after another and left the cave dwelling.

221. The Big Battle Begins

Three days later, the area under the Ancient Origin Sect's arena was already crowded with people. It was filled with disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect. The Ancient Origin Sect's arena, whether they were true disciples, inner disciples, or outer disciples, all could challenge on the stage.

Ordinary disciples could go to the stage to resolve their conflicts, but they cannot kill the opponent. Otherwise, whether intentional or unintentional, they will be heavily punished!

After all, martial artists are all impulsive. They could start a fight at the slightest disagreement. If life-and-death battles were allowed, many disciples probably would go to the stage and fight to the death. By then, the Ancient Origin Sect would also lose many talented disciples. This was undoubtedly an unnecessary loss. Fighting was okay. Resolving grievances was also okay. But they cannot kill the opponent. This was the bottom line of the Ancient Origin Sect.

At this moment, the area under the stage was crowded with people. This was because the people who challenged the stage today were extraordinary.

Ordinary disciples fight on the stage to resolve grudges. Actually, the disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect had grown accustomed to it. But this time it was different. One side was Ao Yunxiao, who was currently gaining prominence among the true disciples!

It is said that Ao Yunxiao, whether in physical strength or true essence was not far from condensing the Energy Flower and Qi Flower. Moreover, Ao Yunxiao was still accumulating momentum. He had already defeated many true disciples. Once he defeated his opponent today, then Ao Yunxiao's momentum could be established. There is a great possibility of comprehending the martial momentum!

By then, Ao Yunxiao could even become a seed of Martial Sovereign in the Ancient Origin Sect! Being able to witness the birth of a Martial Sovereign seed with their own eyes was something that many disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect cannot miss.

As for Ao Yunxiao's opponent, he was not a nobody. Dao Seeker Lin Fei! The title "Dao Seeker" alone was enough to make Lin Fei famous! After all, "Dao Seekers" were often associated with some legends. Even, there's a saying a seeker will surely become a Golden Core!

That is to describe those Foundation Establishment seekers. What if it's a Martial Saint Seeker? Some people speculate that was it possible that they must become Martial Sovereigns!?

Of course, this was just speculation. Or some private guesses. And when Lin Fei was a beginner, he suppressed hundreds of Martial Saints with his saber momentum with his own power! Such a feat was not inferior to Ao Yunxiao!

Therefore, the battle between Lin Fei and Ao Yunxiao could be described as a fierce battle between dragons and tigers. It immediately attracted the attention of all the disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Even some of the top Martial Saints who have condensed the Energy Flower and Qi Flower were all paying attention to this battle.

"Who knows who will win this battle?"

"Ao Yunxiao has been in the Ancient Origin Sect for many years, stepping up from an outer disciple to a true disciple. Such a true disciple, both in talent and intelligence, is among the best. I favor Ao Yunxiao more!"

"Ao Yunxiao is indeed strong and has even defeated many true disciples. However, Ao Yunxiao has not comprehended the Momentum, which is his biggest disadvantage. A Martial Saint with or without Momentum is completely different."

"Even without Momentum, Ao Yunxiao's true essence and physical body have reached the level of top Martial Saints. How long has Lin Fei been a beginner? He hasn't even studied his techniques for a few days. Even if he has Momentum, he is not invincible."

For a time, many people were discussing, analyzing the odds of victory between Lin Fei and Ao Yunxiao. There were some elders also among the crowd. They had a better understanding of Ao Yunxiao.

"Ao Yunxiao, this kid is extraordinary and determined. In this battle, he will most likely win. Once he wins, he will definitely comprehend the Martial Momentum!"

Most of the elders, actually, favored Ao Yunxiao. Only they knew how strong Ao Yunxiao's physical body and True Yuan were.

Although, true essence, the physical body, especially the physical body seemed that they could be stacked with resources and quickly become strong. But even if they could be stacked with resources, the entire Ancient Origin Sect, even the true disciples, how many of them could condense the Energy Flower?

Easy to say, hard to do.

Moreover, Ao Yunxiao also had powerful true essence. On the other hand, they just knew that Lin Fei had comprehended the saber momentum. Even, the saber momentum had reached transcendence.

However, those saber momentums could be very effective against martial artists of average will. For a martial artist like Ao Yunxiao with a firm will, even if there was a suppression effect, Ao Yunxiao could withstand it.

Having saber momentum, even saber momentum transcendence, was not invincible. However, it didn't matter who favors whom. The fight hadn't started yet. Only when the fight is over could they see who was the winner.

"Ao Yunxiao is here!"

Suddenly, someone looked up at the sky. A streak of light fell directly onto the stage.

Ao Yunxiao was in a white robe. He didn't bring any weapons, because he practiced boxing. No need for any weapons.

Ao Yunxiao landed on the stage. He glanced around. Then closed his eyes and stopped talking. Even if Lin Fei didn't come. He was not anxious at all. Very steady. Very calm. As if he had the victory in his hands! For a while, the noise below the stage gradually diminished.

"Is that 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei?"

Suddenly, another figure flew from the void.

"Dao Seeker" Lin Fei. The current elder of the Ancient Origin Sect's outer door, although there was much news about "Dao Seeker" Lin Fei in the Ancient Origin Sect, and even though Lin Fei's fame was not small, very few people had actually seen him.

Most people did not recognize him.

Only today when Lin Fei step by step, descended from the sky and landed on the stage, did the disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect see Lin Fei and recognized him.

"'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei is quite calm!"

"Worthy of someone who can suppress hundreds of Martial Saints with his own power."

"This kind of courage is not inferior to any true disciple!"

With the arrival of Lin Fei, there was complete silence around the stage, all eyes were on Lin Fei.

"Swish".

Ao Yunxiao opened his eyes.

"Lin Fei, you're finally here!"

Ao Yunxiao's voice was very calm. Although this battle was very important to him, he was still not impatient.

Lin Fei's gaze was also looking at Ao Yunxiao. He did not see any arrogance or domineering on Ao Yunxiao's face. What he saw was only confidence. Extreme confidence!

This kind of confidence, Lin Fei also has. Or to say, Ao Yunxiao and Lin Fei were actually the same kind of person.

"Ao Yunxiao, you intentionally injured Shen Lianxin for the second time, didn't you? How could a person as determined as you start a fight because of some words? You intentionally injured Shen Lianxin to show me. To provoke my anger, forcing me to take action! Once I take action, you defeat me, you can fully comprehend the Martial Momentum!

You are very confident. You are confident that you can win! I have to say, you succeeded. I indeed have a bit of anger. All your plans and every step were successful. But you can't defeat me. If this step fails, you will fall into the abyss! You should never have injured Shen Lianxin to force me to take action. With me here, you won't comprehend Momentum!"

Lin Fei spoke word by word. Although his tone was calm, every word was attacking the heart. He spoke out all of Ao Yunxiao's plans. Injuring Shen Lianxin was just a trick. Everything was just Ao Yunxiao's plan, in effect, he was forcing Lin Fei to take action.

This was very dangerous. Once defeated by Lin Fei, all the momentum that Ao Yunxiao had accumulated before would become nothing, even casting a shadow on Ao Yunxiao's mind, harder to comprehend the Martial Momentum again.

Ao Yunxiao's move was like betting all he had, betting everything, leaving no room. This was ruthless. Ruthless to others. Even more ruthless to himself!

Ao Yunxiao's plan was exposed by Lin Fei, but he didn't look surprised. Instead, he calmly said, "The path of martial arts is like rowing against the current, if you don't advance, you will retreat. Without the courage to go all out, how can one reach the peak of martial arts? Moreover, I will definitely win this battle! No one can shake my belief!"

Indeed, Ao Yunxiao's belief was very strong. A verbal confrontation. Both sides were equally matched. No one had the upper hand.

Lin Fei didn't speak anymore. There's no point. A martial artist still has to prove himself with his strength!

"You want to fight, I will give you the opportunity! However, whether you can seize this opportunity, it's not up to you. I'm the one who has the final say!"

"Boom".

On Lin Fei's body, a huge, fierce aura burst out instantly. A circle of white light instantly enveloped the entire stage.

Without any hesitation, Lin Fei released his saber momentum at the first moment!

222. I will break your momentum

No one who hadn't directly faced a saber momentum especially a transcendent saber momentum would ever know how terrifying it was. And Lin Fei's saber momentum was not just ordinary saber momentum.

Lin Fei's saber momentum was the integration of dozens of top-notch saber techniques. It was supported by the foundation of hundreds of saber techniques and eventually evolved into the current saber momentum.

Therefore, Lin Fei's saber momentum was different from other people's saber momentum. Some people's saber momentum was quite extreme. But Lin Fei? His saber momentum encompassed everything. It had countless saber technique foundations. It had the integration of countless saber momentum. There's no weak point at all. Very comprehensive.

But comprehensive doesn't mean mediocre. On the contrary, once saber momentum is comprehensive, it will be even more terrifying. Under the suppression of the saber momentum, a peer's strength will be suppressed to a very low level.

"What a terrifying saber momentum! Fame is not as good as seeing it in person."

"Although it was known long ago that 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei suppressed hundreds of Martial Saints with his saber momentum, I thought it was simply because those hundreds of Martial Saints were loose cultivators and were too weak. But now it seems that this is not the case. It's just that Lin Fei's saber momentum is too strong! Even if it is also saber momentum transcendence, it will be suppressed by Lin Fei's saber momentum. This level of saber momentum, once it reaches perfection in the future, will be the top martial momentum, no one can compare!"

Laymen watch the bustle of the crowd, while professionals perceive the knack and how. Those inner sect elders who had condensed the Energy Flower, Qi Flower, or comprehended momentum could see the terror of Lin Fei's saber momentum at a glance.

Martial momentum also had strengths and weaknesses. And Lin Fei's saber momentum was top-notch saber momentum, second to none. Under this kind of saber momentum suppression, one's strength would be reduced to a very low level.

At this moment, on the stage, Ao Yunxiao personally experienced the horror of Lin Fei's saber momentum. He felt as if his whole body was being cut by countless sabers. Even the true essence in his body and his physical body were suppressed. Moreover, this suppression far exceeded Ao Yunxiao's imagination.

"Swish".

Ao Yunxiao raised his head. He looked at Lin Fei and said word by word, "Worthy of 'Dao Seeker', your saber momentum is much stronger than I imagined. But if you think that you can suppress me just by relying on saber momentum, then you are wrong, very wrong! I'm not one of those martial artists with a weak will. Even if it's saber momentum, it can't break my will!"

In the next moment, Ao Yunxiao's body also burst with momentum. It was just momentum, not martial momentum. But a person's momentum represents his mental will. What's more, the true energy in Ao Yunxiao's body was like a volcano erupting. It exploded violently.

"Boom."

Under such terrifying saber momentum, Ao Yunxiao's true essence was still able to flow smoothly. Even more, the more Lin Fei's saber momentum was suppressed, the more Ao Yunxiao's true essence was shaking violently.

At the same time, Ao Yunxiao's body also moved.

One step, two steps, three steps...

Every step Ao Yunxiao took was under the immense pressure of Lin Fei's saber momentum. Every step he took came at a great cost. It was as if he was carrying several large mountains on his back, but not even Ao Yunxiao's back bent a bit, showing the strength of his body.

Ao Yunxiao was getting closer to Lin Fei. In a blink of an eye, he was very close to Lin Fei. It must be said Ao Yunxiao could be considered the strongest opponent Lin Fei had ever seen, whether among the Martial Saints or Foundation Establishment level. Facing his terrifying saber momentum, his mind and will were not affected at all.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei flicked his finger. Suddenly, a saber essence flew out instantly and turned into a rainbow light. In the blink of an eye, it reached Ao Yunxiao's face.

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique! This is a real Martial Saint level saber technique. Many true disciples might not necessarily be able to cultivate it to transcendence. But now, Lin Fei just used a saber essence to display Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique. And the speed of that rainbow light was definitely a transcendent Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique!

How long had Lin Fei joined Ancient Origin Sect? At most, not even a month!

"Bang."

The rainbow transformation saber slashed at Ao Yunxiao. Ao Yunxiao's eyes were indifferent. He punched out directly.

"Boom."

This punch seemed to shake the entire saber momentum. After all, Ao Yunxiao's punch was not just physical. True essence also exploded together!

Whether it was the physical body or the true essence, Ao Yunxiao was infinitely close to condensing the Energy Flower and Qi Flower. But Lin Fei's rainbow-transforming saber was not weak either. It was a Martial Saint level, transcendent saber technique. Moreover, it was also boosted by saber momentum. Its power was increased by several times!

What's more important was Lin Fei's saber essence. It was not any divine weapon. But it was more terrifying than any divine weapon. It contained terrifying power.

"Bang bang bang".

Ao Yunxiao threw several punches in a row. Above his head, it seemed that there were shadows of mountains and rivers. That was his fist technique.

Lin Fei's eyes were cold and his face was expressionless.

"Shoo."

He flicked his finger again. Another saber essence flew out.

"Boom."

This saber essence was like a volcano erupting. There was a faint sense of heat as if it was a ball of fire. It broke through the void and slashed toward Ao Yunxiao.

"Is that... Flame Burning Heaven Saber!"

"How can Lin Fei display two kinds of Martial Saint level saber techniques?"

"This Flame Burning Heaven Saber is not at transcendence, but it should be at the mastery realm. Moreover, it seems not far from transcendence."

"Flame Burning Heaven Saber and Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique. Both of these are Martial Saint level saber techniques, and both can evolve saber momentum. Generally, Martial Saints who can learn one saber technique have already expended countless efforts. Lin Fei actually practices two saber techniques?"

"Moreover, he can even evolve it from within his saber momentum. How amazing is his true essence?"

For a moment, the esteemed practitioners of the saber technique rose abruptly from their seats, their gazes riveted upon the figure of Lin Fei on the stage.

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique, and Flame Burning Heaven Saber – two distinct saber techniques. To the observers, it appeared as if two saber saints had taken control. Lin Fei, though stationary at the center of the stage, put Ao Yunxiao in a challenging defensive position. The two saber techniques were not to be easily quelled, let alone when enhanced by the power of saber momentum!

Yet, before Ao Yunxiao could fully grasp the situation, Lin Fei's finger twitched in another subtle motion, "Whoosh," unleashing the third surge of saber essence. This time, the saber essence was suffused with a divine, monumental aura, akin to the grand arrival of celestial spirits from above, directing their wrath towards Ao Yunxiao.

The Holy Spirit Saber Technique! Three successive saber techniques, each one a pinnacle of martial saint level, all under the empowerment of saber momentum, increasing their force manifold.

"Bang, bang, bang."

One saber attack followed another, ceaselessly, each strike potentially lethal for a typical martial saint. Even Ao Yunxiao could barely stand against such an onslaught. Consequently, he took a step back.

One step, two steps, three steps...

From whence Ao Yunxiao had come, he retreated, continuing further until he was nearly at the edge of the stage.

And Lin Fei? He remained as placid as a tranquil cloud, hands casually behind his back, showing no signs of exertion. The mere three saber essences had put Ao Yunxiao into a retreating position, nearly at the brink of defeat. This spectacle left the disciples, who were expecting a fierce clash, with wide-eyed disbelief. This was no fierce duel – it was a downright crushing defeat!

Yes, a crushing defeat!

Lin Fei was overpowering Ao Yunxiao, leaving the latter helpless, unable to retaliate. No one had expected such a lopsided battle.

"Ao Yunxiao is being overwhelmed by Lin Fei – completely suppressed. Is saber momentum truly that potent?"

"There's a vast difference between having martial momentum and not. But hasn't Ao Yunxiao defeated those who transcended martial momentum before?"

"It's not that Ao Yunxiao is weak, it's just that Lin Fei is too strong! Lin Fei's saber momentum is unbelievable, arguably one of the strongest. At least in the current Ancient Origin Sect, there's no martial momentum this powerful. Moreover, Lin Fei's comprehension of the saber technique is unimaginable. The Holy Spirit Saber Technique, Flame Burning Heaven Saber, Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique – mastering any of these saber techniques requires a martial saint to dedicate decades or even a century

But what about Lin Fei? It hasn't even been a month since he joined the Ancient Origin Sect. In other words, he mastered these three saber techniques in less than a month. Even though they haven't reached perfection, it's only a matter of time. Such saber talent and comprehension are stunning, making him a born saber genius! And what about the true essence Lin Fei exerts? Do any of you think it's just true essence? It's far stronger! Along with the saber technique and saber momentum, they seem to be perfectly fused. That's why Lin Fei is so strong!

However, don't assume Ao Yunxiao will be easily defeated. He's been gathering his energy. Now it's a crucial moment. With Ao Yunxiao's willpower, he might be able to overcome the immense pressure and perceive his fist momentum. Who wins and who loses is still uncertain."

Many disciples were abuzz with talk. Even some with discerning eyes saw the current situation of Ao Yunxiao. His situation was indeed dangerous. But for Ao Yunxiao, was it not also an opportunity? Under pressure, Ao Yunxiao might understand the martial momentum!

Indeed, Ao Yunxiao was doing just that at the moment. His whole body was trembling violently. That was the power being exerted to its extreme. Even his genuine energy and physical body were suppressed to the utmost by Lin Fei, injuries started to appear on him, and Ao Yunxiao's fighting will do not diminish at all. Instead, his fighting spirit was rising more and more prosperous.

"No one can defeat me, no one can! I will counterattack under pressure! Lin Fei, the pressure you give me is destined to make me understand the martial momentum. I have to thank you for that! Today, I will comprehend the momentum!"

With a roar, the next moment, Ao Yunxiao threw a punch. With this punch, the air trembled. Vaguely, Ao Yunxiao seemed to be about to break through a certain threshold. As if a great martial momentum was about to be born.

Under pressure, in the dire straits, Ao Yunxiao was about to break through and understand the martial momentum! This was also what Ao Yunxiao had been dreaming of. This was his fundamental goal of fighting Lin Fei.

However, Lin Fei's eyes became colder and colder. His battle with Ao Yunxiao today was not to help Ao Yunxiao succeed, was it? Ao Yunxiao had injured Shen Lianxin. Shen Lianxin would be unable to cultivate for a year. Lin Fei had to make Ao Yunxiao pay ten times, a hundred times the price. If he could not kill Ao Yunxiao, he would make Ao Yunxiao regret it for a lifetime!

"You want to comprehend the momentum? Then I will break your momentum!"

Lin Fei's eyes were icy cold. The next moment, his saber momentum shrank violently, almost condensed to a point. At the same time, the three sabers merged into one. In the void, a terrifying great saber appeared.

"Slash!"

The next moment, saber momentum, saber essence, and saber law all merged into one, transformed into a heavenly saber, descending from the sky.

A saber slashed into Ao Yunxiao's body. Ao Yunxiao only felt a tremor in his body. It felt as if his body was being torn apart. The genuine energy instantly became chaotic. But that was not important. He knew very well that Lin Fei would not kill him. This was the iron rule of the Ancient Origin Sect!

Since he would not die, he would have no fear. He only wished that the martial momentum could succeed! However, Lin Fei's saber was not just the saber essence and saber technique. It also contained saber momentum!

This saber, actually directly severed Ao Yunxiao's fighting will that was about to reach a critical point, causing Ao Yunxiao's momentum to collapse in an instant.

"No... my momentum!"

Ao Yunxiao roared, his voice even carrying a touch of fear.

"Sputter."

The next moment, Ao Yunxiao's momentum plummeted. He spat out a mouthful of fresh blood and was knocked off the stage by Lin Fei's saber!

223. Shocking Ancient Origin Sect

Silence. A deathlike stillness enveloped the entire arena.

Defeat. Ao Yunxiao had been defeated.

However, many were well aware the defeat of Ao Yunxiao, in truth, held no significance. Ao Yunxiao had always been gathering momentum. Even in the battle against Lin Fei, it was all for the purpose of building momentum.

Just moments ago, under intense pressure, his fist momentum was almost taking form. Once that occurred, success or failure, for Ao Yunxiao, his objective would have been achieved.

Yet, who would have thought?

Lin Fei had unexpectedly cut through Ao Yunxiao's momentum with a single strike of his saber. Ao Yunxiao, on the brink of comprehending his fist momentum, was abruptly severed!

Momentum was not something one could grasp immediately upon comprehension. It required the right time, advantageous ground, and opportunity amongst other factors. Only when combined could one, in a fleeting moment, understand the momentum of martial arts.

Even Ao Yunxiao had spent an expanse of time, practicing a singular fist technique, even deliberately embarked on the path of accumulating momentum, having defeated numerous true disciples in succession. Finally, he reached the present moment, on the verge of comprehending his fist momentum.

But, at that crucial juncture of imminent success, his fist momentum was broken! This sort of blow was almost a fall from the pinnacle to the nadir. No martial saint could bear such an impact. Ao Yunxiao was no exception.

"Pff."

Ao Yunxiao spat out another mouthful of fresh blood. However, this was not a result of physical injury. Rather, it was the blood expelled due to a mix of anger, self-blame, and frustration. His complexion was pale as a sheet. His spirits plummeted drastically. If he could not recover from this, he would never comprehend the martial momentum for the rest of his life. Even more, whether he could still condense the Energy Flower, Qi Flower, was uncertain.

Lin Fei's single strike of his saber had almost severed Ao Yunxiao's path to Martial Sovereign!

"You're ruthless! Severing my path. We are irreconcilable!"

Ao Yunxiao gritted his teeth in rage. Even with his level of composure, at this moment, he was on the verge of erupting, unable to bear such a consequence.

Lin Fei's gaze remained calm, staring coldly at Ao Yunxiao. He spoke slowly, "You want to build momentum, that's fine. But, you intentionally injured Shen Lianxin, forcing my hand. So, I did as you wished, I acted. You should know, when you forced my hand, you should be ready to bear all consequences! Didn't you want to use me as a stepping stone to aid you in gathering momentum? Then I will sever your momentum! This is a lesson!"

Lin Fei's words echoed across the entire arena. Everyone understood the reason. Lin Fei intentionally severed Ao Yunxiao's momentum to give Ao Yunxiao an unforgettable lesson. Only, this lesson was tremendously harsh. It was possible that a shadow would shroud Ao Yunxiao's life henceforth.

"Lin Fei, such ruthlessness indeed! He almost obliterated the path of Martial Sovereign for Ao Yunxiao."

"And it occurred just as Ao Yunxiao was about to succeed."

"In the throes of Ao Yunxiao's ecstasy, all his hopes were shattered."

"This... this is simply too cruel!"

"But wasn't Ao Yunxiao cruel too?"

"In order to provoke Lin Fei, Ao Yunxiao purposefully injured Shen Lianxin."

"To my knowledge, Shen Lianxin journeyed across the sea with Lin Fei, adrift for several months. They are comrades who have stared death in the face together. And what was the result? Ao Yunxiao twice injured Shen Lianxin, rendering him unable to practice martial arts for a year due to his recuperation. Ao Yunxiao's actions led Lin Fei to retaliate in this way, defeating Ao Yunxiao. He was merely avenging Shen Lianxin! Having a friend like Lin Fei is truly a blessing!"

At that moment, the disciples began to converse fervently. Despite Ao Yunxiao's failure to comprehend the Momentum of Martial Arts was indeed a pity. Yet, this was the essence of cultivation! Smooth sailing was never guaranteed.

Furthermore, if Ao Yunxiao truly possessed unyielding mental strength and exceptional willpower, he would certainly rise again, dispelling the shadow in his heart. When that time came, Ao Yunxiao's comprehension of the Momentum of Martial Arts would surely become smoother.

However, if he could not dispel the shadow in his heart and forever wallowed in desolation, it would imply that there were still flaws within Ao Yunxiao's spirit. Even if he had comprehended the Martial Momentum now, in the future, he would not be able to condense the Spirit Flower. Not to mention achieving the Three Flowers and challenging the realm of Martial Sovereign.

The path of martial arts is indeed the path of tempering one's spirit. If one's spirit is not resilient, or if there are defects in one's spirit, one will not reach the pinnacle of martial arts. Temporary fortune will not last forever.

"I will comprehend the Momentum! Moreover, I will condense the three flowers. I will attain the Sovereign of Martial Arts, and no one can stop me!"

Ao Yunxiao's voice resonated like a low beastly roar. His teeth gritted, his expression ferocious. However, no matter how fiercely he swore, whether he could truly rid himself of the shadow in his spirit, nobody knew. Supported by several true disciples, Ao Yunxiao departed.

Lin Fei also stepped forward, descending the stage.

"Whoosh."

The crowd automatically made way. Lin Fei saw a familiar figure. Shen Lianxin! Although Shen Lianxin was injured, His actions were not impeded. The duel between Lin Fei and Ao Yunxiao was caused by him after all. How could he not be present?

"Brother Lin, you've grown stronger."

Shen Lianxin's expression was somewhat complex. He did not utter words of gratitude. Between him and Lin Fei, there was no need for pleasantries.

Lin Fei glanced around, calmly stating, "Brother Shen, the most important aspect of martial arts is the spirit! Your spirit does not fall short compared to anyone else. Your path of the saber does not fall short compared to anyone else."

Shen Lianxin remained silent. He merely nodded gravely. Subsequently, Lin Fei, along with Shen Lianxin, departed straight from the dueling stage.

"Spirit..."

Many disciples heard Lin Fei's words. They contemplated them earnestly in their hearts. Was the spirit indeed so important?

Some disciples harbored doubts. After all, they believed that talent, insight, and opportunity were the most crucial elements.

Yet, spirit... Intangible, unseen. No one thought that the spirit held such significance. But from Lin Fei's perspective, he appeared to prioritize the spirit above all else!

For a moment, subtle shifts began to transpire within many disciples' hearts. The elders and top martial saints hidden throughout the dueling stage all fell silent at this moment.

"This young man, he has the potential to become a Martial Sovereign! Without even consolidating his Energy Flower and Qi Flower, he already realizes the importance of the spirit. And moreover, he places such emphasis on the spirit. No wonder it is said that the 'Dao Seekers' are exceptional and destined to form golden cores."

"I say, it's more than just forming golden cores. They are destined to become Martial Sovereign! Elder Lin Fei possesses potential that surpasses many true disciples, even those who are seen as seeds of the Martial Sovereign."

"In our Ancient Origin Sect, we have another top martial saint whose potential rivals that of a Martial Sovereign seed! What a joyous occasion!"

Many elders showed faint smiles on their faces. As for Ao Yunxiao? He was a failure! In the Ancient Origin Sect, no one cared about the failures. Unless one day, Ao Yunxiao could truly shed the shadow in his spirit and comprehend the momentum of martial arts anew. Only then, perhaps, would people regard him highly.

Otherwise, continuing like this, Ao Yunxiao might not even be able to retain his status as a true disciple. After all, the statuses of true disciples and inner disciples were not forever guaranteed. If their martial arts did not progress, if their strength did not improve, they might even be expelled from the inner sect, or lose their status as true disciples, only to become elders.

The difference between a true disciple and an elder, the disparity was as vast as heaven and earth. The elder served while the true disciples dedicated themselves solely to cultivation. They were the future of the Ancient Origin Sect and could not be treated on the same level.

...

Lin Fei escorted Shen Lianxin back to his cave dwelling. Although Shen Lianxin could not cultivate, this pertained only to his true essence and physical body. It didn't affect his understanding of the saber momentum.

On the contrary, Shen Lianxin had made a blessing of misfortune. In this period, he was completely at peace, fully devoted to comprehending the saber momentum.

Unexpectedly, Shen Lianxin indeed gained some understanding. At most, within a year, Shen Lianxin would likely comprehend his own saber momentum!

Regarding Shen Lianxin's impending understanding of the saber momentum, Lin Fei wasn't surprised. After all, Shen Lianxin was renowned for his martial obsession. He was devoted to the saber dao.

With an incredibly steadfast spirit, having traveled across seas with Lin Fei to seek the Dao at the Ancient Origin Sect, if he couldn't understand the saber momentum, then he would not be Shen Lianxin.

"In the coming days, I can visit regularly to assist your understanding of the saber momentum to help you grasp the saber momentum as soon as possible."

Lin Fei said to Shen Lianxin.

"I am in your debt, Brother Lin."

Shen Lianxin didn't decline. After all, having the stimulus and honing Lin Fei's saber momentum, his own understanding of the saber momentum would come more quickly.

"Alright, then concentrate on understanding the saber momentum. I'll return in a few days."

After finishing, Lin Fei turned and departed from Shen Lianxin's cave dwelling.

224. Essence Enhancement Pills

Lin Fei returned to his cave dwelling.

News about him in the outside world was undoubtedly being spread far and wide. After all, he had overpowered Ao Yunxiao with great force that day. Furthermore, he had severed Ao Yunxiao's Dao with a single saber stroke.

Whether Ao Yunxiao could recover remained uncertain. As for harboring resentment in Ao Yunxiao's heart, Lin Fei was even less concerned. Until this day, had there been any shortage of individuals who bore ill will towards him? He Mountain Dao, Guardian Primordial Mountain, Sky Reaching Sect - didn't each hold a grudge against him? Yet, he had destroyed the top ten immortal sects of Great Chang.

Therefore, Lin Fei was indifferent to others holding any resentment towards him. Those he had surpassed, none had ever managed to catch up!

Lin Fei carefully savored the battle with Ao Yunxiao. Although Ao Yunxiao was defeated by him, in fact, Ao Yunxiao had his merits. For example, Ao Yunxiao's physical body and true essence were indeed strong. Even when Lin Fei had given his all, displaying his saber momentum and the three saber skills at the Martial Saint level, he was still unable to do anything to Ao Yunxiao.

In the end, he had to combine three saber strokes into one, concentrating his saber momentum to defeat him with a single, most powerful saber strike! If that one saber stroke still failed to defeat Ao Yunxiao, then ultimately, Lin Fei could only resort to attrition. This also allowed Lin Fei to see some of his own shortcomings, or rather, his areas of weakness.

"Merely relying on saber momentum, if my saber momentum does not reach perfection, then there can be no substantial improvement. However, for my saber momentum to reach perfection, there is still a long way to go. Therefore, to enhance my power, I should focus on my physical body and saber essence.

I have saber momentum. When using it to perform saber skills, the stronger my saber essence, the stronger my power, even increasing exponentially. On the other hand, the strengthening of the physical body can be delayed. It is not easy for the physical body to condense an Energy Flower.

To enhance saber essence, given the nature of my True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique, I can transform heaven and earth and the sun and moon. Some heavenly treasures or elixirs can rapidly enhance the cultivation progress of my True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique, increasing saber essence. Seems that a trip to the Treasure Exchange Pavilion is in order."

Lin Fei analyzed the area he should now focus on enhancing. Saber essence! Or rather, he should enhance the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique.

The True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique could transform heaven and earth, the sun, moon, and stars, leaving nothing untouched. As long as there are heavenly treasures or elixirs, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique could improve.

However, this martial art was difficult to cultivate successfully. Yet Lin Fei had used the True Intention Scroll, swallowing this martial art, so this martial art had become Lin Fei's skill. Now, without the need for heavenly treasures or elixirs, his cultivation progress could increase by 1% each day.

In a hundred days, approximately three months, he could break through to the mid-stage of Martial Saint. This was an incredibly terrifying speed. But Lin Fei still found it too slow.

With elixirs or heavenly treasures, the speed would undoubtedly be faster. So, Lin Fei left his cave dwelling and flew towards the Treasure Exchange Pavilion.

Soon, Lin Fei arrived at the Treasure Exchange Pavilion. The pavilion was bustling with people coming and going. Many disciples could come here to trade various treasures. Here, one could not only buy but also sell. And the transactions could only be made using contribution points.

Lin Fei arrived at the Treasure Exchange Pavilion and directly took out his Elder token. The one who attended to Lin Fei was an inner sect disciple. He was only at the innate level. He was likely there to earn some negligible contribution points.

Seeing that Lin Fei was an Elder, the disciple's eyes brightened slightly. His demeanor became more respectful: "Elder, may I know what treasures you need?"

"Do you have any elixirs that can directly enhance a Martial Saint's True Essence?" Lin Fei asked directly.

"Elixirs that enhance a Martial Saint's True Essence? Yes, definitely. And, there are many types of elixirs."

Then, this disciple took Lin Fei to see those elixirs. Based on different effects, the elixirs were also categorized into several types. For example, there was the Great Revival Pill, which had a mild but lasting effect. It could increase Martial Saint's True Essence without damaging the foundation. But, it was too expensive! And honestly, its effects were not very noticeable. It also required time to refine.

Then there were the impressively effective Essence Enhancement Pills! These Essence Enhancement Pills were indeed very effective. They could have excellent effects on the True Essence of early and even mid-stage Martial Saints. However, they were not easy to refine. Often, it required immense energy to refine. And, in a word, expensive! In two words, very expensive!

Many Martial Saints would rather cultivate slowly on their own. After all, Martial Saints had a lifespan of five hundred years. Slowly cultivating their True Essence, they could also cultivate their True Essence to the peak one day.

"Essence Enhancement Pills, how much do they cost?"

Lin Fei was interested in the Essence Enhancement Pills.

"One Essence Enhancement Pill costs one hundred contribution points."

"One hundred contribution points?"

Lin Fei thought for a moment.

"Give me ten Essence Enhancement Pills."

Thus, Lin Fei spent the remaining one thousand contribution points to buy ten Essence Enhancement Pills. He quickly returned to his cave dwelling.

"Let's test the effect."

Lin Fei directly swallowed an Essence Enhancement Pill.

"Boom."

As soon as the Essence Enhancement Pill went down his throat, a surge of heat quickly flowed through his entire body. Immediately afterward, a large amount of energy radiated from the Essence Enhancement Pill. The True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique rapidly operated and transformed this energy into the saber essence.

One hour, two hours, three hours...

After an entire day, the effect of the Essence Enhancement Pill gradually disappeared. Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique took a whole day to refine a single Essence Enhancement Pill. It should be noted that other Martial Saints could not always maintain the operation of their techniques. And they didn't have the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. Their refining speed was far slower than Lin Fei's.

According to the inner sect disciple from the Treasure Exchange Pavilion, generally, a Martial Saint would need five to ten days to fully refine an Essence Enhancement Pill.

And Lin Fei? It only took him one day to refine a single Essence Enhancement Pill. As for the effect of the Essence Enhancement Pill, Lin Fei could feel that it was not bad.

"System."

Then, Lin Fei immediately pulled up the system panel to check.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Early Martial Saint

True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique: Early Stage (Progress 10%)

Blood Essence Nine Transformations: Seventh Transformation (Progress 12%)

Holy Spirit Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress 58%)

Flame Burning Heaven Saber: Mastery (Progress 65%)

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique: Transcendence (Progress 10%)

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei saw the progress of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. It had increased from 6% to 10%.

That is to say, a single Essence Enhancement Pill could enhance the cultivation progress of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique by 4%. This effect was actually quite terrifying. After all, if he took twenty-five Essence Enhancement Pills, doesn't that mean he could reach the mid-stage of Martial Saint?

"No, Essence Enhancement Pills definitely don't have such a good effect on ordinary Martial Saints. The pills will also have some wastage. Most Martial Saints can't refine all the energy in the pill. As time goes on, the slower the refining speed, the more the pill is wasted. After all, not everyone has the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique and can refine the power of the pill every moment of the day..."

Lin Fei thought carefully. Perhaps, only he himself could utilize the medicinal power of the Essence Enhancement Pills so well. Other Martial Saints, if they could absorb 20% of the power of the pill, would be considered pretty good.

But Lin Fei, because of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique, and because he could refine the power of the pill at every moment almost let this Essence Enhancement Pill have no medicinal power wastage, he absorbed 100% of the medicinal power of the Essence Enhancement Pill. That's why he was able to increase the cultivation progress by 4% all at once. So, Lin Fei continued to take the Essence Enhancement Pills.

Two, three, four, five...

Nine days passed, and the remaining nine Essence Enhancement Pills were consumed by Lin Fei.

Lin Fei opened his eyes. He glanced at the progress of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. The cultivation progress was at 46%. If he took about fourteen more Essence Enhancement Pills, Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique should be able to break through to the middle stage.

Just that, there were no more Essence Enhancement Pills. Even the contribution points were gone, unable to purchase from the Treasure Exchange Pavilion.

"Either find the pill formula for Essence Enhancement Pills and refine the pill myself or buy Essence Enhancement Pills directly. But no matter which method, it requires contribution points."

Lin Fei now also realized the importance of contribution points. Before, he had the six thousand contribution points given by the Ancient Origin Sect, even the true disciple would be envious. But now, the contribution points were spent. If he wanted to improve his strength faster, he could only do tasks to earn contribution points.

The sect is just like that. To get something, one has to give something. Even true disciples are no exception.

So, Lin Fei got up and left the cave, flying towards the task hall of the Ancient Origin Sect.

225. The benefits of reputation

Lin Fei arrived at the Task Hall. Unexpectedly, there weren't many people in there. Because outer sect disciples didn't even have the qualifications to take on tasks. Only inner sect disciples, true disciples, and some elders were qualified to take them.

For outer sect disciples, they need to practice step by step until they enter the inner sect. This also showed the Ancient Origin Sect's attitude towards outer sect disciples. It was like a selection place. Among the countless disciples of the outer sect, select those with outstanding potential and promote them to the inner sect. Only then could they be considered true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect.

On the wall, there were some tasks. There could be private tasks or tasks issued by the sect. However, some tasks were published privately. The contribution points were relatively low.

For example, some true disciples needed some heavenly treasures and there were none in the Treasure Exchange Pavilion. So they submitted tasks, but the contribution points were not much. And, these kinds of tasks were usually more complex.

Sect tasks provide many more contribution points. However, to receive a sect task there was also a special requirement. It was not something one could take at will.

And, many were investigation tasks. One had to spend a lot of energy and time. And it was not necessarily clear. For example, Lin Fei saw a task.

"Investigate the Foggy Sea, the traces of three missing true disciples. Find clues, and you can get 3,000 contribution points. Find the true disciples, and you can get 10,000 contribution points."

This contribution point, indeed, was very generous. Even, Lin Fei was moved. However, of the Foggy Sea, Lin Fei also had heard. It was not in the Tianqi Country. That is to say, it was not within the power range of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Those three true disciples had even been missing for a year. Even with 10,000 contribution points, most people would not be willing to take on this task. However, this also reflected the Ancient Origin Sect's emphasis on true disciples. Just missing, it offered 10,000 contribution points. That's a big shot!

Lin Fei needed at least fourteen Essence Enhancement Pills to break through to the middle stage of Martial Saint.

Lin Fei did a task not just wanting to get over a thousand contribution points, he also hoped that going out once could get enough contribution points. After all, after reaching the middle stage of Martial Saint, he still needed to continue practicing.

Essence Enhancement Pills seemed to be effective for the middle stage of Martial Saint as well. Therefore, Lin Fei continued to look for tasks.

Some investigation tasks were too complicated and draining. Lin Fei didn't even look at them.

Having gone through all the options, finally, Lin Fei found a task that seemed suitable for him.

"In the Imperial City of Tianqi Country, occasionally martial artists at the Martial Saint level disappear. Even members of the royal family are among them. Now, everyone in the Imperial City is in fear, willing to give out 10,000 contribution points to issue a task. They hope that a Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect will go to the Imperial City, find the missing people, and deal with the true culprit behind the scenes. The royal family suspects that the real culprit behind the scenes is powerful. To take on this task, you need to be at the top Martial Saint level."

Lin Fei saw this task. It was a task issued by the royal family. The royal family of Tianqi Country had a close relationship with the Ancient Origin Sect. Many members of the royal family were outer, inner, or even true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect. By rights, the strength of the royal family was not weak. Unexpectedly, they still needed to issue a task, asking for help from the Ancient Origin Sect.

Normally, if a major event occurred in the royal family, the Ancient Origin Sect would send a sect expert to investigate. However, these were just some missing cases. Even if they involve members of the royal family, they were not core members They did not affect the normal operation. Therefore, the Ancient Origin Sect did not send a sect expert to investigate. They just let the royal family solve it themselves. The royal family could only issue tasks. Fortunately, the royal family had accumulated a lot. 10,000 contribution points were not a problem.

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. Although it was also an investigation task, the scope was much smaller. It was just in the Imperial City. Moreover, there were Martial Saints missing. There must be a true culprit behind it.

As long as it was confirmed to be in the Imperial City, then Lin Fei didn't have to search all over the place, wasting time and energy, and even in the end not finding any clues. It was just in the Imperial City.

Lin Fei thought it wouldn't be a problem. Although his saber momentum couldn't cover the entire Imperial City, he could cover it multiple times if necessary. He would always find the true culprit.

Moreover, 10,000 contribution points was definitely not a small amount. Only the royal family, with their wealth and influence, could make such a big offer. After all, the contribution points of the Ancient Origin Sect were very precious.

However, the task required a top Martial Saint to take on. This is a basic condition. Lin Fei didn't know if he now met the condition of a top Martial Saint.

A topMartial Saint should be an existence that is infinitely close to condensing an Energy Flower, Qi Flower. Like Ao Yunxiao, who was a top Martial Saint.

As for Martial Saints who had condensed Energy Flower, and Qi Flower, they were generally referred to as Limit Martial Saints, implying one aspect had reached its limit.

Lin Fei's current cultivation level was only at the early stage of Martial Saint. Although his physical body and blood essence were vast, he hadn't reached the point of condensing an Energy Flower.

However, Lin Fei's saber momentum was in transcendence, this was his biggest advantage. Lin Fei didn't hesitate, he directly went to ask the elder of the task hall. Therefore, Lin Fei walked up to the two elders in the task hall. He pulled out the identity token of the outer sect elder.

"Elder, I want to take the task of investigating the Imperial City," Lin Fei said directly.

"The task of investigating the Imperial City?"

The elder looked up and glanced at Lin Fei.

"It requires a top Martial Saint to accept. You are an outer sect elder...Hmm? 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei?"

The elder in the task hall was slightly surprised. Then, another elder came over. The two discussed for a while. Finally, they nodded and said: "Elder Lin, you just joined the outer sect, and your cultivation level has not been confirmed to reach the top Martial Saint level. Normally, you wouldn't be allowed to accept this task. However, you recently defeated Ao Yunxiao. Ao Yunxiao is a true top Martial Saint. Since you can defeat Ao Yunxiao, your strength must have reached the level of a top Martial Saint. Therefore, you can accept this task."

This was the advantage of having a reputation. Even if they hadn't seen Lin Fei, they knew that "Dao Seeker" Lin Fei's strength was extraordinary. Therefore, others were not eligible to take this task. But Lin Fei was eligible!

"There is no time limit for this task. After the task is completed, the royal family will naturally send out a message to the Ancient Origin Sect. Then, you can come to collect the contribution points. If the task is not completed, you must also come to the task hall to abandon the task."

Lin Fei nodded, indicating that he understood. Then, Lin Fei made a note and received the token for the task. When the time came, he just needed to show the token at the Imperial City. The royal family would know that Lin Fei was a Martial Saint from Ancient Origin Sect who came to take the task. They would certainly cooperate with Lin Fei in investigating the case of the missing Martial Saint in the Imperial City.

"By the way, has anyone else taken this task before?"

Lin Fei suddenly asked.

"You are the first Martial Saint to take this task."

The elder shook his head.

"The first one?"

A strange light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He could tell this task had been issued for some time. Why was he the first Martial Saint to take the task? 10,000 contribution points. For many Martial Saints, it's a large number.

The elder of the task hall laughed and said, "Hahaha, there must be Martial Saints who want to take this task. But they need to have the qualifications. Do you think that any Martial Saints in Ancient Origin Sect can be called a top Martial Saint? They must be evaluated by us. Otherwise, they are not qualified to take the task."

Lin Fei understood. There were indeed many Martial Saints in Ancient Origin Sect. But there weren't so many that could be called top Martial Saints.

10,000 contribution points were indeed a lot, but those top Martial Saints were all busy condensing Essence Flower or Qi Flower. Few of them would do this task. It could be considered Lin Fei's luck.

"Thank you, both elders."

After saying that, Lin Fei left the task hall with the token.

226. Another Martial Saint Disappears!

Lin Fei returned to his cave dwelling. He didn't immediately go to the Imperial City of Tianqi Country. Since he had taken the task, he first needed to understand the place where the task was located. He couldn't go to the Imperial City blindly.

Lin Fei first looked for a miscellaneous record. It recorded some power distributions of the Ancient Origin Sect and Tianqi Country. For example, the royal family. The first emperor of Tianqi Country was named Gu Xuan! In fact, he was an inner elder of the Ancient Origin Sect who had condensed an Energy Flower. He was sent by the Ancient Origin Sect to conquer all sides. Finally, he established Tianqi Country.

Therefore, the royal family of Tianqi Country was the Gu family. Later, the royal family of Tianqi Country also respected the Ancient Origin Sect. Even the selection of the heir to the emperor must also get the consent of the Ancient Origin Sect.

Of course, the royal family was rich and powerful, with a deep foundation. They had successively sent many true disciples into the Ancient Origin Sect. Among them, there were even Limit Martial Saints who had condensed Energy Flower and Qi Flower!

However, that was all in the past. In the past few hundred years, the royal family's talent has withered. Although there were also members of the royal family who became the true transmission of the Ancient Origin Sect, they couldn't reach the level of the Limit Martial Saint. Even the top Martial Saint was not reached. This is also why the royal family had no way to handle the case of the missing Martial Saint in the Imperial City this time. The strength was really weak.

Of course, the weakening of the royal family's strength would not cause any problems in Tianqi Country. After all, the entire Tianqi Country was the power of the Ancient Origin Sect. As long as there was no problem with the Ancient Origin Sect, even if the royal family died, there will be no impact at all. At most, just change a person or a family to be the royal family of Tianqi Country.

Lin Fei had a pretty good understanding. The royal family of Tianqi Country seemed weak and the Ancient Origin Sect didn't have a strong master stationed in the Imperial City. There were only one or two ordinary Martial Saints.

Moreover, the real culprit behind the case of the missing people seemed to know the measure. He didn't move the Martial Saint of the Ancient Origin Sect. Otherwise, the Ancient Origin Sect would have intervened long ago. It showed that the real culprit was also very afraid of the Ancient Origin Sect.

This point didn't need to be thought about. The Ancient Origin Sect was the overlord of Tianqi Country. No one would not fear the Ancient Origin Sect.

"It seems that I just need to go directly to the Imperial City. If the royal family has clues, that's fine. If there are no clues, then directly use saber momentum to search forcefully! As long as you are in the Imperial City, the murderer won't escape!"

A sharp light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He made up his mind.

Lin Fei directly left the cave dwelling. He quickly flew into the sky and disappeared into the horizon in the blink of an eye.

......

Tianqi Country, Imperial City.

Inside the palace, the Emperor was furious. Even the Martial Saints of the royal family all had gloomy faces.

Because, Gu Yujian, the King of Leisure, was missing! The King of Leisure was the younger brother of the current Emperor. He was now a Martial Saint. Although he didn't enter the Ancient Origin Sect, he was also a Martial Saint master among the royal family. But he had also disappeared. Just like the other missing Martial Saints in the Imperial City.

Sudden and there were no traces left. They couldn't be found no matter what. In this case, the odds were more likely bad than good. Although the Emperor sent people to search, they didn't find any trace of the King of Leisure. Not even a single trace as if he had evaporated from the world.

The Mansion of the King of Leisure.

Gu Lin, the little daughter loved by the King of Leisure. Now she was biting her lip tightly. Her eyes were red. She looked haggard. It looked like she hadn't slept for many days.

Gu Lin had not bestowed any title. However, everyone knew that she was the most beloved daughter of the King of Leisure. Her status in the mansion was also very high.

In front of Gu Lin, there were two Martial Saints dressed in the Ancient Origin Sect's attire.

With a "plop" sound, Gu Lin knelt down in front of the two Martial Saints.

"Uncle Qiu, Uncle Li, you have always been good friends with my father. Now my father is missing, and his life or death is unknown. Although the Emperor sent people to search, no Martial Saint dares to go. How could they find any clues? Please, the two Martial Saints, help to look for my father. Perhaps you can find a clue about my father."

These two Martial Saints were sent by the Ancient Origin Sect to the Imperial City. They basically had no hope of promotion. Sent to the Imperial City was also considered as retirement. They enjoyed luxury and wealth. It was a comfortable job. Both of them and Gu Yujian, the King of Leisure, got along well. Every day, they enjoyed painting, chess, and music, and had fun. It was indeed a happy life.

However, the King of Leisure had now disappeared. Suddenly, the two of them were somewhat unprepared. Even, there was a hint of vigilance in their hearts. After all, they were also Martial Saints! The mysterious killers seemed to specialize in capturing Martial Saints. Their strength must be very terrifying.

Seeing Gu Lin kneel down and ask for their help, the two were quite helpless. They could only shake their heads and say, "Gu Lin, get up first. It's not that we don't want to find Brother Yujian. It's really that our strength is limited. Even Brother Yujian, who is as strong as us, was captured without any resistance. If we go to search, it's nothing more than walking into a tiger's den."

Gu Lin's face turned pale. She said tremulously, "So, there's no way?"

"Of course there is a way! That is to wait! Your royal family has issued a task in the Ancient Origin Sect. They have offered a reward of ten thousand contribution points. I believe that soon the top Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect will take the task and come to investigate the case of the missing Martial Saints. At that time, they will naturally find out the real culprit, and even kill the real culprit!"

"The top Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect?"

Gu Lin's eyes widened. It seemed to show a glimmer of hope again.

"But when will the top Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect arrive?"

"Nobody knows that. Only when a top Martial Saint takes the task will they come to the Imperial City."

"But what if no one takes the task for a long time? Won't no one come to the Imperial City to investigate then?"

The two Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect looked at each other, both fell silent. Theoretically, this possibility exists. No one takes the task. Otherwise, after so long, the top Martial Saints should have come down from the mountain. But so far, no Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect has come to the Imperial City.

"If you don't go and look for him, then I will go by myself!"

Gu Lin gritted her teeth. She immediately stood up, ready to leave the mansion to go look for clues on her own.

"Nonsense!"

The Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect snorted coldly.

"My father's whereabouts are unknown, life or death is uncertain. Others may choose not to look. But as the daughter of my father, how could I sit idly by and wait in the mansion? What's more, you are Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect. How would that mysterious killer dare to target you? If you are willing to investigate, as long as there are any clues, you don't need to act. Just pass the clues to the royal family. The royal family's Martial Saints will naturally take action!"

The faces of the two Martial Saints changed constantly. What Gu Lin said made sense. In fact, that mysterious killer, although rampant, had never offended anyone from the Ancient Origin Sect. Obviously, the other party was also wary of the Ancient Origin Sect. If they both went to investigate, there would probably be no danger. But they just didn't want to take risks. What if the other party dared to take risks? Wouldn't they be in danger then?

Looking at Gu Lin's expectant expression, the two Martial Saints sighed and said, "Fine, we are good friends with Brother Yujian. Moreover, we have already lived for more than four hundred years, and we are not far from our lifespan. Even if something unexpected happens, it's enough! We will go out together and look for clues about Brother Yujian!"

Gu Lin was overjoyed in her heart and bowed respectfully, "Thank you, both Martial Saints!"

"Alright, there's no need to talk nonsense. Brother Yujian hasn't been missing for long, there may still be some clues."

So, the two Martial Saints took Gu Lin, left the mansion, and went to the Imperial City to look for clues about the disappearance of Gu Yujian.

227. Sudden Changes in the Imperial City

Gu Lin and the two Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect together went out to look for clues about Gu Yujian's disappearance. However, after searching for a day, there were no traces at all. It was as if Gu Yujian had truly evaporated from the world.

For a moment, Gu Yujian was like a dead man. She was desperate!

Qiu Long and Li Yuan, the two Martial Saints, at this moment, were helpless as well. They had searched for a day. Indeed, they hadn't been attacked by the mysterious killer, but they also couldn't find any clues. Clearly, the other party had a great ability to hide. If this continued, even if the Ancient Origin Sect really sent people, it might be hard to find the real killer.

"Report. Zhang Xuan, the Marquis of Yang Martial in the east city, has also mysteriously disappeared. However, there are traces of a struggle at the scene. The royal family has already sent a Martial Saint there."

Suddenly, a servant from the royal mansion hurriedly reported.

"Marquis of Yang Martial? Let's go and see. Marquis of Yang Martial just disappeared, there might be some clues."

So, Gu Lin and the two Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect immediately set off. The three quickly arrived at the Zhang Mansion.

At this moment, Zhang's mansion had been surrounded by people from the royal family. Gu Lin is the daughter of King Xiaoyao. Naturally, she could go in.

"Greetings to the two Martial Saints."

The royal general inside, upon seeing Qiu Long and Li Yuan, immediately gave a respectful salute. After all, Qiu Long and Li Yuan represented the Ancient Origin Sect.

"Tell us, what clues do you have?" Qiu Long asked in a deep voice.

"There are indeed some clues. Although Marquis of Yang Martial didn't know the mysterious killer would target him, he was prepared. He sprinkled a kind of medicine powder on himself. This medicine powder is colorless and tasteless. Only a special kind of bug can track it."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan were overjoyed in their hearts. As long as they find the Marquis of Yang Martial, Zhang Xuan, perhaps they could find the King of Leisure. So, the two hurriedly asked, "Where is the tracking bug? We're about to set off."

"Good, let's go find it together!"

So, the royal family dispatched two Martial Saints. Qiu Long and Li Yuan were also two Martial Saints. Four Martial Saints, accompanied by a large number of guards, began to follow the tracking bug.

The bug flew fast. It crossed many streets. Suddenly, an open space appeared in front of them. They actually arrived at a cemetery. There were tombs everywhere here. It was the cemetery of the Imperial City. Generally, no one would come here. The entire cemetery was now filled with a gloomy atmosphere.

When the bug arrived here, it stopped. It seemed to want to fly inside. But it seemed to be afraid of something and didn't dare to enter the cemetery.

"Look, there are footprints on the ground."

"There are traces of blood too."

"Go in and search, Marquis of Yang Martial must be near the cemetery!"

So, a large number of guards rushed into the cemetery.

"Roar..."

Suddenly, a low roar echoed from within the cemetery. Following this, a tomb exploded violently. A pitch-black corpse, emanating a foul stench, burst from the ground. And it charged straight toward the guards.

"Splat."

"Is it a zombie?"

"Someone is keeping and refining zombies here!"

"And this zombie has a very strong power."

The two Martial Saints of the royal family took action at the same time. Even if it was a zombie, with their Martial Saint's strength, they were naturally unafraid. However, as soon as the two Martial Saints took action, they immediately regretted it. A big mistake!

A Martial Saint, indeed, doesn't have to fear a zombie. But what if the zombie is at the level of a Martial Saint?

"Bang, bang."

With just two punches, two royal Martial Saints were directly blown up. They didn't even have the strength to resist. Seeing this scene, everyone was filled with immense fear.

"Run!"

Qiu Long and Li Yuan didn't hesitate. They almost instantly pulled Gu Lin and fled frantically backward. As for those guards who had entered the cemetery, they were no longer important. Qiu Long and Li Yuan now only wanted to escape with Gu Lin.

The three were lucky. The zombie did not pursue them. They fled all the way back to the royal mansion only then did they let out a sigh of relief.

Gu Lin was even trembling all over. She asked with a hint of fear in her voice, "What...what kind of monster was that?"

Gu Lin was indeed very afraid. Those were two Martial Saints! In the Tianqi Country, no matter where Martial Saints were absolutely strong. They were comparable to Foundation Establishment cultivator! Living up to five hundred years! Moreover, those two Martial Saints, in a strict sense, were Gu Lin's elders. They were the Martial Saints of the royal family. But now, they were directly blown up by a zombie.

"It's a zombie! And it's a Martial Saint level zombie! Seems that a Foundation Establishment True Person is refining Martial Saint level zombies. No wonder that mysterious killer keeps capturing some Martial Saints. No wonder there are Martial Saints disappearing continuously. The other party is refining those Martial Saints into zombies!"

For a moment, the voices of Qiu Long and Li Yuan were also trembling.

Zombie! A Martial Saint level zombie!

This is definitely not something that an ordinary Qi cultivator can achieve. Only a Foundation Establishment True Person! Even, it must be a top Foundation Establishment True Person who can achieve this.

"So, my father has already..."

Gu Lin seemed to suddenly realize something. Her face instantly turned pale. Qiu Long and Li Yuan also fell silent. They didn't speak. Obviously, Gu Yujian was most likely turned into a zombie by the mysterious Foundation Establishment True Person. He was already dead!

However, the Tianqi Country was the territory of the Ancient Origin Sect. Everyone here was a martial artist. Where would there be Qi cultivators? Even top-tier Foundation Establishment True People?

"Gu Lin, this is no longer something we can handle. We will report to the Ancient Origin Sect immediately. There is a Foundation Establishment True Person capturing Martial Saints to refine Martial Saint level zombies. The Ancient Origin Sect will surely be furious and send top-tier Martial Saints to deal with this matter. All we can do now is wait!"

Indeed, that zombie was too terrifying. Two royal Martial Saints couldn't even block one attack. Moreover, the previous Martial Saints who were taken away were not just one. If all of them were that strong, then even if all the royal Martial Saints gathered together, they wouldn't be a match.

Gu Lin's heart now was like ashes. Her father had become a zombie. He could never be saved again!

On the faces of Qiu Long and Li Yuan, there was also a hint of worry. They even thought about leaving the imperial city directly. After all, the mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator dared to capture Martial Saints in the royal city of Tianqi Country to refine them into zombies. This was happening under the nose of the Ancient Origin Sect.

The other party certainly knew that it was dangerous. But they still risked it. There's only one reason for this. The other party had a big plan! It's probably not just as simple as refining zombies. With their strength, staying in the imperial city was too dangerous.

Who can guarantee that the mysterious Foundation Establishment True Person wouldn't go crazy and capture them too, turning them into zombies?

"buzzing~"

Just as Qiu Long and Li Yuan were uneasy, suddenly, their communication stone began to vibrate violently. This kind of communication stone is made in the way of certain Qi cultivators' magical artifacts. As long as it's within a certain distance, it will react.

"Is it...the sect sent Martial Saints?"

"We haven't reported the situation in the imperial city yet, the sect can't possibly know about the zombies. There's only one possibility. A Martial Saint from the sect has accepted a mission from the royal family and has arrived in the imperial city!"

"It must be so! Let's hurry to meet them, the person who came must be a top-tier Martial Saint!"

A look of surprise appeared on the faces of Qiu Long and Li Yuan. At this time, the arrival of a top-tier Martial Saint from the sect would also be a kind of safety guarantee for them!

"Top-tier Martial Saint?"

Gu Lin abruptly lifted her head, her eyes shining.

"A top-tier Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect accepted the royal family's task. That must mean he's here to solve the disappearances in the imperial city. Now that we know there's a Foundation Establishment True Person causing trouble. Can this top-tier Martial Saint take action to kill the Foundation Establishment True Person and avenge my father and the other Martial Saints? I wonder if this top-tier Martial Saint can handle those Martial Saint level zombies?" Gu Lin asked solemnly.

"This..."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan looked at each other. Then they gritted their teeth and said, "The top-tier Martial Saints of our Ancient Origin Sect are extraordinary. Although those zombies are strong, they certainly cannot be the opponents of top-tier Martial Saints."

Both of them were elders of the Ancient Origin Sect. They knew what top-tier Martial Saints within the Ancient Origin Sect signify.

"Alright, then I will also go with the two Martial Saints to welcome this top-tier Martial Saint!"

Gu Lin gritted her teeth and stood up. Qiu Long and Li Yuan did not stop her. Gu Lin is a member of the royal family. It is only right for her to go and welcome the top-tier Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect.

"We should not delay, let's go to welcome him!"

After that, Qiu Long and Li Yuan, together with Gu Lin, quickly flew toward the direction where the communication stone was sensing.

"I wonder, who is the top-tier Martial Saint who accepted the task this time?"

Although Qiu Long and Li Yuan were not in the Ancient Origin Sect, they knew something about some of the top-tier Martial Saints in the Ancient Origin Sect. If they saw them, they would probably know. After all, they had lived for more than four hundred years. They were quite ancient.

Soon, the communication stone on the three of them began to vibrate more and more intensely. They flew to the city gate. Then, they slowly landed. They saw a man in white standing with his hands behind him at the gate. His gaze was calm, just standing there quietly.

Although there was no momentum on his body, he stood in the crowd, with a temperament that was incompatible with ordinary people. At first glance, he was not an ordinary person.

"Is this the top-tier Martial Saint from our sect?"

Qiu Long and Li Yuan looked at each other. There was a trace of doubt in their eyes. Because they didn't recognize the Martial Saint in front of them. In their memories, the man in white did not match the characteristics of any top-tier Martial Saint in the Ancient Origin Sect.

Could it be that the Martial Saint who accepted the task this time is not a top-tier Martial Saint?

228. Lin Fei Descends

"Qiu Long, Li Yuan?"

Lin Fei regarded the two Martial Saints assessing him from a distance. The communication stone vibrated. Instantly, he discerned their identities.

Qiu Long and Li Yuan. Two Martial Saints were dispatched by the Ancient Origin Sect to the Imperial City of the Tianqi Country. Each a venerable Martial Saint over four hundred years old. Facing imminent demise, they arrived at Tianqi Country's Imperial City to relish life's pleasures.

Qiu Long and Li Yuan hurriedly approached, bowing in respect, "We're not certain which True Disciple you might be?"

True Disciples held an extraordinary status within the Ancient Origin Sect. Even the Inner Sect Elders were inferior to True Disciples.

Lin Fei calmly stated, "Outer Sect Elder, Lin Fei."

"Outer Sect Elder?"

The pair blinked in mild surprise. Of course, they understood the term 'Outer Sect Elder'. Though Outer Sect Elders were Martial Saints, the rank primarily encompassed ordinary Martial Saints. There were none among them who were top-tier Martial Saints. How could the Sect allow an ordinary Martial Saint to undertake an Imperial City mission?

Qiu Long seemed to seek further confirmation, asking again, "Elder Lin, are you here for a mission?"

"Indeed, the Imperial City Disappearance Case, ten thousand contribution points. I'm Lin Fei. I'm here to unravel the mystery of it."

Upon hearing Lin Fei's confirmation, Qiu Long and Li Yuan exchanged a glance. Their eyes concealed an undeniable disappointment.

Lin Fei, being able to accept this mission, perhaps had some distinctive traits. But, what use could they be?

The current Imperial City Disappearance Case involved a Foundation Establishment True Person capable of turning Martial Saints into zombies. What use could an Outer Sect Elder be?

Lin Fei perceived the disappointment in Qiu Long and Li Yuan's eyes. He could guess why. The two, no doubt, had not heard his name before, which was reasonable. After all, they had been in the Imperial City for quite some time. Their information wouldn't be up-to-date. Moreover, it was only recently that Lin Fei defeated Ao Yunxiao. His name had just begun to circulate throughout the Ancient Origin Sect. It was forgivable if the two were unaware.

"Have there been any new developments in the Imperial City Disappearance Case, honorable Martial Saints?" Lin Fei inquired.

"Well..."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan hesitated. Even if they explained, what use could Lin Fei be? However, Gu Lin didn't know the considerations within the Martial Saints' minds. She only knew that someone from the Ancient Origin Sect had finally arrived and possibly a top-tier Martial Saint! Perhaps he could deal with the enigmatic Foundation Establishment True Person.

Therefore, Gu Lin quickly intervened, "Elder Lin, we already have leads in the Imperial City Disappearance Case. It involves a mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator. He has captured many Martial Saints and turned those Martial Saints into zombies. My father has also been captured and is now likely in grave danger. I beg you, Elder Lin, to kill this Foundation Establishment cultivator, to avenge my father and the numerous Martial Saints of the Imperial City!"

With a choked voice, Gu Lin collapsed to her knees.

Lin Fei glanced at Gu Lin. His expression remained tranquil. He stated, "I am here only to investigate the Imperial City Disappearance Case. If it pertains to the case, I will take action. Other matters are not of concern to me. Esteemed Elders, is her account accurate?"

Lin Fei turned his gaze toward Qiu Long and Li Yuan. Both Martial Saints gritted their teeth and nodded, "Elder Lin, every word Gu Lin uttered is true. Her father is Gu Yujian, the King of Leisure, also a Martial Saint who vanished abruptly a few days ago. We investigated together and happened to find the Marquis of Yang Martial also disappeared.

We followed a trail to a graveyard, where we discovered zombies of Martial Saint strength. Two Martial Saints from the royal family could not withstand even a single strike. To deal with such zombies, only top-tier Martial Saints might stand a chance. And there are true culprits behind the scenes. So, we planned to report to the Ancient Origin Sect, requesting that they dispatch top-tier Martial Saints to deal with the situation."

This matter pertained to a mysterious Foundation Establishment True Person who's kidnapping Martial Saints in the Imperial City. The Ancient Origin Sect would undoubtedly not turn a blind eye. A Foundation Establishment True Person running rampant in the Imperial City was almost an affront to the dignity of the Ancient Origin Sect!

Once reported, the Ancient Origin Sect would certainly send a formidable Martial Saint to the Imperial City. The implication of their words was to let Lin Fei wait a while longer. To report together and wait for the arrival of the Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect.

Lin Fei naturally understood what Qiu Long and Li Yuan meant. However, he neither agreed nor disagreed. He even disregarded it entirely and said directly, "Take me to the cemetery to have a look. If the real culprit behind this can be caught sooner, I can return to the sect earlier to hand over the mission."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan were stunned. Was Lin Fei really going to intervene in the Imperial City Disappearance Case? They had already made it clear. In the Imperial City, there was a powerful Foundation Establishment True Person. It might even be a top-tier Foundation Establishment True Person. Only a top-tier Martial Saint, or even a Limit Martial Saint, would be able to deal with them. If Lin Fei intervened now, wouldn't it be dangerous?

However, the two were now the only Martial Saints stationed in the Imperial City by the Ancient Origin Sect. Their status wasn't even equal to Lin Fei, an Outer Sect Elder. Therefore, after some hesitation, they still nodded.

"Elder Lin, let's be careful and go see what's happening at the cemetery."

So, the group of four quickly headed toward the cemetery. When they arrived at the cemetery, they discovered that the entire place was in ruins. Blood and corpses were everywhere on the ground. The thick stench of death permeated the entire cemetery.

"This is the cemetery. I don't know if the zombie is still here?"

Qiu Long and Li Yuan were still somewhat apprehensive. If they hadn't acted decisively and run fast, they would probably have been killed by the terrifying zombie by now.

Lin Fei took a step forward and "swoosh", he instantly entered the cemetery. Qiu Long, Li Yuan, and Gu Lin followed closely behind. The ground was littered with the corpses of the royal guards.

"We found them, these two were royal Martial Saints, blown up by a single strike of the zombie. Now they're just a pile of flesh and blood. But the zombie seems to have disappeared. Did it escape?"

The group only found the shattered corpses of the two Martial Saints. They didn't see the zombie. If it escaped, it was normal.

After all, if the mysterious culprit chose to hide, they must have some scruples. Once their whereabouts were discovered, they naturally had to hide.

"Could it be that mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator has escaped?" Gu Lin suddenly spoke.

Indeed, there was this possibility. After all, this incident had caused quite a stir. Perhaps the Ancient Origin Sect would send a powerful Martial Saint. After all, this was the Ancient Origin Sect's territory. No matter how powerful a Foundation Establishment True Person was, how dare they confront the Ancient Origin Sect?

"Since the mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator dared to risk kidnapping some Martial Saints in the Imperial City to turn into zombies, there must be a reason he had to do it. I think the goal of the mysterious Foundation Establishment has not been achieved yet, he might not escape for the time being. However, I fear he will become more frantic. He will definitely seize the opportunity before the Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect descend from the mountain, to frantically capture Martial Saints. I'm afraid the entire Imperial City's Martial Saints are now in danger." Qiu Long said in a deep voice.

"That makes sense. However, as long as he doesn't leave the Imperial City, it's good news. Capture him or kill him, then the disappearance case in the Imperial City would be solved." Lin Fei calmly said.

"But how can we catch that mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator? Up until now, we have only seen his zombie. And that Foundation Establishment cultivator has not shown his face. Even a city-wide manhunt by the royal family hasn't found him." Gu Lin gritted her teeth as she spoke.

If it were that easy to find, she would have found his father long ago. Unfortunately, that mysterious Foundation Establishment cultivator seemed very good at hiding his figure. So far, there had been no clues.

"As long as he's still in the Imperial City, I will definitely find him! Time is of the essence. To prevent the Foundation Establishment cultivator from escaping, I will have to go all out!"

Lin Fei's words left Qiu Long, Li Yuan, and Gu Lin momentarily stunned. They didn't understand what Lin Fei meant.

"Go all out? Elder Lin, you..."

Qiu Long was about to say something.

"Boom".

Suddenly, a white light instantly radiated from Lin Fei. And it quickly spread out in all directions. Everyone was enveloped by the white light. Even if they were Martial Saints, they felt their bodies trembling and broke out in cold sweat. Their bodies felt as if they were being weighed down by several mountains.

"This... is this... saber momentum?"

Qiu Long and Li Yuan looked up. Their eyes were filled with astonishment as they looked at Lin Fei.

229. Lin Fei's Move

Without hesitation, Lin Fei deployed his saber momentum. The vast saber momentum covered all directions. Everyone was enveloped by the saber momentum. They lifted their heads in shock, looking up into the void.

This was the Imperial City. There were countless martial artists. Moreover, there were even more saberists with sabers. At this moment, as the saber momentum enveloped them, not only did the martial artists feel as if they were carrying a heavy mountain on their bodies, moreover, the sabers in those saberists hands even started to tremble violently.

"Buzz."

Countless sabers were trembling and humming.

"What on earth is that?"

"Why does my saber seem to be drawn by some force?"

"What a terrifying pressure, what's happening to the Imperial City?"

"That's saber momentum and not an ordinary one."

"That Martial Saint, possessing such a terrifying saber momentum."

"Could it be that someone from the Ancient Origin Sect has come?"

In the Imperial City, there were definitely many strong individuals. Thus, they immediately recognized it. This was saber momentum! Generally, only a Martial Saint could comprehend saber momentum. Moreover, this saber momentum was very powerful. Under the envelope of the saber momentum, anyone's strength would be suppressed. Many Martial Saints were also suppressed. However, they were not terrified. Instead, they were delighted.

Because of such saber momentum most likely only the top Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect could possess. Which meant. the Ancient Origin Sect had finally sent someone.

Qiu Long and Li Yuan were both shocked. Such terrifying saber momentum was clearly a top Martial Saint!

Gu Lin was not a Martial Saint. But she was also suppressed. But she was very happy. The stronger Lin Fei was, the more likely it was to catch the real culprit. Even, kill the real culprit.

Lin Fei, however, did not pay attention to the thoughts of these people. He just stood quietly in place, trying to expand his perception to the extreme.

In terms of perception, in fact, Martial Saints are at a disadvantage compared to Foundation Establishment True Persons. Those Foundation Establishment True Persons have spiritual consciousness, which could sweep a large range. Even a single spiritual consciousness could easily cover the entire Imperial City.

Under the sweep of spiritual consciousness, any different person can be easily found. But it's different for Martial Saints. Martial Saints don't have such abilities. Although the five senses of a Martial Saint are very sharp and the range that the five senses can perceive is just too small. It's nearly impossible to find a hidden person from the vast sea of people.

However, once a Martial Saint comprehends the momentum of martial arts, things will be different. The momentum of martial arts is vast and can cover a large range. Under the coverage of martial arts momentum, all people would have their strength suppressed. Moreover, the Martial Saint knows everything that happens within the martial arts momentum.

Therefore, Lin Fei immediately unleashed his saber momentum, directly sweeping a radius of several miles. Although it couldn't cover the entire Imperial City, just a few rounds of saber momentum coverage would sweep every corner of the Imperial City.

Lin Fei carefully sensed for a while. He didn't find any Foundation Establishment cultivators. Even, no zombies. However, Lin Fei didn't rush. After all, his saber momentum could only cover part of the Imperial City.

"Swoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei walked in the air. He turned into a streak of light, flying toward the sky. Qiu Long and Li Yuan looked at each other. Then they gritted their teeth and said, "Follow him!"

So, the two of them, along with Gu Lin, also followed Lin Fei, flying toward the sky. On the way, Lin Fei maintained the coverage of his saber momentum. In less than the time it took for an incense stick to burn, Lin Fei could cover every corner of the Imperial City with his saber momentum. It's as if he also searched the entire Imperial City. Under the saber momentum, any trace could not escape Lin Fei's perception.

"Hmm?"

Suddenly, Lin Fei stopped. His saber momentum sensed he found a trace of spiritual power.

Spiritual power! Only Qi cultivators have spiritual power. And the entire Tianqi Country was full of martial artists. Where did the Qi cultivator come from?

"Swoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei's figure appeared on the street. His gaze was quietly fixed on a shop. It was a coffin shop. Qiu Long and Li Yuan also flew over. Seeing Lin Fei's gaze, the two immediately shouted at the crowd below, "Everyone get away quickly."

Immediately, many people ran in all directions in case a real fight broke out. Being able to tread in the air. That must be a Martial Saint. The aftereffects, how terrifying? Being slightly affected, ordinary people can't stand it.

"Elder Lin, did you find the real culprit?" Qiu Long asked softly.

Lin Fei didn't answer. Instead, he began to shrink his saber momentum. The more saber momentum is compressed, the stronger the power. Lin Fei's saber momentum had shrunk to only cover the coffin shop.

"Whoosh."

Suddenly, the coffin shop owner raised his head abruptly. His cloak shattered in an instant. There was a vague talisman, floating around. It seemed to be struggling to resist Lin Fei's saber momentum suppression.

In the face of Lin Fei's saber momentum suppression, even the most hidden Foundation Establishment True Persons would reveal flaws. Because their magic bodies would involuntarily operate the spiritual power. Therefore, this deeply hidden Foundation Establishment True Person, in front of Lin Fei, has nowhere to hide.

"Why? Why must you find out who I am? I really don't want to kill wantonly. But, tribulation is difficult. I just wanted to cultivate a few Martial Saints with the Yin Day Birth attribute and form the Nine Yin Zombie Array. I hope to get through the tribulation and achieve the golden pill. But, you insist on finding out who I am. Then I can only kill wantonly!"

This Foundation Establishment True Person slowly stood up. Even though there was the terrifying suppression of the saber momentum, the talisman around him seemed to be able to resist the suppression of the saber momentum.

Qiu Long and Li Yuan's faces changed dramatically.

"A tribulation-crossing true person? Not good, this Foundation Establishment True Person is actually about to cross the tribulation. Elder Lin, let's go quickly, we probably are not his match!"

This was not alarmist. The true persons who can cross the tribulation, even if it is just approaching the tribulation, are very terrifying. They are equivalent to those Limit Martial Saints who have condensed Energy Flower and Qi Flower.

Of course, Foundation Establishment True Person and Martial Saints are different. The strength of a Foundation Establishment True Person depends on spells and magic treasures.

"Bang bang bang".

As the Foundation Establishment True Person operated the spiritual power. Immediately, the coffins in the coffin shop were broken open one by one. One after another, zombies flew out of the coffins.

Zombies! All zombies! And, all were Martial Saint-level zombies!

"Swoosh swoosh swoosh."

One after another, zombies flew into the void. The corpse energy from their bodies was emitted, vaguely forming a cloud of darkness, covering Lin Fei and the others within.

These zombies, actually, are not affected by the saber momentum at all. After all, zombies are no longer considered alive. They have no consciousness of their own. They are just walking dead. Saber momentum can't suppress zombies.

"Eight zombies!"

"What a terrifying momentum, even a top Martial Saint might find it difficult."

"The Nine Yin Zombie Array, that is an array that can resist some of the power of tribulation, how terrifying!"

"This time, I'm afraid we are in great danger..."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan's faces changed dramatically. They couldn't escape anymore. The sky was full of corpse energy. If they were not careful, they might even be corroded by the corpse's energy. Even if they were Martial Saints, they would be corroded all the same.

Moreover, eight Martial Saint-level zombies formed a large array. The entire void, as if it had become purgatory in an instant. This was the method of a Foundation Establishment True Person. Without a powerful magic treasure, they can use the array to replace it.

Even if these eight zombies were resurrected, just eight Martial Saints wouldn't be so terrifying. But, refined into zombies by the Foundation Establishment True Person, after forming the large array, they became so terrifying. The strength had increased at least ten times even dozens of times!

"Today, this True Person will kill wantonly. If I can't find the ninth Yin Day Birth Martial Saint, then I will use you three Martial Saints even the blood of the entire Imperial City to help me refine a blood corpse, to replace the ninth zombie! Hahaha, the Eight Yin Zombie Array, kill!"

The voice of the Foundation Establishment True Person was filled with madness. He actually wanted to use the blood of the entire city to forcefully refine blood corpses!

For a moment, the entire Imperial City seemed to be echoing with the mad laughter of the Foundation Establishment True Person. At the same time, the sky also gradually darkened. Countless Yin Qi and corpse energies converged together and shrouded the entire Imperial City.

This Foundation Establishment True Person actually had preparations early on. Even the array had been set up. He wanted to refine the entire Imperial City with blood! This is indeed extremely mad. Even at any cost. Even the Ancient Origin Sect couldn't make this Foundation Establishment True Person stop his madness.

"I'm afraid you're going to be disappointed!"

Suddenly, a cold voice rang out.

"Whoosh."

Immediately afterward, a saber pierced through the darkness. Just like a burning sun, it emitted endless heat and flames, shining brightly, dispersing all darkness and corpse energy.

230. Three Sabers Merge into One

"Slay!"

Lin Fei's voice was cold, carrying a hint of killing intent.

Immediately, the hundreds of meters long saber in the void emitted surging flames, falling from the sky and slicing onto the eight zombies.

"Boom".

The raging flames were burning madly. Flame Burning Heaven Saber! Although it was just a saber technique, under the impetus of saber essence and saber momentum, this saber seemed to really have the power of burning heavens and boiling seas.

Moreover, Lin Fei used most of his saber essence to execute this saber. Therefore, the power of this saber was beyond belief. Of course, the key point was that the Flame Burning Heaven Saber carried flames, which could precisely restrain these zombies.

Otherwise, just in terms of the power of the saber technique, Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique, and Holy Spirit Saber Technique, none of them were inferior to Flame Burning Heaven Saber. But when facing the eight zombies, Flame Burning Heaven Saber undoubtedly could play a stronger role.

As this saber fell, endless flames, seemed to fill the entire void.

The Yin Qi and corpse Qi on the eight zombies, under this saber, seemed to have all turned into fuel for the fire, thereby enhancing the fire, burning even more fiercely.

"No...Come back to me!"

The expression on the mysterious Foundation Establishment True Person was twisting, madly forming hand seals, wanting to recall the eight zombies. After all, this was his only hope of crossing the tribulation. He had gone through all kinds of hardships to find the eight martial saints who were born on Yin days, only then would he be able to form the Nine Yin Zombie Array to help him resist the heavenly tribulation.

He even risked coming to Tianqi Country, under the eyes of the Ancient Origin Sect, to undertake this risky task. It was because there were enough Martial Saints in the Imperial City of the Tianqi Country only then was it possible to find Martial Saints born on Yin days.

Originally, he was about to succeed. He was short of only one zombie. Just give him a little more time, he would be able to successfully gather nine zombies born on Yin days and thus achieve great success!

But everything was ruined. The arrival of this Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect, not only did it expose him ahead of time, it even destroyed his eight zombies. Now, he had no hope of crossing the tribulation. For a top Foundation Establishment True Person, the most important thing is to cross the tribulation!

For the purpose of crossing the tribulation, these top Foundation Establishment True Persons could do anything at any cost! But, if anyone ruins their hope of crossing the tribulation, then they would immediately become insane.

"You destroyed my hope of crossing the tribulation! You destroyed my Dao! Then let the entire Imperial City accompany me in burial!"

This top Foundation Establishment True Person, his Magic Body's spiritual power vibrated.

"Boom."

Immediately, above the entire Imperial City, a huge Spiritual Qi cloud gathered. Like a huge vortex.

At this moment, Lin Fei didn't make a move. Because voices were echoing in his mind.

"Your Flame Burning Heaven Saber, having slain the Yin-Evil Martial Saint zombie, comprehended the Supreme Yang state, cultivation progress increased by 100%."

"Your Flame Burning Heaven Saber has broken through to transcendence!"

Lin Fei's Flame Burning Heaven Saber, unexpectedly, had reached transcendence at this time.

"Supreme Yang state?"

Lin Fei closed his eyes. A piece of memory also appeared in his mind. With a slight organization, he immediately understood the so-called Supreme Yang state. However, that top Foundation Establishment True Person was trying to cast a terrifying spell that could destroy heaven and earth. He had gathered such a terrifying Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth.

"Suppress!"

Lin Fei's saber momentum suddenly contracted. A terrifying suppressing power suddenly all fell on that Foundation Establishment True Person.

Immediately, the Foundation Establishment True Person's expression changed. His whole body was trembling. Obviously, he was enduring tremendous pressure. However, the talisman in front of him was truly miraculous. It could actually withstand Lin Fei's suppressing saber momentum.

"It's useless, with my Void Talisman here. Even if your saber momentum is stronger, it won't affect me. Unless it's a Limit Martial Saint, otherwise, no one can kill me! Today, all of you will die!"

The Foundation Establishment True Person's expression twisted, his demeanor was like madness.

"Is that so?"

Lin Fei's expression was still calm.

Qiu Long and Li Yuan, looking at the huge Spiritual Qi cloud in the sky, were almost in despair. Such a terrifying Spiritual Qi cloud, once a spell was cast, how strong would the power of that spell be? Even if a Martial Saint could barely resist it without dying. But what about ordinary people? The entire Imperial City, with a population of millions. Now, they are probably all going to die under this terrifying spell.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei flicked his finger. The hundreds of meters long Flame Burning Heaven Saber was suspended in the void.

"Shoo."

Another saber essence. The hundreds of meters long Holy Spirit Saber also appeared in the void.

"Shoo."

A rainbow light flashed past. That was the hundreds of meters long Rainbow Transformation Saber.

Each saber emanated a formidable heavenly might, all reaching hundreds of meters!

"Unite, three sabers as one!"

The thought flitted through Lin Fei's mind. Instantaneously, the three terrifying heavenly sabers merged into one. They formed an imposing heavenly saber, reaching one thousand meters high. Near this heavenly saber, even the void itself seemed to birth a multitude of dark lines. These were fractures in the fabric of space!

"Slay!"

With a single slash, Lin Fei struck down. This fusion of three sabers was even more powerful than the last, several times over. Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique was advancing rapidly. Though he hadn't broken through, his saber essence was continually increasing, and at a breakneck pace. The power of Lin Fei's united three sabers depended on his saber essence and saber momentum. The stronger the saber essence, the greater the power of the saber!

As Lin Fei slashed his saber, the void itself seemed to be rent open by the blade. Every person within the imperial city looked skyward, their eyes drawn to the void. The awe-inspiring heavenly saber elicited a feeling akin to suffocation. This saber was no longer of the mortal realm!

"Mere martial saint yet to reach the limit, how could you possibly wield such a saber?"

The Foundation Establishment True Person, driven to madness, was suddenly stirred to lucidity by the stimulation of the endless saber points. However, it was too late. The saber descended mercilessly, striking his Void Talisman. The Void Talisman flickered wildly, even sending out ripples. But, after just a moment, the spiritual light on the talisman dimmed.

"Snap."

The talisman shattered, instantly turned to ashes by the saber essence. A trace of fear flashed across the eyes of the Foundation Establishment True Person. Despite his madness, he didn't want to die. If this saber fell, his death would be certain!

"No..."

The Foundation Establishment True Person let out a horrified scream.

"Boom."

In the next moment, the saber fell. The entire coffin shop, and even the whole street, was instantly turned to ashes. Not ruins, but truly ashes, completely annihilated by the terrifying saber essence. There was no corpse left, not even a trace of blood.

The entire imperial city was eerily silent. Everyone was staring blankly at the void and the powerful saber. The Foundation Establishment True Person was dead! The once frenzied, Foundation Establishment True Person, who was on the brink of a breakthrough, had been ground to dust under Lin Fei's terrifying saber. Even the Spiritual Qi cloud in the void gradually dissipated until it vanished without a trace.

With the fall of the Foundation Establishment True Person and the collapse of the aura cloud, the void, which turned pitch black by the shadowy and necrotic air, brightened again. A ray of warm sunlight fell on everyone's faces.

"This saber..."

Qiu Long and Li Yuan were so shocked they couldn't utter a word. Even if they had been in the Ancient Origin Sect, they had never seen a martial saint unleash such terrifying power.

Was this the power of a top martial saint? Clearly, it was a power of a Limit Martial Saint! Even an average Limit Martial Saint might not have such terrifying power. Only a martial saint who had condensed the Spirit Flower and evolved his martial arts to perfection could potentially unleash such a terrifying saber.

"Something must have happened in the Ancient Origin Sect that caused Outer Sect Elder Lin Fei..."

The two men understood very well that a man like Lin Fei couldn't remain nameless. But they hadn't heard of him. It could only mean one thing: they were out of touch with the Ancient Origin Sect, and maybe something major had happened there recently.

"Mission accomplished. Remember to report to the Ancient Origin Sect. I need to go back to debrief on the mission."

Lin Fei didn't seem particularly shocked. He looked quite calm. He was more concerned about the ten thousand contribution points from the sect mission.

"Elder Lin..."

Qiu Long wanted to say something more, but Lin Fei had already taken a step, transforming into a streak of light that disappeared into the horizon.

231. The higher the profile, the more important it is

Ancient Origin Sect, Task Hall.

"Elder, I have completed the mission of the Imperial City disappearance case."

Lin Fei arrived at the Task Hall, ready to hand over the mission.

The elder of the Task Hall opened his eyes. A glint flashed in his eyes.

"We have already received the details of the situation. You did well on this mission, and the Imperial Family has highly praised you. However, do you know the identity of that top Foundation Establishment True Person?"

Looking at the gaze of the elder of the Task Hall, Lin Fei's eyes slightly narrowed. He began to contemplate.

In fact, Lin Fei had thought a lot. After seeing that top Foundation Establishment True Person, Lin Fei knew that person was definitely not an unknown individual. He must be a Foundation Establishment True Person from some major sect. Otherwise, for a typical independent cultivator, it's already a fluke to successfully establish the foundation. Let alone reach the point where one can overcome the tribulation.

That's impossible! He must be a Foundation Establishment True Person from one of the major sects of the immortal gate. His identity was probably extraordinary.

But Lin Fei killed him anyway! Even without hesitation. He was a Foundation Establishment True Person from a major sect of the immortal gate. So was he, an outer sect elder of the Ancient Origin Sect, a decoration?

Lin Fei directly responded, "Is the identity important? He was in the Imperial City of Tianqi Country, capturing Martial Saints to make zombies. No matter who he is, this is something that the Ancient Origin Sect does not allow. I killed him to uphold the dignity of the Ancient Origin Sect!"

Lin Fei's words made the elder reveal a hint of a smile.

"Well said, no matter who it is, if they commit a crime in the Tianqi Country, they are challenging the authority of the Ancient Origin Sect! Of course he should be killed! That Foundation Establishment True Person was from the Profound Light Cave Heaven, a sect no less prestigious than our Ancient Origin Sect.

His name‘s Xuan Yun, one of the top Foundation Establishment True Persons of the Profound Light Cave Heaven. He was nearing the end of his lifespan and was preparing to draw down the heavenly tribulation in an attempt to achieve the Golden Core. But in fact, his chance of success was minuscule. Otherwise, he would have overcome the tribulation long ago, why wait until now?

And what's more, in order to overcome the tribulation, he even used a forbidden method, secretly capturing Martial Saints in the territory of our Ancient Origin Sect to make zombies. He intended to set up the Nine Yin Zombie Array. Hmph, he didn't even think about it. Even if he really set up the Nine Yin Zombie Array, how could he truly overcome the heavenly tribulation? It was nothing more than wishful thinking.

You killed him, the Profound Light Cave Heaven has nothing to say. Moreover, this time, you also upheld the dignity of the Ancient Origin Sect. Therefore, in addition to the 10,000 contribution points from the imperial family's mission reward, the sect will reward you with an additional 10,000 contribution points. That's a total of 20,000 contribution points."

Lin Fei's eyes brightened.

"20,000 contribution points?"

Lin Fei was a bit surprised. The imperial family gave 10,000 contribution points. The other 10,000 contribution points were rewards given to Lin Fei by the sect. It's said that it was a reward for Lin Fei for upholding the dignity of the sect. But, the dignity of the Ancient Origin Sect, did it really need him, an outer sect elder, to uphold?

That Xuan Yun, even in the Imperial City of Tianqi Country, was always cautious, not daring to be discovered by the Ancient Origin Sect. Where would he dare to challenge the dignity of the Ancient Origin Sect?

For a moment, Lin Fei thought of a possibility. Among the inner disciples or true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect, there had always been a rumor circulating.

The Task Hall elder said to his colleague, "We have to admit, the boy does have potential."

His colleague responded, "Indeed. With the way he handled the mission and his performance in the sect, it's clear that he has a high chance of reaching the peak of Martial Saints."

The first elder chuckled, "Well, seems that our Ancient Origin Sect will have another promising disciple in the future."

His colleague nodded and said, "Yes, let's see how far he can go."

The elders watched as Lin Fei's figure disappeared from the Task Hall. Meanwhile, Lin Fei was feeling very happy with his reward. He realized that the Ancient Origin Sect had a very unique way of cultivating their disciples. They took care of their disciples in subtle ways without making it obvious, thus maintaining fairness within the sect.

The Ancient Origin Sect didn't directly give resources or favor to disciples with potential, instead, they utilized their system of missions and rewards to provide extra help. This method not only encouraged the disciples to work harder but also helped to increase their sense of belonging to the sect. This was an important reason why the Ancient Origin Sect could continue to prosper. The sect knew the heart of people well and applied it to their management method.

As for whether Lin Fei could reach the level of the peak Martial Saint, that would depend on his future performance. But for now, Lin Fei had already proven his worth and potential to the sect. As he walked away from the Task Hall, Lin Fei couldn't help but feel a sense of anticipation for his future in the Ancient Origin Sect.

As soon as the Essence Enhancement Pill entered Lin Fei's body, it began to dissolve, releasing a large amount of pure and rich energy. Lin Fei instantly mobilized his cultivation method to absorb and refine these energies.

In his Dantian, the Spiritual Sea began to ripple and churn as the Spiritual Qi from the Essence Enhancement Pill was poured into it. The Spiritual Qi was refined and converted into martial energy, which began to circulate around his body, strengthening his meridians and nourishing his body.

Lin Fei could feel his cultivation level rising steadily. The barrier to the middle stage of Martial Saint seemed to be getting thinner and thinner.

With his concentration completely immersed in cultivation, Lin Fei lost all sense of time. He continued to consume Essence Enhancement Pills one after another, absorbing the released Spiritual Qi to increase his cultivation level.

Finally, after an unknown period of time, a powerful energy explosion occurred within Lin Fei's body. The barrier to the middle stage of Martial Saint was broken through, and his cultivation level successfully reached the middle stage of Martial Saint.

But Lin Fei didn't stop there. He continued to take the Essence Enhancement Pills, aiming to reach the late stage of Martial Saint. As he continued his cultivation, the Spiritual Qi within his body became denser and denser, and his cultivation level continued to rise steadily.

With the help of the Essence Enhancement Pills, Lin Fei could clearly feel his strength growing at a terrifying speed. The desire for strength in his heart grew stronger and stronger.

"I will not stop until I reach the perfection stage of Martial Saint and form my Qi Flower!" Lin Fei declared to himself, his determination unwavering. With this goal in mind, he continued to consume the Essence Enhancement Pills, immersing himself in his cultivation journey.

232. Crazy Upgrade

With each Essence Enhancement Pill, Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique was able to refine in one day. One pill could improve the training progress of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique by 4%.

So, in his cave dwelling, Lin Fei declined all visitors and started taking Essence Enhancement Pills.

One day, two days, three days...

In the blink of an eye, fourteen days had passed. Lin Fei had already taken fourteen Essence Enhancement Pills, and the cultivation progress of his True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had increased by 56%.

"Boom."

The next moment, Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique reached 100%. He felt a sense of immense joy as he had finally made a breakthrough. The True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had broken through to the middle stage, causing his saber essence to soar several times over! And all he had used up were fourteen Essence Enhancement Pills.

"Continue."

Lin Fei didn't stop his cultivation. After all, he had only consumed a mere fourteen Essence Enhancement Pills. This time, he used his contribution points to buy a whole two hundred Essence Enhancement Pills. His goal was not just to reach the mid-stage of Martial Saint.

Thus, Lin Fei continued to take an Essence Enhancement Pill. Still refining one pill per day. However, when he refined a pill, Lin Fei noted the effects of the Essence Enhancement Pill. One pill could only improve the cultivation progress of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique by 2%. The effect was halved.

Lin Fei estimated that this was related to his increased cultivation level and the fact that the more pills he took, the less effective they would become.

2% cultivation progress seemed small but in reality? It was quite a lot. After all, if he didn't take any pills at this time and only relied on the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique to "work hard" every day, even if he didn't stop, he wouldn't be able to improve his cultivation progress by 1%. This is due to the higher cultivation level requiring more saber essence, resulting in slow cultivation progress.

However, if he took Essence Enhancement Pills, he would only need fifty pills to make another breakthrough. Thus, Lin Fei closed his eyes again and continued to take the Essence Enhancement Pills.

Ten days, twenty days, thirty days, forty days, fifty days...

After fifty days, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique within Lin Fei's body shook violently. Following this, the saber essence in his body soared once more.

"Boom."

A terrifying aura radiated from Lin Fei's body. This time, he didn't exert any saber momentum. The mere power of his own saber essence was terrifying to such an extent, it was unthinkable.

This time, Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique directly reached the late stage! His cultivation level also reached the late stage of Martial Saint!

From the early stage of Martial Saint to the late stage of Martial Saint, from the previous fourteen days to the current fifty days, Lin Fei only took sixty-four days, almost two months' time.

The saber essence in Lin Fei's body had already soared to a terrifying extent. Originally, his saber essence was much deeper than the True Essence of a Martial Saint at the same level.

Now, Lin Fei even had a feeling that he could try to condense the Qi Flower! Of course, this was just an illusion. Like his physical body, although it was very strong, it was still far from reaching the limit of Energy Flower. At least, if he tried to condense the Qi Flower now, the probability of Lin Fei failing was very high! Once failed, it could even harm his foundation or lead to more severe consequences. He might never be able to condense the Qi Flower.

Thus, the Saber Essence that Lin Fei possessed was indeed considerable. However, Lin Fei had not yet entertained the thought of condensing a Qi Flower. He had to ensure complete success, only then would he opt to condense the Qi Flower.

In condensing the Qi Flower, if he were to guarantee absolute success, the best choice, of course, was to elevate the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique to a state of perfection!

Once the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique reached perfection, the Saber Essence of Lin Fei would, without a doubt, surge to a terrifying extent. When the time came to attempt the condensation of the Qi Flower, success was bound to be within his grasp!

Thus, Lin Fei's attention returned to the Essence Enhancement Pills.

"There are still one hundred and thirty-six Essence Enhancement Pills. There are many, but I wonder if they would still have an effect after reaching the latter stages of Martial Saint? Or, is the effect greatly diminished?"

Lin Fei did not hesitate for long. One could only know by trying. Hence, Lin Fei ingested another Essence Enhancement Pill.

A day later, Lin Fei opened his eyes. He examined the progression of his practice of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. This time, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had only improved by 1%.

Nevertheless, Lin Fei was delighted beyond measure.

"Not bad, even though the effects have halved once again. An effect of 1% is already quite good, even exceeding my expectations. At this rate, it would only require one hundred days, roughly over three months. For the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique to break through again, reaching perfection! Once perfection is achieved, I can attempt to condense the Qi Flower!"

A glint of determination flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. Such was the benefit of "contribution points". As long as one had a sufficient number of contribution points, a substantial amount of resources could be exchanged. In certain aspects, when resources were abundant, it could truly save a lot of time and energy.

Hence, Lin Fei hesitated no more. He continued to consume the Essence Enhancement Pills.

One month, two months, three months... Just this once, Lin Fei's seclusion had been longer than ever before. For more than three whole months, Lin Fei remained motionless within his cave. Even considering the additional two months prior, Lin Fei had almost been in practice for over five months!

"Boom."

After Lin Fei had consumed another hundred Essence Enhancement Pills, His True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique broke through once more. Progressing directly from the late stages of Martial Saint to the state of Martial Saint perfection. Moreover, his internal Saber Essence experienced a dramatic increase, surging several-fold in an instant.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"System."

Without a second thought, Lin Fei promptly called upon the system to examine the state of his martial prowess.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Late Stage Martial Saint

True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique: Perfection

Blood Essence Nine Transformations: Seventh Transformation (Progress 12%)

Holy Spirit Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress 58%)

Flame Burning Heaven Saber: Transcendence (Progress 65%)

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique: Transcendence (Progress 10%)

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had already reached perfection. Even the progress meter behind had vanished. This indicated an inability to further advance. Even consuming more elixirs would prove futile.

However, Lin Fei noted, even though the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had reached perfection, in terms of the realm, Lin Fei remained in the late stage of Martial Saint. He had not yet reached the Limit Martial Saint.

In truth, this was because Lin Fei had yet to condense a Qi Flower. Only upon condensing at least one of the three flowers could one be termed a Limit Martial Saint!

Lin Fei had only achieved perfection in his technique, he had not yet condensed the Qi Flower.

"Only thirty-six Essence Enhancement Pills remain. Seems their effectiveness is waning."

Lin Fei murmured under his breath. There was no need to fear the Essence Enhancement Pills were wasted, unused ones could be returned and exchanged back into contribution points.

The Ancient Origin Sect was quite considerate in this aspect. Of course, some intended to exploit this, procuring their own elixirs from outside, to "return" to Exchange Treasure Pavilion, acquiring contribution points.

Once such a scheme was confirmed, one might even be expelled from the Ancient Origin Sect. No one would risk the greater picture for such small exploits.

Lin Fei was not overly concerned about the thirty-six Essence Enhancement Pills, they could be returned at any time. What Lin Fei was more focused on was his cultivation. The True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique had reached perfection and the Saber Essence had surged to an inconceivable extent.

At this moment, Lin Fei was confident he could condense the Qi Flower. Upon a Martial Saint condensing a Qi Flower, they would be a Limit Martial Saint!

If one were a true disciple, they could instantly become a Martial Sovereign candidate, enjoying the best resources in the Ancient Origin Sect. Their status would be of the highest esteem.

Although Lin Fei was not a true disciple, once he had condensed the Qi Flower, his status and standing would undoubtedly be elevated. Let alone, the Ancient Origin Sect always valued Martial Saints with potential. The more exceptional Lin Fei's performance, the more attention he would receive from the Ancient Origin Sect.

Considering Lin Fei's time in the Ancient Origin Sect, in total, it might only be half a year. Condensing the Qi Flower so quickly, Was it not too swift? This concern was completely needless for Lin Fei.

In the Ancient Origin Sect, some even stumbled upon fortunate encounters, emerging from Martial Saint and condensing a Qi Flower within just ten days. Half a year for Lin Fei was indeed considered quite a length. Of course, that's the most exceptional geniuses throughout history.

In the current Ancient Origin Sect, being able to condense a Qi Flower within half a year indeed marked one as an unparalleled, top-notch genius. This was beyond doubt.

"To condense the Qi Flower, I need a tremendous amount of Heaven and Earth Spiritual Qi. Therefore, I must go to a specific place. Seems I need to make a trip to the Spiritual Qi Pool!"

Lin Fei knew that there were some special places within the Ancient Origin Sect. For instance, the Spiritual Qi Pool. It was reserved for those Martial Saints preparing to condense a Qi Flower.

Lin Fei did not hesitate in the least. He rose to his feet directly, transforming into a streak of light in an instant, soaring toward the Spiritual Qi Pool.

233. Spiritual Qi Pool

The Spiritual Qi Pool, as the name implies, is a pool made up of Spiritual Qi. However, it's not merely Spiritual Qi within this pool but Spiritual Essence! That is to say, Spiritual Qi is continuously compressed, finally becoming a liquid, bound within the Spiritual Qi Pool. This involves not merely a simple array, but also some treasures containing rich Spiritual Qi. In short, this Spiritual Qi Pool is precious to the Ancient Origin Sect. It is one of the Sect's important locations.

The Ancient Origin Sect expended considerable effort to construct this Spiritual Qi Pool. The fundamental goal was to assist the Martial Saints within the sect to successfully condense the Qi Flower.

When Lin Fei arrived outside the Spiritual Qi Pool, there were not many people there. After all, the Spiritual Qi Pool was for condensing the Qi Flower. How many Martial Saints within the whole Ancient Origin Sect are qualified to condense a Qi Flower?

However, to maintain the consumption of the Spiritual Qi Pool, it was also open to inner disciples and true disciples. The reason is simple. These inner disciples and true disciples, either innate or martial saints, have certain requirements for Spiritual Qi, and though not as great as those Qi cultivators, there is still a demand.

The wealthier ones could spend contribution points to cultivate within the Spiritual Qi Pool. Cultivating here, the results would be twice as effective with half the effort. But it's expensive! One day requires a thousand contribution points. Therefore, the martial artists who can come to the Spiritual Qi Pool all seize every minute to cultivate.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei arrived outside the Spiritual Qi Pool. Many disciples saw Lin Fei and also recognized him. After all, Lin Fei was not an unknown person in the Ancient Origin Sect now. He was the one who defeated Ao Yunxiao under everyone's watch, He was a prominent figure in the Ancient Origin Sect. Moreover, Lin Fei was a "Dao Seeker." Therefore, when he arrived, all eyes were focused on him.

"Isn't that Elder Lin, the 'Dao Seeker'?"

"Elder Lin has actually come to the Spiritual Qi Pool."

"He's only in the early stage of Martial Saint, having just arrived at the Ancient Origin Sect about half a year ago, does he already need the aid of the Spiritual Qi Pool for cultivation?"

"Elder Lin has an extraordinary understanding of saber momentum. However, he doesn't seem to have anything particularly outstanding in physical cultivation and True Essence. Therefore, spending contribution points to come to the Spiritual Qi Pool to assist with True Essence cultivation seems normal."

Many people knew about Lin Fei's past. They knew Lin Fei was a "Dao Seeker". He had joined the Ancient Origin Sect for only half a year. And he was merely in the early stage of Martial Saint.

How much could he improve in half a year? They didn't think much about it. Instead, they assumed that Lin Fei was here to cultivate using the Spiritual Qi Pool. After all, cultivating in the Spiritual Qi Pool gives one twice the result with half the effort, and it's much more efficient.

Lin Fei did not pay attention to the discussions of others. He walked straight into the Spiritual Qi Pool. There was more than one Spiritual Qi Pool. There were nine.

There is a difference among these nine Spiritual Qi Pools. There is one located in the best spot. Its Spiritual Essence is the densest. But regular disciples can't go in and even ordinary Martial Saints can't go in. Even if they spend contribution points, they can't go in. Because this Spiritual Qi Pool is for those Martial Saints who are condensing the Qi Flower and it doesn't cost any contribution points. But once one enters the Spiritual Qi Pool, he must try to condense the Qi Flower.

This rule deters most people. And no one would try to exploit loopholes. After all, once one enters this Spiritual Qi Pool, he must condense the Qi Flower. If he doesn't attempt to condense, he will be severely punished!

There was no one in this Spiritual Qi Pool at the moment. After all, in the whole Ancient Origin Sect, there are very few instances of two people attempting to condense the Qi Flower at the same time. Most of the time, this Spiritual Qi Pool is empty. Now was the same.

However, when Lin Fei headed straight for that one Spiritual Qi Pool, the elder who was guarding the Spiritual Qi Pool had already blocked Lin Fei's path.

"The Spiritual Qi Pool, one thousand contribution points for one day's use."

The Martial Saint Elder spoke calmly.

"Do I also need to spend contribution points to use that highest Spiritual Qi Pool?"

Lin Fei asked.

"Hm?"

The elder raised an eyebrow. He examined Lin Fei carefully from head to toe. Seemingly, he realized something.

"You are the 'Dao Seeker' Lin Fei, I recognize you. You defeated Ao Yunxiao, and your understanding of saber momentum is indeed strong. But you've only been in the Ancient Origin Sect for half a year. Even if you've been cultivating True Essence all this time, how far could your cultivation have progressed? If you forcefully try to condense the Qi Flower and fail, it could even damage your foundation, making it impossible for you to condense it in the future."

The Martial Saint Elder was also reminding Lin Fei. Going to that Spiritual Qi Pool, one must condense the Qi Flower.

"Please open the Spiritual Qi Pool for me, elder."

Lin Fei's tone was still calm. But it was filled with unwavering determination. The elder didn't try to persuade him any further. After all, whether or not to condense the Qi Flower was Lin Fei's own choice.

So Lin Fei passed the elder directly. He entered the highest-located Spiritual Qi Pool.

The disciples around who were originally cultivating hard all opened their eyes one by one, looking at Lin Fei in surprise.

"That... That is the Spiritual Qi Pool for breakthroughs, Elder Lin is going there, is he trying to condense the Qi Flower?"

"So Elder Lin didn't come to cultivate with the help of the Spiritual Qi Pool, but to try to condense the Qi Flower. But, he just joined the Ancient Origin Sect half a year ago, can he condense the Qi Flower?"

"Even if Elder Lin's talent is high. How much True Essence can he cultivate in half a year? If he fails to condense the Qi Flower, it will damage his foundation."

"Elder Lin is too impatient. Energy Flower, Qi Flower, Spirit Flower. Among these three flowers, the Spirit Flower is the hardest. But Elder Lin has already transcended in saber momentum, he has a great chance to condense the Spirit Flower first. When the time comes, wouldn't it be better to slowly condense the Essence Flower and Qi Flower, with the guarantee of successful condensation? He's being too rash."

Many disciples were somewhat puzzled. Lin Fei was trying to condense the Qi Flower so early. This is very hard to succeed. Did Lin Fei think that condensing the Qi Flower was easy? Or was Lin Fei too confident? Almost everyone was surprised and puzzled by Lin Fei's choice to condense the Qi Flower now. They even felt it was a pity.

But Lin Fei didn't hesitate at all. His expression was still calm. Step by step, he came to the front of this Spiritual Qi Pool.

Lin Fei looked down. Inside the Spiritual Qi Pool, the green Spiritual Essence filled the whole pool. Moreover, around the Spiritual Qi Pool, there were at least dozens of array formations densely packed, keeping the Spiritual Essence fixed within the pool.

These array formations were set up by the Foundation Establishment True Persons who were invited. Presumably, the Ancient Origin Sect also paid a heavy price. Only with these dense array formations could they firmly fix that Spiritual Essence inside the Spiritual Qi Pool.

Lin Fei took a deep breath. Then, without hesitation, he jumped directly into the Spiritual Qi Pool. With a "plop", Lin Fei had already fallen into the Spiritual Qi Pool. Suddenly, a large amount of Spiritual Essence surrounded him. They desperately tried to drill into Lin Fei's body.

If one cultivates here, the efficiency would increase at least tenfold, or even higher! No wonder so many innate martial artists or Martial Saints were willing to spend a thousand or even several thousand contribution points. However, Lin Fei did not come to the Spiritual Qi Pool to cultivate. He was preparing to condense the Qi Flower.

Lin Fei closed his eyes. He slowly adjusted his state. He could sense numerous gazes around him were focused on him, but Lin Fei didn't care. He slowly calmed his mind. His thoughts gradually calmed down as well.

It's not known how long it had been.

"Whoosh".

Lin Fei opened his eyes. His eyes were as calm as an ancient well. Clearly, he had completely adjusted his mood. Moreover, having soaked in such precious Spiritual Essence for such a long time, his body was also almost adjusted to its best condition!

"Let's start."

Lin Fei took a deep breath, no longer suppressing the True Essence in his body.

"Boom".

The next moment, Lin Fei's True Essence exploded from within his body. A terrifying aura emanated from him, instantly enveloping the entire Spiritual Qi Pool.

234. Limit Martial Saint

Lin Fei sat cross-legged in the Spiritual Qi Pool in a calm manner. A large amount of Spiritual Essence was frantically trying to drill into Lin Fei's body.

Lin Fei's True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique was operating. Terrifying saber essence emanated. Its power instantly covered the entire Spiritual Qi Pool.

Suddenly, everyone in the Spiritual Qi Pool, whether they were disciples or elders, even the top-tier Martial Saints, all felt a terrifying pressure. This wasn't the pressure of saber momentum. It was completely different from saber momentum. It was purely the pressure of True Essence. Or to put it another way, it was the pressure of Lin Fei's saber essence!

Just this pressure alone made many disciples in the Spiritual Qi Pool feel as if they were unable to breathe.

"This aura... has the cultivation technique reached perfection?"

"Such terrifying True Essence, there can be no mistake. Elder Lin must have perfected a technique for cultivating True Essence. Otherwise, it's impossible to have such a terrifying pressure of True Essence."

"How long has Elder Lin been in the Ancient Origin Sect? It's only about half a year at most. How could he have perfected a cultivation technique?"

"Incredible, it's truly incredible! I originally thought Elder Lin was just talented in saber momentum, a natural Saber Saint. I didn't expect that in the cultivation of True Essence, Elder Lin is also a top-tier genius."

"Could Elder Lin really be able to condense the Qi Flower?"

Many disciples were uncertain. Their hearts were filled with shock. They had cultivated for decades, even a hundred years. and they might not be able to reach the point of condensing the Qi Flower.

But what about Lin Fei? It was just a mere half a year. The elders of the Spiritual Qi Pool also immediately changed their expressions.

"All of you leave the Spiritual Qi Pool immediately and go outside. Otherwise, under such great pressure, you won't be able to cultivate. As for the contribution points you've paid, you can continue to cultivate in the Spiritual Qi Pool after Elder Lin finishes condensing the Qi Flower."

Actually, without the elder's words, many disciples also got up and left the Spiritual Qi Pool. Under these circumstances, they simply couldn't cultivate at all. Continuing to stay in the Spiritual Qi Pool was just a waste of time. So, the disciples inside the Spiritual Qi Pool all left the Spiritual Qi Pool one after another and came outside.

However, from the outside, they could still see the situation inside the Spiritual Qi Pool. Almost all the disciples did not leave. The elders didn't stop them either. As long as they weren't noisy and didn't affect Lin Fei's condensation of the Qi Flower. After all, being able to witness a Martial Saint condensing a Qi Flower with their own eyes and seeing the whole process would be of some help to them when they tried to condense a Qi Flower in the future.

Even, some disciples started to send messages to each other. They notified their friends one after another.

"Get to the Spiritual Qi Pool quickly. Outer Sect Elder Lin Fei is about to condense the Qi Flower."

"It's absolutely true, hurry up."

"'Dao Seeker' Elder Lin, is trying to condense the Qi Flower half a year after defeating Ao Yunxiao. It would be a pity to miss this opportunity."

Inside the Ancient Origin Sect. the distance is very close and there are array methods that are interconnected. Therefore, they can communicate with each other.

For a time, many disciples came to the Spiritual Qi Pool. Innate martial artists, Martial Saints, and so on. Even some of the top-tier Martial Saints also came to the Spiritual Qi Pool upon hearing the news.

After all, compared to the ordinary disciples who came to watch the excitement, these top-tier Martial Saints were the most qualified to condense the Qi Flower.

The number of people outside was increasing. But Lin Fei in the Spiritual Qi Pool was not disturbed at all. He didn't pay attention to the situation around him. His entire attention was on himself. Especially the saber essence within his body.

The True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique kept operating. Because he had devoured a Martial Saint-level technique. Therefore, Lin Fei naturally knew how to condense the Qi Flower. A large amount of saber essence was surging and spouting out of his body. At the same time, Spiritual Essence drilled into his body, trying to transform into saber essence.

However, it was of no use. The saber essence in Lin Fei's body had already reached its limit. The greater use of this Spiritual Essence was to help Lin Fei compensate for some of the losses caused by condensing the Qi Flower. The saber essence within Lin Fei's body had completely emanated from his body and gradually started to condense above his head.

"Let's begin."

Lin Fei took a deep breath. He immediately took over control of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique. According to the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique, he activated the method to condense the Qi Flower.

"Boom".

Immediately, the vast saber essence around Lin Fei actually started to expand frantically, continuing to expand. Finally, it exploded with a loud bang. With the explosion of the saber essence, terrifying power was shaking.

However, at the same time, the countless exploding saber essence above Lin Fei's head faintly condensed into a flower.

Qi Flower!

Lin Fei very smoothly condensed the Qi Flower! It was as easy as eating and drinking. Too easy!

Lin Fei even thought about the possible troubles he might encounter. But he didn't encounter any of them. The phrase "when water flows, a channel is formed" couldn't help but emerge in Lin Fei's mind.

Yes, Lin Fei now felt, condensing the Qi Flower was like water flowing into a channel.

In fact, Lin Fei felt that even if he didn't do it in the Spiritual Qi Pool, he could still condense the Qi Flower.

Too easy! But is condensing the Qi Flower really that easy? Just look at the stunned disciples outside with shocked expressions. Some top-tier Martial Saints had tried to condense the Qi Flower. Unfortunately, they failed. It took them many years to slowly recover. Therefore, they knew very well how difficult it was to condense the Qi Flower. But now they saw Lin Fei actually did it in one go. The whole process was too smooth.

There were no twists and turns, even more, there were no earth-shaking moments. Just like nature, everything falls into place. The Martial Saints who understood the significance of this couldn't help but feel a tremor in their hearts!

"This is the real meaning of 'when water flows, a channel is formed'! When the True Essence reaches a certain level of profoundness, the condensation of Qi Flower is as natural as water flowing into a channel, without any difficulty. I didn't believe it before, but now seeing Elder Lin condensing the Qi Flower, I believe it..."

"So, it can be so easy to condense a Qi Flower."

"Easy? Even if one practices the technique to perfection, it's not necessarily easy to condense a Qi Flower. It can only be said that the technique Elder Lin has practiced must be sophisticated. Moreover, the level of True Essence in Elder Lin's body is unimaginable, far surpassing other top Martial Saints."

"Does this mean that our Ancient Origin Sect has given birth to another Limit Martial Saint? And he is an outer sect elder?"

"Worthy of being a 'Dao Seeker', not only is his combat power amazing, but even in terms of cultivation, his talent is not inferior to any true disciple."

"Elder Lin is now ranked as a Martial Sovereign seed, and his potential is even greater than other Martial Sovereign seeds..."

Many disciples had serious expressions. A hint of excitement flashed in their eyes. When water flows, a channel is formed! Although it was difficult, Lin Fei had proven it. When the True Essence reaches a certain level of profoundness, one can truly naturally condense a Qi Flower.

There is no need to rely on luck. Otherwise, if the True Essence is not profound enough, forcing oneself to condense a Qi Flower can only rely on luck! And even if one condenses a Qi Flower, there is still a difference.

Like Lin Fei, with such a profound level of True Essence, once a Qi Flower is condensed, True Essence will surge. Even among Limit Martial Saints, the level of True Essence might vary greatly.

What's more important is that condensing a Qi Flower is not the end. On the contrary, it's just the beginning. To become a Martial Sovereign, one must unite the three flowers. If the Qi Flower is strong enough, obviously, the chance of becoming a Martial Sovereign can greatly increase.

At this moment, the Qi Flower appeared above Lin Fei's head. At the same time, the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique within Lin Fei's body began to crazily absorb the spiritual essence. A large amount of spiritual essence was absorbed into his body, quickly transforming into saber essence.

One time, three times, five times, ten times...

In just a moment, the amount of saber essence in Lin Fei's body surged and increased by more than ten times in an instant. Such a terrifying increase, no wonder Limit Martial Saints are powerful on a different level. It's a world apart from ordinary Martial Saints.

"Splash."

Lin Fei stood up directly from the Spiritual Qi Pool.

"Boom."

The Qi Flower above Lin Fei's head emerged again. Moreover, the shadow of the Qi Flower immediately reflected in the sky above the Spiritual Qi Pool, forming a huge flower. Grand and impressive, like a huge cloud.

All the martial artists under the coverage of the Qi Flower. Whether they were innate martial artists or Martial Saints, everyone felt that the True Qi, the True Essence in their bodies seemed to be under great pressure. This Qi Flower actually had a similar ability to suppress opponents like martial momentum. It just targeted True Essence and True Qi.

At this moment, no one doubted anymore. Lin Fei had condensed the Qi Flower. He truly reached the pinnacle of Martial Saints, becoming a Limit Martial Saint!

A note from RighteousEgg

After months of building up, the Patreon chapters are over 60!

235. Have a Reputation Far and Wide

"He did it!"

Lin Fei retracted his Qi Flower. The momentum gradually disappeared. This time, although it was a bit different from what he had imagined, as long as he could condense the Qi Flower, it would be fine.

Moreover, this also gave Lin Fei a reference. To condense the Energy Flower or Spirit Flower, he still needs to practice the technique to perfection. In that way, the chance of condensing the three flowers should be greater.

"Congratulations to Elder Lin, for successfully condensing the Qi Flower and achieving the status of a Limit Martial Saint!"

The elder of the Spiritual Qi Pool also hurried forward to congratulate him.

In the Ancient Origin Sect, Limit Martial Saints hold a lofty status. Basically, they were all high-ranking figures of the Ancient Origin Sect. If they were true disciples, they were seeds of Martial Sovereigns. All kinds of resources would be tilted towards them to the greatest extent.

Whether they were disciples or elders, once they reached the status of ultimate Martial Saints, they would become the real core. Their status was second only to the Martial Sovereign of the sect.

Lin Fei nodded.

The disciples outside the Spiritual Qi Pool also shouted in unison: "Congratulations to Elder Lin for condensing the Qi Flower and achieving the status of a Limit Martial Saint!"

Everyone knew that with Lin Fei achieving the status of Limit Martial Saint, he was set to rise to prominence. His identity and status would undergo qualitative changes. This was completely different from the battle with Ao Yunxiao.

Lin Fei defeated Ao Yunxiao. At most, he was just given attention by the sect. But he was still an outer sect elder. His status and identity did not improve at all. But becoming a Limit Martial Saint, he automatically entered the core high levels of the sect. It's a world apart from before.

Lin Fei also nodded at the many disciples, but he didn't say anything. Instead, he took a step and left the Spiritual Qi Pool.

As Lin Fei left, the news of Lin Fei condensing a Qi Flower and advancing to Limit Martial Saint also immediately spread throughout the entire Ancient Origin Sect. This was no small matter. Lin Fei was also a famous Dao Seeker. He entered the Ancient Origin Sect half a year ago and he condensed a Qi Flower. When this news came out, it immediately shocked the entire Ancient Origin Sect.

In Ao Yunxiao's cave dwelling, Ao Yunxiao's injuries were actually healed a long time ago. However, he was still in closed-door cultivation. His injury was not physical but in his soul. He was defeated by Lin Fei in front of everyone. Not only did he fail in his build-up, but also a shadow was cast on his soul.

If this issue of the shadow on his soul was not resolved, then Ao Yunxiao should not think about comprehending the momentum of martial arts anymore. It was equivalent to cutting off the path of martial arts!

Therefore, for the past half year, Ao Yunxiao had been adjusting his state, gradually adjusting his soul. After half a year of adjustment, he had already made some progress. However, to completely resolve the issue of the shadow on the soul, how easy could it be? It still needed a long time to adjust slowly.

However, it finally gave Ao Yunxiao some hope. He was confident. Within ten years, he would definitely be able to resolve the issue of the shadow on his soul.

Even more, Ao Yunxiao had a feeling. Once he resolved the shadow on his soul, he might be able to turn a calamity into a blessing and rise to great heights, even directly comprehend the martial momentum!

It's just that the time frame of ten years might be a bit long. But Ao Yunxiao could wait! He had patience.

Step by step at the beginning, he was able to become a true disciple because he had patience. Even if it wasted ten years, Ao Yunxiao firmly believed that he could get rid of the shadow on his soul. Even condense the Spirit Flower and achieve the pinnacle of martial arts! At this moment, his maid ran back hastily from outside the cave.

"Report! Master, the outer sect elder Lin Fei, today in the Spiritual Qi Pool, in front of everyone, has condensed the Qi Flower and achieved the status of Limit Martial Saint!"

"What?"

Ao Yunxiao widened his eyes. The aura on his body even became chaotic. The confidence that had just been established disappeared without a trace in a blink of an eye. Even in the depths of Ao Yunxiao's heart, there was a deep sense of defeat.

"How is it possible? Lin Fei has only joined the Ancient Origin Sect for a mere half a year. How could he condense a Qi Flower?"

Ao Yunxiao murmured to himself in a low voice. His voice was trembling. He didn't believe it!

"Master, it's true. The news has now spread throughout the entire Ancient Origin Sect. It's absolutely true!"

"Bang".

Ao Yunxiao's fist slammed into the ground.

"Get out!"

The maid was in a panic, her face pale. It was Ao Yunxiao who had always asked her to collect information about Lin Fei. She didn't dare to linger and immediately fled the cave-like she was escaping.

Ao Yunxiao's face was as pale as paper. The confidence that had just been built up was gone completely. In the dark, he seemed to feel that the little belief that he had been holding onto in his heart had completely collapsed!

......

In the cave of Shen Lianxin. He had been injured by Ao Yunxiao. It's been a whole half year. Half a year's time, he kept recuperating. Although he couldn't cultivate true essence, it was a blessing in disguise for Shen Lianxin. Because his understanding of the saber momentum improved by leaps and bounds. Half a year's time, he kept pondering over saber techniques, saber intent. For the evolution of saber momentum, he already had confidence.

"Report! Master, the outer sect elder Lin Fei, today in the Spiritual Qi Pool, in front of everyone, has condensed the Qi Flower, and achieved the status of a Limit Martial Saint! Now the entire Ancient Origin Sect has been shaken up.."

When the maid entered the cave, after informing Shen Lianxin of the news.

"Swish."

Shen Lianxin instantly opened his eyes.

"Limit Martial Saint......"

Shen Lianxin murmured to himself in a low voice. He wasn't shocked. It was just a bit unexpected. But even if he felt surprised, upon careful thought, it seemed to be within reason.

Shen Lianxin understood Lin Fei too well. Among the entire Ancient Origin Sect, the person who understood Lin Fei the best was Shen Lianxin.

"Master, you don't seem surprised? News about Elder Lin is now being spread all over the Ancient Origin Sect. There are all kinds of speculations."

The maid seemed a bit puzzled. She came to the cave to serve Shen Lianxin, but the number of words she heard from Shen Lianxin was few and far between. She even felt Shen Lianxin could remain silent for years. But such big news, how could Shen Lianxin not be surprised?

"You don't understand," Shen Lianxin shook his head, speaking in a calm tone, "Even if it was a month, not half a year, I wouldn't be surprised if Lin Fei became a Limit Martial Saint. Back in Great Chang, Brother Lin grew all the way and fought unbeaten under the heavens, which was much more shocking than this. If he didn't become a Limit Martial Saint in a year or so, I would be the one surprised."

Shen Lianxin shook his head. Lin Fei became a Limit Martial Saint, condensing the Qi Flower had been within his expectations. Shen Lianxin was not surprised at all. However, even though he wasn't surprised, there was still a slight ripple in his heart.

"Brother Lin, I came to the Ancient Origin Sect with you. Now that you've become a Limit Martial Saint. I can't fall too far behind you. Today, let's evolve the saber momentum."

Shen Lianxin felt a sense of happiness in his heart. He immediately felt that the opportunity had come! After all, Lin Fei becoming a Limit Martial Saint was also a stimulus to Shen Lianxin. He couldn't possibly be truly indifferent. If he were truly indifferent, then his martial arts path would certainly not go far.

"Boom."

The next moment, Shen Lianxin's saber intent erupted. It was vast and mighty, filling the entire cave. Finally, the terrifying saber intent began to evolve. The various saber techniques Shen Lianxin had practiced before all appeared within the saber intent.

This is evolution! The evolution of saber momentum! Everything fell into place naturally. At this moment, Shen Lianxin also successfully evolved the saber momentum!

236. The Invitation of the Martial Sovereign

Lin Fei returned to his cave. He sat cross-legged on the ground.

"System."

With a thought, he summoned the system to view his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Limit Martial Saint

True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique: Perfection

Blood Essence Nine Transformations: Seventh Transformation (Progress 12%)

Holy Spirit Saber Technique: Mastery (Progress 58%)

Flame Burning Heaven Saber: Transcendence (Progress 65%)

Rainbow Transformation Saber Technique: Transcendence (Progress 10%)

Saber Momentum: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

Lin Fei's martial arts hadn't changed much. Only the martial arts realm had risen from the late stage of Martial Saint to the Limit Martial Saint. It might seem like just a change in name. But Lin Fei knew very well. This step was a qualitative metamorphosis!

In the entire Ancient Origin Sect, the number of Martial Saints was actually quite large. If it looked at the entire Ancient Continent, the number of Martial Saints would be even greater.

But the Limit Martial Saint was different. As the strongest existence below the Martial Sovereign, their status was very high anywhere.

Lin Fei had been in retreat for more than five months. Refining Essence Enhancement Pills was part of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique, Lin Fei couldn't run around. Because once he used the saber essence, it would consume the saber essence. And then it would affect the cultivation of the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique.

During the period when the True Intention Myriad Transformation Technique was refining Essence Enhancement Pills, it's best to stay put and not move. Therefore, this five-month retreat could be considered the longest retreat Lin Fei ever had.

"I wonder how Shen Lianxin is doing?"

Lin Fei thought about it. So, he got up and went directly to Shen Lianxin's cave. When Lin Fei arrived at Shen Lianxin's cave, he saw that Shen Lianxin was actually practicing True Essence, swallowing the Spiritual Qi.

"Huh? Brother Shen, have your injuries healed?"

How did Shen Lianxin recover in just a few months? After all, Ao Yunxiao injured Shen Lianxin with such an injury. It would take at least a year to recover.

A rare smile appeared at the corner of Shen Lianxin's mouth as he slowly spoke, "Brother Lin, you're here. I haven't congratulated you yet on successfully condensing the Qi Flower, achieving the status of Limit Martial Saint."

However, Lin Fei shook his head and said, "It's just the condensation of a Qi Flower, it's nothing to mention. There's still the Energy Flower and Spirit Flower that hasn't been condensed. Even if all three flowers are condensed, it's nothing unless I achieve the status of Martial Sovereign."

If he didn't know Lin Fei and didn't believe that what he said came from his heart, Shen Lianxin might even think Lin Fei was a bit insincere.

Limit Martial Saint. How many martial artists dream of reaching that realm? In the Ancient Origin Sect, there were countless Martial Saints who fail to condense any of the three flowers in their lifetime. And Lin Fei, in just half a year after joining the Ancient Origin Sect, condensed the Qi Flower and became a Limit Martial Saint.

Such an achievement was already awe-inspiring. But Shen Lianxin knew what Lin Fei said was genuine. He knew that Lin Fei's goal was not the Limit Martial Saint but the Martial Sovereign!

"By the way, Brother Shen, you still haven't answered me, how did your injuries heal?" Lin Fei continued to ask.

Shen Lianxin smiled slightly and said, "The sect gave me a healing treasure, which healed my injuries."

"The sect gave you a healing treasure?"

Lin Fei frowned slightly, seeming a little puzzled.

"Hahaha, Brother Lin, what do you think of my saber momentum?"

Shen Lianxin burst into laughter. In the next moment, a unique saber momentum erupted instantly.

"Boom".

Although it was just newly evolved saber momentum and it hadn't even reached mastery yet, it was a genuine saber momentum.

In the Ancient Origin Sect, anyone who could evolve martial momentum was considered a genius! Moreover, Shen Lianxin was only about forty years old. Among the Martial Saints around forty was very young. Such a young age and he had already evolved saber momentum. Obviously, the Ancient Origin Sect also regarded Shen Lianxin as a top genius to cultivate.

Lin Fei immediately understood. It seems that the Ancient Origin Sect also saw Shen Lianxin's potential. Therefore, they directly gave some resources and benefits, just like Lin Fei.

However, the Ancient Origin Sect gave Lin Fei contribution points, and what they gave to Shen Lianxin was a healing treasure, letting Shen Lianxin heal as soon as possible and then continue to cultivate.

"Not bad, Brother Shen, it was only a matter of time before you evolved saber momentum. I just thought that it would take a year or two for you to possibly evolve saber momentum. I didn't expect that in just a few months, you have evolved saber momentum."

Lin Fei was a bit surprised. He didn't doubt that Shen Lianxin would evolve saber momentum. But he didn't expect it to be so fast.

Shen Lianxin nodded and said, "I have to thank Brother Lin for honing my saber intent with saber momentum. We both traveled from Great Chang to seek the Dao. I can't lag too far behind Brother Lin."

So, the two discussed saber momentum again. Of course, Shen Lianxin's saber momentum was far inferior to Lin Fei's. Lin Fei also shared his experience of condensing the Qi Flower with Shen Lianxin.

Shen Lianxin was also determined. He must cultivate his technique to perfection and then try to condense the Qi Flower.

Lin Fei stayed in Shen Lianxin's cave for a few hours. Then, Lin Fei returned to his own cave.

Just after returning to his cave, Lin Fei saw a Martial Saint.

"Elder Lin."

This Martial Saint took the initiative to approach Lin Fei.

"Are you an elder of the Law Enforcement Hall?"

Lin Fei noticed the attire of the Martial Saint. He roughly knew that the other party was from the Law Enforcement Hall.

However, the Law Enforcement Hall was divided into the Outer Law Enforcement Hall and the Law Enforcement Hall of the entire Ancient Origin Sect. Lin Fei himself was an elder of the Outer Law Enforcement Hall.

"Elder Lin, I'm under the order of the master of the Ancient Origin Sect Law Enforcement Hall. I'm here to deliver a token to you. You are now the vice hall master of the Ancient Origin Sect Law Enforcement Hall."

"Vice hall master?"

Lin Fei knew that the other party was referring to the entire Law Enforcement Hall of the Ancient Origin Sect. This was not a leisurely position. It held great power!

After all, the Law Enforcement Hall was responsible for enforcing the law. They might be dealing with some true disciples. At that time, it would be up to the Law Enforcement Hall to take action. And the vice hall master was obviously high above, belonging to the high level of the Law Enforcement Hall.

"The position of vice hall master holds high authority, and I am only interested in cultivation, I'm afraid..."

Lin Fei was preparing to refuse. If they want him to be an elder, that's no problem. But the vice hall master? That was a position that required action. Even if it had various benefits, he didn't want to waste his cultivation time.

However, this Martial Saint smiled and said, "Elder Lin, don't worry, our Law Enforcement Hall's vice hall master actually doesn't need to do much. Only certain major matters need to be reported to you. Moreover, the vice hall master has many benefits. It's much better than being an elder. Besides, this was something the hall master personally instructed."

"The hall master personally instructed?"

Lin Fei knew that the hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall is a Martial Sovereign. In fact, throughout the Ancient Origin Sect, the power of the Law Enforcement Hall is the most formidable. Therefore, the hall master must be a Martial Sovereign. As for other Martial Sovereigns, most of them are Grand Elders or sect masters. Every sect master of the Ancient Origin Sect is a Martial Sovereign.

"Vice hall master, if you have any questions, you can ask the hall master directly. The hall master is still in the Law Enforcement Hall, waiting to see Vice Hall Master Lin."

Lin Fei looked at the Martial Saint in front of him. He knew that this Martial Saint was not only here to deliver the token but also to invite him.

After some thought, Lin Fei nodded and said, "Alright, please lead the way."

After all, it was a personal invitation from a Martial Sovereign. Moreover, Lin Fei was indeed curious. What did a Martial Sovereign look like? This was an opportunity.

So, Lin Fei and this Martial Saint turned into two streaks of light and flew towards the Law Enforcement Hall.

237. Wind Sovereign

The Law Enforcement Hall was a place that everyone in the Ancient Origin Sect feared. There was no disciple who wanted to be taken into the Law Enforcement Hall. Because, once that happened, it basically meant that they had "caused trouble". Moreover, the trouble would certainly not be small. Otherwise, there would be no need to mobilize the Law Enforcement Hall.

This was Lin Fei's first visit to the headquarters of the Ancient Origin Sect's Law Enforcement Hall. This was not the Outer Law Enforcement Hall but the one that governed the entire Ancient Origin Sect's inner sect and true disciples. Even the elders of the Ancient Origin Sect were all within the jurisdiction of the Law Enforcement Hall.

As long as someone "caused trouble", the Law Enforcement Hall would take action. Therefore, the hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall held high authority.

The power was so great that it was only below the sect master. Therefore, the hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall has always been held by a Martial Sovereign. If not for the Martial Sovereign, probably no one could uphold the reputation of the entire Law Enforcement Hall.

Following the Martial Saint of the Law Enforcement Hall, Lin Fei arrived at a spacious room.

"Vice Hall Master Lin, please, the hall master is inside."

Lin Fei nodded and walked straight in. As soon as he entered the room, Lin Fei saw an old man. The old man had his eyes closed. He was sitting cross-legged on the ground. There was no strong aura around him.

However, Lin Fei vaguely felt a kind of oppressive feeling as if the old man in front of him was a terrifying existence.

Lin Fei had never felt this way before. So, he was taken aback. He knew that the old man in front of him was extraordinary. It was probably the hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall, Wind Sovereign!

Wind Sovereign, the hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall. It's pretty much well-known in the Ancient Origin Sect.

"Swish".

Wind Sovereign opened his eyes.

"You must be Vice Hall Master Lin, right?"

"Lin Fei pays his respects to Wind Sovereign!"

Lin Fei respectfully saluted. A Martial Sovereign equivalent to a Golden Core True Person. With a lifespan of a thousand years, Wind Sovereign was one of the real core figures in the entire Ancient Origin Sect, even considered a pillar of heaven!

"No need to be so formal. Vice Hall Master Lin must be very curious now. Why did I summon you and even make you the vice hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall?"

Lin Fei nodded. He was indeed curious.

"Very simple, strength!" Wind Sovereign smiled and said, "You defeated Ao Yunxiao, and you are very strong in your own right. Now that you have condensed a Qi Flower, coupled with your saber momentum. Your strength, even among the Limit Martial Saints, can be considered top-notch. Therefore, it's only fitting for you to serve as the vice hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall!"

Lin Fei's face remained calm. He knew it wasn't that simple. If it was simply because of his strong strength that he was appointed as the vice hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall, there was no need for Wind Sovereign to summon him personally.

Not to mention Lin Fei, even a Limit Martial Saint who had condensed Qi Flowe and Energy Flower might not necessarily be able to meet Wind Sovereign.

Martial Sovereign, high above. Even if two flowers have been condensed, as long as one does not become a Martial Sovereign for one day, there will always be a world of difference with the Martial Sovereign.

Seeing that Lin Fei didn't speak, Wind Sovereign's expression turned serious and he said in a deep voice, "Of course, there is indeed a reason for making you the vice hall master of the Law Enforcement Hall so quickly. The vice hall masters of my Ancient Origin Sect's Law Enforcement Hall are in charge of the inner hall and the outer hall respectively. The inner hall mainly deals with disciples or elders who have violated the rules of the Ancient Origin Sect, mainly responsible for internal matters of the Ancient Origin Sect.

The outer hall mainly deals with external matters. For instance, if the disciples or elders of my Ancient Origin Sect are killed by external forces or individuals, the outer hall of the Law Enforcement Hall will handle it. A big incident has recently occurred in my Ancient Origin Sect. Three true disciples were killed by some Foundation Establishment cultivators. But the culprits escaped to the Illusion Worry City. This Illusion Worry City is a bit special. It has two city masters, namely Illusion Heart True Person and Worry-free Sovereign! One is a Golden Core True Person, the other is a Martial Sovereign.

It is located at the junction of the three forces: Ancient Origin Sect, Profound Light Cave Heaven, and Red Hades Mansion, but it has become a no man's land! Anyone can enter the Illusion Worry City, and no fighting is allowed there. Over time, Illusion Worry City has become a carefree place in the eyes of some Martial Saints and True Persons. But this time is different. The culprits killed three true disciples of our Ancient Origin Sect, one of whom even had the potential to become a Martial Sovereign seed.

Originally, I planned to personally go down the mountain. But the Ancient Origin Sect, Pround Light Cave Heaven, and Red Hades Mansion once had some agreements with the two city masters of Illusion Worry City. Martial Sovereign and Golden Core True Persons are not allowed to enter Illusion Worry City without permission. So, the matter of capture can only be handled by the Martial Saints.

You have grasped the transcendence saber momentum, which is currently the only one in the Law Enforcement Hall. When it comes to arresting people, your saber momentum has more advantages than other Martial Saints who have condensed two flowers. Moreover, your strength is not bad, it may not be worse than the Martial Saints who have condensed two flowers. It's most appropriate for you to capture the real culprit."

Wind Sovereign didn't hide anything. He revealed the hidden information. It turns out that Lin Fei was to be sent to capture some troublesome figures.

Illusion Worry City. No man's land and there were even Golden Core True Persons and Martial Sovereigns. It doesn't sound like an easy task.

However, Lin Fei was originally an elder of the outer Law Enforcement Hall. The Law Enforcement Hall has the right to order Lin Fei to perform some tasks. This is also a duty of Lin Fei as an elder of the Ancient Origin Sect. After all, he has gained cultivation techniques from the Ancient Origin Sect.

He got resources. Since he got the benefits, then of course he has to pay.

"Wind Sovereign, Illusion Worry City has Golden Core True Persons and Martial Sovereigns. And it's explicitly forbidden to take action in Illusion Worry City. If I go to Illusion Worry City to arrest or even kill people, wouldn't that break the rules of Illusion Worry City? If the Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign take action..."

Lin Fei didn't continue his words. But Wind Sovereign naturally understood Lin Fei's meaning.

If the Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign took action, then Lin Fei would be in danger. Even if he's strong, how could he possibly contend with a Golden Core True Person or a Martial Sovereign?

Wind Sovereign smiled faintly and said, "You don't need to worry about this. You represent my Ancient Origin Sect. The Ancient Origin Sect, Profound Light Cave Heaven, and Red Hades Mansion had an agreement with Illusion Worry City. The two city masters of Illusion Worry City are not allowed to take action against people from our three sects.

Similarly, our three sects' Golden Core True Persons or Martial Sovereigns are not allowed to enter Illusion Worry City and take action. So, when you take action in Illusion Worry City, you don't need to worry about Golden Core True Persons or Martial Sovereigns.

However, the strong ones under the command of the two city masters and those who killed the true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect may take action against you. And the Law Enforcement Hall will also dispatch some elders to accompany you to Illusion Worry City."

Lin Fei understood. The Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign would not take action. After all, if they take action, it would be equivalent to tearing up the agreement. It's not a difficult task for the Ancient Origin Sect to raze Illusion Worry City to the ground with all its strength. But the strong ones below the Martial Sovereigns could take action. So, this trip of Lin Fei actually faced a great challenge!

Wind Sovereign stopped talking. He waited quietly. Lin Fei also closed his eyes. Many thoughts flashed through his mind. He was quietly considering his options.

238. Accept the Task

"Wind Sovereign, since the sect has assigned me to carry out this task, I naturally comply. However, I still feel unsuited to the position of vice hall master. Just a leisurely elder will suffice. If the Law Enforcement Hall needs me, I am at its disposal at any time."

Lin Fei opened his eyes and said slowly. His words meant that he had agreed. However, he rejected the position of vice hall master. Even if it's more leisurely, as a vice hall master in charge of external affairs, how could it possibly be truly leisurely?

Even if the position of vice hall master has great benefits, Lin Fei didn't want to be entangled in mundane affairs, which would affect his cultivation. His goal is to reach the pinnacle of martial arts. How could he be distracted by dealing with mundane affairs?

Wind Sovereign laughed. He nodded slightly and said, "Alright, since you don't want to be the vice hall master, then be an elder. However, this time you will definitely represent the Ancient Origin Sect, and even more so, the Law Enforcement Hall. A common elder is also not suitable. With your strength, you should be the first elder of the Law Enforcement Hall! This position happens to be vacant."

Wind Sovereign gave Lin Fei another arrangement. This "First Elder" is suitable. After all, "First Elder" is just an honorary title. In terms of specific duties, he is still an elder. And the elders of the Law Enforcement Hall, most of the time are quite leisurely. Unless something big happens in the Ancient Origin Sect. Then the elder will be dispatched. As for Lin Fei, this First Elder, unless there's an extremely big event, he probably won't be disturbed.

"Thank you, Wind Sovereign!"

Lin Fei gave a slight bow.

"Alright, Elder Lin, you can go back to your cave dwelling first. Once the Law Enforcement Hall arranges the candidates, you can set off for Illusion Worry City together. This is equivalent to going on a mission. The sect also offers a large number of contribution points as rewards."

Lin Fei nodded.

There are rewards for going on missions. For this kind of task where the sect needs a Martial Saint to exert great effort, the reward of contribution points is extremely generous. Therefore, Lin Fei was not worried about the rewards at all. With his current strength and potential, the Ancient Origin Sect would only look for more excuses to give him contribution points.

Lin Fei returned to his cave dwelling. Although he believed that Wind Sovereign would not deceive him, he had to lead a team to a strange place. Even places where Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign are stationed.

Lin Fei of course had to be more careful. So, he found some information about Illusion Worry City. He learned about the beginning and end of Illusion Worry City.

The establishment of Illusion Worry City actually carries some legendary color. Illusion Heart True Person and Worry-Free Sovereign are actually independent cultivators!

Lin Fei found it somewhat incredible to see the introduction to the information. After all, it's not easy for independent cultivators to become Martial Saints or Foundation Establishment True Persons. Not to mention achieving the level of Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign. But it is indeed the case.

Illusion Heart True Person and Worry-Free Sovereign rose step by step and were chased to the place where Illusion Worry City is now. There, they were protected by a group of martial artists and Foundation Establishment True Persons who were also independent cultivators. Later, they grew step by step, and actually achieved Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign. This is indeed legendary.

Of course, Lin Fei also knew. The past experiences of these two people are not simple. There must be some adventures. Because, according to the information, Illusion Heart True Person and Worry-Free Sovereign were not ordinary Golden Core True Person and Martial Sovereign. They could be considered among the top existents in Martial Sovereigns and Golden Core True Persons.

Therefore, the three major forces of the Ancient Origin Sect, Profound Light Cave Heaven, and Red Hades Mansion, finally acknowledged the existence of Illusion Worry City. Otherwise, with the domineering style of these three forces, where would there be any no man's land? Only with strength can the existence of Illusion Worry City be guaranteed.

After the establishment of Illusion Worry City, because of its relative safety and the freedom of trading, and even many treasures that could not see the light of day could be traded through Illusion Worry City, gradually, it developed.

Nowadays, even some disciples of the three major forces would go to Illusion Worry City to exchange for some things they couldn't get in their sects. It had truly become a big scene!

Among them, Illusion Worry City is known for its "safety". No matter how malicious, once in Illusion Worry City, it's safe. Because, within Illusion Worry City, fighting is not allowed. Once a fight happens, the law enforcement team of Illusion Worry City will strictly punish it!

Lin Fei finally understood why even Wind Sovereign was troubled. Even specifically summoned Lin Fei. Turns out, going to Illusion Worry City to catch someone is not easy at all.

Once a fight happens, it will inevitably conflict with Illusion Worry City. Either immediately kill the real culprits who killed the Ancient Origin Sect disciples. Then leave Illusion Worry City immediately. Once out of Illusion Worry City, the forces of it would not take action or confront the forces.

Over the years, Illusion Heart True Person and Worry-Free Sovereign had also recruited a lot of Limit Martial Saints and top Foundation Establishment cultivators. Therefore, their power is very strong.

A slight carelessness. Lin Fei and others might even be in danger. If they break the rules of Illusion Worry City and get killed inside, perhaps the Ancient Origin Sect wouldn't make a fuss about it.

Therefore, this trip carries certain dangers. However, it's not really dangerous for Limit Martial Saints. To kill a Limit Martial Saint is too difficult. Moreover, it's not just Lin Fei going this time. There are also some elders at the Law Enforcement Hall. Among them, there are Limit Martial Saints!

"Although it's dangerous, I now have saber momentum, and with the Qi Flower condensed, my saber essence has greatly increased. Even if I'm not a match, I shouldn't be in danger."

Lin Fei muttered to himself. How strong his strength is now, even Lin Fei himself was not clear. After all, Lin Fei's strength cannot be quantified. His current strength was made up of saber momentum, saber essence, and saber method. Only by really giving a full fight, perhaps, can Lin Fei's real combat power be confirmed.

Lin Fei waited for three days. Finally, he received news from the Law Enforcement Hall.

So, Lin Fei went directly to the Law Enforcement Hall. This time, he didn't see Wind Sovereign but a total of thirteen Martial Saints. Almost all were elders of the Law Enforcement Hall.

Among them, there were two Limit Martial Saints who had condensed Energy Flower in their bodies, and one who had condensed Qi Flower. Apart from them, there were ten powerful Martial Saints in total. Such a lineup was actually very strong. It showed that the Wind Sovereign of the Law Enforcement Hall was not just talking.

They were really serious. Those who killed the true disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect, the Ancient Origin Sect must kill them even if it had to chase them to the ends of the earth.

This is the style of a big sect! Otherwise, a sect that can't protect its true disciples, where would there be any cohesion?

"Respect to the First Elder!"

These Martial Saint elders apparently already knew Lin Fei's identity. Upon seeing Lin Fei, they immediately paid their respects. However, Lin Fei could vaguely feel. The three Limit Martial Saints, their gazes seemed a bit strange.

Lin Fei's eyes grew cold. His gaze swept over these Martial Saint elders. He said coldly, "I want to ask a question first. Does anyone feel that I, as the First Elder, am not qualified? I give you a chance. One move, if I can't beat you, I will voluntarily resign to Wind Sovereign. The opportunity is given to you. If you want to try, you can step forward!"

After speaking, Lin Fei just stood there with his hands behind his back, quietly standing in front of the thirteen Martial Saint elders. The atmosphere in the whole Law Enforcement Hall immediately became tense.

241. Saber Splits Limit Martial Saint

"It's Liu Hong!"

"Deputy captain of the Illusion Worry City Enforcement Team, Liu Hong! He has condensed the Qi Flower, acts decisively, and is utterly impartial."

"Liu Hong has slain countless Martial Saints and Foundation Establishment True Persons who have stirred up trouble in Illusion Worry City."

"It's Liu Hong in person! It seems that Illusion Worry City has been keeping an eye on the people of the Ancient Origin Sect."

"These Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect are really bold. They dare to take action in Illusion Worry City. I'm afraid they won't be able to leave the city today."

"They are from a major martial arts sect after all. They are used to being domineering and would not care about Illusion Worry City."

"Let's see how these Martial Saints from the Ancient Origin Sect handle this. If they aren't careful, they might have to stay in Illusion Worry City today."

Many martial artists and Qi cultivators in Illusion Worry City were talking. And they didn't seem to like Lin Fei and the others. There were quite a few sarcastic remarks. This was quite normal.

Lin Fei represented the Ancient Origin Sect, which was a major martial arts sect that usually acted very domineering. The disciples of the Ancient Origin Sect always had a superior feeling when they went down the mountain. This was the truth.

Most martial artists and Qi cultivators in Illusion Worry City were independent cultivators. It would be strange if they had a good impression of the Ancient Origin Sect. Under the intimidation of Liu Hong's voice in Illusion Worry City, the Martial Saints of the Ancient Origin Sect's Law Enforcement Hall also stopped.

"Didn't you hear my command? Spare no one from Spiritual Rhythm Three Immortals!"

Lin Fei's voice was already somewhat cold. These Martial Saints from the Law Enforcement Hall seemed to have thought of something.

They immediately gritted their teeth and attacked the remaining two Foundation Establishment True Persons of Spiritual Rhythm Three Immortals.

Lin Fei's command was "Spare no one." Therefore, they didn't need to capture them alive. They directly aimed to kill the remaining two Foundation Establishment True Persons.

"Dare to take action again?"

Liu Hong was very fast. However, he was still too late. The Martial Saints of the Law Enforcement Hall had already taken action.

More than a dozen Martial Saints, among them, were even three Limit Martial Saints. How difficult could it be to kill two Foundation Establishment True Persons?

"Ah..."

The two Foundation Establishment True Persons screamed and were immediately killed. At this point, all members of the Spiritual Rhythm Three Immortals were killed!

Liu Hong was extremely furious. It had been a long time since anyone had dared to be so presumptuous in Illusion Worry City.

"Surround them all! Kill anyone who dares to resist!"

Liu Hong yelled loudly. The many Martial Saints and Foundation Establishment True Persons behind him quickly surrounded the entire courtyard. Lin Fei and the others were in the middle of the courtyard.

At the same time, Liu Hong had already punched out, directly aiming at Lin Fei. Because Lin Fei was blocking the entrance to the courtyard, clearly intending to obstruct the Illusion Worry City Enforcement Team.

"Suppress!"

Lin Fei gave a soft shout.

"Boom."

The transcendental saber momentum exploded instantly. It was as if the void had suddenly solidified. Under the cover of the saber momentum, everyone felt as if they were carrying several heavy mountains on their backs, making them unable to move. For a moment, even Liu Hong's fist, which was shot from the air, disintegrated directly under the suppression of the saber momentum.

"Transcendence saber momentum!"

Liu Hong's face was solemn, and he said each word distinctly.

"Boom."

Liu Hong's words seemed to ignite the surrounding martial artists and Qi cultivators. Even though they were independent cultivators, they understood what the transcendence saber momentum meant due to their mutual exchange in Illusion Worry City.

After all, it is difficult to comprehend the momentum of martial arts. Among the three flowers of a Martial Saint, the Energy Flower and Qi Flower are not particularly rare. But the Spirit Flower is really rare. To condense a Spirit Flower, one needs to cultivate the momentum of martial arts to perfection. This is a hurdle that blocks more than 90% of Martial Saints.

Many Martial Saints can't even comprehend the momentum of martial arts, let alone cultivate it to perfection. But now, this Martial Saint from the Ancient Origin Sect had comprehended the transcendence saber momentum.

"The Ancient Origin Sect came prepared."

"Transcendence saber momentum, how rare it is! Even within the Ancient Origin Sect, that's an absolute top-tier Martial Saint."

"A top-tier Martial Saint? It must be a Limit Martial Saint!"

"Why did the Ancient Origin Sect send such a top talent down the mountain, even to kill the Spiritual Rhythm Three Immortals in Illusion Worry City? What do they want to do?"

"Aren't they afraid that Illusion Worry City will kill him?"

"Perhaps the Ancient Origin Sect has confidence in this Martial Saint? Or they feel that Illusion Worry City would not dare to do anything to him."

"Heh heh, Martial Saint Liu Hong is famous for his mercilessness. Once he takes action, it's a fight to the death!"

More and more people flocked to the scene. Liu Hong is known for his violent temper. Once he takes action, it's a fight to the death. This was a big battle!

"Transcendence saber momentum? Break!"

Just as others had said, Liu Hong was indeed fearless. A Qi Flower suddenly appeared above his head.

"Boom."

With the emergence of the Qi Flower, the pressure of Lin Fei's transcendence saber momentum seemed to disappear instantly. At least that was the case for Liu Hong. A Qi Flower could block the suppression of the saber momentum to some extent. Of course, this was only because Lin Fei's was the transcendence saber momentum. If Lin Fei's saber momentum reached perfection and even condense the Spirit Flower, the saber momentum would suppress opponents.

Endless True Essence pressure erupted from Liu Hong. Limit Martial Saint! For the first time, Lin Fei faced a Limit Martial Saint directly.

At the same time, Liu Hong also made his move. When he made his move, it was like a mountain collapsing and the earth cracking, the terrifying True Essence explosion, the power of a single punch, was earth-shattering.

No wonder Liu Hong was able to become the deputy captain of the Illusion Worry City Enforcement Team. With such terrifying strength, even if he was just a Qi Flower martial artist, he was a standout among them.

"Shoo."

The next moment, Lin Fei flicked his finger, and a saber essence flew out instantly.

"Boom."

Fierce flames seemed to ignite the void with the emergence of the saber essence. Everyone couldn't help but look up. They saw the flames in the void. No, not flames. But a saber. A saber that was burning with fierce flames, or rather, a saber made up of flames! One thousand meters tall! And it exuded an endless fierce aura.

Lin Fei only flicked his finger lightly, and less than one-tenth of the saber essence inside his body erupted. But he condensed more than one thousand meters of saber essence.

This is the Flame Burning Heaven Saber. A remarkably powerful saber technique.

"Slash!"

Facing Liu Hong's Qi Flower explosion and an all-out punch, Lin Fei's Flame Burning Heaven Saber, under the blessing of the saber momentum, slashed down.

Even during the slashing process, Lin Fei's saber essence was still increasing. The Flame Burning Heaven Saber was also still expanding.

One thousand meters, fifteen hundred meters...

No one could describe this saber. Lin Fei didn't even display the Qi Flower, yet how could he condense such a terrifying saber?

"Boom."

Finally, the Flame Burning Heaven Saber slashed down. It slashed directly against Liu Hong's punch.

Liu Hong was a true Limit Martial Saint. Even if all his True Essence erupted, this punch, under Lin Fei's fifteen hundred meters Flame Burning Heaven Saber, was as weak as tofu. It was instantly cut open by the flame saber. The fierce flames fell directly, instantly engulfing Liu Hong!